To be continued...
Heart strength
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it
What is this?
Barga is a monster that is strong
He is the arm of a monster
that can defeat him
He is only a shadow
and a child
Who is he?
Alpha
Tonight
Before the sun sets
You have to go back to the secret room
and take the stone of eternity for me
To be continued...
What are you doing? Get out of there!
When are you going to kill the kid?
Ouch!
Ray!
How did you know?
You were unconscious just now
I was unconscious
But because of you
I got sick
Let me try using a mantra
Dangdut Davang
Why is it dangdut?
That's right
If you don't use the mantra
Okay
I got it
Dangdut Davang
This is it
Let's go
Dangdut Davang
Davang
To be continued...
How do I catch him?
Dad!
To be continued...
Oh my God!
My medicine didn't make it!
What is this?
What poison is this?
This is poison from the Three Heads
What?
The Three Heads?
Oh my God!
This is poison from the Three Heads
There's no antidote yet
You better go to Megantara now
Huh?
What do you mean?
Captain Megantara
Because he's taking care of Megantara
That dragon
Hurry!
Okay, I'll go to Megantara now
Go!
To be continued...
His body movements are so fast
I need to concentrate
Now, by listening to this
I can know what's going on
Sir!
To be continued...
Soldier!
Wake up!
My bird is gone!
Because of you, the chicken is gone
My sore thighs!
Come on, soldier!
Help me, soldier!
What's wrong with me?
I'm a three-headed dragon
And Dr. Pertiwi doesn't have an assistant
That's why I'm asking for help
What's going on?
Why did he enter the forbidden room?
Because we want to take...
We?
You mean not just Shirea?
Yes
Explain it
Who are we?
We are...
I, Rey...
And Alfa
Alfa, you're such a troublemaker!
Oh no, soldier!
Alfa is not wrong
He went in there...
Just to take the stone from the forbidden room
No one can bring Alfa...
Wake up!
Wake up, sir!
Where is he?
What's going on, sir?
Sir, what are those angels?
They are not angels...
...but they are...
...the princesses of angels.
Princesses of angels?
Yes.
See?
They turned into beautiful princesses.
Vega...
...now it's your turn.
You approach them.
You figure out a way...
...to get them to the clinic...
...to treat Ray, okay?
Why me, sir?
I already know Ray.
Think of me, sir.
So?
Here's the problem.
They are...
...the creatures that don't like...
...a male creature like me.
And I'm handsome.
They will be allergic.
Enough.
Don't think too much.
Do you want Ray to be cured?
I want Ray to be cured.
Let's go.
Hey, who are you, little kid?
You called us here, didn't you?
Yes.
I called you.
Because I really need your help.
My friend is a 3rd head monster.
You are the only one who can cure my friend.
Why do we have to help you?
We don't even know you.
Why are you saying that?
Please.
I promise.
I will do whatever you want.
Please.
Right.
You can do whatever you want.
Yes.
Okay.
If you want to do whatever we want,
you have to make us happy and laugh.
But how?
Think about it.
We haven't laughed for a long time.
Am I right, girls?
You are right.
It won't take long.
I will count to three.
If not, we will leave.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Eleven.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Right.
I can do it.
Trust me.
Let's go.
You are great, Figa.
One problem solved.
Sorry, soldier.
Oops.
Guys.
I'm not a guy.
How are you?
You said you are bored with guys.
What are you waiting for?
Let's beat him up.
Figa.
Don't.
Attack.
It's dangerous.
Don't.
Yes.
We are party.
I made you laugh.
Now, help my friend.
Help me.
Yes.
Quick.
Guys.
Let's go.
Sembunyi!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now, tell me.
Why are you in that room?
Here's the thing.
Alva said...
this school is in danger.
And...
he needs that stone...
to save this school.
If not, many lives will be in danger.
Right?
She's so stubborn.
Alva doesn't need that stone.
What is she doing?
Where's Alva now?
To Be Continued...
Hey!
What are you doing?
What are you doing in there?
Alva?
Ma'am?
How's Alva?
Yes, Ma'am.
I got the stone.
Excuse me.
To Be Continued...
Sambung Bayi!
Alakusi!
Help!
Alva fainted!
Dad!
For the next two hours,
your voice will change to the voice of a pet.
To Be Continued...
Ma'am.
I gave up taking the stone.
So, this school is safe, right?
What do you mean, Alva?
I managed to get the stone.
And I gave it to the professor, right?
I never told you to do that.
Alva.
Why did you take the stone?
Professor Agni asked me to.
Because this school is in danger.
Only the stone can save this school.
Alva.
I never asked you to take the stone.
But yesterday afternoon,
Professor Agni asked me to take the Stone of Eternity.
No, Alva.
I never asked you to take the stone.
Professor.
The Stone of Eternity has...
The Three Headed Dragon.
It destroys everything.
Alva.
How did you know all of this?
Professor Agni...
Professor Agni told me.
And Professor Agni also told me...
about the food of the Three Headed Dragon.
Alva.
I never asked you to do all of that.
Come on, Professor.
Alva.
You should go back to your dormitory now.
But, Professor.
I really gave the stone to Professor Agni.
And after that, I don't remember anything.
I think someone followed me until I fainted.
I never received anything from you, Alva.
That's impossible, Professor.
I can't be lying.
Look, Alva.
I'm not lying.
The stone can't save this school.
On the contrary.
If the stone falls into the wrong hands,
this school could be in danger.
For example, the Dark Prince.
The Dark Prince?
Who is he?
You shouldn't be hearing this name.
And you don't need to know who he is.
Based on your bad behavior,
you're a thief.
You even brought a brick to this school.
Enough.
Go back to your dormitory now.
I'm sorry, Professor.
This time, you're really naughty, Alva.
You went into the room,
took the stone,
and the stone was gone.
And you lied to Professor Agni.
But, Tentara, I'm not lying.
I don't believe it.
How can you believe it?
Professor Agni has been a teacher at this school for decades, Alva.
So, it's impossible for him to be lying.
But, I'm telling the truth, Tentara.
I'm not lying.
Professor.
Tentara.
Who is the Dark Prince?
The Dark Prince?
It's not time for you to know, Alva.
What's clear is that
the Dark Prince is very dangerous, Alva.
Not a single person hopes he'll come back.
Rey.
You've recovered.
I know everything.
You stole the Stone of Kabadian.
And you lied.
You said Professor Agni told you to do it.
But, you didn't.
Now, you're denying it.
Is that true or not?
No, Rey.
That's a lie.
I gave the Stone of Kabadian to Professor Agni.
And suddenly, someone attacked me.
And I don't know what happened next.
Really?
But, I don't believe it.
Vega.
You don't believe me, either.
Alright.
If you don't believe me, it's okay.
I'll prove that my words are true.
He's angry.
I should be the one who's angry.
I've defended him until he's poisoned.
But, he's just a victim of PHP.
I think he's not wrong, Rey.
What do you mean?
You mean Professor Agni lied?
That's right.
Guys.
You've heard it, right?
Alva is a thief.
She stole the Stone of Kabadian.
How can a thief be allowed to enter this school?
That's right.
It turns out that Klepto doesn't feel ashamed at all.
Even though he's a thief, he still dares to come here.
Guys.
It's not fun if there's a thief in our school.
I have an idea.
We have to make a petition.
What do you think?
Do you agree?
Agree.
Let's make a petition.
Petition has been signed.
Wow.
There are so many signatures.
If it's like this, the thief will be out of the school soon.
Do you agree?
Agree.
Alva.
Come here.
Ray, what are you doing?
Ray.
You're the one who should be ashamed of Alva.
Alva betrayed us.
Ray, Alva is a good person.
She saved me from the thieves.
A good person like Alva can't do that.
I'm sure she's being trapped now.
And she's in the trap.
No, she's not.
Listen.
I don't want to be poisoned anymore.
If you want to help Alva, just go there.
I want to sleep.
Ray.
Alva said she was possessed in front of the forbidden room.
I think I need to go to that room.
Maybe there's evidence left there.
Ouch.
What's going on?
Ouch, it hurts.
Don't go there.
Alva is in the forbidden room.
Why is this room sealed?
Wasn't it...
Yes.
Because Alva was in this room.
And this is a forbidden room.
That's why this room is sealed.
So, no one can get in.
And you.
Don't try to get in this room.
Marti.
I'm leaving.
If she's using a spell,
she must be able to open it.
I need to find a spell to open this seal.
Now, no one believes me.
Tentara.
Ray.
And Vega.
They think I'm lying.
But I don't have any proof.
And I don't know who I am.
I don't know where the body switch is.
Hi, bro.
Why are you smiling?
Do you believe me?
Yes.
Here's a magic spell from me.
Take it.
One for you, one for me.
Thank you.
Yes.
Let's open it.
It's good, right?
Yes.
How did my voice become like this?
What you got is a voice changer spell.
So, for the next two hours,
your voice will turn into an animal's voice.
That's a lesson.
Who's that?
You're expelled from school.
Don't ever say a spell in front of a mirror.
Because the spell will come back to you.
For that,
there's a spell you can use.
You have to say this spell...
before you say the spell you want to say.
Repeat after me.
Javangan Pantung.
One more time.
Alpha.
Why don't you repeat the spell?
Do you think you're smart enough?
Why don't you say anything, Alpha?
Come on.
Repeat the spell.
You insulted me, Alpha.
Quiet!
You've gone too far, Alpha.
For that, I'll punish you.
I'm sorry.
Attention.
All students gather in the classroom.
One more time.
Attention.
All students gather in the classroom.
One more time.
What do we have to discuss...
so that I have to leave my students?
What steps do we have to take against Alpha?
I don't think we have to discuss that.
Alpha has to be expelled.
Javangan Pantung.
Expelling a student from the school...
is not an easy task.
But, Professor.
What Alpha has done...
is out of the question.
If we don't expel him...
we will be protested by the parents.
That's right.
The full moon is in three days.
And if in the full moon...
the Dark Lord gets the Stone of Eternity...
he will get an unlimited power...
that will destroy this world.
And all of that will happen because of Alpha.
Professor.
During the break...
some students gave me this petition.
The petition says...
that all the students in this school...
agree to expel Alpha from this school.
Looks like...
we have no other choice, Professor.
Alpha has to be expelled from this school.
Megantara.
Call Alpha.
Tell him to come here.
I'm glad my voice is back.
If not...
Professor Aldebaran will be angry.
Megantara.
We have to go.
Why did you call me?
Good morning, Professor.
The words you are about to hear...
will not be pleasant to the ears.
But you have to keep listening.
What is it, Professor?
You are expelled from this school.
Now...
get your things ready.
Tomorrow morning, the school guard will take you to the dance.
I'm done talking.
You can go now.
Goodbye, Professor.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Rolf.
Did Alpha...
really take the stone?
No.
The child is innocent.
If it's not Alpha...
it means Professor Agni is lying.
No.
Agni is not lying.
Something has happened...
and we have to find out.
What really happened?
Rey.
I was just called by Professor Aldebaran.
You don't want to know...
what punishment I got from Professor Aldebaran.
It's my fault.
I'm tired of being lied to.
Let's go.
Rey.
Rey, come here.
Come and help me.
I have to find the mantra to open the seal.
Come on.
I don't want to read it.
I'm here to have fun...
not to read a book.
I don't want to know. You have to help me.
Dufuduk.
I don't want to read a book.
The last mantra.
Reyka.
Come on.
I'm so sleepy.
Give me the mantra.
You can sleep later.
But I'll wait for the mantra.
I'm so tired.
I got the mantra.
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
Amen.
No.
I'm sweating.
The mantra.
But it's useless.
You're out of the ring.
What's going on?
I don't want to read a book.
I'm so tired.
You can sleep later.
But I'll wait for the mantra.
I'm so tired.
You're out of the ring.
What's going on?
Give me the mantra.
I don't want to read a book.
I'm so tired.
You're out of the ring.
Why are you still here?
I'm scared.
A kid got possessed.
He fainted here.
Don't ask.
I'm so scared.
Don't ask anything.
I don't want to tell you anything.
Understand?
But you have to tell me.
Who attacked Alva?
At first, there was Professor Agni.
Professor Agni?
Then, this place was so smoky.
So, I didn't see who attacked the kid.
But, he used magic.
I'm sure he's very powerful.
I want to move to another place.
It's scary here.
I think I know...
...that Alva is not wrong.
Where are we going?
Wait.
Where's Alva?
Do you see Alva?
Alva was kicked out of the school.
What?
Now, she's home.
Why is she sleeping here?
What's going on?
Is she crazy?
Ri, wake up.
Ri.
Alva, Ri.
Alva was kicked out of the school.
Come on.
Let's ask the principal.
Yes.
The news you heard is true.
Alva is being brought to the lake by the principal.
It's my fault.
I was mean to Alva.
She wanted to tell me about the punishment.
But, I didn't want to hear it.
You're too much.
You're so insensitive.
Everyone says that.
Even though I'm handsome, I'm not sensitive.
Why?
But, sir.
Alva didn't do anything wrong.
We have to bring her back to the school.
But, we don't have any proof.
You're talking nonsense.
There can't be any solid proof.
But, we have to investigate this together.
Besides, Alva is a soldier's friend.
How can a soldier...
...see his own friend who didn't do anything wrong...
...being punished like that?
Alva.
Take this boat.
This boat will take you back.
Do you want to go home?
Goodbye, Vega.
Goodbye, Rey.
I'll try to get along with Rey and Vega.
But, if I do that...
...they won't care.
They already hate me.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
You're out of the school.
Why?
Why are you still here?
Sabina's ring.
I know who stole the stone.
Who?
Professor Tulua.
I'll prove that I'm right.
Just wait and see.
Let's go.
Don't let the Abadian stone...
...be given to the evil leader.
Professor Tulua.
Follow your dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with all your might
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Let's dream
Never stop