To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud, Go! Go! Go!
Let's dream, Go! Go! Go!
We can do it.
Calm down, kids.
We will find out what has happened.
Megantara, you'd better get the kids out of here.
And don't let a single kid fly away.
Professor, who installed this horrible magic in this gate?
I don't know, Megantara.
What's clear is that you can't leave this village.
And we can't enter the village.
You saved Grandpa.
Because you saved Grandpa.
Grandpa, now you're going to be killed by Grandpa.
The power of the magic defeated the monster.
And locked it in a secret cave.
No one knows where the secret cave is.
But this magic doesn't last forever.
So the monster can be released.
And later, we have to find out...
...who's the descendant of the magic...
...that can lock the monster inside.
I'm surprised.
How can a snake talk to you?
I'm surprised too.
But I used to talk to a snake.
Maybe it's the descendant of the magic.
No way.
I can't be the descendant of the magic.
I'm new here.
No way.
You can be the descendant of the magic.
How can you lock the monster inside?
Did your parents ever tell you about Grandpa?
I don't know them.
I don't even know who they are.
My parents said...
...they died a good man.
You're such a coward.
Okay, I'll listen to you.
We have to learn magic from him.
If not, we'll be locked in a cave.
Yes.
I want to learn too.
Let's learn together.
What's that?
It's a small snake.
I can get rid of it.
Right?
Because it's a king snake.
You pretended to be sick, didn't you?
You're exaggerating.
No, I'm not.
It looks like they're more confident now.
Because they've got a new magic.
That's good.
But we can't give up.
We have to find out about these attacks.
What about Professor Purwa?
Do you have any leads?
The book doesn't mention...
...what kind of monster it is.
Its shape.
Especially its weakness.
If it's like this,
how can we defeat it?
And we can't go home.
Because the village gate is haunted...
...by a very powerful magic.
We're all trapped here.
Alva.
It's so scary.
What's wrong, Vega?
The teachers already know about the monster.
But they covered us...
...so we won't be scared.
What's worse,
the village gate is haunted...
...by a very powerful magic...
...so the students can't get out.
That's why...
...Professor Alibari can't get in here.
Look.
I think someone's watching us.
How is it?
The monster has attacked two of our students.
How much longer?
How much longer do I have to wait?
Soon, sir.
They're locked in the village.
All the students will turn into stone.
Including that special student, sir.
So...
...you just have to wait.
What took you so long?
I'm bored here.
I want to go back to school.
Really?
The food isn't tasty at school.
Yes.
You told me...
...you want to eat chocolate alone.
Yes, share it with me.
If you want.
Here.
My chocolate!
Give it back!
Rita, what's wrong?
My chocolate...
...was taken...
...by Jack and Mike.
They ran away.
That's a problem, kid.
I know.
In a situation like this...
...it's still a problem.
Rita, don't be sad.
I'll chase them.
Don't worry.
I'll go with you.
Ray, don't be late.
Let's go.
It smells good.
What's wrong?
Why did you stop?
Let's chase Jack and Mike.
Okay.
Let's go.
My stomach hurts.
Mike, wait for me!
Mike.
Mike!
That's Jack's voice.
Maybe it's another monster.
Let's go.
Mike!
Help!
I'm scared, Prof.
Jack saw Mike being attacked.
That's why he's still in shock.
Enough.
Take them inside.
I'm sorry, Professor Purwa.
Let Mike handle it.
Let's go.
Alva, let's go with them.
How?
Do you want to try?
Yes.
Kids.
Don't go anywhere.
Stay here...
...and be alert.
Alva.
To be continued...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
If you drink that...
...you'll be calm.
Tell me what happened.
Just now...
...I was putting on my shoes.
Then, Mike ran away.
Then, the monster came.
It was scary.
Then, it turned Mike into a rock.
He just disappeared...
...at the crime scene.
Usually, students are attacked...
...when they're alone.
Professor Agni.
Let's read his mind.
Yes, Professor.
Ouch.
It hurts.
Mike, wait for me.
Hurry up.
To be continued...
Mike!
The monster is scary.
I think...
...the monster likes chocolate.
That's weird.
How can a monster like that...
...like chocolate?
To be continued...
Wait a minute, Professor Purwa.
I have to make sure of something.
To be continued...
How is it, Professor Agni?
I think it's true.
When Tole was attacked...
...chocolate was there.
And when Nick was attacked...
...Nick's test...
...he was carrying chocolate.
Megantara.
Go back to your students.
Watch them.
Don't let anyone panic.
And take care of them.
Don't let anyone pass the village gate.
It can be very dangerous for them.
Yes, Professor.
To be continued...
How is Jake, Megantara?
Don't worry.
Jake is resting now.
He's sleeping.
What about Mike?
Mike is being treated now.
Medicine with mushroom.
Aren't you afraid?
We're not afraid.
Right, guys?
Good.
Who said we're not afraid?
This place is getting more dangerous.
But it's our turn now.
Guys, let's get out of here.
Do you agree?
Now we know...
...the monster likes chocolate.
So, we have to warn our friends...
...not to eat chocolate.
I agree.
So, they won't be attacked by monsters.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
We're late.
I'm scared.
They're running away.
I'll go through the village gate.
I have to stop them.
Tantara.
Where are you going?
Now...
...it's time for the monster to do its job.
To be continued...
If you want to run away, come on.
Now, go back to your house.
We want to go home.
This place is getting more dangerous.
So, that's all you got?
Did you hear that?
You're special kids.
You're spoiled kids...
...who are not owned by other kids.
If you're cowards...
...and have no courage...
...what's the difference between you and other kids?
Do you know why you're still asked to stay here?
Do you?
Look at this.
Tantara.
This place...
...has been haunted by a very evil black magic.
If we go through it...
...all of you will be destroyed.
What should we do, Tantara?
What should we do?
Let's fight it.
Remember.
Be aware.
You're special kids.
Go back to being farmers.
Go back to being brave.
Agree?
Agree!
Louder. Agree?
Brave?
Brave!
That's it.
Now...
...you know the situation.
But...
...don't be shocked by the situation.
You have to calm down...
...and be ready to face it.
You have to be happy.
We can't. We're scared.
Yes, we're scared.
This fear is our enemy's target.
If we're scared, the enemy will be happy.
But if we're happy...
...the enemy will be jealous of us.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
That's good.
I'm sorry.
Alright.
Mr. Futar!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
It's not fun.
I want to win.
I want to win!
What if we lose?
What if we win?
Mr. Futar!
Now, it's your turn.
I'm so happy.
Sometimes, I play alone.
I don't have friends here.
But from now on...
...you won't be lonely.
Because we're your friends.
But if you go back to school, I'll be lonely.
I promise.
We'll come here often.
Wait a minute.
Mr. Futar!
I think they're having fun.
I'm going to use this situation.
What are you doing here?
What?
You're going to make a mess, right?
You're right.
And you.
You're going to help me commit that crime.
Opo.
Are you going to help me commit a crime?
Hush.
What's this?
This is a communication mirror.
If we use this mirror, we can communicate even from a distance.
Cool.
Let's try it.
Let's go.
Mr. Vega.
Can you see me?
Yes, I can.
Of course, I can.
Be careful, Mr. Vega.
He's going to hurt you.
I know how to make you happy.
How?
How about we make something delicious?
What is it?
Let's go.
Good.
Very good.
Finally, my plan went well.
And now...
It's time for Monster Legenda to do its job.
You have to destroy all the chocolates in the village.
If necessary, destroy all the chocolate trees there.
So the villagers can't make chocolates anymore.
Yes, sir.
And remember, watch the children.
Their safety is very important.
Yes, sir.
I will try to find another way to get into the village.
Hey, you're wrong.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
Milk?
What?
Kawat, Kawat.
We're in danger.
Danger? What do you mean, Popo?
You stupid kid.
I taught you how to make chocolate.
Kids? Who are you?
I'm your friend.
What are you doing?
Watch out.
Hold on.
There are kids making chocolate.
Chocolate?
That means...
That means the monster is coming.
Yes, we're in danger.
We have to stop it.
Let's go.
The monster is coming.
Run.
This looks delicious.
Mom.
Tommy, Tommy.
Don't eat the chocolate.
Hurry, throw it away.
We're tired of making chocolate.
Then, why did you tell us to throw it away?
I don't know.
Tommy, Jack.
This chocolate is dangerous.
It can lure the monster here.
Don't lie.
No monster likes chocolate.
It's you.
Guys, take care of the chocolate.
Don't let Alva eat it.
I don't want to be told.
Go away.
Tantara.
I smell chocolate here.
Yes, Tantara. They want chocolate.
Yes.
I don't understand.
Why is there so much chocolate here?
Tantara told us to have fun.
But, we're making chocolate.
It's delicious.
Now, throw all the chocolate away.
Why?
The chocolate is delicious.
This chocolate...
...will make a disaster for all of you.
Do you know...
...why Mike, Jack, and Tole...
...become bandits?
Because they ate the chocolate.
If you're still making chocolate, it means you're ready to be eaten by the monster.
Tantara.
Oh, God.
Go...
...and deliver the food...
...to the Japanese.
Do your job...
...and destroy them.
To be continued...
This is the only way...
...to defeat the monster.
Dafatang Afangsa!
To be continued...
Yippie!
There's another man.
Why is that man calling us?
He must be working for us.
Hey, young ladies.
I'm here...
...to invite you to a fight.
What?
A fight?
Yes.
The loser...
...must follow the winner.
What do you think?
Why?
Are you scared?
It's okay.
We're never scared.
Especially with a man.
Come here.
Let's get changed.
Enough.
I admit defeat.
You're amazing, Putri Angsa.
We don't believe what men say.
Thank you.
Okay.
Now...
...you can punish me.
Anything.
But please, don't put me in the water.
Because I'm afraid of water.
Especially in this lake, there's a hole...
...that can lead to the magic village.
Don't take me there.
I'm afraid of the place. I'm afraid of the hole.
He's afraid of the hole.
Let's just take him there.
He's also scared.
Because you're afraid of water...
...we'll take you to the magic village.
Come here.
Let's go.
Thank you for showing me the way.
One.
Two.
Three.
Six.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Imran!
The snake's eyes are shining.
Now you have to remember, Alva.
Don't look at those shining eyes.
Remember.
Don't ever look at those shining eyes.
Don't ever...
...look at those shining eyes.
Those are the snake's eyes.
Guys!
Don't look at the snake's eyes!
Help!
Wait for me!
Run!
It's dangerous. I have to help them.
No, it's dangerous.
Just run.
Help!
Don't!
Alva!
It's so close!
Yes.
I'm coming!
Damn it.
Vi!
It's so close.
This is fun.
Wake up!
Vi!
Alva!
Don't look at the snake's eyes!
Help!
I'm glad I'm not a stone yet.
Is that all?!
Look carefully!
What's that update?
When someone's appeared in the blink of an eye.
Except one person.
What the hell is that?!
Who are you...?
Mike!
Mike?
Why did you turn into a stone?
Anis also turned into a stone.
Oh...
Hey, Mike!
He's dead.
Let's attack him.
Let's go, Vilan!
To be continued...
Why are you panicking?
What are you two doing here?
Praise be to God.
It's a normal quest.
Normal?
What happened to me?
Why did you turn into a stone?
Enough.
Let's get out of here.
I'm sure our friends know what happened to us.
Let's go.
To be continued...
We have to get out of here.
Take the children out of this village.
I've found a way to get out of this village.
But, Professor.
What about the mantra that has blocked this village?
That mantra is for us.
As soon as we get out, that mantra will be gone.
Rey! Rey!
Wake up, Rey!
Rey! Wake up!
Alva.
Alva didn't get eaten by a monster, did she?
No.
Let's go.
Is everything messed up?
What's going on?
Maybe they're playing a war game.
Guys, look!
We got Rey!
Kids, let's go back to school.
Professor, what about the monster?
We managed to get rid of the monster.
But, it's not dead yet.
You guys have to stay alert.
And now, we have to go back to school.
Take the children to a safer place.
But, the teachers and I will come back here to get rid of the monster.
Thank you, Professor Ladebaran.
Rita, I have to go.
You'll come back here, won't you?
Of course.
But, don't forget.
We'll contact you through this phone, okay?
To be continued...
This well connects to the lake around our school.
And we'll go in there one by one.
As soon as you get in, you have to swim as fast as you can to the lake.
You'll pair up.
And the teachers will help you.
Wait!
Don't think that you can leave this village so easily.
It's nice to meet you, Angkara.
But, unfortunately, we have to say goodbye.
Oh, don't be arrogant, Ladebaran.
The science that I'm in charge of now is much better than the last time we fought.
Angkara.
Don't talk too much.
You can't even beat me.
How can you beat Professor Ladebaran?
Professor, it's better if you bring your children.
So that I can face you.
To be continued...
I haven't lost.
And I will never lose.
To be continued...
Everyone is home.
I'm the only one left.
Hi, Mahlis.
I don't want an accident because of me.
I have to handle this.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
To be continued...
Alhamdulillah, there's someone inside.
Help.
Felita, what's wrong with you?
Felita.
Help me. I'm scared.
Hello, everyone.
Felita is in my hands.
And you tell Alfa...
if Alfa still wants this child to live...
then he has to surrender himself.
Basar Ninjik.
It's up to you what you want to say, Alfa.
The important thing is you have to find me quickly.
Felita and Antaboga will be waiting for you.
Huh? Antaboga?
Your time is only 1x24 hours.
If you're late...
then this child will be gone forever.
Forever.
I will return to Sihir Village...
to lock that monster in Gua Krama.
Take care of the children.
And stay alert.
Because Angkara won't give up so easily.
He will definitely do anything.
I'm sorry, sir.
But the professor can do it.
Because as far as I know...
according to the legend...
only the descendants of Masati...
can open and close that cave.
I will keep trying...
so the people of Sihir Village can live in peace.
Alfa!
Don't be stubborn.
If you go there alone...
you will be attacked by those monsters.
Yes, sir.
Let's report it to the soldiers and the professor.
I'm sure they will accompany you.
Besides, if you go with the professor...
you will be protected.
Yes, sir.
The professor can turn into a bird.
Professor Agni can also turn into a cat.
The soldiers can also change.
No.
I have to help him.
Alfa, don't be stubborn.
No.
I will go back alone.
I don't want anyone to be in danger because of me.
I have to do this.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Alfa!
Why is it so close?
Let's report it to the professor.
You're evil!
You left me!
I can be miserable.
I can be in pain.
I can die!
Popo.
Alfa.
It didn't work.
Popo, what are you doing here?
Nothing.
I'm just sitting here.
Why did you come back?
I'm looking for the treasure cave.
Do you know where it is?
What?
What are you doing there?
Lita was kidnapped.
Lita was captured.
I have to help her.
Do you know?
I don't know.
Good.
Accompany me there.
Alfa.
It's so scary there.
There are ghosts.
Popo has a bad experience with ghosts.
Experience?
What kind of experience?
At that time...
Popo accidentally...
fell into the cave.
And...
Popo met a ghost.
What?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
What is that sound?
The sound of a flute played by the Dark Lord made Antaboga calm and calm.
And since then, Popo became close to the Dark Lord.
Oh, so Antaboga can be calm if we play the flute?
Oh, I can play the flute.
Not just any flute, Antaboga likes a special music.
If you make a mistake, just hit the note.
You can be angry, you can be slapped by Antaboga.
You teach Antaboga the flute note.
How? I'll think about it.
Come on, Popo. Teach me, please.
Okay, I'll teach you.
Seriously?
Even if you don't like it, even if you're forced to.
Thank you, Popo.
I'm going back to that village.
Pelita wants to be kidnapped by Professor Rangkara.
And Professor Rangkara said,
Alva must go there.
No one accompanies her, she must go alone.
If not, Pelita will be in trouble.
Hooray, I can!
Yeah!
Thank you for teaching me.
Popo is hugged.
Usually, all gods treat Popo with love.
Love is not something you should bring on a journey.
What do you really know about her?
Unfortunately, you're too late to find out.
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, strive with all your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we will