To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
It's locked.
What should I do?
I'm getting more and more scared.
I think this is an attack.
Then, Professor, what is this?
This is one of the special powers of one of the students in this school.
What about Alfa?
Alfa has been locked inside twice.
I was bitten by Alfa.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
This is messed up.
Alfa must be in pain.
I have to help Alfa.
Hey!
There's a snake eating a stone and a papaya.
Guard!
Open the door for me!
Open the door!
Open the door for me, quick!
I'm holding the door handle.
Guard!
Open the door!
I'm freezing, Prof.
I'm freezing.
I'm cold.
I'm freezing to death.
I can't move, Prof.
I have to get the firecracker.
But, Professor,
the firecracker is in the highest tower in the school,
and I have to move.
There's no other way.
Only the firecracker can warm this room.
Ami,
you take the firecracker
and give me this bell.
Yes, Prof.
Davatang,
give me the bell.
Megantara,
come back quickly.
The magic school is in trouble.
And I have brought the bell back,
because Dana is freezing.
Davatang,
give me the bell.
I'm freezing.
Davatang,
find Megantara.
I'm so hungry.
Me too.
Thank you for finishing your meal.
Now, it's time for you to drink juice.
Yes, drink juice.
MEGANTARA
What are you doing?
Run!
I'm lost.
I have to do this.
Yes, Mega. You have to be patient.
I have to do this. I have to fight this for Alva.
MEGANTARA
You did that for me?
Alva, what's wrong?
Alva!
It's so bad.
My body is covered in snake skin.
What should I do?
MEGANTARA
It's so weird.
Every time I send a letter, I have to type it first.
It's here.
This is Professor Ardebar's trademark.
It means,
there's something important at school.
What should I do?
Alva's business is not done yet.
There's another problem.
Don't type my words.
It's useless. Just type it.
Delete it.
He's so used to type.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
But, wait.
Wait until Alva's business is done.
Wow.
That's so cool.
If this is the way,
I don't have to do homework anymore.
You're such a lazy kid.
That's why you're always left behind.
Go back to Professor Agni.
MEGANTARA
This is so cool.
It's so weird.
I feel like he's gone.
MEGANTARA
Now, you have to do another test.
It's a board painting competition.
Here's the rule.
You have to do it manually.
No magic.
No mantra.
The last one...
will be eliminated and can't continue to the next stage.
Please go to the painting house.
Painting is easy.
But, I'm not good at it.
Both of you will fail.
You know,
there's a saying,
A blank can't find the sound.
It means,
a person is noisy but has no brain.
I'm sorry.
If a ghost fights a human,
the ghost will win.
Who said that?
Humans are more noble.
So, humans will win.
Ghost.
Human.
You have to paint the wall that has your name on it.
Do it neatly and quickly.
The one who takes the longest,
the most messy,
will be eliminated.
We'll start on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Twenty.
Vega.
You shouldn't be like this.
Because of me
you end up losing.
It's okay.
Our goal here
is to get the joint.
So if one of us lost,
what else could we do?
The important thing is you have to move on.
You have to win.
Okay?
Just make sure
my fight with Ray is not in vain.
Thank you, Vega.
I'm sorry, Vega.
You have to go home now.
I'm sorry.
Vega.
You failed.
Vega?
What else could I do?
I have to check.
After that,
Alva is so weak.
I have to help her.
And I still lose.
Vega.
What about you?
You know Alva is weak.
Why did you let her win?
But the way of life
is to love Alva.
What about you?
Oh, right.
I forgot.
Why didn't I think of that earlier?
Yes.
I regret
to let Alva win.
Hey.
Shut up.
A wild boar eats a pond snail.
Vega is not stupid.
Vega is just nice.
Whatever the reason,
fighting and sacrificing for a friend
will never pay off.
But, soldier.
You don't have to say that.
It's better for Vega
to fight for a friend
and work hard
than you
to fail
because you don't want to eat vegetables.
Vegetable chicken.
This is the final round.
The final round
will determine
who is worthy
to get the life fluid.
You have to run
until the finish line.
Whoever arrives first
is the winner.
Remember.
You can't use any magic here.
I'm exhausted.
But, I won't give up.
I won.
I believe in you, Vega.
One.
Two.
Three.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Hurry up.
Alva,
come on.
It won't take that long.
Let's just run.
I'm sure I'll win.
This is called
winning without fighting.
I'm excited.
I can't do this.
I'll just wait.
Alva.
Alva, wake up.
You guys.
Wake up, Alva.
You can't die.
But,
I can't take it anymore.
My body hurts.
Alva.
You can't use your friends' fight.
I'm sorry.
They've sacrificed for you.
Don't let them be in vain.
Alva.
Alva, wake up.
Vega,
you shouldn't be like this.
Because of me,
you lost.
It's okay.
You're here to win.
So, if one of us lose,
what are we going to do?
We just have to move on.
You have to win.
Okay?
You're right.
These are my friends.
Good, Alva.
Now, stand up.
And be brave.
Be brave.
You're right.
We have to move on.
I won't give up.
Now,
it's time to say goodbye to the ghost.
It's so scary.
To be continued...
Thank God.
This firecracker is really useful.
But we can't continue like this, Professor.
We have to find the informant.
And stop him before he freezes this school.
You're right.
We have to find the informant.
I order all teachers to find the informant.
Split up to find him.
Kids.
You stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
I will leave the firecracker here.
So, you won't be left behind.
To be continued...
Life.
Because you're at the finish line at the same time,
you both have to take the liquid of life.
The one who finishes first,
is the one who gets the liquid of life.
One.
Two.
Three.
Start!
Yes! I did it!
I did it!
I lost.
I didn't get the liquid of life.
Even though,
I thought I've sacrificed a lot for you.
Now, it's time for you to leave me.
I will be a beautiful human now.
Yes!
Where's the bottle?
Eva.
Did you take the bottle?
Give it back.
You're so mean.
I don't know.
Why is it in my hand?
But...
It's gone.
Where is it?
It's not here.
Alva.
What are you doing?
Give it back.
It's mine.
I don't know.
Raya.
In this competition,
the participants have to be honest and fair.
They can't cheat.
What?
You've cheated and you're not sporty by pushing Alva.
So, you're out.
And we decided,
Alva won this competition.
Yes!
Thank you, jury.
Thank you so much.
Flita.
Where are you?
She's not here.
Then,
let's just look for my crystal ball.
Okay.
Hurry up and look for it.
Daftar,
crystal ball.
There she is.
I found it.
What happened to my crystal ball?
I'm so sorry.
Soon,
we'll know where Flita is.
My little sister,
why are you crying?
Who are you?
I'm Pangeran,
from a faraway country.
I'm here to find Flita.
Why are you crying here?
I'm a weirdo.
Everyone hates me.
I don't want to be friends anymore.
I'm sorry.
Then, we're the same.
What do you mean?
I don't have friends anymore.
Almost everyone in this world hates me.
I'm considered a troublemaker.
What if we become friends?
But, are you afraid of me?
I have a weird power.
I can freeze everyone.
Since we're friends,
I'll tell you my secret.
I also have a weird power.
I can't freeze.
Flita
Are you sure you want to be friends with me?
Hold my hand.
You can see for yourself.
I can't freeze.
Professor Aldebaran,
I got a message from Professor Agni.
School is in danger.
But, who's going to do it?
We can do it
Who's that?
Where's Aldebaran?
Ri, wake up.
Look, it's morning.
What time is it?
I want to ask you something.
Alfa hasn't come yet.
Where's Alfa?
Alfa hasn't come yet?
Alfa hasn't come yet.
I'm scared.
Alfa?
What's wrong with you?
You succeeded, right?
Are you okay?
No.
Alfa.
What's wrong?
You must be possessed by a very evil spell.
What kind of spell is this?
Alfa.
You're possessed.
Alfa, congratulations.
You succeeded.
Come here.
Alfa.
I'm so relieved.
Finally, you're safe.
Yes, Alfa.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Here.
Centara.
Forgive me.
But...
Thank you, Centara.
Centara.
Forgive me.
Thank you, Centara.
What's wrong, Centara?
What's wrong?
I almost forgot.
We...
must go to school immediately.
Why?
This is a letter from Professor Ali Baran.
I got a letter from him.
Our school is in danger.
What?
Danger?
What danger?
Yes.
So, we must go back to school immediately.
This letter...
will make us...
able to go to school.
Let's go.
Hold this.
Ready?
Ready.
Welcome, Alfa.
I'm glad...
you're safe now.
Thank you, Professor.
Professor Ali Baran.
I got a letter from Professor Aki.
Our school is in danger.
But...
who did this?
It was Plita.
Plita?
But, that's impossible.
We didn't expect it either.
But, it turns out...
Plita has a special ability.
But, unfortunately...
she can't control that ability yet.
So, when she's angry,
angry,
sad,
feeling lonely,
scared,
that power can come out.
And whatever touches her...
can freeze.
So, where is Plita now?
Until now, we haven't been able to find her.
Telescope.
Ray.
Try using this telescope.
Where is Plita?
Let's go.
The food is so delicious.
There's ice cream,
peanuts,
meatballs.
Ray.
Focus.
Find where is Plita.
You always think about food.
It's cold.
I'm hungry.
Plita.
I want to see Plita.
That's her.
That's Plita.
Alpha.
Plita is with a man in a veil.
But, who is that, Prof?
Or maybe...
Professor Ankara.
But, they look different.
Plita.
I brought you some warm chocolate.
Here.
To keep your body warm.
I want to see Plita.
Plita.
Wake up, Plita.
Wait.
Who are you?
TO BE CONTINUED...
Popo?
We can do it.
Alpha.
Where are you?
Where are you, Po?
Alpha.
That's Aldebar's voice.
I can't face him with this kind of power.
TO BE CONTINUED...
Alpha.
Wake up.
You're a handsome boy.
Why do you look like this?
Alpha.
Who did this to you?
TO BE CONTINUED...
How is it, Professor?
It's nothing.
We should all go back to Earth.
Let's help Alpha.
Megantara's feeling says...
...that Professor Aldebaran...
...is hiding something.
To Be Continued...
How long are we going to stay here?
It's going to be a long time.
Be patient.
Professor is trying to make us all recover.
Let's just wait here.
Because of our monster, we're like this.
The school is frozen.
We can't play.
Let's just wait.
We'll know if we want to go back.
I'm worried, Bi.
So, this is how you play when you're cold?
I know how to make the most of this situation.
To Be Continued...
If Chris isn't here...
...they'll all be in trouble.
And Aldebaran won't be able to use his magic...
...because it's too cold.
To Be Continued...
Bobo?
Where are you taking me?
I'm taking you to a place where you can rest.
I don't want to.
I want to go down.
Calm down.
I'll stop.
You can go down.
To Be Continued...
Let's go, Bobo.
This boy is so nice.
He always says hi to me.
And his friends at school...
She's lying.
I'm the one who threw the ball to her head.
Just throw it away.
I didn't do anything wrong.
She kicked me out of school.
Because I don't want to see her again.
She did it herself.
I want to go with her.
I want to be kicked out of this school.
Guys, let's go.
Why are we wasting time with her?
Let's just go with her.
Let's go.
To Be Continued...
Calm down, El.
I didn't mean any harm.
Why are you here?
I want to tell you a secret.
To Be Continued...
Although his face was slightly injured...
The bad news is...
The eighth prince has taken Plita away.
Purwa.
I want you to find Plita.
As soon as you find her, let me know.
Yes, Professor.
All of you can go back to the clinic.
And stay alert.
I will call Alfa.
To train her to be stronger.
Because one day...
She might meet the eighth prince.
Yes, Professor.
To Be Continued...
He was right.
Professor wants to see me.
Alfa.
I called you here...
Because I want to teach you...
The Pegasus Mantra.
Pegasus Mantra?
What is that, Professor?
Pegasus Mantra...
Is a mantra...
That can create friends when you're alone.
And you have to fight strong enemies.
Like before.
I will set an example for you.
Pegasus!
That's so cool.
Alfa.
Now, go to me.
Yes, Professor.
Alfa.
My friend...
Will protect me until the end.
Be careful.
And I can pull myself away from the enemy.
Or distract the enemy's attention.
Pegasus!
Alfa.
What animal do you like the most?
Garuda, Professor.
Very good.
Now...
Concentrate.
And imagine Garuda's feather on your head.
Then...
Say the Pegasus Mantra.
Concentrate, Alfa.
Yes, Professor.
Pegasus!
Why is it a chicken?
Alfa.
Your enemy can't be afraid of a chicken.
Come on, try again.
Pegasus!
Wow.
He's so young.
I'm going to be laughed at by the enemy.
Alright, Alfa.
That's all for today.
Now, you should rest.
We'll continue tomorrow.
Yes, Professor.
I'll go now.
To be continued...
What were you doing there?
I was taught a new mantra.
A new mantra?
Yes.
So that I can be stronger than the enemy.
Who was the enemy you met?
Yes.
I asked around.
I'm so worried.
I don't know.
I'm worried about my brother.
Don't worry, Alfa.
The dark side.
Who did this?
Come out!
To be continued...
Ksatria, Alfa.
It's been a long time, Professor Purwa.
He hasn't told me anything yet.
There's a letter.
We want you to meet one of your teachers.
Meet us...
...in the snow forest at the end of the forest.
Who is he, Professor?
I don't know.
But I'll go there.
I'll go with you.
To be continued...
Wait.
Calm down.
We don't want to cause any trouble.
Aldebaran.
Is it true?
You're the one who stole our fire crystal?
You want to kiss my cheek?
That's too much.
Don't dream.
I'm Professor Aldebaran.
I'm not a thief.
Don't lie.
The one who stole the fire crystal...
...was our brother, Pancas.
Yes.
Pancas is my twin brother.
And we heard that...
...Pancas is dead.
Popo is missing.
And until now...
...we haven't found the crystal that Pancas had.
And someone told us...
...that the crystal...
...is now in Silvia's school.
And our assistant, Popo...
...has turned him into an assassin.
Calm down.
Be patient.
I'll tell you what really happened.
A few years ago...
...I met Pancas.
At that time...
...Pancas was fighting the 8th Prince.
...I saw that Pancas was exhausted...
...and was about to lose.
And when I tried to save him...
...he was badly injured.
I couldn't save him.
PANCAS
This guy...
...has a very valuable firecracker.
So, in the end...
...Pancas gave the firecracker to me.
So, I didn't steal the firecracker.
He gave it to me.
Don't lie to us.
Yes.
How can we believe...
...that Pancas was killed?
You...
...shouldn't accuse Professor Aldebaran.
PANCAS
Aldebaran.
We'll give you until tomorrow morning.
If you don't come back...
...and our servants are no longer normal...
...we'll attack the magic school.
And your teacher...
Your teacher will never come back.
A man's dog...
...eats a man's dog.
Are they patriots...
...or traitors?
If they come, they're not invited.
If they go home, they're not escorted.
How is this possible?
We can't give them the firecracker.
If we give them the firecracker...
...the children will die of cold.
What do we do, Gantara?
Do we have to defend them?
I'm worried they'll hurt Purwa.
But I'm sure Professor Purwa can handle it.
Because he has very high knowledge.
He's lying. We didn't do that.
We didn't steal the firecracker.
He's a traitor.
He's behind all of this.
It's all clear now.
Lita.
You have to make a decision.
Either you stay here with me...
...or you go with them.
To be continued...