To be continued...
The power of the heart
Go, go, go
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can do it
Why was he sent to a magic school?
Three days until the full moon
And what if in the full moon
The dark prince gets his divine stone
He will get unlimited power
And will destroy this world
I will prove that I'm right
Just wait and see
I will not let anyone disturb my mission
To take the stone to eternity
And from now on
The school has decided
That Alva will not be expelled from the school
Good night
Alva, let's eat together
Let's eat, come on
Okay, let's go
Come on, let's eat, don't just sleep
It's hot
Why are you shaking like that?
I got a pimple
If it's a pimple, just do it
I'm afraid my food will be eaten by the khalijan
No, just do it
Really?
Yes, there's a toilet over there
Hurry up
The toilet is still down there
The toilet is still far away
There's a lake there
I'll go to the lake
I want to meet the guards
Alvaro!
Let me go!
You will regret it because you have caught me
And don't you think
The 8th prince will not arise
Because you have caught me
Terror will not end here
And in the end
You will lose
This school will be destroyed
Let me go!
Watch him
Yes, sir
Let me go!
Don't let the students hear his scream
Yes, sir
Let me go!
Alvaro!
Students
Now I will teach you
How to destroy the enemy's weapons
You pay attention, okay?
Lepafa weapon
Now it's time for you to practice
Try Ray and...
Tole
Where's Tole?
I can't find Tole
I don't know where Tole is
What should we do?
Professor Adni
Please excuse me for a moment
Students
I have told you thousands of times
Gorilla, moro
Dream of a giraffe
If you want to be a child, don't be a coward
Throw the rest of the food in the trash
Who did this?
Hey, Alva
That's Tole's chicken
That's right
Now he's a chicken
Because he's afraid of me
Megantara
Where did you get that chicken from?
Near the lake
He swallowed it
Then he ate it with me
That's so cute
Here, Karim
This is a gift for your birthday
Why only for me?
Here, Karim
This is for you
Thank you, Nick
You're welcome, Karim
Nick, Nick
Why is it shaking?
I don't know
Karim
Professor
Karim is kidnapped
How did it happen?
We were lost in the lake
A few dogs followed us
Karim just disappeared
What should we do?
Calm down, kids
Megantara
You should take the kids back to school
Tell the others
Don't leave the school until it's safe
Yes, Professor
Come on, kids
Follow me
Megantara
I have to go back to the lake
Who knows
If I can save Tole
I might be a champion like Alva
Come on, kids
Follow me
Come on
And this is our savior
Rey
She saved Tole and Karim from the attack
Hold this
Where's Rey?
Where is she?
That's Rey
Why is she there?
She's not far
Wait
Something's not right
She's not like this
Let's follow her
Maybe she has a plan
Let's go
I can't be afraid
Because I'm going to be the champion
But
I don't know what she's like
What if she's fierce?
What if I get bitten?
Tole's friend
What are you doing here?
We're going to the lake
We're going to beat up the guy who kidnapped your friend
Tole
He's a good friend
Good
I'm sorry
We're not good
We just want to be champions
We don't care about Tole's friend
He's just like me
I want to be a champion too
What if we go there together?
Let's go
Where is she?
I don't know
Maybe she's at the lake
We have to find her
Let's go
Where do you want to go?
All students are ordered to leave the school
Go back
Or I'll give you a punishment
Why are you making a mountain out of a molehill?
B-U-K-A-K
B-U-K
Why are there so many of you?
Why are there eight of you?
Kak Karim?
Kak Karim, wake up
Get up
Where am I?
I don't know either
We must be escaped here by Duyung
Mama, Papa
I'm scared, Budak
Help
Where are you?
I'm sorry, Tom. It's scary
It's so scary, Tom. We don't know who's in front of us
We're trapped
If Duyung doesn't show up, let's fish him
Then we catch him
What should we do, Tom? Duyung is not here
Yes, Tom
Someone must swim to the middle
Please, Tom
I can't swim
You know I can't swim
Don't tempt me
I don't feel good, Tom
Yes, Tom
Don't you dare
Okay, let's do this
If you lose, you have to swim to the middle
There's a fly
Let's catch it
I'll go with you
If I get caught, my mom will be mad
Tom, do you want to be expelled from this school?
Yes, Tom
It means one of you has to swim
Let's swim again
Yes
Two more
It means you and Ray have to swim
If you lose, you have to swim to the middle
Yes!
It should be him
Jacky can't swim
He's already drowning before he reaches the middle
Don't waste time, let's swim
Shoot!
Go to the middle
I have to swim to the middle
You want to be a swimmer, right?
Yes
Let's swim
Hurry up, Ray
Let's go
Hurry up, Jacky
Hurry up, Ray
Hurry up
Don't swim too far
Go to the middle
You want to be a swimmer, right?
Yes
Let's go
What are you going to do?
Hurry up
Guys!
Attack!
Help!
Help me!
Do you think it's easy to beat a swimmer?
Do you think you're great?
Because of your behavior, some students have to be treated in the treatment clinic
Until there's a serious problem, this school can be closed
What do you want?
No, sir
Now, all of you go back to the dormitory
And no one can leave the school without any reason
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am
All of you, I order you to clean the school toilet without magic
What are you waiting for? Go there!
Now, I want to talk to Professor Alubarai
I'll go with you, Professor
Let's go
I'm sure that the swimmers are just being treated
It seems like there's a bigger force controlling them
I agree, the swimmers are good
Good?
They kidnapped the students and hurt them
That's right, Professor
Nine people were hurt and three of them are missing
And if the parents find out, this school can be closed
I think we should take action against the swimmers
I disagree
The swimmers are good
If we don't take action against the swimmers, there will be more victims
We have to take action now
I agree
To be continued...
Help!
Dad!
Stop the attack!
They can hurt the students
We should be able to defeat the swimmers
But we can't do anything
They kidnapped Karin, Tole, and Rey
That's right
Sir, Rey was kidnapped by the swimmers
We have to help her
They are so stubborn
They are stubborn
I told you, they won't listen
The swimmers are good
There must be a reason
Soldier!
Why did you have to scare me?
What is it?
Do you know that Rey was kidnapped by Putri Duyung?
Yes, I know
We want to talk to Rey
Do you know what her weakness is?
I don't know
But Putri Angsa might know
Where are you going?
We want to find Putri Angsa
Ouch!
Ava, I'm going to call Angsa
And you better hide
Angsa doesn't like men
What is it, Angsa?
What is it, Vega?
Is there anything we can do?
Here's the thing, Angsa
The swimmers are attacking us
And my friends are being attacked by the swimmers
I want to help
That's weird
As far as I know, Duyung is a good person
Really?
But why are they attacking my friends?
I don't know
But as far as I know, Duyung doesn't like to attack people
They prefer to have sex
And if they have sex, it can last for hours
Is it true, girls?
It's true
We got Vega's weakness
Duyung likes to watch
So, we have to bring them to the mirror
There's a man!
Help!
Ava, don't go out
He doesn't like men
Help!
They're so fierce
Stop playing
We're almost there
Let's go
To be continued...
We got Vega!
We got the mirror!
We got the net!
Are you blind?
If you want to be free, answer my question
You're our friend
Why do you have to help them?
It's so late, Vega
We'll meet them tomorrow
Let's go
What's that sound?
Let's check it out
We got the mirror!
Duyung!
Yes!
Let's get ready
This is perfect, Mike
If we bring them to the mirror, we can be heroes
Yes, bro
We can be famous than Tommy
You're right
Let's go
It's so heavy
Shut up!
It's heavy!
It's coming!
Why are you two being chased by the devil?
It's not true
We attacked Duyung
Both of you went to the lake
Duyung is at the back of the school
Are you serious?
Yes, I am
That's why it's so dangerous
We have to get out of this school
I'll call my parents
Where are they?
There must be something
Vega!
He's bleeding!
We have to help him
Why did he run away?
I don't know
Maybe he's afraid of us
Let's give him the mirror
So he can calm down
Mirror!
It's broken
Medicine!
Here you go
Duyung!
That's not fair
They're friends with Duyung
Maybe they're the ones who planned the terror
I have to report this
He's smiling
That means he's not angry anymore
Maybe he knows that we're going to cure his face
I think he wants to kiss you
Duyung!
Now we're friends, right?
Answer me!
Where are my friends?
The lake!
What is this for?
Eat it
What is this?
I read in a book
The mirror from Duyung
Can make the person who eats it
Breathe in the water
That's so cool!
It feels so weird
But now we can breathe in the water, right?
Show your spirit
Get your friends ready
Run, run, jump, climb the tower
Be brave
Don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go!
You're in jail
They're in the lake
Don't!
You have to attack my friends
Where are our friends?
Where are they?
You don't want to tell me?
Where are you taking us?
Don't!
Don't do it!
You're in jail!
They're here!
Wake up, Vega!
Vega, wake up!
Vega!
You bought soap using a table
And you're playing hide and seek
Don't do it!
It's because of you!
Hide!
We better bring Vega to the clinic
Hurry, Megantara
Let's go!
Dr. Pertiwi!
Where's Dr. Pertiwi?
Dr. Pertiwi?
Why are you here?
I need Dr. Pertiwi
Dr. Pertiwi ran away
Ran away?
Why did he run away?
Dr. Pertiwi ran away
Professor Adebaran told him to go to a nearby village
To treat people with diseases
So I'm the one who's in charge
Okay, that's enough
Now, please, Vega
He's under the spell of Professor Purwa
Oh no, Purwa!
That was close!
I mean, Professor Purwa
Ma'am
Do we need to call Purwa?
Like when we cured Ray?
I don't think so
I think it's worse
It's worse
So, what do we do?
He has to use the spell
Now the spell is gone
What do we do?
Vega
Wait for me
I'll find the spell for you
To be continued...
I brought my beloved son, Tommy
Because I think he's not safe here
Right, Tommy?
Right, honey?
Sir
Can Mike and I go with you?
Of course, sir!
We'll ride the ship
Oh, sure!
You've prepared the ship, let's go
I can't ride the ship
I won't hold you back
If you want to take your son home
And I, as the head of the school
Apologize for all the inconveniences
Your son has gone through
And I'll try to solve this problem as soon as possible
Are you crazy?
Tommy!
Vega!
I'm sorry, sir
I didn't mean to
It's okay, Alva
How's Vega?
Well, sir
I want to tell you
If there's a way to save Vega
Use the spell
The spell?
Okay, Alva
Let's go find the spell
So Vega can be saved
Come on
Alva!
Let me call the spell
No, sir!
The spell will be scared
Let me do it
Putri Duyung!
Where are you?
I need your help!
Putri Duyung!
Putri Duyung
Vega is still unconscious
Because of the spell
The spell is called your tears
Your tears
Can I ask for your tears for Vega?
The spell is called the glass
Alva, put it here
Putri Duyung
Thank you, Putri Duyung
You're so kind
Putri Duyung!
Who did that?
I did it
What do you want?
It's none of your business
You better go now
Bring the tears to your friend
Now!
Alva, you better bring the tears now
Poor Vega
I will make sure
Putri Duyung will be fine
Go now!
I'm sorry, Putri Duyung
I have to go now
But I will help you
Daphatang Kurungan!
Putri Duyung!
Putri Duyung
She's recovered, Vega!
She's recovered!
I was being teased by Professor Purwa
What happened to Duyung?
He ran away
Thank God
But he came back
Why?
Because the only way to make you realize
Is the tears
He came back just to help me?
Yes
Because he came back
He was caught by Professor Purwa
We have to help him
I don't want him to get hurt
Come on, let's help him
I managed to catch Duyung
And now we can interrogate him
To find out where the students were taken
Come, I'll show you
It's so good
Let's go home, honey
Thank God you came here quickly
Or else we could have kidnapped Duyung
That's right
Who's going to help me?
Alva and Vega will be kidnapped by Duyung
That's right
What's going on?
Mike? Jack?
Tommy?
Why are they here?
I don't know
Let me go!
You're so heavy!
Your mission is over
And I will return your voice
Remember
One of the children
Must be named Alva
Alva?
That's a familiar voice
Yeah, I think so too
But who is it?
I don't know
Yeah, it's weird
Do you know Alva?
Who is she?
Alva
You're wrong if you think I've lost
I've never lost, Alva
I will never lose
Where did he go?
Aldebaran
The terror will continue
Until I get the chosen one
Under the lake
Everyone wants to attack the castle
We can't
Now tell me
Where are the students hiding?
Come on, answer
Answer the question
Don't joke around
Or I'll fry you
Calm down, Professor
Come in
Get out, Professor
Let's go
Tommy
Tommy, my son
He's been kidnapped
Tommy
I'm sorry
What happened?
Something happened
A huge wave
Suddenly
A parade appeared
And dragged Tommy and his friends out
Tommy
That's why we're here
To ask for your help
We have to find the parade
And destroy the castle
I agree
Let's attack the parade
They've gone too far
I disagree
Is Duyung really a good person?
Megantara is right
The proof is
He wants to give his reputation to Vega
If Duyung is a good person
Why did they kidnap the students?
I agree
I'll help them
There must be something
Forcing them to do that
Megantara
If you dare
You can stay here
But you're too soft
Get ready
Let's go
Your friends have kidnapped the students
We won't stay still
We'll attack your castle
To free the students
Megantara
Do you see where Duyung is going?
He's going to the lake
To attack Duyung's castle
Alva, let's follow him
Let's go
Alva
Megantara
Why are the students
In danger?
Wait!
You're wrong!
Duyung is a good person
They're evil!
Professor Purwoh
Did you hear what Alva said?
Yes
I think
We should stop this attack
Rather than doing stupid things
And endangering people
No
I have to find my son, Tobi
And I have to avenge Duyung
Because he helped me
Yes
Duyung must have brainwashed Alva
What should we do?
We're late
Let's just follow them
Alva
Vega
What are you doing?
You can swim
You can attack
Palm trees
Turquoise trees
You can't dive
But you can eat
We don't have a choice
We don't want to hurt Duyung
Let's use this method
This is the method
Daffatang
Bevebaju
Beverenang
Wow!
Cool!
By using this
We can breathe
And talk
Ready?
One, two, three
Up!
That's where Duyung's palace is
Let's call them
Hi, Duyung
Come out
We have captured one of your friends
If you don't come out
Your friend will be punished
Why don't they show up?
Calm down
We'll wait a little longer
They will show up
Be ready
You are a worm
You are a bait
Alva, it's dangerous
We don't have a choice
Mom!
I'm scared
We are all scared
And hungry
Karim!
Open your mouth!
Shut up!
Remember
If you dare to do anything
I will make you a fish
Show your spirit
Get ready
My friend
Run, jump
Jump, climb
The stars
Be brave
Don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with all your heart
Be proud of yourself
Go, go, go
Let's dream