To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Be proud of yourself!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
Stop! Stop!
I'm sure...
The dwarfs are only in war.
Run!
It seems there is a greater power...
controlling them.
Run! Run! Run!
Terror will continue to spread...
Run!
Until I can get the chosen child.
Do you see where the dwarfs are?
Under the lake.
Everyone wants to attack the dwarfs.
Why aren't they showing up?
Be patient.
We'll wait a little longer.
They will show up to attack him.
Be patient.
What are you doing?
They are very agile.
Let's hide first.
Wait until they show up.
Then we attack.
Wait.
Attack!
Now answer my question.
Where did you hide the dwarfs?
Don't play around.
Answer my question.
Do you think you can play around?
Fine.
I will show you.
Attack!
Don't hurt them.
They are evil.
Putri Duyung!
Putri Duyung, are you okay?
Thank you for saving me with your tears.
I promise I will set you free...
with your friends.
Vega, attack.
Hurry.
We are here to save our friends.
Good.
If we attack...
the dwarfs will be punished.
We can't hurt the dwarfs.
We have to work with them.
You don't know how to teach me.
Professor Purwa.
It's not our fault.
We don't have much time.
If you are lying...
you have to bear the consequences.
Let's go, Fang.
So, the dwarfs are in the mirror.
Then, why do we waste our energy...
just to fight?
That's why we have to fight.
We also have to listen...
to their opinions.
They are still kids.
But sometimes...
they can be smarter than adults.
Alpha.
Ask them now.
Where are our friends?
Putri Duyung.
Please tell me...
where are our friends...
that you kidnapped?
What are you doing?
Are you playing?
Calm down.
Putri Duyung can't talk.
Lightning!
I think...
Alpha is right.
They are not lying.
But they can't talk...
because of something.
But how can they lose their voices?
Why?
Why can't you talk?
Who is he?
Did you order him?
Do you want me to read your mind?
To be continued...
Help!
Help us!
So, because of that attack...
you can't talk?
Alpha.
I...
have decided...
to steal your voices.
And if you want your voices back...
then...
you have to kidnap...
eight kids from a magic school.
And one of those kids...
must be a boy named Alpha.
Those kids...
must be taken to the headquarters...
in the underground.
The headquarters is a secret.
So...
you can't tell anyone about it.
And if one of the Duyung...
leak it...
then...
all of you...
will be cursed to be bullies.
The eighth call says that you have to kidnap...
eight kids from a magic school.
So...
you have to kidnap...
eight kids from a magic school.
Mom!
What are you doing?
Karim!
Help!
Food!
Thank you, Karim!
Hurry up!
Kristi!
More grass!
Where's the others?
What are we going to do?
What if we get caught?
I'm ready, Mom.
And...
I've learned the Imo Kavari.
So, I'm sure...
I can protect myself.
Yes.
Alpha isn't alone.
I'll protect him.
What kind of dragon is that?
Oh my God!
It's dangerous!
Don't worry, Tentarang.
We've fought the three-headed dragon.
So, we're sure.
Okay. I think there's no other choice.
I'll count to three.
If there's no better idea,
we'll use Alpha's idea.
Professor Purwa!
One.
Two.
Three.
We'll use Alpha's idea.
Kavatang Poveris.
I've installed the protective equipment...
and the tracking device on you.
Alpha. Vega.
Wait.
Alpha.
Vega.
You have to be careful.
I promise.
I'll save you.
Kuti Ruyung.
Let's get through this.
Yes.
Take us to the eighth dimension.
What should we do?
I'm sorry for getting hurt.
But I can't tell you where it is.
Hurry up, Kuti Ruyung.
We don't have much time.
We have to save my friend.
Good.
Very good.
Finally, I got what I wanted.
Leave it to me.
Mama!
I'm scared, too.
We're all scared.
And hungry.
Karin!
I knew it.
I've been thinking about how to get out of here.
I've been crying.
I want to go home.
To be continued...
What happened?
It can't be.
They must know about the trap.
And they destroyed it on purpose.
Without the trap, how can we help them?
It's all because of Professor Purwa.
Because of you, Purwa.
Now, Ava's life is in danger.
What do you mean?
It's not my fault.
But that's how it is.
You accused me.
I'm trying to save the children.
You're useless.
Enough.
To be continued...
I want to die.
Remember.
Don't be afraid.
If you're afraid of anything...
I'll turn you into fish.
Don't.
I'm hungry.
Raika.
Wake up.
It hurts.
Where are we now?
We're trapped.
Where's our cage?
Oh, right.
Where's my cage?
Don't.
What if they find out?
If we lose our cage, they won't know where we are.
We won't be safe.
We don't know where we are.
We're trapped.
Open it.
Shut up.
Remember.
If you're afraid of anything...
I'll turn you into fish.
Wake up.
You can't turn us into fish.
Guys.
Let's get out of here.
Wait.
Not that easy.
We're trapped.
Professor Ranggara.
Thank you for getting to know me.
Professor.
Why are you here?
You should be in jail.
You're underestimating me.
A prison like that...
is nothing to me.
And you, Alva.
Don't be happy...
because you took my Tongsi.
Because without my Tongsi...
I can still use my magic.
Go back to Rizal.
Suck their energy.
Alva.
What should I do?
I feel bad for Alva and Vega.
They're my friends.
But if I tell them about their escape plan...
I...
Shut up.
Vega.
Alva.
Rafa, get in there.
This is wrong.
There's no point in fighting.
Now we have to find the kids.
But what do we do?
We don't have a choice.
He told us to follow him.
He knows where the kids are.
Let's go.
Wait.
What if we're trapped?
Do you have a better idea?
Let's go.
What is this place?
This must be a trap.
He told us to follow him.
Let's go.
He told you to press the stone.
If you lie to us...
you'll be punished.
Rafa.
To save them...
I have to do something.
Even though I've destroyed their plan.
How could I know?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Let's get out of here.
How are we going to get out?
Let's follow the stone.
Let's go that way.
Let me.
Let's go.
We're trapped.
Angkara?
There are two ways.
One is to go straight.
Which one should we take?
We should split up.
Wait.
I think that's smoke.
It's a message from the children.
Let's just follow the smoke.
So, we don't have to split up.
Let's go.
So, Professor Angkara...
run away from the prison.
Don't you dare.
The Dark Lord won't rise again...
because you've captured me.
The terror won't end here.
In the end...
you'll lose.
Kidnapping children.
Angkara must be the one.
Don't be afraid.
Let me deal with this.
Everyone, be alert.
We'll continue our journey.
Let's go.
We'll use the water.
Okay.
Let's go.
Move away from the water.
The Dark Lord won't rise again.
The terror won't end here.
In the end...
you'll lose.
The terror won't end here.
In the end...
you'll lose.
The terror won't end here.
Thank you.
Let's go!
Angkara?
So it turns out...
you're the one behind all this.
Angkara...
it turns out you managed to escape from Botan's prison.
Hey...
you're underestimating my magic power.
You think...
I can't escape...
from a cheap stone prison like that?
Angkara...
let me handle this.
You guys, save the children.
Come on, hurry.
You guys, go!
Come on, hurry!
A coconut eaten by a tiger.
Where do you think you're going, Angkara?
The door is broken.
Let's go.
Wait.
Isn't this the energy transfer crystal?
This is a very dangerous weapon.
This crystal...
can gather the energy of the people...
who want it.
And it can absorb...
all the energy.
We don't have much time.
We have to destroy this crystal ball.
Because if the crystal ball is full...
it means the children's energy has been taken.
The children could die.
I will destroy it.
Avancur!
Let's attack.
Good bye, Professor Megantara.
Go to Japan through the north.
It's easy to defeat Megantara.
Avancur!
Let's destroy it together.
Tommy.
Tom.
Are you okay?
It seems that the destruction of the crystal...
destroyed this place.
We have to get out of here.
Let's go.
Vega.
Professor!
Megantara is still inside.
Centara is also inside.
He is fighting against Ankara.
Centara.
Alpha.
Megantara.
Where are you?
Alpha.
Professor.
I'm here.
Centara.
Alpha.
Professor.
I'm here.
Thank you, Professor.
This is Centara.
Everything is closed.
What should we do, Professor?
Alpha.
Professor.
Look.
There is a hole.
It looks like it belongs to two people.
Alpha.
Come on.
Go inside that hole.
Hurry.
Come on, Professor.
Follow Alpha.
No, Megantara.
You go inside.
You can take care of it.
Professor.
Go inside, Professor.
Stay in the middle.
Where is it, Professor?
Professor.
What's going on?
Don't leave me again.
To be continued...
Centara.
Wake up, Centara.
Megantara.
Centara.
Wake up, Centara.
Alpha.
Meg.
Megantara.
Centara.
Be careful.
Don't push me like this.
I'm going to kill you.
Prof.
Kelavan fruit.
Kedandong fruit.
Alpha.
Don't cry.
Smile.
I promised you...
...that I will save you all.
Captain Megantara.
I never break my promise.
Okay.
Where's your tuxedos?
Are you all okay?
Cidiyung.
You can talk now?
Yes.
It must be because the effect of the magic is gone.
The place is destroyed.
Thank you, Cidiyung.
I'm so happy that you've helped us.
My name is Tiara.
I'm so happy to meet you.
We can come here again.
Right, Alpha?
Yes, I'm happy to meet you too.
You're good kids.
Thank you for helping me.
Tiara, what's wrong?
Tiara, are you sick?
Tiara!
Where are you?
This is all because of the curse of the Dark Lord.
Mutiara has leaked the children's whereabouts.
And now...
...she's being bewitched.
Tiara.
It's better to play than to sleep.
What if we go to the sea?
I don't want to.
I don't want to go to the sea.
I don't want to. I'll remember you.
I don't want to.
He left me.
Fine.
If you don't want to play, I'll play.
Where is he?
Don't go that way.
Don't!
Don't leave me again.
Don't be afraid.
We're not human anymore.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Are you alone?
What else can I do?
Alpha and Vega are still sad.
Because Mutiara is bewitched.
That's right.
Come here.
I want to talk to you.
What is it?
I'm leaving, Alpha and Vega.
I'm going to be a ghost.
Please, don't go.
Mutiara, don't go.
Mutiara, I'm sad.
Go!
I have a surprise for you.
I'm Jamon.
I'm sure you won't regret it.
No.
We're going to Asrama Purnama.
Me too.
It's true.
You don't want to meet Mutiara.
Don't be silly.
It's true.
I'm going to meet Mutiara.
Don't lie.
There's one condition.
You have to be a girl.
That's not funny.
It's true.
Just follow me.
Is that a boy or not?
I don't know.
I don't feel good.
Hurry up.
Where's Mutiara?
If you're lying, I'm going to buy you a tree.
Just wait.
They're coming.
They?
Yes.
Let's go.
This way.
That's Mutiara.
Remember what I said?
I met Putri Duyung.
Putri Duyung told me...
...that if a girl takes Mutiara's boy...
...Mutiara can live again.
Then Mutiara becomes a girl.
Hurry up.
Come here.
I'm waiting for you.
They don't like boys.
Hurry up.
I love you.
Now!
It's so fun!
There's another boy!
Thank you, Rek.
I'm so happy to meet Mutiara.
Me too.
It's just for a while.
But I'm happy because he's a good boy.
I know.
But my body aches.
Attention, boys.
Starting tomorrow...
...you're going to have a semester vacation.
And you're going to do a field trip...
...to a magic village not far from the school.
There, you're going to stay at a guest house...
...and have fun with the magic people.
Professor Agni, Purwa, and Megantara...
...will accompany you...
...to keep an eye on you...
...so that you don't do anything stupid.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
There's going to be a sports competition in the village.
It's going to be fun.
There's a lot of food.
I can't wait to go there.
Yes, sir.
There's a result.
I just heard...
...that the kids from the magic school...
...are going to start a field trip to the magic village.
And I think...
...we can attack Alfa there.
I don't want to fail this time.
So that I can regain my strength.
I have to get that kid.
Don't worry, sir.
I'll give you whatever you want.
To be continued...
That's enough.
We'll always be waiting for you.
Hey!
Where is he?
It was just a dream.
But...
What does this mean?
Why is it forbidden to join the field trip?
What's wrong?
Those two...
...always appear in my dreams...
...and give me a headache.
Kids.
We're going to leave now.
On the count of three...
...let's chant the mantra together.
One.
Two.
Three.
Fly!
To be continued...
They're here.
Oh.
Yes.
As the saying goes...
...it means...
...one of them...
...will open the door...
...and create chaos in this village.
Nik.
Now you have to find the village of magic.
His name is Mr. Galaxy.
Tell him...
...that we're here.
And then...
...you come back here.
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, kids.
Let's see.
What's that sound?
Is that Nik?
It's a noise.
Nik.
Faiqa.
What's wrong?
Where are you?
We can't be separated.
We have to stay together.
Come on, kids.
Come on, everyone.
Faiqa.
Nik.
That's Nik's voice.
Yes.
Nik.
Why is it turning into a rock?
Maybe it needs something.
It turns out...
...Ramalan is right.
The disaster is here.
We're all going to be affected...
...by the monster legend.
Yes, that's right.
The monster legend?
What did those people mean?
What is the monster legend?
What really happened in the desert?
Don't worry.
Megantara...
...will be back.
Who are you?
Please.
You're amazing.
Bro.
How did it go?
I want to go with you.
I really want to go here.
I have a clue...
...about what happened.
Come on.
To be continued...