To be continued...
Go, go, go!
We can do it!
We don't have much time.
We have to destroy the crystal ball.
Because if the ball is full...
it means the children's energy is taken.
It's impossible. The children could die.
Muthiara!
This is all because of the Dark Lord's curse.
Muthiara has leaked where the children are now.
Starting tomorrow, you will have a mid-semester vacation.
And you will do a field trip to Sihir village, not far from the school.
I just heard that the children from Sihir village...
are going to do a field trip to Sihir village.
And I think we can defeat Alva there.
I don't want to fail this time.
It's true.
The plan has arrived.
We will all be attacked by the legendary monster.
Yes, it's true.
Legendary monster?
What did those people mean?
What is a legendary monster?
Go home!
Silence!
All of you!
As students of Sihir school...
you can't be afraid.
What if we become a stone?
Calm down, children.
We will find out what happened.
Megantara, it's better if you take the children out of here.
And don't let a single child escape.
Yes, ma'am.
Tavan.
Bafinda.
Children.
Let's go to Sihir village.
We have to stay together.
And don't let anyone escape.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
We have to tell Professor Aldebaran about this.
Yes, sir.
Good afternoon, Professor Aldebaran.
Something terrible has happened.
When I was about to report to Galaxi village...
all of a sudden...
he turned into a stone.
Nick turned into a stone?
Who did that?
We don't know, sir.
It all happened so suddenly.
But now all of the children have been taken to a safe place.
Okay.
Keep an eye on the students and keep an eye on them.
I will go there with the officers to treat Nick.
Yes, sir.
Sihir Village
Stop!
Stop, stop, stop!
Why did you stop all of a sudden?
What's the problem?
It hurts!
We can't enter this village.
Why?
Is there something stopping you?
Oh, no!
I'm lucky I didn't go in there.
If I didn't, I would have been burnt.
What really happened to this village?
Sihir Village
Mr. Lura.
For a child who experiences something like this...
what should we do?
Outside this village...
there is a lake that can cure all kinds of diseases.
Who knows...
it can cure this curse.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Lura.
I will go to the lake right away.
Please, keep an eye on the children.
Yes, sir.
Be careful, Tara!
Be careful, okay?
There is a lightning.
It's coming late.
Don't worry.
The lightning...
Megantara...
will return.
Megantara Returns
Stop, Megantara!
Megantara.
Don't go through this gate.
Professor Aldebaran?
Concentrate, Megantara.
Look slowly.
Professor.
Who installed this terrifying spell in this gate?
I don't know, Megantara.
Clearly...
you can't leave this village.
And we can't enter the village.
But, Professor Aldebaran...
I have to look for a lake outside this village.
Because the water of the lake...
can restore Nick as if he were dead.
There is another way, Megantara.
In this village forest...
there is still a mushroom that can cure the curse.
Right?
Let's look for the mushroom now.
If in three hours...
Nick can't be cured by the mushroom...
he will be a stone forever.
Dr. Jutir.
There are millions of mushroom in the forest.
Which mushroom can cure Nick's curse?
The mushroom...
is different from the others.
The head is down.
The position is upside down.
Hurry up.
Okay.
I will look for the mushroom...
by using the Davatang spell.
Wait, wait, wait.
You can't do that.
Don't use magic.
The mushroom's power will be reduced.
It's better to use...
your hands.
Remember.
Don't use magic, you know?
And one more thing, Megantara.
You have to stay calm.
Don't show your temper to the children.
If they get scared...
they will run to this gate...
and endanger them.
Yes, Professor.
Soldiers.
Where are the soldiers?
Yes, that's the medicine for Nick.
I happened to meet...
Professor Aldebaran.
And...
Professor Aldebaran is sorry.
He can't come with you...
because he has something to do.
What should I do?
I want to go home.
Me too.
We want to go home too.
Children.
Professor Aldebaran...
has a message for you.
So that you can help me...
to find the forest mushroom.
Mushroom?
Yes, the forest mushroom.
Because according to Professor...
this forest mushroom can cure Nick.
But this is not just any mushroom.
This mushroom grows the fastest.
It grows under the umbrella.
The mushroom stem is on top.
And...
pay attention, this is important.
This mushroom cannot be taken...
by using a manual.
Professor Aldebaran also has a message...
for all of you.
When in the forest...
please...
you have to focus.
Don't play around.
Don't look around...
and don't touch unimportant things.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Alright.
Please get ready.
I...
want to talk to...
Professor Purwa first.
Megantara.
Is there a problem?
This village gate...
is given a very strong mantra.
That's what makes people here...
unable to leave...
and enter.
Because of that...
Professor Aldebaran...
cannot come here.
Professor Aldebaran has a message.
So that we can protect...
and protect our children.
Don't let...
a child dare...
to break the gate.
Because this will be very dangerous for them.
Wait.
Children.
Before we go into the magic forest...
to look for forest mushrooms...
I will...
divide you into groups.
One group.
Five people.
Daffatang Pluit.
Now you have been divided into groups.
If one of you...
has found the mushroom...
you just have to ring the pluit.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
And if there is a danger approaching you...
you just have to ring the pluit.
Professor.
Why is Tintara alone?
Because she is Megantara, Alva.
She is very strong and tough.
But for you...
you can't be alone.
You still need a companion.
Let's go.
The forest is very big.
Amir!
What are you doing?
Focus on finding the mushroom that grows upside down.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Don't touch anything in this forest.
Hurry. Go back to your friends.
Daffatang Pluit.
Srigala.
I am Megantara.
Bang Lewat.
Yes, sir.
There is something wrong.
There is a tree in Jebatan Besi.
A smart boy.
Megantara.
Excuse me.
Good.
Wow, it's so cool.
Oh, yes.
Professor Aldebaran said...
I can't touch anything...
and I can't see anything.
I'd better look for more mushrooms.
A Strange Cat
I'm in the middle of a forest.
But where am I now?
This location should be blocked.
I'm lost!
I'm in the middle of a forest.
But where am I?
This location should be blocked.
Where am I?
I'm in the middle of a forest.
What's this?
I can use a mantra.
But how?
I'll try using a mantra.
That's impossible.
I'm in the middle of a forest.
That's it.
I know how to do it.
How did it go, Vika? Did you find the mushroom?
I did, Prof.
But it's over there. I can't get it.
Don't worry. Just leave it to me.
Vika?
Thank you, Prof. You're so kind.
You'd better keep your voice down...
...so that the other kids will know we've got the mushroom.
Okay, Prof.
We've found the mushroom.
That means I can get the mushroom.
Let's go there.
I'm so happy.
Help!
Let's go there.
Let's go.
Help!
What's going on?
Alva!
Alva, where are you?
It's useless to look for Alva.
Maybe Alva has turned into a rock.
Yes, she's gone.
Let's go.
Alva, where are you?
Alva!
We can't just leave her like that.
Let's look for Alva.
Alva!
Help!
My arm!
Let me go!
Don't be noisy!
Help!
Let me go!
I want to go back to the group!
They will definitely find me!
Help!
It's good that you don't ask me to help you!
Are you sure you want to go back to the group?
Who are you?
I'm Bobo!
The mighty Bobo!
You have to join...
...the 8th prince!
The 8th prince?
Help!
I want to go to the sky!
I don't know...
...if you want to attack me...
...or not...
...or you want to lie to me.
But it's okay.
Maybe...
...I can help you.
Let's go!
Help!
Everyone, weapons!
There's a lot of them.
I'll fry them.
To be continued...
Now...
...do you know...
...how great I really am?
Now...
...take your magic wand...
...and...
...count to ten.
Ten.
If you don't take your magic wand...
...tomorrow morning...
...you'll be my breakfast.
The eighth day.
One.
Two.
Three.
Why are you so quiet?
I'm just kidding.
I'm serious.
Can't you see?
Take your magic wand!
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Fourteen.
Seventeen.
Why are you so quiet?
I know how to get rid of him.
I summon Avanza!
What are you doing here?
Why are you attacking there?
Avanza!
There are so many of them!
I'm going to fry them!
Pretty girl.
There are so many of them!
I know...
...you don't like men.
But now...
...you have to help me.
Malak is evil.
He wants to take me to the eighth day.
Girls.
Avanza is kind.
He once helped me.
So, we have to help him.
Let's help him.
Avanza!
You're so annoying.
You don't know who we are, right?
How dare you mess with me?
Now, feel this.
Avanza!
I can do it.
Girls.
Help!
Alva.
You should go now.
It's all your fault.
Poor her.
She can't swim.
She will drown.
What if she drowns?
She will die.
I'm scared.
Just let her die.
Men are not persistent.
That's why men hate them.
Let's go, girls.
Let's go.
Help!
Thank God.
Why are you looking at me?
Help!
What's wrong?
You saved me.
Now, you want to kill me?
No.
Now, I have to go back to the group.
Wait.
Do you think I like it?
I have to do it.
Fine.
I won't ask you to do it.
It's not like that.
Can you imagine?
The one who saved your life...
...will be your duty.
If not...
...you will die.
But you promised me.
So, do you want to...
...be my employee now?
So?
Yes.
I'll be your servant.
But...
...I have to go to the village.
I have to meet many people there.
Just say it.
I'm your servant.
You're right.
Let's go there.
Go?
Yes.
The right one.
It's not there yet.
You'll be eaten there.
It's scary.
If I don't go, what should I wear?
It's okay.
So?
Who is this, Alva?
What are you doing?
To be continued...
Both of them...
...be good.
Prof.
How is Netolai and Kanik?
Don't worry, Vega.
Both of them will recover...
...within 48 hours.
Mosquitoes are very contagious.
So, they will recover.
To be continued...
Why is Popo so strong?
I've never been bitten by Popo.
Popo.
Don't be like that.
Poor thing.
How can I find him?
Dad, help!
Dad.
Those kids came in from our roof.
Alva.
Thank God.
It's okay, dear.
Don't be afraid.
Alva is your friend, too.
Alva, where have you been?
I was worried about you.
I thought you were a rock.
You've been lying to me.
I wasn't lying.
I was just worried.
Stop fighting.
The important thing is, Alva is safe now.
That's right.
Popo is no longer a kid.
I'm a man.
Stop fighting.
Then?
Who is this, Alva?
What are you doing?
Popo.
Don't be rude.
Who are you?
Introduce yourself.
My name is Popo.
Where are you going?
I'm going with Alva.
Because Alva is kind enough to help Popo.
Popo.
I live in Sebatang Karang.
I don't have a place to stay.
Can I stay with you?
You don't have to.
You can't do that.
You have to be polite.
Popo.
You can stay here.
Then, let's eat.
Let's eat.
You must be hungry.
Yes.
Let's eat.
Shut up.
Don't be rude.
Popo is forced.
If he's forced, he doesn't have to.
Alva.
Why did you bring him here?
He's scary.
You can't trust him.
He looks scary.
He's creepy.
Look at your son.
I'm sorry, boss.
I'm sorry.
How could we be trapped here?
Don't be harsh, Professor Purwa.
We have to cover this up.
Don't make them panic.
Yes.
I feel sorry for them.
We brought them here for a field trip.
To have fun.
But in the end...
...we're all trapped here.
I have an idea.
There's a cave down there.
It's a new disease.
Don't worry, professors.
Tomorrow, we'll ask them to do something fun.
Rita.
Alva.
What's wrong?
Why are you panicking?
I'm scared, Vega.
Why?
What happened today...
...could be a legend.
A legend?
What legend?
A LEGEND
Alva.
Why are you crying?
We asked you to come here, Alva.
But why did you refuse?
This place is dangerous for you.
Who are you?
Why do you keep showing up in my dream?
I'm Gama.
I'm Queen.
And we both...
...hate you, Alva.
Now you have to remember, Alva.
Don't ever look into those eyes again.
Remember.
What do you mean?
Whose eyes?
Gama.
I'm Queen.
Alva.
Ri.
Why did you wake up?
Were you dreaming?
And?
I can't sleep.
Why?
I don't know.
But I have a feeling.
What should we do?
I think the teachers are hiding something from us.
Hiding something?
There are two victims.
But we can't go home yet.
And that's Professor Lebaran.
He said he's coming.
But he's not here yet.
If this legend is true...
...then the monster is gone.
And we have to find out...
...who took the power.
What are you doing here?
I have a clue about what happened here.
Come here.
Hurry.
Here's the book.
100 years ago...
...the people of Sihir village lived in peace.
Until one day...
...a disaster came to the village.
Help!
The disaster was a curse.
The village was in chaos.
And many people turned into stone.
My son!
It's so scary.
The only hope of the village...
...was a great sorcerer called Bimbang Sakti.
Bimbang Sakti
The villagers were still scared.
They couldn't trust anyone.
Even a good sorcerer like you.
No.
What's wrong, Bambi?
Help!
Save this village, Bimbang Sakti.
Look.
This village is like dead.
No one dares to leave the house.
Because they're afraid of being cursed into stone.
Help!
Why did you curse the snake?
My family...
...was destroyed...
...by that monster.
Finally, Bimbang Sakti faced the monster.
Dig!
Bimbang Sakti defeated the monster...
...and locked it in the cave.
No one knows where the cave is.
But...
...the spell didn't last forever.
So, the monster can be released.
Only the fifth generation can open it.
If this legend is true...
...it means the monster is released.
We have to find out...
...who is Bimbang Sakti's descendant...
...who can lock the monster inside.
Who is it?
All the disciples and teachers in the village are in danger.
What should I do...
...so that I can enter the village...
...and help them?
Children.
Even though we're on vacation now...
...we still have to learn magic.
Magic?
Children.
Now, I'm going to teach you...
...a magic.
This magic can neutralize...
...the enemy's attack...
...that makes you powerless.
That makes you stiff.
And you can't do anything.
But if you use this magic...
...you will be free...
...and normal again.
Yes. Great.
I have to be able to do this...
...so I won't be stiff like Tole.
Teach me.
Okay.
Now, get ready.
We're going to make you stiff...
...and powerless.
Kavaku...
...Bada.
Concentrate.
Now, I'm going to teach you...
...a magic that will make you free...
...from your powerlessness.
The magic is...
...free first.
Come on, children.
Concentrate.
Who can be free first...
...can take the chocolate on the table.
And if you can't...
...free yourselves...
...you will be punished.
To be continued...
Free, free, free!
Don't!
Don't bother us!
You're the one who's bothering me!
But she didn't mean to.
She was so scared.
She said the wrong magic...
...and she got you.
Forgive her.
Free!
Down!
Children!
Help me!
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
I'm surprised.
How can a snake talk to you?
I'm surprised too.
But...
...I used to talk to a snake.
Back then?
When?
When I lived with my uncle and aunt.
It's weird, right?
I can talk to a snake.
Wait.
You can talk to a snake when you're sick.
What else can you talk to a snake?
You're lying.
The snake's teeth can kill.
But you can kill it...
...through the snake's teeth.
You're talking nonsense.
What if I become a snake again?
If this is the case...
...how can we get out of here?
And we can't go home.
Because the village gate...
...is haunted by a very powerful magic.
We're all trapped here.
Now we know...
...that the monster likes chocolate.
So we have to wake up our friends...
...so they don't eat chocolate.
I agree.
So the others won't be harmed by the monster.
Let's go.
Opo.
Will you help me...
...in my mission?
To be continued...