To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
We're not done yet, Megantar.
We still have to close that cave with a mantra.
So that Antaboga won't appear again forever.
When I was a kid, I only had my dad.
Now he's gone.
I'm all alone.
Megantar, you're not alone.
We're still here for you.
You went to school with us.
Now you're free.
You're not a servant to anyone.
Free?
Yay!
I'm free!
I have to get that light.
I have to defeat everyone.
So that I can be happy.
And remember.
The liquid of life is very rare.
Only one person can get that very rare liquid of life.
No one can defeat Raya.
She's beautiful.
I'm not afraid of you.
She's so clingy.
What's wrong with her?
Whatever.
I'm going to make her lose.
I have to win.
Really, Pegah?
I don't know.
Guys.
Pegah.
You've been in the toilet for so long.
I'm sorry.
I met a ghost.
A ghost?
That's scary.
It's not scary anymore.
But it's annoying.
It's annoying.
It's singing.
It's trying to scare the contestants.
So that they'll fail.
Really?
There were some kids who gave up.
And threw the white flag.
And then they got rejected.
That's why we have to be careful.
And remember.
We can't give up.
Let's go.
Ray.
Don't.
Did you hear the judges?
We can't eat this.
I know.
If we eat it, we'll fail.
No way.
I know.
But I really want to eat it.
It looks delicious.
I'm hungry.
Ray.
Do you want to fail?
Thank you.
Let's go.
I have to seduce them.
So that they'll eat it.
If I do this.
I'll become a normal kid.
It's so delicious.
Hi.
Do you want some?
Just eat it.
It's so delicious.
But they said you can't eat it.
Who said that?
Just eat it.
I want to eat it.
Just a little bit.
I don't want to be caught by the judges.
Just eat it.
It's true.
I did it.
Hi.
I'm Raya.
I'm Ray.
The ice cream looks delicious.
Yes, it looks delicious.
Just eat it.
If I eat it.
I'll fail.
Who said that?
I've tried it.
You've tried it?
Yes.
Just eat it.
You'll regret it.
I want to eat it.
You again?
What are you doing?
Help!
Wait.
What are you doing here?
You made me lose.
So what?
It's none of your business.
Listen.
I'm the winner.
I'm the one who will get the best ice cream.
So, you're the winner too?
We're the winner too.
We'll win against you.
Okay.
You'll win against me.
So, just give up.
Just give up.
I won't give up.
Yes.
It's up to you.
If you lose, don't cry.
What are you doing?
We're doing our homework.
Let's play.
No, we don't want to play.
Just say it.
We're doing our homework.
Let's play.
I'm not in the mood.
You're in the mood.
Let's go.
I don't want to play with you.
I'll call Vega.
Can I borrow your phone?
I don't have it.
You're so annoying.
Guys, let's go.
Why are you wasting our time?
Let's go.
Okay.
Vega doesn't care about me.
He only cares about Alva.
There's a key.
I miss you.
I'm all alone.
I'm lonely.
I miss you.
A key?
What should I do?
I'm getting more scared.
I'm scared.
I want the key.
Don't.
Just a little.
I can't.
Don't be afraid.
Alva, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Alva.
Alva, wake up.
Vega.
What did I do?
You bit my hand.
I'm sorry, Rey.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
It hurts a little.
Don't eat this.
We're here to get the key.
For Alva.
I feel sorry for Rey and Vega.
Because of me, they're having a hard time.
Let's go.
We have to save the key.
Don't.
Don't touch me.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Come here.
No.
Don't.
Let's go.
There are a lot of pearls in this park.
Your task is to collect 100 pearls...
...in 30 minutes in a bucket.
Those who succeed will go to the next round.
Those who fail will be eliminated and sent home.
Get ready.
Start.
Remember.
You can't eat the pearls you collect.
Those who eat them will be sent home.
Those who fail will be eliminated.
Yes, I got the key.
Go, go, go.
Never stop.
Fight with all your might.
Go, go, go.
Make your dream come true.
Let's dream.
Go, go, go.
We can do it.
Show your spirit.
Get ready, my friend.
Go, Raya.
Why are you so slow? I'll go first.
You better be brave.
Go, Raya.
Watch out, Raya.
Chase your dreams.
Go, go, go.
Make your dream come true.
Never stop.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
5.
4, 5.
Look, I got two papers.
You're so arrogant.
Go, go, go.
Make your dream come true.
Fight with all your might.
Go, go, go.
Oops.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Watch out.
Raya.
I missed.
Watch out.
It's a ghost.
That's enough.
Gather your friends who fell.
Let's go.
Where are they?
Raiga.
I just remembered.
Maybe they went that way.
That means...
It's because of Raya.
Raya.
Raiga.
Rai.
Calm down.
There's still time.
We still have time.
What?
We don't have time.
We still have time.
We still have 5 minutes.
Where are they?
I'm scared.
Raiga.
I'm going to faint.
Calm down.
If we lose because of him,
I won't forgive him.
Where's your camera?
Where's my camera?
There it is.
Let me try.
Here.
There are two of them.
Try again.
I'm going to faint.
We did it.
Now, let's feed the kids.
Let's go.
You won.
Friends forever.
Best friends forever.
I think they're my biggest rivals.
I have to beat them.
And win their trust.
Because that's the only way I can live again.
You lost.
Friends forever.
Hello.
Alpha.
I'm coming.
I'm coming, Alpha.
Where's Alpha?
I'm coming.
Don't call me that.
I'm Kurcaci Ganjang.
If you call me that again, I'm going to be a monster.
I'm coming.
Don't be mad at me.
Okay.
Where's Alpha?
I want to see him.
Alpha is looking for medicine.
With them.
Alpha is sick.
They're looking for medicine.
Why didn't you invite me?
What's that?
A new mantra?
I don't know.
That means you don't know.
That's a story.
It's better to talk to pretty people.
Than to talk to ugly people.
Hey, you!
Get out of my way.
I'm Kurcaci Ganjang.
I'm here.
Hello, Pelita.
You still remember me, right?
I'm Kurcaci Ganjang, Alpha's friend.
What?
Yes, I still remember you.
Don't you want to take over Popo's job?
I'm sorry, Popo. I can't.
Why can't you? You're not polite.
Popo left me.
I want to be alone.
What?
Because Popo is Kurcaci?
So, you don't want to take over Popo's job?
You're arrogant.
No, I'm not.
I'm not arrogant, Popo.
Look.
I still have my dignity as Kurcaci.
My dignity is being trampled by you.
So, you have to take over Popo's job.
No, Popo. Just go.
Go.
I'm not arrogant. Just go.
No, Popo.
Popo!
Someone found out about this.
If they find out, I'll be expelled from school.
Ulita!
To be continued...
You're so mean, Popo.
I'm sorry, Popo.
I have to let you stay here.
To be continued...
Maybe there's another attack, Professor.
We have to report this to Professor Lebaran.
Let's go.
Okay.
This is weird.
I feel like the weather is changing.
A few hours ago, it was 30 degrees Celsius.
Now, it's 17 degrees Celsius.
Yes, you're right, Professor.
Maybe this school will be attacked again.
I don't feel any negative energy from this.
I don't think this is an attack.
Then, what is this, Professor?
This is one of the special powers of one of the students in this school.
Who is he? Who is his son?
I don't know either.
But we have to find him.
If this power is not controlled, it can be dangerous.
Now, I'm wearing gloves.
If my friends touch me, they will be in elementary school.
Hey, Rita!
Rita, come here for a second.
No, I don't want to.
Hey, don't be rude.
But, I don't want to.
She's so rude.
She's just like her friends, Alva, Vega, and Rey.
They're both rude.
Don't call Alva, Rey, and Vega.
They're best friends in the world.
Best friends in the world?
I don't think so.
Help!
What's going on here?
Professor, he's a monster!
What are you doing here?
I'm not a professor.
I don't know what's going on, Professor.
It's a lie!
He's a liar!
I saw it with my own eyes, Professor.
He must have left the school.
Or just let him go.
I didn't do anything wrong, Professor.
Don't kick me out of the school, Professor.
Because I don't have anyone else.
He's the one who kicked you out.
Don't go with him.
He's the one who kicked you out of the school.
He's the one who kicked you out.
Maybe what Tommy said is true.
I can't be here.
Because I can hurt innocent people.
Like Popo.
Rita!
I'm sorry, Professor.
I didn't mean to.
Rita!
Now, all of you have to walk through that bridge.
Here, you have to use your own power.
You can't use magic.
You can't fly.
And you can't use magic.
Don't forget.
You have to be careful here.
Because if you fall,
you'll be in danger.
Popo can fly.
I'm sure he'll be number one.
But don't worry.
I can make other kids fall.
But the camera is for focusing.
Then, why do we have to cover it?
Let's try it.
I have to hear it. I can't lose.
That's the sound of light.
Apparently, this thing can hear people's voices.
Later, when I pass by,
I'll tell Vega, Ava, and Ray
to fall and bring smoke.
Just watch.
I'll make them lose.
Guys, wait.
Do you know how to use it?
I know.
It's supposed to hear people's voices.
I heard Raya was about to attack us.
Are you serious?
We have to be careful.
Raya is behind us.
Okay.
To be continued...
I can't fall.
If I fall, I'll fail.
What should I do?
I can't fly.
If I fly, I'll fail.
Guys, let's just leave him.
Let's just help him.
But how?
I feel sorry for Vega.
What if he really falls?
I feel sorry for him.
He's a ghost now.
It's useless to help him.
If he falls, he won't die.
We can't just leave him.
We have to help him.
Let's go.
No, Vega.
We have to help him.
Wait here. I won't be long.
Ava.
Raya.
Give me your hand.
It's you, right?
My mom.
Yes.
We're rivals.
That's fair.
Give me your hand.
Thank you, Ava.
If you don't help me, I'll fail.
You're welcome, Raya.
Ava, what's wrong?
Ava.
It's because of you, Raya.
What should I do?
In five minutes, you have to arrive at the next gate.
The children who are late will be sent back to the gate.
What should we do?
Oh my God.
So, this is what that girl did?
Yes.
I've heard of a power that can turn everything into ice.
Freezing.
Even a child can't handle it.
And it can turn this school into freezing.
Ice.
And it can freeze itself.
This is very dangerous.
The three of you can proceed to the next gate.
Yes.
Thank you for helping me.
Now, we're in the first gate.
And there's one more gate that we have to pass.
I want to tell our teacher that we're on an adventure today.
Here.
Why is it on?
Maybe Blita is calling me.
Maybe.
Blita.
Blita, are you calling me?
Blita, answer me.
Blita.
Don't go.
Don't leave me.
Vega.
Come on, let's go.
Why are you wasting your time with him?
If they see my hand like this,
they'll be afraid to be friends with me.
What should we do?
We can't give up.
Rian has already fallen.
So, we have to hold on.
We can do this.
To be continued...
This is all because of you.
My power is gone.
No.
Sir.
Help me, sir.
To be continued...
I have to give up.
But, sir.
Your power hasn't recovered yet.
You won't be able to fight Aldebaran.
But now I have a great weapon that can defeat Aldebaran.
And I will get my chosen child.
To be continued...
Nede.
Why is he not answering?
Maybe he's playing with his friend.
It's possible.
Okay.
I'll tell him later.
Let's continue our journey.
Okay.
Let's go.
Welcome back, children.
I'd like to congratulate all of you.
Because you have passed the first gate.
The gate of dreams.
This second gate is called the gate of patience.
As the name implies.
In this gate, you will be tested for your patience.
In this gate, you can't be angry.
You can't be selfish.
And you can't force your opponent.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
This is the canteen.
Now, you can eat first.
Yes.
Finally, we can eat.
The food must be better than before.
That's right.
Yes.
There must be grilled chicken.
Where is the food?
Enjoy your meal.
This must be delicious food.
Food?
Let's open it.
One.
Two.
Three.
Ta-da.
Why is it like this?
It's delicious.
I thought you don't like vegetables.
I don't want to eat.
Me too.
I don't like vegetables.
I don't want to eat vegetables.
Rai.
As I said before.
This place is for trial and error.
You have to finish the vegetables and don't get angry.
If you get angry or give up, you'll go back to the beginning.
And if you finish the food, you'll go back to the beginning.
What should we do?
We can't give up.
Rai has already fallen.
So we have to hold on.
Yes.
We have to be patient.
Even though I don't like tomatoes.
But I have to hold on.
I have to eat this tomato.
As long as I have a snake in my body.
I want it.
I want to eat meat.
Especially this.
We have to be patient.
You have to handle your emotions.
Because we have to do all of this.
Yes, Vega.
There is no other way.
Only the fire of the firefly can warm this room.
I reaffirm once again.
If the power owned by this woman is very dangerous.
She can endanger the magic school and the students.
And the temperature in the room is also below 20 degrees, Professor.
This is dangerous.
Let's go.
Let's check the children.
You have to concentrate.
And read the body warming mantra.
So you can stay stable.
Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Oh my God.
They must be cold.
And they fainted.
It's better if we lift them up with a pole.
Okay.
Daffata.
Pole.
Why is the magic useless?
The magic can't work.
Because the air here is too cold.
Now.
How can we save them?
Let's lift them one by one.
Let's go.
It's bad, Professor.
Jack and Neil fainted.
Mike too.
This child too, Professor.
We have to hurry.
If we're late.
These children will die.
Rai, you're out too?
Yes.
I don't want to eat vegetables.
You don't want to eat vegetables?
Vegetables are good for your health.
Why do you have to eat vegetables?
It's not good.
Rai.
Where is Alfa?
Alfa was buried twice.
It's been a long time.
It's better to give up.
I will win.
This is called winning without a fight.
I'm excited.
What if we become friends?
But Alfa won't be afraid of me.
I have a strange power.
I can make everyone freeze.
Now the school is frozen.
But who will do it, Professor?
The one who will do it is Prita.
Prita?
To be continued...