To be continued...
We must destroy all the chocolate trees in the village.
If necessary, destroy all the chocolate trees in the village.
The snake is not dead.
It just ran away.
So, the snake can come back?
It can come back if it smells chocolate.
The candle is in my hand.
And you tell Alva,
if Alva still wants this child to live,
then she must surrender herself.
The sound of the flute played by the head of the darkness,
makes Alta Boga calm,
becomes calm.
You teach her all the notes, okay?
Okay, I'll teach her.
Seriously?
Even though I don't like it, even though I'm forced to.
Eat it, Momo.
Professor.
What's up?
What's wrong, Vega?
Alva went back to that village.
What's wrong with Alva?
Because,
the police kidnapped Professor Ankara.
And Professor Ankara said,
Alva must go there.
No one can accompany her.
She must be alone.
If not, the police will be in trouble.
I don't care.
I will go after Alva.
I won't let Ankara hurt Alva.
I will also go with you, Professor.
I have to save Alva.
Remember, Alva.
If you touch Ankara,
not even a hair from Alva,
I will tear her body apart.
I will also go with you, Professor.
You can go with me.
Yes!
But there's a condition.
What's the condition?
Infinity Vega Dendri.
I'm sorry.
Why did Professor Ankara become a witch?
What does that mean?
We're going to be a witch.
We're going to be a witch?
Yes, we're going to be a witch.
With you being small like this,
it will be easier for me and Megantara to protect you.
Me and Megantara will go.
Wow.
Professor Aldebaran's clothes are so fragrant and clean.
Eat it, Vega.
Wow.
A witch's permanent.
That permanent won't end until next week.
Eat it.
Thank you, Professor.
Oh, it's itchy.
I'm going to throw up.
Ouch.
Zoro.
I'm going to throw up.
What are you doing?
Chicken satay and permanent.
Relax, man.
It's still a long way to go.
It's still a long way?
I can't breathe here.
I'm going to die.
Zoro.
I'm going to throw up.
Ektara.
When is the last time you took a shower?
For me, cleanliness is number one.
The last time I took a shower...
was three weeks ago.
Huh? Three weeks ago?
Ektara.
I want to throw up.
Excuse me.
Professor.
Thank God you came.
Please help me, Professor.
Plita was kidnapped. Please, Professor.
Yes, I know.
That's why we came here.
Thank you, Professor.
I'm sure you can find Plita.
Come on, Professor. I'll show you my way.
Ouch!
That's not how you do it, Alva.
I taught you.
I'm sorry.
I'm still learning.
I'll try again.
That's enough.
You're always wrong.
Stop it.
I'm going to kill you.
That's not how you do it.
I'll try again.
Boko, where are you going?
You're right.
Boko must be dancing with the music.
Hooray! I can do it!
Yes!
Thank you.
Thank you for teaching me.
The next day
Huh?
Boko was hugged?
Usually, everyone treats Boko rudely.
Boko, why are you crying?
Boko, try to pet me.
Okay.
You can do it.
Let's go to the cave.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Galaxy, are you still okay?
We're still fine, Prof.
The next day
Felita!
Oh, no. I'm holding Felita.
Poor thing. She must be lonely over there.
The next day
Felita, it's me. Can you hear me?
Why did you hide me?
I'm so scared. It's so dark here.
Stay still. I'll hide you, Boko.
What's going on?
Why did you hide me?
Dad!
Shut up!
You can't talk to a kid anymore.
The next day
I've never walked that road with my dad.
It's full of rocks and it's dark.
Please help me.
Slowly.
I'm going to use that mirror without my permission.
Felita!
Professor!
I don't think this is the right way.
Galaxy, who's the real one who took Felita?
Alkahara, Prof.
How do you know?
Wasn't Felita in her room at that time?
And why did you take us here?
Shouldn't you take us to the rocky road?
Do you know the right way?
I don't know, Prof.
Unfortunately, you're too late to know that.
This is sandstorm.
You're right, Prof.
This sandstorm reflects magic.
All magic is useless here.
I'm sorry, Professor.
I can't take you to the rock road.
Only Alpha can go there.
Galaxy!
Where is it?
It's still far away.
Prof, it's over there.
Okay, let's go there.
Be careful.
To be continued...
Thank you for saving me.
Hang in there.
To be continued...
It's coming!
Keep going!
Hang in there.
Thank God, we're safe.
Vega, Ray, thank you.
You two have saved us.
You're welcome, Prof.
It's not a loss if you bring me and Vega.
To be continued...
Why, Galaxy?
Why did you do that?
It's none of your business, Professor.
To be continued...
Please, Professor.
I don't want to lose you.
Mr. Galaxy.
But you know...
where the real treasure is, right?
I know, Prof.
Come on.
I'll show you the way.
To be continued...
How do we get in?
Do you know how to open the door?
What's that?
And then?
Cekuwok Bagul Bagul!
I'm scared!
If I'm still alive, I can be killed by Professor Ankara.
Because I've lost.
If you're scared, you don't have to go in.
Let me go in alone.
I can't.
Even though I don't want to.
Even though I'm suffering.
I have to go in.
Alright, you can go in.
But, you have to be careful.
Alright.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me!
I said don't touch me!
I'm scared!
Pita!
Where are you?
Pita, where are you?
I'm scared!
Pita!
Welcome, Alva.
And thank you for keeping your promise to come here alone.
Very good.
Antaboga.
Bring it on!
Antaboga
I'm scared.
No one can help you now, Alva.
Fight Antaboga.
Pita, let's hide over there.
I'm scared.
Dad, wake up.
Wake up, Alva.
I'm scared.
Let's go, Pita.
We're finally together.
Yes.
Dad, thank you for saving us.
Alva, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Let's go.
Why are you here?
You can't leave just like that.
Because we're not done yet.
You're a traitor.
It's your turn...
...after her.
Open fire!
To be continued...
Now, feel this.
Don't.
Wake up.
Dad.
Wake up, Dad.
Professor Jahat.
Dad.
Dad, wake up.
Wake up, Dad.
Alva, wake up.
Dad.
Dad, wake up.
Alva.
Looks like Alva...
...is dead.
Avalilintar!
Avalilintar
Professor, we're not done yet.
We still have to close the cave's door with a spell.
So, Antaboga will never appear again.
That's right, Professor.
Kurufung!
Let me try, Professor.
What if we try together?
Anyone can do it.
Let's do it.
Kurufung!
Wake up, Dad.
Why is the door so strong?
You try, Alva.
I'm sorry, Professor.
But, Alva's condition...
...is impossible for her.
Alva.
Do you want to try?
Come on. Concentrate.
You can do it.
Kurufung!
Alva is so cool!
You're amazing, Alva.
Don't say that.
My guess is right.
Alva is...
Alva!
Wake up!
Dad.
Wake up, Dad.
Vega.
Ray.
Andara.
Welcome, Alva.
Vega.
Where's Glita?
She's fine.
But, Mr. Galaxy...
What about Mr. Galaxy?
Mr. Galaxy...
Mr. Galaxy saved you and Glita.
He was attacked...
...by Professor Ankara.
Now, he's being cured...
...by Professor Lebaran.
Dad.
Dad, wake up.
Be patient, Glita.
You have to be sincere.
So, your dad can rest in peace.
When I was little, I only had my dad.
Now, he's gone.
I'm all alone.
Glita.
You're not alone.
We're here for you.
I want to go to school with you.
Do you want to?
Yes.
Come with me.
You want to, right?
You're so nice.
Thank you.
6 months later
Now, we can go back to Sihir School.
Glita.
Now, we'll always be together.
So, don't be sad.
Dad.
Wait.
I want to go with you.
You can't.
We're going to school.
If I don't go with him, I'll die.
Alva.
There's only one way...
...so that I won't go with you.
You won't be his teacher anymore.
But, what should I do?
The only way is to cut your hair.
Then, he'll be free.
Cut.
6 months later
This is for Popo?
Yes.
Are you serious?
Now, you're free.
You're not a servant anymore.
I'm free?
I'm free!
Thank you, Alva.
You're the best teacher ever.
You're welcome, Popo.
You've helped me a lot.
I'll go now.
6 months later
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Now, I'm going to introduce a new student.
Her name is Pelita.
Pelita.
Hi.
I'm Pelita.
My name is Tolik.
Pelita, please sit with me.
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
Children, please continue your meal.
Yes, sir.
Okay, sir.
Alva.
You're so big.
You don't eat for a week.
I don't understand.
Why am I always like this?
I feel hungry.
I don't understand.
6 months later
Alva.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know. It's weird.
Why?
I don't know.
I want to eat a rat.
Do you want to try?
Alva.
What's wrong with you?
Wake up.
Alva.
Help.
Wake up.
We can do this.
Alva.
How do you feel now?
I feel dizzy.
Alva was poisoned by a snake.
The snake must give her medicine.
If not, in three days...
Alva will turn into a snake.
It's horrible.
Where's the medicine?
The medicine?
It's in a place that's far away from here.
It's in a mysterious island.
A mysterious island that's far away from here.
The medicine is very rare.
It's called the liquid of life.
The medicine is very powerful.
It can cure...
...all diseases.
All diseases.
It's said that...
...the medicine can revive a dead person.
Very amazing.
Professor.
I'll go there to find it.
You can't, Megantara.
Only children can go there.
Okay, I'll go there.
Me too.
We can't let a child go there.
You're right, Professor.
I'm worried too.
Professor.
This is a difficult decision for me.
I don't think I can let the children go there...
...without our protection.
But we can't let Alva turn into a snake.
Professor.
We often pass dangerous obstacles.
Because we're always compact.
So, we can overcome this obstacle.
Yes, Professor.
I hope we can overcome this obstacle.
Yes.
Okay.
I agree.
Thank you, Professor.
You're welcome.
Come on, Alva.
Don't say that.
You don't have to be like that.
We're your friends, aren't we, Ren?
Yes, we're friends.
So, no matter how difficult it is, we'll be together.
You're right, Ren.
Best friend.
Go, go, go.
I'm Pelipir.
I'm Nangka.
I'm from Pasar Raya.
You don't know me.
I'm Megantara.
Tentara.
Why?
Am I too cute when I was a kid?
But I'm pretty, right?
You're right.
Tentara, will you join us?
Yes.
Let's go inside.
I can do it, right?
Yes.
Tentara!
Turns out, I'm not that smart.
This island is smarter.
Tentara!
Don't!
Don't use magic here.
It's dangerous.
But, Tentara...
If you use magic, it will come back to you.
Tentara...
Let it burn.
Keep it well.
It will be very useful for you at the right time.
Tentara...
Alva...
Vega...
Ray...
Both of you.
The three of you. Remember.
You have to be alert.
Tentara Kira.
We don't want to be seen.
I know.
We brought this.
But Tentara said...
This will be useful.
It's better if we keep it.
Tentara Kira.
Welcome to the Mystery Cave.
You will pass through the first gate.
That is...
The Gate of Dreams.
A place where you can eat all kinds of food.
But remember.
Once you eat that food...
You will not be able to continue your journey to the next place.
If you give up...
Raise the white flag.
Automatically...
You will be at the first gate.
That's great.
Ray.
We don't have to bring it.
It's better if we pass all the challenges.
The first one to place the blue flag...
Is the winner.
And if there is a disqualified contestant...
He will be disqualified.
I have to get that liquid of life.
I have to lose everything...
So I can live again.
And remember.
That liquid of life is very rare.
Only one person can get that very rare liquid of life.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Before we start...
You can get ready.
The toilet is over there.
And the costume room is over there.
There is no one who can beat Raya.
She is beautiful.
She will also do the challenge.
I think someone is missing.
I have to make them scared.
So they will run away.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
Nine...
Ten...
Eleven...
Twelve...
Fourteen...
Fifteen...
Sixteen...
Seventeen...
Twenty-one...
Twenty-two...
Twenty-three...
Twenty-four...
Twenty-five...
Twenty-six...
Twenty-nine...
Twenty-eight...
Twenty-ten...
Fishing for anchovies...
that got a stone.
This is Mystery Island.
It turns out...
there are a lot of ghosts.
Then, what about Vega, Alba, and Reng?
Can they get...
the water of life?
To be continued...
Dad, I miss you.
Now I don't have anyone else.
I miss you too.
The power is back.
It's been a long time since you last appeared.
Mom...
Don't leave me, Mom.
Who will take care of me?
Lita...
Are you done, honey?
Yes, Mom.
LITA'S DREAM
Lita...
Sadness that is too deep and long...
will make your strength appear.
If you are angry,
it will endanger yourself...
and others.
So, you have to be careful.
You have to be able to control your emotions.
If you are sad,
don't cry.
And you have to be calm, okay?
I can't be sad.
I have to be strong.
Don't let the power reappear.
Why isn't it turning off?
There's a ghost here.
He will also make me scared.
There's someone missing.
I'm so scared.
Give me the flag.
Give it to the jury.
That's it.
If I throw the white flag,
it means I failed.
I can't be scared.
Why is he throwing the white flag?
I'll scare him again.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared of you.
Come out.
Why? You're scared of me, right?
Look at your face.
You're so scared of me.
You don't know who I am, Raya.
I'm not scared of you.
I've been to Jaksa,
Naga Kepala 3.
You don't know anything.
Really?
Look at your face. You're so scared of me.
See?
I'm not scared of you.
I don't like him.
He's so weird.
Whatever.
I'll make him lose.
I have to win.
Where are you going?
No.
Alva.
Wake up.
Raya.
I have to get rid of him.
And win his trust.
Because that's the only way I can live again.
He's so handsome.
To be continued...