To be continued...
Heart's strength
Go, go, go
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can do it
Alva, why did you take that rock?
Professor Agni asked me to
Because this school is in danger
No, only that rock can save this school
In three days, he will gain unlimited power
And will destroy this world
You are expelled from school
What's this?
To be continued...
What are you doing?
Where am I?
Maybe they want me to follow them
To be continued...
It's moving
You guys!
Why are you here?
Come on, hurry up
I'm sorry, Alva
I don't trust you anymore
Okay, if you're still mad
It's fate
Because I was wrong
No, I'm not mad
Are you serious?
Yes
Alva
You're my friend, right?
BSD forever!
Alva
We believe that you're not wrong
That's why
We prevent you from leaving
Yes, if that's the case
I want to be expelled
I can still go to school, right?
Unfortunately, only the three of us
Who believe in you
So
You're still expelled from school
That's why we have to do this
We have to clear your name
So you can go to school again
But how?
The way
We have to catch the person who took the stone
That's right!
Yes, that's right
The person who slandered you
The Dark Lord, right?
Not the Dark Lord
But the person ordered by the Dark Lord
This person's magic is very powerful, Alva
That's why
I will train the three of you
So you can fight him
Especially
You, Alva
The Dark Lord
So cool!
Vega
Take the stone
And throw it to me
But
Come on, hurry!
The Dark Lord
Throw it as hard as you can
So cool!
Now you try to cast a spell
Okay, Dark Lord
Spell!
Rey
You throw Alva with the stone
Really, Dark Lord?
Come on, Rey
Let's test Alva's spell
Alva
The spell you made is still too thin
Not enough
You have to concentrate more
In reading this spell
Come on
Try again
Okay
So cool!
Throw it as hard as you can
Sorry, bro
I think
That's enough training
We will continue later
No, no
No, soldier
I still want to try again
I have to keep training
Don't, Alva
You are too tired
If you are forced
It can be dangerous for you
Come on, Rey
Where are you going?
Alva
You have to stay here
We have to leave here
Because we will be searched
Okay?
Alva
If there's anything
Just say my name three times
But if it doesn't come up
Just run away
At least
There's still someone who believes in me
Thank you
Thank you for helping me
We are happy to help you
Right, girls?
Yippee!
Dragon fruit
I also
Want to say
Thank you
There's a man
Attack!
Run!
It's so quiet
Without Vega and Rey
I have to train
So that I can
Hurry up!
Buffer, Zai!
Zai!
Ouch
It hurts
I can't give up
Buffer, Zai!
Where are you?
Alva
You have to act faster
Before it's too late
Don't let the stone
Fall to the ground
Yes
I'm looking for that man
Remember
Don't leave me
In the sea, maybe you don't know
But in your heart
It's not dead
You have to believe in your heart
Stop!
Why do I always dream about them?
But they're right
I have to stop the darkness
From getting that stone
I have to keep training
Buffer, Zai!
Yes, I won!
I won!
Hurray!
Alva won!
I won!
Hurray!
You're great, Alva
Perfect
That means
Now
You can do
Your research
Yes!
Now, let's make Agni sad
I agree
Let's not make him sad
You do it, Alva
Huh?
You're going to interrogate Prof. Agni
By pretending to be Prof. Aldebaran
Huh?
Here's the report
With this report
You can be Prof. Aldebaran
Are you sure?
I'm sure
I've followed everything in the book
Prove it
I want to see the result
Okay, I'll prove it
Alva
Now, stand in this chair
Wow, that's so cool
Now, I'm Prof. Aldebaran
But, what else can I do?
There's only one way
You can't get wet
If you get wet
You're going to be your original self
Right, Dara?
Yes, that's right
Remember that, Alva
Prof. Aldebaran
Come in
Good afternoon, ma'am
Eh, Prof
What is it, Prof?
Is there anything important
That made you come to my office?
I'm studying
Self-defense
I need your help
To try to attack me
Attack you?
Yes
You tried to attack me
With a strong mantra
Until I fainted
That mantra is
Meriamfang Mantra
And it's a black magic
Ma'am
I've never studied that
And I can't do it
Ouch
My hand suddenly hurts, Prof
Try this
Professor, take a look
Ouch, it hurts, Prof
Try this
There's no ring
Where's the ring, Prof?
You don't wear a ring?
I've never worn a ring
I'm sorry, Prof
Let me help you
Oh my god
I forgot
I can't get wet
I have to get out of here
Prof
I'm sorry
Excuse me
I need to go to the toilet
Prof, I need your help
It's okay
Professor
Professor Purwa
Alva
You've been expelled from this school
Why are you still here?
Sabine's ring
So, Professor Purwa did it
The one who took the ring
How dare you kill me like that?
Now, you're coming with me
We're going to face Professor Aldebaran
You have to leave this school
Let's go
How dare you fight me?
Alva
Sabine
Professor
Alva
Where do you think you're going?
Get out
Alva
You can't run away, Alva
Stay there
Alva
What's that?
Where is he?
He was here
I think Professor Purwa can't see me
Is it because of this test?
Alva
It's true, he can't see me
Where are you, Alva?
It's been a long time
I want to sleep
You're so annoying
It hurts
How dare you fight me?
What are you doing, Rey?
You're the one who's fighting
What did I do to you?
Don't pretend
Who's pretending?
Stop fighting
It's better to be calm
It's more comfortable
It's safer
It's more balanced
Oh no
Both of you are angry
How dare you fight me?
This is the army
Just fight
No
It's not the army
Rey
Stop fighting
Alva?
When did you come?
Because I'm wearing this
It's a magic wand
If we wear it, we won't be seen
This is a magic wand
Where did you get this magic wand?
This magic wand fell from the sky
When I was chased,
Professor Purwa was trapped in a labyrinth
Thanks to this magic wand, I'm safe
I know who the stone thief is
Who?
Professor Purwa
He's a man wearing a cow moon ring
He's the one who chased me until I fainted
And he took the stone
Are you sure?
Yes
I saw him wearing that ring
I'm sure
He must be the thief
Don't make excuses
If you don't have any evidence
That's why we have to look for Professor Purwa's office
Who knows, the stone was hidden there
Where is it?
We have to hurry
Don't make any noise
If we do this, we'll be caught
Can you be quiet?
Yes
Shh, don't make any noise
Okay, let's look for it
Let's go
Where is it?
Let's walk slowly to the door
Then we run away
Okay
Let's go
Help!
Stop!
Stop right there!
Help!
I said stop right there!
Stop right there!
Help!
Where did they go?
Professor Langkara?
Thank you for saving us.
Kids, now everyone is at my house.
Is there anything you want me to talk about?
Yes.
From there, I already know that Professor Purwa is the culprit.
He's the one who took the bottle.
That's why we have to investigate the room.
Because when the body was found, the room was still quiet.
Kids, what you've done is very dangerous.
I'll try again.
Remember.
Next time, you have to be careful.
If you want to investigate,
you have to make a plan in advance.
And don't make a mistake.
Okay?
Yes, Professor.
You can go now.
Let's go.
What is this?
Don't pretend.
You did it, didn't you?
Answer me.
What do you mean, Purwa?
Fine.
I'll make you understand what I mean.
Langkara.
What is this?
It's nothing, Professor.
I just want to make sure that Professor Langkara...
The enemy is right in front of us.
We should be united.
Not divided.
You're right, Professor.
I'll prove that I'm right.
Just wait and see.
Tomorrow is Ramadhan.
And we haven't found the stone yet.
We have to keep an eye on Professor Purwa.
Tomorrow, he'll go back to school...
to give the stone to the Dark Lord.
So, we have to follow him.
Not us.
But me.
But it's impossible, Alva.
You can't do it alone.
Because it's dangerous.
Hold on.
If you and Ray follow me,
the teachers will be suspicious.
I'm the only one who can escape...
without being suspicious.
Because everyone knows...
that I was expelled from school.
Alva, wait.
We're friends.
Whatever happens, we have to be together.
Vega, Ray.
Please.
Follow me.
You've helped me a lot.
And now, I have to solve this myself.
But, this is all my fault.
This is all my fault.
I took the stone.
And now, I have to break it again.
Alva.
Enough, Ray.
To be continued...
I'm scared.
It's wet.
There's no use hiding.
I'm scared.
To be continued...
Why are there two Professor Purwa?
One of them must be using a form of change of existence
You can't reach the water
If you don't run away from the water
You will be in the distance
Water, water
I have to find water
Where's the water?
There she is
She's gone, get her!
To be continued...
Alva!
Don't push Alva
She's dangerous
What are you talking about, Purwa?
You're the bad guy
I came here to curse Alva
Alva
What do you think?
Who do you trust the most?
I give you three minutes
To clean this page
To be continued...
I'm working with Professor Angkara
Good, Alva
Now you help me attack him
Let's attack him together
To be continued...
You bastard
You don't deserve to be in this school
Alva, help me!
Alva, stay there!
To be continued...
I'm sorry, Professor Purwa
But I won't let anyone
Disturb my mission
To take the Stone of Eternity
Why are you surprised, Alva?
Yes
I'm the culprit
To be continued...
Yes
I'm the culprit
I took the Stone of Eternity
To give it to the 8th Prince
So?
I hypnotized Professor Agni
By using Professor Purwa's body
So I can ask Alva
To take the Stone of Eternity
Be careful
Then I protect you
With your friends
So you can trust me
Yes
And you're suspecting Professor Purwa
And I've conspired to be Professor Agni
To take the Stone of Eternity easily
And lastly
I hypnotized you again, Purwa
To defeat you
Thanks to me
The 8th Prince will rise again
His power will recover
And all of you will be destroyed
The destruction of this school
Will begin with you
But
The first one I will destroy is you
To be continued...
Alva
Are you sure you want to fight me?
The power you have
Is nothing compared to the power I have
I don't want to be evil
I won't let you destroy anyone
Whatever
I give up
In that case
I will destroy you both
To be continued...
Forgive me, Professor Purwa
Because I've accused you wrongly
Your action is very reckless, Alva
You could have been killed
Attention, everyone
Please listen to this important news
As you know
The Stone of Eternity has been stolen
But now
I'm happy to inform you that
The thief has been caught
Now
I will call a child
Who has helped us find the thief
Alva
To be continued...
And from now on
The school has decided
That Alva will not be expelled from the school
And even
The school will give Alva a medal
For all her efforts
Go, go, go
Never stop
Fight with all your might
Go, go, go
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can do it
Congratulations
Thank you, Professor
Alva
Go, go, go
Never stop
Never give up
Go, go, go
Be proud of yourself
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can do it
Achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go
Never stop