To be continued...
What are you doing to my sister?
I'm here to see you.
You have my permission.
No one can stop you.
Good afternoon, children.
Wow, you can make the hat.
Wow, it's so cool.
Don't you dare to enter this room.
Alfa entered the secret room and met the third-in-command.
What we fear will happen.
What's going on?
Calm down, children.
Calm down, everyone.
What's going on?
Calm down.
There's a monster that managed to get in.
Monster?
Is it a food for children?
Yes, ma'am.
Don't make noise.
You're not safe now.
And don't go out before I order you.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go.
Did you see Vega?
Vega?
Where's Vega?
Where are you?
I was with Vega.
He said he wanted to go to the bathroom.
He's over there.
Don't go.
We can't go out with him.
He's safe.
But, he's our friend.
What if something happens to him?
It's dangerous.
Wait for me.
What's going on?
No!
I am...
Varga!
It's huge!
Why is it so small?
What's going on?
We're going to be late.
It's Vega!
Let's go!
I am...
Varga!
Where are we going?
Help!
I am...
Varga!
This way.
Vega!
Let's go!
Varga!
Let the kid go!
C-3PO!
Varga!
Help me!
What's going on?
I am...
Varga!
Magneto!
I am...
Varga!
C-3PO.
His teeth can really kill.
Let's go.
But you can kill him...
...through his teeth.
Concentrate.
And use your lollipop.
I am...
Varga!
Alva.
Thank you, Alva.
It's not your fault.
You're the only one who can do this.
Why me, Professor?
Alva.
Promise me.
Don't tell anyone...
...what just happened.
...that you've defeated the monster.
Now...
...go back to the lab.
Let your friends take care of it.
The monster?
What do we do?
Varga is a very powerful monster.
He's the hand of the 8th Prince.
The only one who can defeat him...
...is the 8th Prince...
...and a chosen child.
Who is he?
Alva.
He's the chosen child.
The son of Gamma and Aquila.
He will be our savior.
That's why...
...we have to take care of him.
Train him...
...with all our abilities.
So that when the time comes...
...Alva can fight the 8th Prince.
Agni.
Keep this a secret.
Don't let anyone know...
...that the chosen child is in this school.
If anyone finds out...
...the 8th Prince...
...they will know sooner than we think.
Yes, sir.
We are ready...
...to be sworn.
I swear.
My monster!
Where is my monster?
Calm down, Ray.
There's a monster here.
Really?
But I was in my room.
Weren't we fighting the monster?
Of course.
But you fainted.
Then?
Where is my monster now?
Who defeated him?
Again?
Hold it.
Don't shout like a thief.
I'm so curious.
I was in my room when I woke up.
You fainted.
Then the teachers and Professor Aldebaran came.
Professor Aldebaran defeated the monster?
Yes.
I'm the monster.
Professor Aldebaran was defeated.
As long as Professor Aldebaran is here, we are safe.
That's right.
Why am I here?
Thank God.
Both of you are awake.
Professor Ali.
Where is my monster?
Calm down, Professor Pula.
My monster has been defeated.
So the Dark Lord is here.
Because only he can defeat him.
Calm down, Professor Pula.
The Dark Lord is not here.
But the chosen one has defeated him.
Who is he?
I'm sorry.
But I promised not to tell anyone.
What's clear is that...
the chosen one is among our students here.
Alfa.
You have to protect the Stone of Eternity in this school.
What is the Stone of Eternity?
The Stone of Eternity is a very strong stone.
The stone cannot fall into the wrong hands.
You have to protect that stone.
But how do I protect it?
Protect it with your sincerity, Alfa.
How do you know this school?
And you know my name?
Who are you really?
One day you will know who we really are.
Hey! Who are you?
What is it?
I had a weird dream.
What dream?
This.
A statue.
What?
I was visited by someone.
And that person is really nice.
I can feel it.
They love me.
And the weirdest thing is...
They told me to protect the Stone of Eternity in this school.
The Stone of Eternity?
What is that?
I've never heard of it.
Maybe it's just a dream.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Wait!
The dream is real.
It's real.
The person in the dream must be serious.
Who is the person in your dream?
I don't know. I don't know.
How about this?
Let's ask Tantara tomorrow.
Maybe she knows.
Where is Tantara?
There he is.
Oh yeah.
Let's go.
Tantara.
What is the Stone of Eternity?
The Stone of Eternity.
The stone that guards the three-headed dragon.
So, there really is the Stone of Eternity.
Alva.
You...
How do you know the Stone of Eternity?
You're just in the first grade.
You don't know it yet.
Over there.
I'm busy cooking for the three-headed dragon.
Oh.
So, the three-headed dragon...
likes rendang, gudeg, and asinan.
This.
This is my cooking.
I love eating gudeg, asinan, and rendang.
I'm hungry.
Don't disturb me.
Let's go.
Gosh.
My mouth.
I can't keep it.
There's a stone behind the dragon.
And the dragon guards the stone.
What's so special about the stone?
I don't know.
To be continued...
Don't you dare to eat...
or do anything...
during my lesson time.
You all know it.
The students have entered our school.
And for that, there's a new rule that will be applied.
After 8 p.m.
All students are forbidden to leave the classroom.
And if anyone steps in...
the perpetrator will be punished.
And one classroom will be punished.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Now, I'm going to teach you a new mantra...
that you can use...
to take other things.
Pay attention, all of you.
Lafathang Buku.
Now...
Concentrate.
All of you, try it.
Start!
Lafathang Buku.
It's so cool.
Alfa.
I assign you to clean this page.
How much time do you need?
Three hours, Prof.
Living in this world...
is not as easy as living in the real world.
I assign you three minutes...
to clean this page...
and you must be able to finish it.
Do you understand?
Three minutes.
Prof.
I think, Prof...
for Alfa's size...
the punishment is...
too heavy.
This is still in my class.
So I have the right to decide anything...
for the students' education.
I forgot, Prof.
If that's the case...
please continue.
Thank you.
Alfa.
Do as I say.
If you can't finish it...
your punishment will be heavier.
Three minutes.
Two minutes and fifty-nine seconds.
One box, please.
One box.
There's a ripe fruit.
Sir.
I'm hungry.
Try it.
It must be delicious.
Ripe...
fruit.
Ripe fruit.
Oh, yes.
I've learned...
Mantra Bindai Menda.
It's a good idea.
I can use the mantra...
for this punishment.
Try it.
Ripe...
small paper.
It's so big.
Yes!
I did it!
It's clean!
Yeah!
To be continued...
You must answer my question.
Who is the chosen one?
I can't answer, Professor.
Because my mouth has been swore by the mantra...
to tell anyone.
I see.
Now, you must do...
what I ask you to do.
Because you...
know who the chosen one is.
You must be able to...
tell the chosen one.
To enter the secret room...
and take the stone.
Yes, Professor.
One more thing.
You must lead the chosen one...
to take the stone.
Alva.
We want to help you with the punishment.
Yes.
Do we still need to work?
No.
No need.
The punishment is over.
Huh?
Why is it so fast?
Yeah.
How is it possible?
Alva.
Come to my room now.
What's wrong, Alva?
You're smart.
You know everything.
But I don't know everything.
Let's find out.
Alva.
I called you...
because you must do something for me.
Tonight.
Before the sun rises.
You must return to the secret room.
And take the Stone of Eternity for me.
Isn't that forbidden?
This school is in danger, Alva.
And only the Stone of Eternity...
can save us all.
But why do I have to take the stone?
Because you managed to defeat Varga.
That monster...
will come back to life...
when the sun rises.
But how, ma'am?
There's a three-headed dragon there.
And that dragon is very strong.
I will tell you...
the story of the three-headed dragon.
Three hundred years ago.
There lived three great warriors...
and three great dragons.
They loved those dragons so much.
They gave them their favorite food.
Until one day...
they were faced by the Dark Lord's army.
And the three of them were defeated.
Ashifa and Daini died.
The three of them felt very lonely...
because they lost their master.
The cries of the three of them...
lit up the sky.
This brought the three of them together.
Senua and Daini...
became the three-headed dragons...
and they were very powerful.
So, the three of them...
can eat the same food...
as their master.
I saw the army...
cooking three different foods.
Is that true for the three-headed dragons?
It's very true, Alva.
I've already told you...
everything.
Now...
it's up to you.
You're the only one...
who can take the Stone of Eternity...
and save our lives.
We can do it!
It's scary when it's narrow.
It's 6 o'clock.
What we have to do now...
is to make three different foods...
that the three-headed dragons like...
which are...
rendang, budek, and asinan.
And finally, we have to cook...
the Stone of Eternity.
That means we have to go to the kitchen.
There it is.
Let's go.
Professor!
Who's there?
Come out!
I said, come out...
or I'll have to use magic.
One.
Two.
Stop!
I want to talk to you.
Can you let me out?
Okay.
The Stone of Eternity
Ouch.
That hurts.
Don't wait.
We have to take it off.
Let's talk later.
Now, let's go to the kitchen...
and cook.
Okay.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Help me.
The Stone of Eternity
It's time.
It's time to show up.
Like someone who's cooking.
Who's in there?
The Stone of Eternity
It's heavy.
Be careful.
The Stone of Eternity
Rey, Vega.
If you don't like this food...
and it's getting worse...
you have to turn around...
so I can face it.
Let's go.
The Stone of Eternity
Be careful.
It can drown you.
Rey, wake up.
Her face is blue.
Rey, she's possessed.
The Stone of Eternity
Vega!
Rey!
Someone's coming! Let's go!
Her face is blue!
Rey!
She's poisoned!
Poison gas can kill you if it's not in your body!
What should we do?
We have to take her to the clinic!
No, no, no!
Just do your job!
You have to take her to the hospital before the sun sets!
So I can take care of her, Rey!
But...
It's okay!
Rey!
We're here!
Let's go!
Let's go, Rey!
Alpha!
You have to succeed!
The three of you are still not ready!
You better go to Vega now!
They are not just any ordinary people...
...but they are...
...the princesses of Angsa!
I will save you!
Alva, why did you take that stone?
Professor Agni asked me to do it...
...because this school is in danger.
Only that stone can save this school.
Alva must be released.
Three more days until the lunar month.
And if in the lunar month...
...the Dark Lord gets the Kabadian Stone...
...he will get an unlimited power...
...that will destroy this world.
To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Achieve all your dreams!
Never stop!
Go! Go! Go!
Fight with all your might!
Be proud of yourself!
Go! Go! Go!
Let's dream!
We'll make it!