This story is purely fictional. If there are similarities in names, characters/figures, and places in this show, it is merely a coincidence without any element of intentionality.
MDentertainment presents
🎵 "Show your spirit, get your friends ready" 🎵
🎵 "Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars" 🎵
🎵 "Be brave, don't give up" 🎵
🎵 "Chase your dreams and hopes" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, never stop" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, fight with all your heart" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, make yourself proud" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, let's dream" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, we can do it" 🎵
🎵 "We can do it!" 🎵
When the dark lord attacked you,
there was a power that appeared in you
and made the dark lord furious
When he wanted to attack you again,
he realized that he had lost all his power
What do you want, Angkar?
I will grant it
I want to be the head of the school of magic
What a coincidence, Angkar
That's what you're thinking
I will allow you to live here
but on one condition
What condition, sir?
You have to fight me
What?
Fire!
I will make this school the second head of the school of magic
Just watch me
You will know that I'm better than you
The second round
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Angkar, you're dead!
The soul stone will spread all over the school of magic
It's far away, thousands of kilometers
And it will be rain, thunder, and sand
Will you be able to go to the school of magic like that?
Enjoy the last round of the final round
Because tomorrow, I will be sitting there
And this room will be my room
Now, let's welcome the new head of the school
The head of the school that we have been waiting for
The head of the school of magic that is the most powerful
Who is he?
We will not wait for anyone else
Professor Angkara!
You're all so good!
Angkara, you're great!
You deserve to be the head of the school of magic
Thank you
I feel like I'm hearing voices
Now, the third round
The third round!
One
Two
Three
Finish it!
[The third round]
I'm going to fall!
You said you're going to finish it!
Wait! Wait!
It can't be like that!
I won the first round
That means I won!
I'm sorry, Professor
The decision of the students can't be changed
What should we do now?
I know the way
Why don't you just tell Alfa to finish it?
That's a good idea!
I agree!
Alfa
The two of you
The one who never gives up
If you're angry, she'll always be angry
Okay?
One, two, three!
We're still the winners!
We're going home
Okay
All of you
We're done singing
I'll take my leave
And the lesson will be continued by Professor Tita
Professor Agni, Professor Yasmin
I'll take my leave
Good afternoon, students!
Good afternoon, sir!
Wow!
You're all smiling!
Do you miss Professor Tita?
Yes, sir!
Now, before the lesson starts
You have to say hello to Professor Tita
Try to imitate her
Say "Ahai" with a smile
Let's try
Ahai!
With a smile!
With a smile, too!
Do you want chocolate?
Yes, sir!
Do you want lollipop?
Okay, I'll give you one
With a smile!
Put your right hand first
Still okay?
Here's your prize!
A mosquito raincoat!
Mosquito!
Ahai!
With a smile!
Very good!
Now, finish the mosquito!
Why are we still drinking mosquitoes?
We want chocolate and lollipop, not mosquitoes!
Mosquitoes are not tasty!
That's right!
You have to go to war
So you have to drink mosquitoes
So you can be strong!
Not like that, Professor Jasmine
Professor Agni
Students, what Professor Tan said is true
Mosquitoes are very pitiful
So you have to drink them all
Yes, ma'am!
Very good!
Okay, I'm going to drink the mosquito!
My students!
Ahai!
With a smile!
Do you feel strong now?
Yes, sir!
Now, I'm going to teach you a mantra
This mantra is called "Airfang Mantra"
Here's an example
Get some airfang!
My students, look!
At the end of this line, there's water
That's the use of airfang mantra
I'm thirsty! I want to drink water!
Airfang!
Me too!
You have to practice seriously
Don't be silly!
You have to face the darkness with spirit
Don't play around!
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Listen to what Professor Agni and Professor Jasmine said
Now, you have to try it together
And whoever can get the most water from the end of the line
Will get a present from me
Okay?
Let's try it now!
Let's try it!
Airfang Mantra
Wow!
Give me a smile!
Very good!
My students, the one who can get the most water from the end of the line
Is me!
So, I'll give you a present
I got a brown one!
Thank you, sir!
You're welcome, Nick
How does it taste?
It's so good, Prof!
The brown one is so tasty!
And it's big inside!
It's so good, Nick!
Nick, choose one!
And for the other students
If you can do this again
You'll also get a present from the professor
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Smart!
Give me a smile!
So, students
Are you all ready to be tested?
What test, Prof?
The bonsai tree is being watered
While the fruit is not yet ripe
Hi, students!
Megantara is here!
Is there anything we can do for you, Megantara?
Of course!
Why are you all here?
Students
There's a task for you
What is it?
I'm sorry, Megantara
But I can't help you with this
You're the one who's responsible for this
I'm sorry, Megantara
But I can't help you with this
You're the one who's responsible for this
I'm sorry, Megantara
But I can't help you with this
You're the one who's responsible for this
You're so pretty
Do you know me?
I'm Jack
My name is Tommy
My name is Mike
There's another attack!
It's a boar!
What?
Eyes right.
Come on, fight.
Find her weak spot.
Come on, Benjo.
Where is Anebaran's last card?
Eyes right.
Eyes left.
Only Nick and three of his friends are alive.
How is this?
Anebaran's last card.
How can you beat the 8th Prince?
You've lost to Duyung.
Megantara.
It seems like they're not ready.
But, Professor Ado.
The Stone of Soul.
They have to get it.
Kids.
Come on.
Use Airfah's spell.
Airfah.
It's Duyung.
Nick.
Yes.
We did it.
Kids.
You've succeeded.
You're accepted.
Yes.
Megantara.
These kids are being tested.
You shouldn't tell them the answer.
What are you doing here?
If other people know, our plan will fail.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm just checking this room.
Because I'll be in this room soon.
"The Stone of Soul"
Help.
Please help us.
Don't hurt us.
Whose voice is that?
Is that the voice?
That's none of your business.
If you feel bothered by that voice,
there's a river nearby.
I'm here to pick up the kids.
Not to have fun.
I don't have money to live.
It's not like usual.
You're looking for freebies?
"The Stone of Soul"
Come here.
I want to warn you.
Don't tell the others about the stone in that room.
Let's go.
Why?
I can't trust the others.
Moreover,
the less people know,
the better.
Because if they find out...
that you and Akulila are still alive,
he'll come after them.
Who's that?
I think he's looking for...
the stone in that room.
Is that so?
We have to keep it a secret.
Don't let anyone know.
Don't let them know.
Agree?
But, listen.
You have to know this.
If you're not the one who's in charge,
he'll be investigated.
Your job now is...
to keep it a secret.
Okay? / Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Ready? / Yes, sir.
"The Stone of Akulila"
Angara.
To make our plan easier,
we'll stay here.
Because this building is near the school.
So, we can keep an eye on them.
Yes, sir. / Let's go.
Sir.
It's true.
We're not supposed to rest in a dirty place like this.
"The Stone of Akulila"
You're amazing, sir.
Wait. / Angara.
Get up.
This is the place.
Then, where do I sleep?
You sleep here.
What's wrong?
Nothing, sir.
For now,
this will be our base.
So, we can keep an eye on them.
Until we get a chance...
to take everything from them.
Yes, sir.
"The Stone of Akulila"
♪ Get your spirit up, get your enthusiasm ready ♪
♪ Friends, friends, friends, friends ♪
♪ Running, jumping, jumping, jumping ♪
♪ Stars, stars, stars, stars ♪
♪ Running, never giving up ♪
♪ Chase your feelings and dreams ♪
♪ Go, go, go ♪
♪ Chase your dreams and dreams ♪
♪ Never stop, go, go, go ♪
♪ Run with all your might ♪
♪ Go, go, go ♪
Be quiet.
I want to sleep.
Don't be noisy.
What? You're fast asleep.
I know.
What?
We're not the same.
So, don't play with me.
I need to sleep.
Do you know that?
What are you doing?
Why do you need to sleep?
I want to lead my parents.
I want to ask them to show me.
I have an idea.
I know how.
I have a mantra.
So, people can sleep soundly.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Okay.
Let me do it.
Sleep soundly.
[Mantra]
It's so cool.
I know. I'm smart.
Dad.
Mom.
Where are you?
What?
Dad.
Mom.
What?
I'm so happy.
Dad and mom can live together again.
You said that we'll be together again.
Yes.
If Gama and Akuwila appear in your dream,
ask them.
Ask them what I have to do...
to wake them up.
Dad.
Mom.
Can you show me?
What is that?
Show me so that you can be supported again.
Alfa.
Is it difficult?
No.
I'll try no matter how difficult it is.
So that you can be supported again.
Alfa.
There's only one way to remove the curse.
That is the blood of the 8th prince.
I don't want to be a burden to you.
I want to be a good son.
I want to be a good father.
Remove the blood of the 8th prince.
Then the curse will be lifted.
What's wrong?
Why did you say the blood of the 8th prince?
I have a clue.
My parents can sense...
if they're being smeared with the blood of the 8th prince.
The blood of the 8th prince?
Yes.
Alfa.
Where are you going?
I'm going to find the 8th prince.
But how?
I don't know how.
But I have to go there.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Let me go.
I miss them.
I want them to live.
Let me go.
I miss them.
That's why I have to find the 8th prince.
So that they can live.
Don't be sad.
I'm crying too.
Don't cry.
Alfa.
We know you're sad.
But don't be sad.
If you want to fight the 8th prince, that's okay.
But we have to make a plan first.
What if you lose?
What will happen to you?
Your parents will be sad.
Do you want that?
Yes.
We know you're sad.
What's that sound?
Someone's coming.
Let's go.
Who's that?
We found you.
Professor Poa is kidnapped.
What are you doing?
I'm dreaming.
You told me that you can't come here.
Shut up.
Don't comment.
I'll make you pay.
Shut up.
We're not done yet.
Not yet.
Where are you going?
I'm going to pee.
Mega Dark.
Are you sure...
...Nik and his friends are ready?
I'm sure.
The four of them have passed the test.
So I think they can help me find the soul stone.
So, where are we going?
The closest soul stone is in a village.
It's far from here.
Thousands of kilometers.
Are you ready?
We're ready.
I'll go with them.
So, don't worry.
Don't worry.
Bring him.
What is this?
It's a detector.
It's like a magnet.
So it won't be suspicious.
When the detector makes a beep, it means there's a soul stone.
And the children can hear it.
"The children can hear it."
Okay, professor.
Go back to your room.
Prepare your things.
We're going to the village tonight.
Yes, sir.
Professor.
It's a test.
I've always wanted to know about people.
What is this?
Yes, sir.
Can I talk to you?
Sure.
I've told my parents.
Your parents?
How is it, Alfa?
What did they say?
I've shown them.
They said they could sense...
...if they were smeared with the dark spirit's blood.
The dark spirit's blood?
Yes, the dark spirit's blood.
Alfa...
It's impossible. It's very difficult.
Especially now, calling the dark spirit and finding its biggest power.
But I have to answer it...
...for my parents.
So they'll be aware.
Okay, here's the thing.
The first thing we have to do is...
...to find out where the dark spirit's base is.
I don't care.
I'll punish them when they arrive at school.
We can do it.
I won't give up so easily.
I'll do it.
"Dark spirit's base"
The dark spirit won't be affected by the fire.
Smart.
"Dark spirit's base"
Stop it!
No, sir.
Maybe it's the old prototype that's affected by Vega.
Let's just continue our conversation.
It's the professor.
Sir, where is he?
He's not here.
It's the professor again.
But his voice was so clear.
He was so loud.
I don't know why.
Maybe he went back to his room.
That's impossible.
Let's go to his room. I'm sleepy.
Me too.
You're so naive.
I'll punish them when they arrive at school.
What if we know where the base is?
After we know the location,
we'll make a plan to get rid of the dark spirit.
Now, we have to do the first thing.
Follow me. I'll ask for help.
Who do you want to meet?
A ghost hunter?
Yes.
His name is Gherbo.
He's a very clever and lonely hunter.
I'm sure he can find the base of the dark spirit.
Great.
Gherbo, find the base of the dark spirit.
[Gherbo's voice]
Are you ready?
Yes, sir!
Listen.
We have a long way to go.
Remember.
Whatever happens,
you have to stay on your lollipop.
Yes, sir!
Wait.
Get ready.
On the count of three.
One, two, three.
Fly!
Where are they going, sir?
It doesn't matter.
Now is your chance.
You'll take the dark spirit's toxin.
Then you'll be the head of the school.
Yes, sir.
What's this lollipop for?
You'll use this lollipop on the dark spirit.
So he can't go anywhere.
Then the fire guard will come and put him in the fire prison.
Our business will go well, Angkara.
Don't fail, Angkara.
Here.
Aldo Baran.
Your time as the head of the school...
will be over.
(laughing)
Password.
What's the password?
Password?
Wrong.
Hey.
Don't play around.
I order you to open this door.
Or I'll act aggressively.
Let's go.
Wrong again.
You only have three chances.
If you make three mistakes, you'll be blocked.
Who are you?
I've never seen you before.
Oh, I'm a teacher.
I'm from the magic school.
Wrong again.
You'll be blocked.
You did that on purpose, right?
You trapped me.
Now, open this door.
Come on, open this door.
No, you're blocked.
Fine.
If you don't want to open this door, I'll do it myself.
(playing the flute)
You're blocking my way.
(explosion)
(screaming)
(laughing)
What's the matter?
It turns out that Professor Badung is also here.
Yes, he's the principal.
He must be the little professor.
He has red hair.
It's none of your business.
Now, let me go.
Hurry up.
Why are you just standing there?
Let me explain.
I'll take revenge on your teacher.
(screaming)
Kids, go out.
Help!
Eric!
(explosion)
(music)
You saw that, right?
The face of the principal is so cute.
So, he deserves to be fired.
(laughing)
The face is so cute.
Why is everyone quiet?
(whispering)
Professor Borowa.
I have to persuade them...
so that they'll know what's really going on in that room.
I'm sorry, Professor.
We're not enough.
I won't scold you.
I even have something for you.
What is it?
A chocolate and a candy.
Chocolate and a candy?
Look at this.
This can be yours.
But, Professor, why are you so mean?
Usually, you're mean when we're fighting.
I'll give this to you.
But, before that...
I want to ask you all something.
I'll even make you my students.
As long as you tell me...
what's behind that room.
I'm serious, Bro.
Serious?
Serious.
I never break my promise.
How is this?
This can be yours.
(whispering)
Look, Professor.
I want to talk to you.
Yes, come on.
Tell me.
What is it?
This can be yours.
Tell me.
What's behind that room?
This can be yours.
Come here.
Professor Nyaga.
Shut up!
You don't appreciate my kindness.
I've been kind.
But, this can be yours.
It's mine.
Professor.
Don't be scared.
Everyone has a secret.
Yes, Prof.
If the secret is Professor, we'll correct it.
Right, Prof?
Yes, right.
Yes, Prof.
Shut up!
Watch out.
You'll get your punishment.
Wait.
What is it?
This is a toy.
A lollipop.
A lollipop for our friends.
And a chocolate too.
Watch out.
Take it.
Come here.
Eat it, Prof.
I want to eat it.
The rain is heavy.
I can't see the front.
Don't panic.
Calm down.
We must fly.
And don't stop.
Stay alert.
Yes, sir.
Help!
Eric!
Thank you, sir.
Yes.
Calm down, Eric.
You too.
I'll protect you.
After we cross the sea, I'll give you a new lollipop.
Yes, sir.
Eric!
Ergo.
How is it?
Have you found the place?
It's over there.
Okay.
Thank you, Ergo.
Alfa.
It's raining.
Virgo is back.
And he has found the base of the Dark Lord.
Thank God.
When are we leaving?
Now.
Okay.
Wake the others up.
We'll leave together.
That's not their business.
They're still sleepy.
Let's just leave together.
Okay.
Let's go.
Where are they?
I've never seen a couple this close.
I'm embarrassed.
We must be apart
Who are you?
What are you looking for?
What is this?
Let's go.
Where are they?
They must have done this on purpose.
They must have hidden.
This is too much.
Alfa and I.
Professor Aldebaran must know about this.
I'll report this to the professor.
Who are you?
I'm asking you.
Answer me.
Who are you?
I won't ask you again.
Amifis!
Lightning!
Who are you?
You must still remember me.
Aldebaran.
Hey, police officer.
Come here.
Your prey is ready.
Come on. Catch him.
Yes, sir.
Let me go.
Goodbye, Aldebaran.
Finally, Aldebaran.
We're here, Alfa.
So, this is the hot one.
Alfa, wait.
Why?
Why can't I?
You see?
If you had passed him, you would feel the same.
Alfa, we have to be careful.
This place is monitored by the Black Mantra.
We must not act recklessly.
Finally.
Finally, I can sit here.
From today,
no one can stop me in this school.
Ankara?
Oh, Purwa.
What is it, Purwa?
Ankara.
Why are you in Aldebaran's room?
Where is he?
Tell me.
Purwa.
Aldebaran has retired.
And starting today,
I'm replacing him as the head of the magic school here.
Retired?
Impossible.
That's impossible.
You're kidding.
I'm not kidding, Purwa.
If you want the proof,
come here right now.
This is impossible.
He must be lying.
Impossible.
What's that sound?
That's good.
I think it's Purwa.
What's wrong?
I'm tired of the head of the magic school.
What if he's trapped again?
Let's go and see.
Let's go.
What's that?
Sir, thank you.
I'm so happy.
I'm the head of this school.
We can do it.
So, how do we get out of here?
The only way...
to get out of here is a light.
A light that is so bright...
that it can destroy the magic school.
The question is,
where do we get the light from?
Oh, right.
I'll ask for help from Putri Bintang.
Putri Bintang?
Putri Bintang!
Alfa?
Hi, Alfa.
How did it go?
It went well.
Thank you for helping me.
Can I ask for help again?
Sure.
I'm ready to help you.
What do you want?
If I can get the light...
to this building.
Okay.
Because your task is to get the light.
So, get ready.
(Go, go, go)
(Reach all your dreams)
(Never stop)
(Go, go, go)
(Fight with the power of your soul)
(Make yourself)
(Go, go, go)
(Let's dream)
Thank you, Putri Bintang.
Bintang!
Yes, Alfa.
If you need anything, just call me.
I'm ready to help you.
Okay.
Alfa.
You're amazing.
You can be friends with the stars.
Not many people are like that.
Okay.
But before that, let's try again.
(Go, go, go)
(Reach all your dreams)
(Make yourself)
(Go, go, go)
Did you make it?
Yes.
I think the black magic is gone.
Mike, now...
I'll plan to go inside.
Okay.
I'll be back.
(The black magic is gone)
Where are you?
Let's go home, Alfa.
The black magic is gone.
Let's go home.
(The black magic is gone)
I've been given a job.
How's your work there?
Sir.
Thank you, sir.
I'm very happy, sir.
Because starting today...
I'm the one who will be the headmaster in this school, sir.
(The black magic is gone)
Good.
Sir.
I went to far away.
But, the black magic is gone.
There's nothing wasted.
Next time, we can come back.
The important thing now...
You have to be there.
That's Professor Poba.
Why?
He was shouting.
I don't know why.
Professor Poba.
Where are you going?
You're angry with the students.
And now, you decide to leave.
Because of me.
Shut up, you.
Now, there's a very serious situation in the school.
I have to go home.
And all of you have to go home now.
But, professor.
Don't lie to me.
I'm serious.
You know.
I contacted the school.
I want to talk to the new headmaster.
But, guess.
Who am I talking to?
Kara.
Professor Kara.
You go home with your parents.
What's wrong, sis?
The headmaster is in my hands now.
And this means...
I'm the official headmaster.
That's scary.
Luckily, it's not a chicken.
If it's a chicken, I can peel it.
I'm dead.
Where's my money?
I'm so lonely.
[music]
Jumping and racing stars
Bravery, unknown words, giving up
Chase love and dreams
Go go go
Reach all the dreams
Don't ever stop
Go go go
Fight with the power of your heart
Make yourself proud
Go go go
Let's dream
We will