Show your spirit, get your friends ready
Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
We can do it
What are you doing to my sister?
I'm here to save you
You have obtained the power of the five
No one can stop you
Good afternoon, kids
Wow, I can do this with Mureh
Wow, Mureh is so cool
Don't you dare to enter that room
Alpha enters the secret room and meets the third force
What we fear will happen
What's going on?
Kids, calm down
There's a monster that successfully entered
Is it a kid monster?
Yes, ma'am
Shh, don't make noise
You better stay here and don't leave before I order you
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am
Come on
Have you seen Vega?
Vega?
Where's Vega?
Vega, smart boy, where are you?
I was with Vega and he said he wanted to go to the bathroom
He's in the bathroom
Don't, sir
We can't go out of the bathroom together because it's not safe
But he's our friend
What if he's in danger?
You're brave
But it's dangerous
Enough
Sir, wait
It's a monster, sir
Bro!
Get out!
It's huge
I hate monsters
I'm so scared
I'm scared
Sir!
He's coming!
Let's go!
You're mine!
Where are we going?
I don't know
Help!
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Help!
Rika!
Run!
Show it to him!
No!
You're dead!
Let the kid go!
Here!
No!
Argo!
What's that?
It's a...
No!
I am...
Argo!
Anadol!
What's that?
No!
I am...
Argo!
Lolipop!
The teeth can kill, but you can kill it through the teeth!
Argo!
Concentrate and use your Lolipop!
Yes!
Argo!
I am...
No!
Argo!
Alfa!
Thank you, Alfa.
We are not wrong anymore.
Only you can do this.
Why me, Professor?
Alfa, promise me.
You will never tell anyone about what happened just now.
Never tell anyone that you have defeated the monster.
Now, go back to the lab.
Let your friends handle this.
The monster?
How?
Barga is a very strong monster.
He is a monster that can be defeated by a single blow.
He is the hand of the 8th Prince.
The only one who can defeat him is the 8th Prince and a chosen child.
Who is he?
Alfa.
He is the chosen child.
The daughter of Gamma and Aqilla.
He will be our savior.
That is why we must always protect him.
With all our abilities.
So that when the time comes, Alfa can fight the 8th Prince.
Agni, please keep this a secret.
Don't let anyone know that the chosen child is in this school.
If anyone finds out,
the 8th Prince will know what we are planning.
Yes, sir.
We are ready to be sworn.
I swear.
My monster!
Where is my monster?
Calm down, Ray.
There is no monster here.
Oh, right.
I can go to the bedroom.
We were fighting a monster, right?
Yes.
You fainted, right?
Then?
Then where is my monster now?
Who is defeating it?
Oh, right.
Hey, Pegah.
Don't be a coward when you go in.
I am so curious.
I woke up and found it in the bedroom.
You fainted, right?
Then the teachers and Professor Aldebaran came.
Professor Aldebaran defeated the monster, right?
Yes, that's right.
I am the monster.
Professor Aldebaran was defeated.
As long as Professor Aldebaran is here, we are safe.
That's right.
Why am I here?
Thank God.
You both are awake.
Professor Ali.
Where is the monster?
Calm down, Professor Purwa.
The monster has been defeated.
That means the 8th prince is here.
Because only he can defeat it.
Calm down, Professor Purwa.
The 8th prince is not here.
But the chosen one has succeeded in defeating him.
Who is he?
I am sorry.
But I have promised not to tell anyone.
Clearly, the chosen one is among our students here.
The 8th Prince
Alfa?
Alfa, you have to protect the Stone of Eternity in this school.
What is the Stone of Eternity?
The Stone of Eternity is a very strong stone.
The stone cannot fall into the wrong hands.
You have to protect the stone.
But how do I protect it?
Protect it with your heart, Alfa.
How do you know this school?
And you know my name?
Who are you?
One day you will know who we really are.
The Stone of Eternity
Hey!
Who are you?
What is it?
I had a weird dream.
What dream?
This.
What is that?
The Stone of Eternity
What?
I was visited by someone.
And that person is really nice.
I can feel that they love me.
And the weirdest thing is,
they told me to protect the Stone of Eternity in this school.
The Stone of Eternity?
What is that?
I just heard it.
Maybe it's just a dream.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Wait!
The dream is real.
It's real.
The person in the dream must be serious.
Who is the person in your dream?
I don't know. I don't know him.
Let's do this.
Tomorrow we ask the teacher.
Maybe he knows.
The person in your dream must be serious.
Where is he?
There he is.
Oh, yeah.
Let's go.
Tentara.
What is the Stone of Eternity?
The Stone of Eternity
is the Stone that is protected by the Three-Headed Dragon.
So, the Stone of Eternity really exists?
Alfa.
You...
How do you know the Stone of Eternity?
You're just in the first grade.
You don't know that yet.
Come on.
Over there.
I'm busy cooking for the Three-Headed Dragon.
So, the Three-Headed Dragon...
likes Rendang, Gudeg, and Salted Fish.
This.
This is my food.
I love eating Gudeg, Salted Fish, and Rendang.
I'm hungry.
Don't disturb me.
Come on.
Let's go.
This is the mouth.
There's a stone behind the dragon.
And the dragon guards the stone.
What's with the stone?
Why is it guarded?
I don't know.
Don't you dare to eat or do anything...
during my class time.
You all know that...
the students have entered our school.
And for that, there's a new rule that will be applied.
After 8 PM,
all students are forbidden to leave the classroom.
And if anyone steps,
the perpetrator will be punished.
And one classroom will be punished.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Now, I will teach a new mantra...
that you can use to take other things.
Pay attention.
Nafatang Buku.
Sambung.
Now,
focus.
And you all try it.
Now, start.
Nafatang Buku.
(The perpetrator is Nafatang Buku.)
That's so cool.
Nafatang Buku.
(The perpetrator is Nafatang Buku.)
Alfa.
You are to clean this page.
How long do you need?
Three hours, sir.
To live in this world.
It's not as easy as living in the real world.
You have three minutes...
to clean this page.
And you have to finish it.
Do you understand?
Three minutes?
Sir.
I think, sir...
for Alfa's size...
the punishment is too heavy.
This is still in my class.
So I have the right to decide...
anything for the students' education.
I forgot, sir.
If so, please continue.
Thank you.
Alfa.
Do as I say.
If you can't finish it...
your punishment will be heavier.
(Alfa's punishment is heavier.)
Three.
Two minutes and 59 seconds.
Two minutes and 58 seconds.
A box of fruit.
There's a ripe fruit.
I'm hungry.
I'll try it.
It must be delicious.
Get the fruit.
I've learned the mantra, "Mindai Menda".
It's a good idea.
I can use the mantra for this punishment.
Let's try.
Get the small piece of paper.
Get the paper.
I did it!
I've finished it all!
(The punishment is heavier.)
You have to answer my question.
Who is the chosen one?
I can't answer, Prof.
Because my mouth has been sworn by the mantra to tell anyone.
I see.
Now, you have to do what I ask you to do.
Because you know who the chosen one is.
You have to make the chosen one...
...enter the secret room...
...and take the stone to the body.
Yes, Prof.
One more thing.
You have to lead the chosen one to take the stone to the body.
Alfa, we want to help you with the punishment.
Yes.
Do we still need to work?
No, the punishment is over.
Why is it so fast?
Yes, how come?
Alfa, come to my room now.
What's wrong with me?
You're smart.
You know everything.
But I don't know everything.
I'm going to find out.
Alfa, I'm calling you because you have to do something for me.
Tonight.
Before the sun rises, you have to go back to the secret room...
...and take the stone to the body for me.
Isn't that forbidden?
I'm not going to do it.
Alfa, this school is in danger.
And only the stone of eternity can save us all.
But why should I take the stone?
Because you have defeated the monster.
It will come back to life when the sun rises.
But how, ma'am?
There's a third head dragon there.
And that dragon is very strong.
I will tell you about the third head dragon.
300 years ago, there lived three great and brave dragon warriors.
They were very loyal to their country.
They fed their livestock.
Until one day, the dragon's head was cut off.
And the man who was responsible for the dragon's head...
...was killed by the dragon itself.
And the dragon was left alone.
Until one day, they were faced by the dark dragon's army.
The dark dragon's army was defeated by the dragon's head.
But the dragon's head was cut off.
And the dragon was left alone.
Until one day, the dragon's head was cut off.
[music]
And the third dragon was defeated.
Ashifa and Imran were killed.
The three dragons were very sad because they lost their parents.
[music]
The three dragons' tears shed light on the world.
This made the three dragons unite.
Senua became the head of the three great dragons.
[music]
So the three dragons can fight if we give them the same food as their parents.
I saw the army cooking three different foods.
Is that right for the three dragons?
That's right, Alfa.
I've told you everything.
Now it's up to you.
Only you can take the Stone of Eternity and save all our lives.
[music]
It's scary when it's narrow.
Now we have to make three different foods.
The three dragons' favorite foods are rendang, kuduk, and nasinan.
The dragons don't need us.
We will help the eternity.
So now we have to go to the kitchen.
That's right. Let's go.
[music]
Professor!
Who's there?
[music]
Come out!
I said come out or I'll have to use magic.
[music]
One.
Two.
[music]
Three.
I want to talk to you.
Can you come out?
[music]
Come.
Oh my.
Don't wait. Let's just take off the mask.
[sigh]
Let's talk later.
Now let's go to the kitchen to cook.
Yes.
Be careful.
[music]
It's time.
Come out.
[music]
It's like someone is cooking.
Who's inside?
[music]
[sigh]
It's heavy.
[music]
Be careful.
Ray, Vega.
If the third-world soldiers don't like these foods and get more and more fierce,
you have to defend yourselves.
Let me face it.
[music]
Yuda, let's go.
It's scary.
Be careful. It can drown the cloud.
[music]
[scream]
Ray, where are you going?
Ray, his face is blue.
Ray, he's poisoned.
[music]
[scream]
We go.
[music]
Ray.
[scream]
[music]
I'm going to get you.
[scream]
[music]
Ray, Ray, Ray, Ray.
Ray, his face is blue.
Ray, he's poisoned.
Poison gas can kill if there is no supply in two hours.
[music]
Where are we?
We have to take him to the clinic.
No, no, no.
You just continue your task.
You have to take the stone to the shrine before the sun sets.
Let me take care of it, Ray.
But...
It's okay.
[music]
I'm going to get you.
Alpha.
[music]
You have to succeed.
I'm afraid this stone is not ready yet.
[music]
You'd better go to the shrine now.
[scream]
They are not just a bunch of angsa.
But they are the daughter of an angsa.
[music]
Alpha, why did you ask for the stone?
Professor Agni asked for it, Professor.
Because this school is in danger.
Only that stone can save this school.
Alpha must be released.
Three days until the lunar month.
And if in the lunar month, the dark lord gets the stone of peace.
He will get unlimited power.
And will destroy this world.
[music]
Show your spirit, get ready to chase your friends.
Run, jump, climb, climb the stars.
Be brave, don't give up.
Chase your dreams and hopes.
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams.
Go, go, go, never stop.
Go, go, go, fight with your heart.
Go, Go, Go. make yourself proud, Go, Go, Go. let's dream, Go, Go, Go, we will.