Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
There is no name, this is just a lie, this is a trap, the evil spirits only want my sweat, tears and blood
You promised me, you will not forget, your promise is only one, if that promise is broken from you
Alfa
We can't give up Alfa to them
So it's better if there is someone among us to disguise as Alfa
Who is this person?
Myself
Who is it?
Who is handsome?
Hi
Come on, let's gather
What's going on?
Why are we gathered here?
I deliberately gathered you all
I want to tell you, if professor Aldebaran is kidnapped by the evil spirits
Kidnapped?
So we have to save the professor and we have to defeat the evil spirits
But how?
The monster is strong, the professor is more powerful than the monster
Calm down, I know how
Actually, the one being targeted is Alfa, not the professor
So if we want our professor to be safe, we have to surrender Alfa
Let's go find Alfa now
Professor is safe
Where are you?
Alfa
Have you met Alfa?
Not yet, she's not in the library
Where is she?
Have you met Alfa?
No, she's not in the library either
Where is she?
She's not in the library either
Where is Alfa?
Where is she?
We're looking for her
She was with us when we attacked the evil spirits, but now she's gone
Maybe Alfa is hiding
Maybe she's running away
Maybe she's in the library
Alfa is not like that
Where is Alfa?
What should we use?
Let's use the kite
That's right, we should use the kite
I'm going to find Alfa
I won't let the evil spirits take the professor away
Gawat, it's really you
What's wrong?
Alfa was kidnapped by the evil spirits
She's in the hallway
Oh no
What should we do?
We're in trouble
What happened?
Alfa was kidnapped
Let's go tell the professor
Let's go
I got you
You're lying
I'm going to find Alfa
I won't let the evil spirits take the professor away
Alfa
I'm going to find the professor
I won't let the evil spirits take the professor away
Professor Langni
Professor Langni is not here
Where is he?
He's in the hallway
I'm scared
He's not here
Professor Purwocoki is not here either
What about him?
Yasmin is not here either
What should we do?
I'm scared
It's weird, how can they be together?
What are you doing here?
We're looking for Professor Agni
Professor Agni and all teachers are on their way
Where are they?
They're going to the place where the dark spirits help the professor
But we're asking for Alfa
Don't worry, be happy
Megantarate is eager to be Alfa
So they're going there with a fake Alfa
Isn't it amazing?
But it's even worse
And then?
We should ask for help from others
Let's go
Oh my god, they're so childish
Wait for me, don't go
I have to defeat Barga before we get to the place where the dark spirits help
We're going to the dark spirit's house
There must be a clue here
I'm going to look for it
The dark spirit's house has a ring
That's very magical
And it can make monsters stronger
I know how to do it
Guys!
I can't do it
I'm going to find the weak point
I'm going to break it
My legs are aching
I can't stand up
What should I do?
It's up to you
With your blood
I can perfect your power
Professor Aldi Baharan
Where is he?
Where is Professor Aldi?
Shut up!
Don't ask questions
How is it? Are we ready?
Yes
Now, let's go
How is it? Are we ready?
Yes
Now, let's go
Let's go
We have to help Alfa
One, two, three
Let's go!
[The power of the universe]
What is it?
Brother!
Brother, I can't stand it anymore!
I'm going to die!
Brother!
Hold on, sister!
Thank you, Brita
You're welcome
Alfa!
Hi, friends
How did you know I'm here?
I'm here because you're flying!
Yes, you're so used to it
You're making yourself a burden
You!
Yes, sister
We're all worried
Well, then
You have no other choice
I'm the only one
Who can help Professor Aldi Baharan
So, I'm chasing after him
Thank you all
For helping me
I'm so proud of you
But, Barga can't be defeated
Alfa, the ring!
Barga's ring has a weakness
If he wears it, he'll be strong
So, the weakness is in the ring?
We'll make a plan
But, before that
Catch him!
You have to eat first
If you eat, your energy will be full
And your leg won't hurt anymore
Okay
My leg doesn't hurt anymore!
You're right, sister!
Let's make a plan!
Alfa, the ring!
Why is it so dark?
Alfa
I'm going to take your blood
Okay
Take the blood
Take it
Alfa
Why are you a murderer?
I don't know
Maybe he's very curious
Because he's the only one who can help Professor Aldi Baharan
Wear the ring
Take the hair
If you want to take the blood
Hurry up
You can wear the shawl
You're lazy
Anggara
I think there's something wrong with Alfa
Maybe she's stressed
It doesn't matter what you do
It doesn't matter
What matters is your blood
With your blood
I can perfect my power
Take the blood
Take it
Is that all?
Have a good time, Alfa
Okay, Professor
I'm going to take the blood
You got it
You're so weak
I feel sorry for you
Attack!
I'm going to take the blood
Rita, that's his ring
Get closer
Okay
Attack!
Alfa, are you okay?
I'm okay
My hand is so big
It's hard to get the ring
What should I do?
I have an idea
Get the oil
I'm going to use it
I hope it works
Okay, guys
Let's attack him
Let's go
Attack!
Rita, get closer
Okay
Attack!
I'm going to take the blood
Get the ring!
Attack!
How is it, brother?
The blood is ready
Good
With this blood
My knowledge will be perfect
And I won't be defeated
Hahaha
I'm going to take the blood
Anggar!
Why don't you react to me?
I don't know, sir
Is it a misunderstanding?
I bought a meatball
I threw it wrong
Why did you do that, Anggar?
I was fooled
It's time
I'm going to take care of the rest
Let's go, Ma
I want to go to Tara
You can use Tongsis
Or you can use Tongsis
It's up to you
It's easy
I'm going to use Tongsis
It's fast
Let's go together
Ouch! It hurts!
It's so hot
I'm hungry
Let's go to the village
Let's go
Don't eat me
I'm hungry
Let's go
We have to be hungry
Don't you know that?
I know
I'm hungry
But I don't want to eat you
You're so mean
But it's not a normal meatball
It's a meatball that has been castrated
Don't you remember Professor Agni?
Now we're going to learn about castration
Which is a magic bean
Now you have a bean in front of you
You plant it in the ground
But be careful
Don't let it get wet
Okay, ma'am
The bean is castrated
Can I?
Please help me, ma'am
You can't
I told you from the beginning
You can't let the bean get wet
Now you'll see what happens
Please help me, ma'am
Remember
Imagine
You want to eat this bean
And if you eat it
You'll get a sting
And you'll get a sting
It's so fun
I can't do it
I don't want to do it anymore
I'm going to the class
Guys
I have an idea
One, two, three
Sting!
Okay
Let's take the bean
Ouch
Sting!
I'm
Sting
Ouch
Guys
Throw the bean
Up
Guys
Count down
To the sky
Sting!
Ouch
Guys!
Professor fell!
Help professor!
Let's go!
Yeah! We made it!
Yeah!
What the Simpsons
Doesn't Joke!
[Laugh]
Yeah!
I'm so happy!
Thank you, guys!
Now, I'm a champion!
[Laugh]
Of course you are!
Don't!
[Laugh]
Stop!
It's better to go to school!
[Laugh]
I think there's something
Anggar, look at that!
There's Alfa!
It means he's with us!
Anggar...
I mean...
Professor Anggar...
Yes, Professor Anggar...
I'm sorry, I...
I'm just walking around...
I'm actually really hungry...
I've been hurt...
You're really Megantara!
You're really lucky...
It's really nice...
To be fooled by Megantara...
You're so rude!
Emotions will never help...
I'm sorry...
Is this an attack?
Why?
You must be scared...
What's wrong?
Are we fighting?
There's a lot of discussion...
Megantara...
I admit defeat...
It's no use to fight...
What did you say?
Admit defeat?
Please take Aldebaran...
And leave!
He's in the next room...
Are you serious?
Bro!
Before we fight...
Okay...
Excuse me...
Watch your fingers...
Guys, this is Aldebaran's office...
I want to see Aldebaran...
Guys, Aldebaran's office is upside down...
Guys, come here...
Aldebaran's office is upside down...
You guys have succeeded...
You're the monsters...
I don't believe it...
Well, it worked...
It's all thanks to Alfa...
You guys are so awesome...
[Laughter]
Alfa is awesome!
Oh my God...
You guys have brought...
Professor Aldebaran back here...
It's a new grip...
You guys are awesome...
Amazing...
I have to tell the other professors...
Professor Aldebaran is back...
He's saved by...
Alfa, Vega, Ray, Tole and Pelita...
Where's Megantar?
Why is he so late?
How's Professor Aldebaran?
Professor Aldebaran is safe...
He's saved by...
Alfa, Vega, Tole, Ray and Pelita...
Thank God...
We were right to educate them...
They're now...
Our best students...
Very brave and brave...
Yes, very good...
Come on...
Now we go back to the school...
Professor Purwa...
How about Megantara now?
Professor Agni...
Since the beginning, Megantara told me...
The most important thing...
Is the safety of Professor Aldebaran...
He can protect himself...
And now...
After we've come this far...
You want to leave Megantara just like that?
Megantara herself offered herself...
To disguise as Alfa...
She knows what the risk is...
Right...
Megantara's knowledge is already high enough...
And she can handle it herself...
No...
I won't go back...
If you want to go home...
You're welcome...
I'll wait here...
It's up to you, Professor Agni...
You're welcome, Lolip...
If there's anything...
Let me know...
So...
How's Professor Aldebaran?
It's okay...
Professor Aldebaran...
In a few hours...
Will wake up...
Good...
Wait...
Why is it just the two of you?
Professor Agni...
And Megantara...
Where is...?
Megantara is now at the palace...
Of the dark wizard...
And Professor Agni is waiting for him to return...
What?
Megantara...
Is there a place for the dark wizard?
Yes...
He's comfortable...
So, what about you?
You didn't say...
Yes...
Because I forgot...
I was thinking about how to fight the wizard...
Okay...
What are you doing?
Megantara has been captured...
And will be destroyed by the dark wizard...
Be careful...
To come...
And you...
Don't be late again...
Or Megantara will not forgive you...
I won't let the dark wizard hurt Tara...
Alpha...
Where are you going?
What is that?
Mega...
Why are you here?
What's up?
Alpha...
Heard the words of the bird...
He was startled...
And he wants to attack Tara...
Alpha...
You're a stubborn child...
Stubborn...
Please, Alpha...
He will be attacked by the dark wizard...
Alpha...
What are you doing here?
I want to meet the dark wizard...
Come back...
Alpha...
Don't be stubborn...
You have to go home now...
No, professor...
I can't go home...
If Tara is still in the dark wizard's castle...
Alpha, I order you to go home now...
I can't, professor...
I don't want to see anyone...
Be a victim because of me...
Dark wizard...
I'm here...
Come out...
Dark wizard...
What are you doing, Alpha?
Now I order you to go home...
Or you will be punished...
Alpha...
You go home now...
Or I will kick you out of the school...
I don't want to be kicked out...
I want to see Tara safe...
Welcome, Alpha...
Dark wizard...
What have you done?
It turns out this time is really Alpha...
If we are together now, it's for me, Alpha...
No, Alpha...
You can't go...
I want to go, professor...
I can take care of myself...
No, Alpha...
You have to stay here, Alpha...
Let me go, Alpha...
No, Ankara...
It's better if you take me away...
You have no rights...
Let me go, Alpha...
No...
I will not let you go, Alpha...
Come on, Alpha...
Alpha...
Let's go, Tiffy...
Soldier...
Soldier, wake up...
Soldier, let's go...
Come here...
Soldier...
Good, soldier...
Good...
Professor Ankara...
What are you doing, soldier?
Why, Alpha?
You must not have thought...
If Megantara...
Has become my son...
My son...
[Laughter]
Megantara...
Now, you take my son's blood...
[Laughter]
Don't, soldier...
Soldier, don't...
Megantara, hurry up...
Do what you must...
Attack him, Alpha...
Attack him...
Defend him...
Yeah...
[Laughter]
Megantara...
How could I hypnotize you?
Ankara...
The sky won't fall for the second time...
Professor Agni...
You successfully hypnotized...
Doctor Pertiwi...
You hypnotized...
But, I, Megantara...
Can't hypnotize you...
[Laughter]
This disguise is very dangerous for you, Megantara...
You must be very careful...
That's right...
If Megantara finds out...
She will definitely be hypnotized...
And she will definitely become their spy...
Umm...
How about...
We learn...
The anti-hypnotism mantra...
Agree...
Let's go...
What is the anti-hypnotism mantra that I remember...
Your Dhotis...
How is this...
It seems like the anti-hypnotism mantra didn't work...
It seems like...
Finally...
Professor Agni has returned...
Yes...
Finally...
Like that...
Now you, Megantara...
Me?
Hypnotized?
Yes...
Who's afraid?
Try it...
Megantara...
[Laughter]
Finally...
Finally what?
Gravure Chobra...
The servant lifts the stone...
You got money to play...
You all got fooled...
You're all in luck...
[Laughter]
Angkara...
You're a cunning human...
A cunning human like you...
Must be faced with...
A way that is no less cunning...
Okay, Megantara...
Let's attack...
Alfa...
Now is the time...
We destroy him...
Come on...
TV Go!
Get ready, Alfa...
He's awake again...
This is Miran...
Enough...
I haven't lost...
Yes...
[Multiple voices]
[Laughter]
Let's do it this way...
We have to check...
Angkara...
Is he insane...
To die...
Or maybe...
Just pretend...
Umm...
Alfa...
I know...
How to find out...
If he's insane or just pretending...
Look...
Eh...
Wow...
He's dead...
Dead...
Yes...
A great army...
Can fight...
Professor Angkara's hypnotism...
Alfa...
This is all because of you...
Because of me?
Yes...
I...
Can control hypnotism...
That's because I have the confidence and the strong will to save you...
Because of the confidence and the confidence...
That's why...
We succeeded...
Because I don't want...
Someone to harm you...
Because of you...
You're my favorite student, Alfa...
Thank you, soldier...
[Laughter]
Oh, soldier...
Later...
Teach me hypnotism, okay?
You want to be able to hypnotize?
For you...
What do I give you?
Don't give me a mantra about hypnotism...
Mantra about the smell of butt...
Mantra about the smell of pussy...
I'll definitely give you something...
Later, you can...
Ouch...
[Laughter]
It's better...
We get out of here quickly...
Come on...
Later...
What else?
Let's run...
Okay...
My backpack...
You're always carrying your backpack...
I'm not a person...
I'm running while carrying my backpack...
I'm a coward...
But it's okay...
Let's go, Nek...
[Laughter]
I'm going to hypnotize you...
Ready...
Alfa...
You won't get away with this, Alfa...
Help, sir...
Help...
Poor Alfa...
Yes, that's right, Sir...
So, you don't want to come with us?
No...
Professor Abel Barante, forget...
Professor Teng, fainted...
He was attacked by a dark wizard...
I'm very, very hurt...
Alfa...