To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Ria, Danrio, and the police
What are you doing here?
What did you put in here?
I didn't put anything
Don't lie
I saw something
And you put something here
What?
Everything is destroyed because of Alfa
She destroyed our party
Alfa is so stubborn
She doesn't care if she meets a kid
She's so stubborn
Unlike Alfa, she's not a snake
Unless there's a clear reason
You should stop defending her
She can grow up
Maybe the map you gave me is broken
What do you mean?
Yes, because there's a professor named Kara
And he's always hanging out with a new kid
His name is Rio
That means there's a professor named Kara near Rio
What confuses me is that Rio is always alone
The professor is using the dust to protect the school
But why is there still a professor named Kara?
I don't know
Maybe because the professor is in the toilet
Rio! Rio! Rio!
Why are they calling me?
Maybe they're influenced by the brown
I have to find out
[Music]
Hey Rio!
Calm down
All of your kids are now influenced
It's time to do the kudeta
What's kudeta?
Rio! Rio!
Kudeta means
To rebel against this school
[Laughter]
[Music]
It sounded like someone was laughing
It sounded like someone was here
Professor Kara!
It's impossible Alfa, impossible
The map can't be broken
If you see the name of the base on this map
It means the base is there
No, I always tease Rio
But she's always alone
Or maybe the professor is pretending to be Rio
Impossible
It's more likely that she's pretending to be something
For example?
Like an animal
Yes, an animal
Ankara might be pretending to be an animal
An animal?
[Music]
That hamster!
Yes, I know that hamster
It looks like Rio
Or maybe it's just Professor Ankara
[Music]
Rio!
Professor Ankara
How dare you to kill my sister?
Rio, you're dead
Professor!
[Music]
You're going to pay for this
Hurry!
Hurry up Rio!
It's been a long time
[Music]
Professor!
Rio, the true leader
I will fulfill all your requests
Very good, Rio
Very good
Then I have to tell the professor about this
I agree, Ava
You should go home now
But, uncle
What about mom and dad?
We haven't found the intruder who likes to come here
If you manage to catch Ankara
All these stupid attacks will stop
Because I'm sure
This is all Ankara's doing
I'm sure
Good afternoon, children
Happy Eid
Where are the children?
What time is it? They haven't come yet
Do you want to learn or not?
Everyone, follow me!
Where are they?
I've been walking around
Rio and Professor Ankara
Have done something to them
Terrible
[Music]
This is my map
Professor!
It's awful!
What's awful, Alfa?
Where are your other friends?
Why haven't they arrived yet?
That's him, professor
Rio, my friends' magician
Magician?
What do you mean by children's magician?
Professor, Rio is evil, professor
He has bewitched children
And he's in a group with Professor Ankara
And Professor Ankara is a hamster
Alfa, you can't just take his people
Where do we find the proof?
Here, professor
This is the map of the sacred place
All the children are here
Look, they're here
They're going to school
I've heard about this sacred place
Here, professor
Look, there's Professor Ankara's writing here
Right?
Alfa, we have to tell Professor Lalebaran now
Come on
So, Rio and Ankara have bewitched the students?
That's right, professor
But why did Rio and Ankara take everyone to the forest?
Where are they going, professor?
Wherever they go
They're bound to go to the 8th prince
Because I'm sure
All of this is a trap from the 8th prince
So, what do we do, prof?
Titan
Ah, hello, senior magician
I'm the professor
You follow them and find out where they're going
Give them a smile
Get ready to do your job
I'll be going, prof
And Agni, you have to make a love potion
A love potion?
Because Rio has bewitched all the children with a love potion
If not, all the children won't obey him
Yes, professor
And Alfa, you help my professor
To make a lot of love potions
Yes, prof
And the rest stay here
Because I'll arrange your plans
Yes, prof
Yes, professor
Rio! Rio! Rio!
Ahai, give them a smile
There they are
From here
Rio! Rio! Rio!
It seems someone is following us
No
No, professor
Where are they?
Let's just continue
Wait
I have a good idea
That can make the eyes come out of their hiding
Guys, lift your tongs
And blow up the tree you like
Now!
Go! Go! Go!
Let's continue
Rio! Rio! Rio!
Mr. Ketua, we're coming
Welcome to our castle
Sir, our plan is going well
All the magic school students are influenced by love potions
So, they all follow all the words from Rio
Good, good
You're smart
Sir, why only Rio?
I'm also a student
So, I'm smart too, sir
What do you want now?
You're jealous of a kid?
Good, good
You're smart
Where's Alfa?
Why isn't Alfa here?
Alfa skipped school, sir
It seems Alfa is heartbroken
Because all her friends are following Rio
Sir, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, sir
Sir!
Now, continue with the plan
Yes, sir
Are you still following my words?
You want to help me, right?
Yes, sir
We'll destroy the magic school
Especially, Agni and Alirbaran
Are you ready?
Yes, sir
Good
How's it going, Agni?
Is Ramona ready?
Yes, sir
Good
Then, we all have to get ready
Because I'm sure
The Dark Palace will attack our school
Are you sure, sir?
We want to attack our own children
I'm sure
The Dark Palace will attack our own children
As long as you all remember
No matter what, they're still our children
So, you have to use another way
Different from how you defeat the adults
Now, listen to me
We'll destroy this school
And crush all the teachers
If you have any problem
Use the magic on your left hand
Understand?
Yes, sir
Good
Then, attack!
In a moment
Alirbaran will be defeated by my soldiers
And the magic school
Will be mine
That's right, sir
And in a moment
I'll be the head of the magic school again
You're always following me
Shut up!
The teacher is coming
Why did the teacher go to the pool first?
That means
We can defeat the teacher
Yes!
That's right
Done
We're in the teacher's hands
That's not my favorite food!
It's mine!
Why are we here?
And why are we in the school?
To sleep?
The teacher is coming
Wake up, sir!
Be quiet!
The teacher is coming
Let's make the school more fun
Yes!
The teacher is just joking
What does the teacher mean by joking?
I don't understand
You have been bewitched by Rio
We were bewitched by Rio!
Rio?
Yes
Do you know?
No
You were told to attack me
And to destroy the school
But luckily, Professor Agni has made a plan to catch you
And you were caught
By the candy you ate
So, Professor Perwang is dead because of us, right?
Of course not
But you will still be punished
Punished?
What did we do wrong, Professor?
Professor's red lips
Be careful
Forgive me!
Don't hurt me!
Please, forgive me!
Who is it?
The one who entered the coconut palace
Please, let me in!
I will give you the candy
Please, don't kill me!
I will kill you!
Don't hurt me!
What are you doing here?
I don't know
Please, let me in!
It's amazing!
Thank God, you all realized
You were hypnotized by Rio
And you were made into the darkness's army
What darkness?
That's right!
Thank you, Rio
Thank you
It's so delicious
It's delicious
Now I'm ready
I don't have to do anything
Thank you
Where did Semin go?
Attack the Philippines!
(laughing)
Why is the professor sitting on the floor?
He's a professor
Good, you all realized
As long as you know, Vela and Feli
You were both hypnotized by Rio
Rio, the great one?
Yes, you don't know who Rio is, right?
Rio is the underling of the darkness's army
You were both hypnotized
Which means
You were made into the darkness's army
Do you understand?
We were made into the darkness's army
Yes, we were
But our hearts
Oh my God
You two are so stupid
You should have known
He's the one who raped my grandfather
I have to avenge him
Punish him!
It hurts!
Rio, why did you have to torture me?
What did I do wrong?
The professor's fault is
You're a liar!
I didn't hear anything wrong
You're the one who made me into the darkness's army
You're so stupid
Let's go!
I want to hear
Why did you do all of this?
Because I want to avenge him
Because professor Agni ordered to kill my grandfather
Rio, who are you talking about?
Professor Alibaran
You're the one who hurt my grandfather
I will avenge him!
Don't be so arrogant
Professor Alibaran is a good man
He won't kill your grandfather
Shut up!
You don't know anything
Enough!
Don't fight
I and professor Agni
Won't kill your grandfather
Rio, we don't even know each other
Impossible!
You must know who my grandfather is
Rio Nero
Rio Nero?
No, that's not my real name
But
Leon?
Yes, my name is Leon
And my grandfather's name is Orion
Professor
Orion?
Isn't he the old man in the fire prison?
Yes, that's right
Good!
You still remember how sadistic he was to kill my grandfather
Leon, I think you're mistaken
What do you mean?
It's obvious that you're the one who burned my grandfather
And you killed my grandfather
That's not true, Leon
That's not true, that's a lie!
Leon, you're wrong
Your grandfather is still alive
He even told me to find you
And save you from the fire prison
If you come with me
Please save my grandfather
Please
I have high hopes for you
That's what I want right now
Let's go
That's impossible!
Come on, Leon
Come with us
Leave the Dark Lord
Yes, Leon
Come with us
Don't follow the Dark Lord, he's evil
Yes, Leon
I believe that the Dark Lord is evil
What do you want?
You don't know anything!
You're lying!
Your story is different from the Dark Lord's story
It's the opposite, Leon
The Dark Lord is the one who lied to you
Not us!
Yes, Leon
No, I don't believe you
You killed my grandfather!
Professor!
Professor Agni!
Leon!
Where are you going?
Leon, don't let him get away
Leon!
Agni!
Hi, Professor
We can do it!
You stay here
I'll meet Professor Agni
But we're going to join the army, right?
We're going to join the army, right?
We miss the army
How dare you to fight me?
Huh?
You don't want to listen to me?
You don't want to obey me?
You're a coward
You're a coward, you're a slave hunter
What are you doing?
Why are we doing this?
We're a soldier
Let me go, soldier
Don't you dare to fight me
You're a bad soldier
You protect them, don't let them go
If one of them is released
Then you're a bad person
I'll make you two
I'll change you
We're going to fight them
Help!
Yes!
Hold the rope
Why are you helping me?
Of course, sir
We're your friends
Why are you guys dropping me?
You should drop Alfa
Alfa is our enemy
We're Alfa's friends
So we won't hurt Alfa
You're our enemy
You guys are
The 8th Pangeran's followers
Kailan is my team
We're aware
We won't be hypnotized anymore
We won't be affected by your emotions
And we won't be with you
You're stupid
You're not allowed to be with the 8th Pangeran
That's noisy
[The 8th Pangeran]
Leon!
You're so slow!
[The 8th Pangeran]
Agni betrayed me
He made me work to free your grandfather
But he poisoned your grandfather
And he even killed his friend
His name is Adeb Lara
Leon, you're wrong
Your grandfather is still alive
He's still alive
He even told me
To find you
And save you from the 8th Pangeran
Come on, Leon
Come
Come with us
Leave the 8th Pangeran
I really don't know who's right
Grandfather
I need you
[The 8th Pangeran]
What happened to him?
He's under the influence of the magic
It's been a while
He's still unconscious
What the...
Professor Agni is poisoned
He's being poisoned
Come on, Professor Yasmin
Please stay here
I want to go back to my room
Yes, Professor
[The 8th Pangeran]
Why hasn't Leon lit the fire?
He should have been in charge of the school
He's the one who lit the fire
What if I find out the truth?
Okay, sir
You find out the truth
Yes, sir
Oh
What else, sir?
You're a hamster now
Oh, right
I forgot, sir
I'm happy
You're back to normal
Yes, sir
We're happy too
But please forgive me about yesterday
Please forgive us, sir
I've already forgiven you
It's not your fault
It's Leon's fault
You're under the influence of Leon's magic
Yes, he's so evil
He's not evil
He's just under the influence of the 8th Pangeran
Soldiers!
Enough!
Let go of him
Or else,
I'll make your body smell bad
Are you okay, soldier?
You're the one who's sick
You're so mean to us, soldier
You're so bad
I just came here to play with you
I'm not a bully
I'm a bully, okay?
Soldier, what do you want?
Don't touch me
Soldier,
You're so mean
Why are you acting like a girl?
Soldier,
You're so mean to a girl
You're such a big kid
You're talking nonsense
You said I'm a bully
As you know,
This is the briefcase I'm using
Not yours
Then, what's that?
It's none of your business
What are you doing?
You're so nosy
You're so mean
Now,
I want to ask you
Where's professor Alibaran?
I want to meet him
He's taking care of professor Agni
Who's fainted
What?
Professor Agni
Fainted?
I'm surprised by this school
A teacher who easily fainted
And became weak
Is still being used as a teacher
Enough
I want to go
I don't want to talk to you
I want to find professor Alibaran
Why are you so mean?
Okay, calm down
Don't think about it
I'll go to the toilet
I'm scared
I can't just stay still
I have to prove who's right
I have to catch the fire
But
I don't know where the fire station is
I'm so scared
Me too
I'm so hungry
One way to be safe
We have to go to school
There must be a lot of people there
Where are we going?
We're going to take a ticket
What?
I know
We have to jump together
That's a good idea
Let's try
1, 2, 3
That's my idea
Let's do it again
1, 2, 3
I'm so scared
Stand up
Come on
One more time
Ready?
There's a fire!
I'm so scared
Sit down
My feet are on the toilet
I'm so scared
Where's Leon?
It's so quiet here
I can smell him
He's in the toilet
[The school is so noisy]
This school is so noisy
Is there a rat in this school?
What kind of school is this?
The rat trap
Why is there a trap here?
[The rat is following me]
Why am I being followed?
I'm so lucky
[I'm safe]
Leon, how was it?
Did you beat all the teachers in this school?
I did!
Leon, you're a great kid
You're so cool
I want to give you a present
What is it?
This is for you
You're so mean
This is for celebrating our success
Okay
[Leon is so cute]
What are you doing?
Hi, Mr. Teacher
How dare you to play with me?
Take this!
God, I finally understand you
Yes, Pratis!
Sorry, Mr. Teacher
I can't believe it!
I'm going to be a fireman!
[I'm going to be a fireman!]
I don't have enough energy
I think this is because I got hurt
But I'm going to try again
Wind, come to me!
No, no!
What's going on?
I'm going to die!
Finally, we're safe!
I'm going to be a fireman!
Let's go now
One, two...
I'm tired
I'm going to be old
Let's get ready!
Why can't I do this?
If I keep doing this,
when will it be my turn?
Who's going to help me?
You're the fireman, right?
The one who saved me that time?
You're going to get married!
No, don't!
You want me to ride on your body?
If that's the case,
can I ask for your help?
Please take me to the fire station
near my grandpa's house
Okay!
Let's go!
[The fireman is on his way]
Doctor!
Let's fly faster!
You're great!
[The fireman is on his way]
I'm tired
Let's dance!
[The fireman is on his way]
Now, it's my turn!
What's that?
I told him to dance
So, his love story is a success!
Of course!
You're so funny!
That's enough!
Now, let's continue our discussion!
Okay!
Professor Ankara!
Let's dance again!
Let's go!
I have to give this to my uncle
Here's your paper and pen!
Uncle,
Professor Ankara's problem is solved
There won't be any more infiltrators in my house
And please, tell your mom and dad
that I miss them
Alfa!
Get my uncle's hand!
Hi, uncle!
Please, do this!
[Alfa's love story]
So, Alfa gave her love story to Professor Ankara?
Yes!
So, Professor Ankara is in love with Alfa?
And you did all of this to prevent the chaos?
That's right, Prof!
Wow, so, you agree with us?
We're good, right?
You're working with us?
To be honest,
I think this is a dangerous plan
and full of risks
But, there's nothing wrong with it
Let's do it!
Yes!
Let's continue our discussion!
Okay!
[The Pupils' School]
Now, I've liberated the school from the dust
And now, the dust is back to its place
So, what's your plan?
What else can I do, Sir?
Professor Ankara, please call Mr. Rd. Jelapan
Yes, Sir
But, you first
I'll call him first
Okay
Good evening, Sir
How's it going?
Any good news?
Our mission is successful, Sir
And now, I'm asking you to come to the school in the afternoon
Right now, Sir
Good, Sir!
I'll be there soon, Sir
Okay, Sir
But, we'll meet in the school's hall
Now, the hall is no longer protected by the dust, Sir
You're great, Sir!
Now, it's time to release Mr. Rd. Jelapan
Stop it!
Megantara has come back to the school!
How's it going? Have you got the soul stone?
What are you doing?
I'm curious
You don't need to know
Now, I want to ask you
Where's Professor Aldebaran?
I don't know where Professor Aldebaran is
How can you not know where Aldebaran is?
You meet him every day
Where is he? Tell me
I don't know!
You're so arrogant!
Just answer me!
Beautiful, amazing!
Why are you so rude?
You're getting more and more arrogant every day
I asked you nicely, where's Aldebaran?
You answered me like that
Where's Aldebaran?
Don't talk nonsense!
I'm Megantara, the fearless warrior!
He's so cute
He's like a little baby
It's better to sleep there
Than to be with a boy like him
Welcome, Dark Prince
Anggara, Leon, and all of you
I'm so happy
Our plan is a success
Who's first?
Leon, and Professor Anggara
And we are Rion's team!
Good, good
Why is Alfa here?
Sir, all the teachers at Sir's school have given up on me
Even Alfa is now your follower
Finally, Aldebaran is bowing to you
And soon, Alfa will be mine too
You're the one who will bow to the Dark Prince
Sir, to celebrate our success
Please drink this
What is this?
That's a herbal tea, Sir
For our body to be healthy and strong
We have to drink herbal tea
I'm sorry, Sir
Herbal tea
Okay, then drink it
Why, Sir?
I'm not ashamed
After drinking this herbal tea
I fell asleep
Who knows
There's something weird about this herbal tea
Okay, Sir
How is it, Anggara?
The herbal tea is good, Sir
If it's good, why did you drink it all?
You should have left some for me
I'm sorry, Sir
Because it's already good, Sir
What is this?
Why is it so bitter?
Get out of here, Prince!
Drink this water, so it won't be bitter anymore
I'm thirsty
Don't look for it!
It's bitter
With this, you won't be able to drink it anymore
We did it!
Yes!
Alphon!
Girls, we did it!
Yes!
Agni, wait
You attacked me?
Just attack me!
I'm not afraid
Attack!
Attack, Alphon!
We can do it
Virgo?
Where are you from, Virgo?
What is this?
Ankara has been successfully captured by Alphon
Good
That's good
I'm a soldier now
Good
That's good
I'm a soldier now
Because I'm sure that after this, no one will come to my house
Thank you, Virgo
What now?
I'll tie it with a rope
Sir, don't
Not yet
Because if you tie it with a normal rope
The monster will be able to escape
It's very strong
Then what do we use?
I have a mantra that can make the rope stronger
And I'm sure that the monster won't be able to escape
That's easy
Ravantai Kufu Cin
What should we do?
You're wrong to say the mantra
Okay, I'll say the mantra
Viva
Ravantai Kufu Cin
If we use this rope, the monster won't be able to escape
But if we tie it, it will be very easy to free it
Viva Kufu Cin
Amazing
Professor Agnita finally realized
Yes, Professor Agnita
Where is she?
Professor Agnita is at the clinic
Perthiwi Beauty Food, amazing
Professor Agnita fainted after fighting Leon
Then?
Where is the other one?
Professor Agnita and Alpha Prime are fighting the villain
The villain is the Darkness Lord
The Dark Lord?
Yes, the Darkness Lord
I have to help him now
Help the Darkness Lord?
Perthiwi is hearing it wrong
Or Professor Agnita is freaking out?
This is dangerous
There must be something
The Dark Lord is coming
I think the voice is coming from this direction
But why is there still a follower?
Isn't Ankara defeated by Alpha?
Professor Lebar
I have an idea
Professor Yasmin and I have an agreement
What if the Dark Lord is imprisoned in the backwoods of the school?
Prison?
Don't worry about the Dark Lord
I can handle it
There is also a truth
Why Ankara?
Then?
Is there a better idea?
Wait
I'll think about it
Professor Agni?
He has recovered?
What is this?
Why are you all defending the respected Dark Lord?
The Dark Lord?
So that's the Dark Lord
There's another Dark Lord
But I won't give up
I have to defeat them
Let's go
Let's fight together
[The Dark Lord is coming]
Who dares to do this?
Stop!
The Dark Lord is evil
He's supposed to be in prison
So he can't make snakes anymore
No, I disagree
You all have to free the Dark Lord
Not in a chain like that
Professor Agni, why is the Professor missing?
Yes
Professor Agni has been acting weird
What did you say?
I'm not weird
I'm not
You all
It's true
You shouldn't have done that to the Dark Lord
What about the other one?
Free the Dark Lord in a chain
Agni!
Professor Agni!
Professor, where are you taking him?
Professor, you're acting weird
Yes, Professor, don't do that
Yes, Professor
Free the weapon
Professor Agni
Defeat the lollipop
The blue one
Professor, the blue one
Professor Agni
Agni, wait
You want to attack me?
Go ahead
I'm not afraid
Attack!
Professor, wait!
Professor Agni!
Guys, let's go after him
Let's go
Professor, wait!
Let me go!
Guys
Let's go after him
Let's go
I managed to get away from them
Agni is defeated
They will lose
I'm really hungry
Now I got a professor from Syri's school
We can do it
Why is Professor Agni acting weird?
Since he realized Ramon is from Leon
Agni must be possessed by Ramon Hijau
Ramon Hijau
What Ramon, Professor?
It's a super quality Ramon
Super quality Ramon?
What does it mean, Professor?
I've heard about Ramon
It's not really different from the Ramon you made
But it's a far more powerful version
So Ramon made Professor Agni become a god
And praise the dark side?
Yes
That's right, Professor
I'm going to talk to him
I want to know what you want
He ran away so fast
He even followed us with his eyes
Who is he?
I'm going to talk to him
He's gone
Where did he go?
There he is
Why am I here?
Who brought you here?
I brought you here
Why are you in my bed?
It's been a long time, Sir
We haven't met
You
Where are your friends?
What do you want?
You
You want to challenge me?
Right?
Let's go
I'm ready to fight you
Don't be mad at me
Okay?
Don't joke around
I'm serious
Who's joking?
Agni
Look at your left hand
There's a mark
It means
Agni has been hit by a green light
It seems
You've been hit by my super love potion
Whatever you say, Sir
What's clear is
I'm ready to fight you
I'm so proud
Now I have a professor from Siri School
Professor?
Yes
How do we make Professor Agni realize?
That's right, that's right
Of course with his offer
I'll make it happen
I've promised him
No
This offer must be given a special gift
Special?
What's that?
The offer must be added with the dark magic
It's scary
I don't want to be a baby
What should we do?
The dark magic has gone
Just leave it to me, Sir
I'll get it
So you'll find the dark magic
And give it to me?
Yes, Sir
Just wait for me
Guys, help our friend
Bro, help our friend
Agni, how can you do that?
It's all because of the soldiers
The soldiers did this to us
Sir, don't write it like that
You got it wrong
I'll finish you
So you can't go back to school
And tell Alfa and Alipa
Ready
Show your spirit, get ready
Find your friends
Run, jump, jump
Reach the stars
Be brave
Don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with your heart
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Let's dream
We'll make it