To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
The monster likes chocolate
How can a cruel monster like chocolate?
You have to destroy all the chocolates in the village
If necessary, destroy all the chocolate trees there
The monster is coming
The monster is great
The monster is not dead, it just escaped
So the monster can come back?
It can come back if it smells chocolate
The chocolate is in my hand
And you tell Alva
If Alva still wants this child to live
Then she has to give up
The flute played by the dark craftsman
Makes the monster calm, becomes a beast
You teach the flute, okay?
Okay, I'll teach
Seriously?
Even though you don't like it, even though you force it
Eat it, Momo
Professor, Professor
What's wrong, Vega?
Alva went back to the village
What's wrong with Alva?
Because the news said Professor Ankara kidnapped her
And Professor Ankara said Alva has to go there
No one will accompany her, she has to be alone
If not, the news will be spoiled
I'm in a hurry, I'll go after Alva
I won't let Ankara take Alva
I'll go too, Prof
I have to go save Alva
If Ankara gets there
If Alva gets a single hair on her head
I'll tear her body apart
I'll go with you, Prof
You can go with me
Yes
But there's a condition
What condition?
Miphi is Vega's daughter
Why is Professor Ankara a demon?
That means we're going to be like this
What? We're going to be small?
Yes, we're going to be small
With you being small like this
It'll be easier for me to hold your hands
I'm sorry, Prof
I'm Megantara Ankara
Wow, Professor's clothes smell so good
[Megantara Ankara]
Eat this, Vega
Wow, a demon's toy
That toy won't run out in a week
Thank you, Professor
I'm stuck
I'm stuck, Prof
Professor!
I'm stuck, Prof!
Chicken satay and fermented fish
Relax, man
It's still a long way
It's still a long way?
I can't breathe here
I'm going to die
Tara!
I'm coming!
Tara, when is the last time you took a shower?
For me, cleanliness is number one
The last time I took a shower was three weeks ago
Huh? Three weeks ago?
Tara! I'm so hungry!
Excuse me
Professor, I'm so glad you came
Please help me, Professor
Plita was kidnapped! Please, Professor!
Yes, I know
That's why we came here together
Thank you, Professor
I'm sure you can find Plita
Come on, Professor
I'll show you my way
Ouch!
Not like that, Alva!
You taught me!
Sorry, I'm learning too
I'll try again
[Siren]
Enough!
You're always wrong!
You should just continue!
You're going to fail!
Not like that, Pooh!
I'll try again!
[Siren]
Where is she?
Yes, you're right!
Because of you, I'm sure she's dancing with the music
Hooray! I did it!
Yes! Hooray! I did it!
Hooray! Yes! Yes!
Thank you! Thank you for teaching me!
Thank you!
[Music]
Huh?
Pooh is hugged?
Usually, all gods treat Pooh with love
Pooh, why are you crying?
Huh?
No, no!
Please, just a little bit!
Now, you can do it!
Let's go to the cave!
Okay, let's go!
Let's go there!
Galaxy, are you still there?
We're still going straight there, Sir
Felita!
Oh my God, I'm leading Felita!
Poor thing, she's still alone there!
[Music]
Felita, it's me! Can you hear me?
Why did you hide me, Sir?
I'm so scared, it's so dark here, Sir!
Stay there, I'll hide you, Pooh!
What's going on?
Why did you suddenly hide me, Sir?
Sir!
Shut up!
Now, you can't talk to a kid anymore!
[Music]
I've never been through that road with my dad!
It's full of rocks and dark, Sir!
Please, help me, Sir!
I'm going to use that mirror without my permission!
[Music]
Felita!
Professor!
Professor Edelberen!
I think this is not the right way!
[Music]
Galaxy, who's actually leading Felita?
Alcara, Sir!
[Music]
How do you know?
Wasn't that the news in the room?
And why did you bring us on this journey?
Shouldn't you be taking us on a rocky road?
Do you actually know the right way?
I don't know, Sir.
Unfortunately, you're too late to know that.
[Music]
This is the sand of the sandstorm!
You're right, Sir!
The sandstorm is a sign of magic.
All the magic is here!
I'm sorry, Professor.
I can't take you to the magic.
Only Alfa can go there.
Galaxy!
[Music]
Where is it?
Popo, it's still far away.
It's over there.
Okay, let's go there.
[Music]
Be careful!
[Scream]
[Music]
It's over there.
Popo, thank you for saving me.
[Music]
Let's go.
Professor, it's over there!
I'm so angry!
Ray, Vega, help me!
Help me, don't just stand there!
You find a rope or something that can help them.
Hurry up!
We have to go, Sir!
Come on, Ray!
[Music]
We're almost there.
Come on, keep going!
Keep going!
[Music]
Megatara.
Hold on, Megatara.
[Music]
[Scream]
Thank God, we're safe.
Vega, Ray, thank you.
You two have saved us.
You're welcome, Sir.
Right, Sir?
It's not a loss if you bring me and Vega.
[Music]
Why, Galaxy?
Why did you do that?
It's none of your business, Professor.
[Music]
Why, Galaxy?
Why?
I'm sorry, Professor.
I was threatened by these backwards.
If every news they send is just a lie,
I don't want to lose the news, Professor.
I'm sorry, Professor.
[Music]
Galaxy.
But you know...
where the real treasure is, right?
I know, Professor.
Come on.
I'll show you the way.
[Music]
So, how do we get in?
I know how to open the door.
And then?
[Chanting]
[Music]
Come on, Popo.
I'm scared.
If I'm still there,
I'll be killed by Professor Ankara.
Because I've betrayed him.
If you're scared, you don't have to go in.
Let me go in alone.
I can't.
Even though I don't want to.
Even though I'm suffering.
I have to go in.
Alright, I'll go in.
But you have to be careful.
Alright.
I'm not a ghost!
[Screams]
[Music]
Popo!
Prita!
Where are you, Prita?
Where are you?
Prita!
[Music]
Where are you, Prita?
Alvas!
I'm sorry, I'm late.
I have to go in.
[Music]
Welcome, Alva.
And thank you for keeping your promise to come here alone.
Very good.
Antaboga.
Come on!
[Music]
I'm scared, Kak.
No one can help you now, Alva.
Fight Antaboga.
[Music]
Prita, hurry up and hide in the bushes.
Hurry up!
[Music]
[Laughter]
Prita, hurry up!
[Music]
What is that?
Dad, wake up!
Wake up, Alva!
[Music]
Dad, wake up!
I'm scared, Alva!
[Music]
Come on, Prita!
Finally, we're the same, Kak.
Yes.
Thank you, Popo, for helping us.
Kak Alva, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Well, I'll go.
Hey, I'm in Ankara!
[Laughter]
You can't just leave like that.
Because our business is not over yet.
And you are a traitor.
Your turn, after him.
[Music]
Open fire!
[Laughter]
And now, feel this.
[Music]
Don't!
Wake up, Sih!
Dad!
Wake up, Dad!
Professor Gaha!
[Music]
Dad, wake up!
Alva, wake up!
Alva!
Dad!
What's wrong?
Wake up!
Alva!
It seems Alva was hit by a shell.
[Music]
Head down!
Prof, we're not done yet, Megantar.
We still have to close the cave door with a spell.
So that the Antaboga won't appear again forever.
That's right, Prof.
Kurufung!
[Music]
Let me try, Prof.
Kurufung!
[Music]
Prof, Prof, Prof.
What if we try together?
Let's do it.
Kurufung!
[Music]
Dad, wake up!
Why is the door so strong?
You try, Alva.
Sorry, Prof.
But it seems Alva's condition is not possible for her.
Alva, why don't you try?
[Music]
Come on, concentrate.
You can do it.
[Music]
Kurufung!
Alva is so cool!
You're amazing, Alva.
Maybe my guess is right.
If Alva is...
Alva!
Alva, wake up!
Wake up!
Alva!
[Music]
Dad!
Dad, wake up!
[Music]
Vega, Rey, Adara.
Welcome, Alva.
Vega, where's Pelita?
She's fine.
But, Mr. Galaxy...
What's wrong with Mr. Galaxy?
Mr. Galaxy saved you and Pelita.
He was attacked by the Karak.
So, he's being healed by the Eid Mubarak.
[Music]
Dad!
Dad, wake up!
[Music]
Be patient, Pelita.
You have to be sincere.
Your dad is calm there.
I only had my dad when I was a kid.
Now, he's gone.
I'm all alone.
[Music]
Pelita, you're not alone.
We're here for you.
I want to go to school with you.
Do you want to?
Yes.
Come to my room later.
You want to, right?
I miss you so much.
Thank you.
[Music]
Now, we can go back to school.
Pelita, we'll be together.
So, don't be lonely.
[Music]
Wait!
I want to go with you.
You can't.
We're going to school.
If I don't go with you,
I'll die.
[Music]
Alva,
the only way...
to make me not go with you...
is by not being your teacher anymore.
But, what should I do?
The way is by giving your hair to the teacher.
Then, he'll be free.
[Music]
Cut!
Is this for me?
Yes.
Are you serious?
Now, you're free.
You're not a servant.
I'm free?
Yay!
I'm free!
[Screaming]
Thank you, Alva.
You're the best teacher.
You're welcome, Poco.
You're also a savior.
I'll go now.
Okay.
[Music]
[Alarm]
Good evening, children.
Good evening, sir.
Now,
I'll introduce a new student.
Her name is Pelita.
Pelita?
Hi, Pelita.
My name is Tolik.
Hmm.
Pelita, please sit with me.
Come here, children.
Please sit with me, Pelita.
[Music]
What do you want to eat?
Children,
please continue your meal.
Okay, sir.
[Music]
What?
Wow.
I'm so hungry.
I haven't eaten for a week.
[Music]
I'm confused.
Why do I keep doing this?
I don't feel hungry.
[Music]
Alva.
What's wrong?
I don't know. It's weird.
I don't know.
I'll scare her.
I want to eat this rat.
Hihih.
It's delicious.
I know it's delicious.
Do you want to try?
[Music]
Alva.
What's wrong?
[Music]
Alva.
What's wrong?
Help.
Alva.
[Music]
How do you feel now?
I'm sick.
I'm dizzy.
Alva T got poisoned by a snake.
The snake's poison must be neutralized by the antidote.
If not, in three days...
Alva T will become a snake.
Oh, it's big.
It's terrifying.
Where's the antidote?
The antidote...
is in a place that's far away.
Long, long, long, long from here.
It's in a mystery island.
A mystery island that's far away from here.
The antidote is very rare.
It's called the liquid of life.
The antidote is very powerful.
It can cure...
all diseases.
Oh, diseases.
And Conan said...
the antidote can revive the dead.
So, very amazing.
Very amazing.
Professor.
I will go there to find it.
You can't, Megantara.
Only small children can go there.
Okay, I'll go there.
Me too.
Why do we let small children go there?
That's right, Professor.
I'm worried too.
This is a difficult decision for me.
I don't think I can let the children go...
without our brother.
But we can't let Alva become a snake.
Professor.
We've often passed dangerous obstacles.
Because we're always compact.
So, we can pass this obstacle.
Yes, Professor.
I hope we can pass this obstacle.
Yes.
Okay.
I agree.
Thank you, Professor.
(Megantara, the best teacher)
Dad, I'm not a bad person, right?
Yes, but don't be so sure.
We're your friends, right?
Yes, we're friends.
Even if it's difficult or we're happy, we're together.
That's right, Ren.
Best.
Ren.
Wow.
I'm Flipir, I'm a kid.
I was bullied in the market.
You don't know me.
I'm Megantara.
Tentara.
Why?
I was cute when I was a kid.
But now I'm handsome, right?
Tentara, you should join us.
Yes.
Let's go inside.
(Megantara, the best teacher)
I can do it, right?
Yes.
Tentara!
It turns out that I'm not that smart.
This island is smarter.
Tentara!
Don't!
Don't use magic here.
It's dangerous.
But, Tentara...
If you use magic,
the magic will turn against you.
(The magic will turn against you)
Alva, Vega, Ray
I told you, this will be useful
Let's get this over with
(The magic will turn against you)
Welcome to the Mystery Cave
You will pass the first gate
Which is
The Gate of Dreams
A place where you can eat all kinds of food
But remember
Once you eat that food
You will not be able to continue your journey to the next place
(The Gate of Dreams)
If you give up
Like a white flag
Automatically
You will be at the first gate
That's great
Ray, don't be a coward
The important thing is we have to pass all the challenges
The first one who can put the blue flag on the Gate of Dreams
Is the winner
And if there is a disqualified participant
He will be disqualified
I have to get the Gate of Dreams
So I can live again
Remember
The liquid of life is very rare
Only one person can get the liquid of life
Do you understand?
Before we start
You can get ready
The toilet is over there
And the costume room is next to it
No one can beat Raya
She is beautiful
She will also do the scary thing
Why is someone missing?
We can do it
I have to scare them
So they run away
What is this?
I'm scared, I want to go home
Me too
Who are you?
Where are you from?
We are from the inside
We give up
Why?
There are a lot of ghosts
The fish that got the stone
This is a mystery island
There are a lot of ghosts
What about Vega, Alba and Reng?
What if they get the water of life?
Dad, I miss you
Now I don't have anyone
Why did the power reappear?
Mom
Don't leave me
Owha..you guys must have been tired...
I'm sure you don't know what happened to me...
I just feel like I'm being dissipated...
Huh?
Why do you seem so whiny?
What's wrong?
I feel like I'm getting older...
I don't want to die anymore...
I only want to continue living...
But I almost died...
You've been living for a long time?
[music]
Pelita,
sadness that is too deep and long
will make your strength appear
and if you're angry,
it will endanger you
and others
so you have to be careful
you have to be able to control your emotions
if you're sad,
don't be too sad
and you have to be calm, okay?
[music]
I can't be sad
I'm afraid of being strong
I don't want my strength to appear again
[music]
Why is the light not turned off?
Where is the ghost?
[music]
He will also make me scared
There's something missing
[music]
I'm scared again
Just give me the real one
Give it to the jury
[music]
Just like that
If I throw a white flag,
it means I failed
I can't be scared
[music]
Why is he throwing a white flag?
I'm scared again
[music]
I'm not scared
I'm not afraid of you
Come out here
Come out, Raya
[music]
Why? Are you afraid of me?
Look at your face
You're really scared of me
You don't know who I am, Raya
I'm not afraid of you
I'm a warrior
A third-world hero
Please, you don't know anything
Oh, really?
Look at your face, you're really scared of me
I'm not afraid of you
[music]
[moaning]
He's so weird
Whatever
I will make him lose
I have to win
You have to
[music]
I'm coming
[moaning]
[music]
Raya
I have to beat him
And win the title of life
Because that's the only way I can live again
You're so cool, Alva
[music]