To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
How was it, Alva?
What did they say?
I waited for them
They said they could sense the blood of the 8th Prince
You used Borgoni, Aldebaran's hand
So he couldn't go anywhere
The fire guard will come and take him away from the fire
Catch him
Yes, sir
Let me go
Thank you, sir
I'm so happy, sir
Because from today, I'm the headmaster of this school
Good, I called the school earlier
And I want to talk to Professor Aldebaran
But first, who should I talk to?
Anggara
Professor Anggara
Soldiers, this is the Segai Sentara
Soldiers, I'm thirsty
Where's the river? I want to drink
We have to keep flying
We can't stop
If you're thirsty, use the water fang mantra
That was given by our professor
Okay, soldiers
Water fang
What's going on? Why are we gathered here in the morning?
Maybe there's another selection
We have to win
Yes, we have to win, Tom
I agree, we have to win
Love with a smile
Good morning, kids
Good morning, sir
We're all here because Professor Aldebaran gave me a letter
He wants to give you all an important message
Good morning, everyone
Anggara, why are you here?
I'm not here to invite you to war
But I want to give you important information
If we start today, I'll be the head of the school
What?
That's not funny
You better tell me where Professor Aldebaran is
Aldebaran has retired
He's no longer the head of the school
You're lying
You don't believe me?
This is the truth
That's Professor Aldebaran's toxin, Brock
Yes, Professor Jasmine
That's right, it's Professor Aldebaran's
This toxin is proof that Aldebaran is no longer the head of the school
And he has resigned
Impossible
Professor Aldebaran would never resign to a cunning and evil person like you
Resigning doesn't have to be a good thing
But sometimes it's better to do it in a cruel way
How dare you hurt Professor Aldebaran?
I'll break you!
Enough, Agni
Just resign
Because the power you have is not as good as mine
You lose
Thank you for the smile
I can't let this go
The magic of the devil
Wow, that's cool
What is that?
Let me see
Aaaaah
Antara
Attack me
Our professor is good at dodging
Yes, he's good at dodging
We meet again, Antara
Watch this
Look at that
Professor Antara is now a fool
Aaaaaah
You're too much, Antara
He's just a kid
Is everyone ready?
Yes, sir
Okay, wait
Where are you, Al?
Answer my question, where are you, Alfa?
I'm sorry, Dad
I'm sorry, Al
I failed to find the cure for the darkness
But I promise
I will get the cure for the darkness
And I will bring you both back to life
Mom, Dad
I'm sorry, Dad
Alfa
Do you really want to find the cure for the darkness?
Yes
Then, go home with your parents
Go back to your parents
Go
I don't want to
I want to protect my parents
For that matter
Trust me
I will protect them
Trust me, Alfa
Even though you're still here
It won't change anything
They will never wake up, Alfa
They will never wake up
Except
If you have the cure for the darkness
That's the key
Now, look at me
Stay with me
You have to go home
Fight Ankara
Defeat him with the other students
If you succeed in defeating him
He will tell you how to fight the darkness
Now, go
Goodbye, Dad
Alfa
I'm sorry, Dad
[Music]
It's okay
I'm here
Realization that...
I will look for a way out of this.
Because I will live a life of hate, jealous.
I'm tired of asking her to go home.
If Alva doesn't want to go home, let her stay here.
Let's go home.
Wait, Bro.
I'm going home too.
Yes.
And I ask you, teacher.
Take good care of them.
Yes!
Alva, you're lucky to be with us.
If not, it's not crowded.
Yes, we have to act as five, right?
Yes.
Yes, Mommy.
Yes, good, Alva.
It turns out you still have a good mind.
And you, Panji.
You don't have to teach me.
I'm their teacher.
Okay, kids.
Everyone, get ready.
Come on.
Don't leave me and my mother.
Of course, Alva.
Alva.
Hi, I'm ready. See you soon, sir.
See you soon.
All together on three!
One, two, three, fly, fly!
Bye, sir!
Professor Aldebaran?
Professor?
[music]
Hello, Professor Agni.
Angkara, why are you here?
Now tell me where you hid Professor Aldebaran.
Agni, don't be so rude.
Isn't it obvious?
The head of the magic school is in my hands now.
And this means I'm the official head of the magic school.
No.
Until this moment, Professor Aldebaran is still in office as the official head of the school.
And you, you're no one, Angkara.
Agni, don't be mad like this.
If you're mad, you won't be pretty anymore.
Agni, how about this?
How about we work together?
Then I'll give you a position as the head of the school.
How about that?
Thank you, Angkara.
But I don't want to work with a stupid traitor like you.
What did you say?
If it's not stupid, then what is it?
You want to work with me as the follower of the prince of darkness?
Agni, it's up to you what you want to say.
What's clear is that I will follow you.
If I'm more worthy of being the head of the magic school here.
Come on.
Welcome to the fire prison.
Once you enter it, you can't get out.
I'm trapped.
Let me go.
Oh my God, it's so hot in here.
Hurry up. Get in.
Let me go.
Please, I'm not guilty.
From today, I officially work as the head of the magic school.
And Aldebaran has been locked up in the fire prison.
He can't get out of there.
Good, Ambaran.
Now Aldebaran is no longer in danger.
And your job is to teach the black magic to the children.
So they all join my team.
Yes, sir.
Finally, everyone in the magic school obeys my order.
Good.
I can't wait to see the classroom and the classroom.
The color has changed to black.
Just like the dark magic.
Come on, kids. You're faster at doing the magic.
Smile.
You have to finish this job.
Yes, sir.
What's this?
How's the job?
Is the professor satisfied with the paint?
Satisfied with what?
I told you to paint it black.
Why is it pink?
Yes, yes.
Give me a smile, professor.
Pink is the color.
The job is done.
Please see the result, sir.
You're a coward.
I told you to paint it black, not pink.
What, sir?
Give me a smile.
Yellow, sir.
So the professor asked for yellow.
We're in the wrong, Professor Jasmine.
What are you going to do?
Wait, wait.
You're playing with me.
Then I'll tie you up.
I'll put you in jail.
No, sir.
He's one of them.
Kids, attack him.
Vega, Plita.
Let's go.
Ray, Tole.
Alva.
Let's go.
Let's attack together.
One, two, three.
Let's go.
He's a coward.
Alva.
Alva again.
What's wrong with him?
Is there anyone else?
Let Professor Debaran go.
After that, leave this school.
Don't come back.
Yes, if he leaves, I'll make him sit on the grass.
Let's go.
You can do it.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry.
You're too late.
Aldebaran is already somewhere.
And he's my enemy.
If you dare to attack me,
I'll make sure...
Aldebaran will never come back here.
You're so arrogant.
You dare to attack me?
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
What should we do?
Where should we go?
Vivi.
Alva.
Alva is here.
Where is he?
Listen, everyone.
I'm the head of this school.
So, you have to follow my order.
If you don't,
there will be only three of you in Aldebaran.
Everyone.
You have to paint it black.
Not pink.
Yes, sir.
How far are we?
Well.
We're only 10.000 km away.
That's still a long way, sir.
We're exhausted.
We're sleepy.
Can we take a break?
If you want to take a break,
you can take a nap.
You can.
As long as you sleep on the tolipop.
And don't fall.
If you fall, I won't be responsible.
What is that?
This is bad.
Get up.
Sleepyhead, wake up.
Don't sleep.
What is that?
Wake up. Don't sleep.
Look.
It's dangerous in front of you.
Wake up.
Turn around.
It's dangerous.
Hurry up.
We're going to be surrounded.
Watch out.
The rail is getting closer.
Hurry up.
We're going to be surrounded.
I got confused.
It's written in the book.
Tornado, don't surround us.
Please.
Help!
To be continued...
Gamma.
I'm lost.
You're awake.
But, how?
Panji, go.
What? Go?
Go, Panji.
Leave us.
But...
Gamma is right.
Go to the magic school.
Save Alva.
What if I'm left alone with you?
We'd better stay here...
so that Virgo can take care of us.
Hurry up, Panji.
Alva is in danger.
Don't.
Alva.
You said the right passport.
Please, come in.
It's just a dream.
I'm not sure if I can make it.
But, why does it feel so real?
Why did Gamma and Aquila ask me to go to the magic school?
Why did they ask me to protect Alva?
What's really going on?
But, it's getting dark.
What should we do?
If we fight,
the professor will get hurt.
I want to be an ice.
Let's be an ice fairy...
so that I can eat.
The ice fairy's arm is so big.
I thought we're going to the magic school.
I don't want to.
It's a must.
I'm tired of being an ice fairy.
(The magic school)
What's wrong, Tole?
Tole.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Tole, wake up!
I smell something.
It's like a chicken.
And a scorpion.
I'm going to be an ice fairy.
I'm tired.
Virgo.
I'm leaving.
Please, protect Gamma and Aquila.
Give them the pearl every day.
Okay.
I'll give them to you.
I'll be back soon.
(The magic school)
That's a wound mark.
With this wound mark...
...Gamma and Aquila will be safe.
If someone tries to hurt me...
...I'll know.
And I'll come to their rescue.
I need water!
I'm thirsty!
Guard!
Help!
(We can do it)
Where are we going?
I don't know.
Let's go.
You're so enthusiastic.
You were so weak.
I know.
I want to eat.
Eat?
Yes.
Where are you going to eat?
We still have an hour.
I don't need to.
I'll eat.
With cookies.
Eat a lot.
You're fat.
We'll eat everything.
I'll eat cookies.
What's this?
Who dares to eat my food?
Who?
(I'm hungry)
This is called temptation.
Who dares to eat my food?
This means...
...he's under heavy punishment.
Yes.
No one dares to insult me as the head of the school.
This is scary.
Luckily, I didn't eat it.
If I did, I could be thinned out.
This is scary.
I'm falling.
I'm not a pig.
This is not a pig.
It's a cockroach.
What are you talking about?
I'll stab you.
Why are you running?
I saw Professor Angkara was angry.
It was scary.
Angry?
Why?
Attention, teachers and students.
Gather in the classroom.
Once again.
I'm Professor Angkara.
The head of the magic school.
Gather in the classroom.
For all the students and teachers.
Hurry.
What's the matter?
He's always angry.
Let's go to the classroom.
What now?
We're not...
Oh my God.
This must be because of...
This is scary.
What should we do?
What's wrong?
I heard Professor Angkara was angry.
Because the food was taken by someone.
It was eaten by someone else.
He said,
if anyone eats the food, they will be punished.
I prayed.
It's not you who ate it.
Tole, it's not you, right?
Yes, it's me.
Be honest.
Don't lie.
It's not me.
Answer me.
Tole.
It's not you, right?
It's not me.
I don't want you to be punished.
Let's go to the classroom.
Okay.
Oh my God.
What should we do?
Please, Tole.
It's so hot in here.
Water.
I'm thirsty.
I need water.
I don't have a bucket.
I can't get water.
Guard.
Guard, please.
I'm thirsty.
I need water.
Guard.
Please.
I'm thirsty.
Tole.
Water.
It's useless to shout.
They will never come.
Sir.
If I may know...
...why are you...
...able to stay in a place like this?
It's not hot.
For that...
...you have to master the knowledge of soul conservation.
Knowledge of soul conservation?
What is that, sir?
There are two sides of life in this world.
Good.
Evil.
Healthy.
Sick.
Hot.
And cold.
When one of them is over...
...the result won't be good.
Because of that...
...you need the balance of the soul.
A balanced soul...
...will release...
...the aura in your body.
So that...
...the heat won't be felt.
So, from that...
...you need the balance of the soul.
And you won't...
...feel the heat anymore.
Sir.
Can you...
...teach me the balance of the soul?
[The balance of the soul]
Quiet!
Listen, everyone.
I gathered you here...
...because there's a thief in this school.
Thief?
That thief...
...has eaten my food.
Because of that...
...I ask for the thief to confess and move forward.
Yes, sir.
I will count to ten...
...and if no one confesses...
...then everyone will be punished.
Confess, quick!
Yes, confess!
Confess!
Who ate it?
You're always finding fault in me.
I don't know.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Confess.
This is a trivial matter.
Just because of the food...
...I can ask you to cook a lot of food for the guests.
This is a school...
...that teaches discipline.
Not to be a thief!
Five.
Confess!
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Confess!
I ate it!
You ate it!
Don't be weird.
You haven't eaten anything.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I'll cook now.
I'm sorry, professor.
I ate it.
To be continued...
How are you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine, soldier.
I'm a soldier.
How about you?
I'm just a soldier.
What about you?
I'm a soldier.
It's better if you're alone.
Try me.
This is a supernatural phenomenon.
Spontaneous, enchanting, romantic.
Asmurat.
The disease lies here.
It's so bad.
Soldier.
The cactus is so big.
It's scary.
This is a cactus.
I think the cactus is the one who's going to be the king.
If it's here, we can see it.
I think it's not friendly.
Watch out. What is it throwing?
Watch out.
It's moving.
The cactus is moving.
It's broken.
Soldier, what should we do?
Our club is broken because of the cactus.
The cactus can talk.
It can talk.
The cactus has a cactus salon.
There's a lady on the table.
I'm sorry, cactus.
We didn't mean to.
Yes, we didn't mean to.
It's angry.
It's showing its tail.
Watch out.
I forgot that we have a fireman in our school.
I'm sorry, too.
But, Sir.
I'm sorry.
You like to eat, don't you?
Alright.
If that's the case, I'll give you a punishment that you like.
We'll cut the table.
Please eat all of these, Alva.
Why, Alva?
Why did you admit that all of these are not poisoned?
If I knew that I was going to be eaten, I wouldn't have been punished.
But you have to listen to the rules.
You have to finish all of these.
No one is allowed to be left.
If anyone is left, you'll be punished severely.
To be continued...
Now, calm down.
Forget your worries.
And forget your fears, too.
Think about the beautiful things in your life.
Now, take a deep breath.
Let out your breath.
Get rid of all the burdens.
To be continued...
How do you feel?
Better?
You're right.
I don't feel the heat anymore.
If it's like this, I think I can survive here.
Thank you very much, sir.
They're coming soon!
Where are they?
It's already 9 o'clock. They'll be here soon.
Who are they, sir?
To be continued...
Hey! Let him go! Don't hurt him!
I can't interfere, professor.
Soon, your time will come.
To be continued...
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Alva! Alva!
Oh, no.
It's so hot.
It's so bad. What should we do?
Alva, why did you stop?
If you stop and spit out all the food,
you'll get a worse punishment.
To be continued...
Alva, I'm sure he's full.
Alva, we have to help Alva.
But, he's starting to walk.
To be continued...
Hey, don't go! I'll take care of him.
Alva, I'll take care of him.
Oh, so you want to be the leader of the lunatics, Tole.
To be continued...
Bro, let me go!
Come on.
Who else wants to be a hero like Tole?
Then, he'll be fished.
And will be given to the raptor to be fed.
To be continued...
Come on, Alva.
Stop, Alva.
So, I can torture you.
To be continued...
Hey, who are you?
You, you!
Catch him!
To be continued...
You have to hold on.
Come on, get up.
Get up.
Eat this.
Come on, eat.
Chocolate.
Chocolate will make you happy.
And will protect you from the attack of the Ruputala Guard and the Fire Police.
The Fire Police will take your good emotions.
Spend all your good emotions with this chocolate.
You will hold on.
To be continued...
How is it?
Thank you, Sir.
To be continued...
I'm not strong anymore.
I can't.
I can't finish all this food.
So, this is the meaning of Gama and Aguliela that I ordered to come.
Hakara.
You are really too much.
How dare you to betray Alva.
It's okay.
To be continued...
What is this?
Why did I suddenly wake up?
And why am I hungry again?
Alva.
Eat all of this.
Finish it.
Alva.
Your body is small, but your intestines are long.
And your intestines are amazing. Full of smile.
Shut up, all of you.
Alva.
You won this time.
But next time, I will make you lose.
And I will give you a heavier punishment.
To be continued...
Buffet, pass me the rope.
Thank you, Sir.
Alva.
To be continued...
Sir, don't.
Don't touch me.
Sir, why are you here?
I want to see your room, Hakara.
Why are you still keeping my bones?
As a souvenir, Sir.
Because I have defeated Panji.
How far have you taught your children?
To teach them, Sir.
But I have managed to persuade all the children and teachers...
...to paint the classroom and classroom walls black, Sir.
And starting tomorrow, I will teach them black science, Sir.
Why do you always delay the children?
I need the rope as soon as possible.
Teach the children right now.
Yes, Sir.
Damn it.
He's coming.
Hey, who are you?
Who are you?
I'm going to kill you.
No.
Where is that person?
Turn around.
I'm going to break your bones.
Yes, me too.
There he is, Boss.
Chase him.
What's this?
My head hurts.
What's wrong, Boss?
No, I don't want to.
What? Hurry up and do it.
No, I don't want to. He's my friend.
We can do it.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Sir.
There was a thief who broke into our school, Sir.
Yes, Sir.
He broke in there.
We chased him inside.
There were three heads inside, Sir.
Yes, Sir.
What did he look like?
He wore a red shirt.
He had a moustache.
He wore a black jacket, Sir.
He wore a orange shirt.
He was wearing a man's shirt.
A man's shirt?
Yes, Sir.
We're going to break his bones.
He's my friend.
Your friend?
Alright.
Then, you stay here.
Tommy!
Come here.
Be careful.
What did you just do?
And where is your intention towards Alva?
Angkara!
Stop!
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm going to kill you.
Stop!
Stop right here.
Don't force me to hurt you.
Sir, I don't like to be disturbed.
If you don't accept it,
it means you're letting me hurt Alva.
Do you want that?
[Tommy is being tortured.]
Tommy, do it quickly.
Yes, Sir.
Let's go, Tommy.
Go!
Run!
[Tommy is being tortured.]
Angkara, it's impossible.
Angkara, calm down.
[Tommy is being tortured.]
[To be continued...]
Never give up, chase the passion and dreams
Go.. go.. go, achieve all your dreams
Go.. go.. go, never ever stop
Go.. go.. go, fight with your heart
Go.. go.. go, make yourself proud
Go.. go.. go, let's dream
Go.. go.. go, we will be sure