Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
If Alfa gets the soul stone, you have to snatch it.
Don't let Alfa destroy it. Do you understand?
Why does the ring have a black color?
It's like a feathered turtle's feather.
Is it true that there's a soul stone in this ring?
No, it's impossible.
We're going to the school of the new year's eve.
There's a task for us.
What task?
We have to find the third soul stone.
Find the soul stone?
What does this mean?
The ring has a soul stone in it?
I think they're going to take the third soul stone.
We have to follow them.
Don't fail, we're going to be punished for the darkness.
Yes, boss.
Let's go.
Siyang, I'm home.
You're home?
Are you hungry? I've cooked your favorite food.
No, I'm going to take it.
I have an important task from school.
I'm going to take it.
What task?
Destroy the soul stone.
Destroy the soul stone?
I'm going to destroy the soul stone.
Yes, because the darkness has 12 parts.
The only way to destroy the darkness is to destroy the soul.
But we have to do it one by one.
But I think that task is too hard for you and your friends.
Aren't you afraid?
I studied magic at school.
And I have a master's degree in magic.
Most of the time, the darkness loses.
We will get the status of the eighth prince.
And we will revive our father.
Okay?
I'm going to take it.
You two, and you, please take care of my mother.
Don't worry, Alfa.
I will take care of your mother from all kinds of disturbances.
Disturbances?
Akilah must be lonely being left by Alfa.
I have to make her happy.
No, no.
That's not for her.
No, that's not for her.
No, no, no.
Guys, I'm sorry. I can't come.
Alfa, I'm sorry too. I can't come.
Because I'm afraid.
Red.
Yes, my mother is also angry with me because I'm afraid.
It's all bad.
It's okay.
Are you ready?
Yes, Alfa.
Okay, then.
Bye.
Let's go back.
Okay, hurry up.
You guys take them to the lake.
Why do you have to change your clothes?
Why do you have to splash?
Who said I wanted to splash to the lake?
You two splash to the lake.
I want to go to the lake.
Where is the boss? I thought he was splashing.
Yes.
This is fun.
I'm your boss.
So you guys splash.
If you're the boss, your job is to watch over the fruit.
I'm lazy.
If you're playing, I'll report you to the police.
So you'll be punished.
No, boss.
That's just a splash.
Hurry up, boss.
One.
Two.
Three.
Did you hear that?
Someone is splashing.
I heard it too.
I heard someone splashing.
But who?
Because Alfa, Vega, and Plita were the first ones to splash.
Just now?
Yes.
But...
I'm confused.
Who was splashing?
What?
That's Tommy, Mike, and Jack.
Why are they splashing?
Mike and Jack are splashing.
Yes.
But they're not told to run for their lives.
Maybe...
Let them splash to the lake.
I'm going back to school.
Let's go.
Guys, stop.
What are you doing here?
Stop asking questions.
We should be the ones asking.
What are Mike and Jack doing in the lake?
No, it's not that far.
There must be a secret.
There must be something.
Be quiet.
Let's go.
Tell me, why are Mike and Jack splashing?
Tell me.
If you don't want to answer, I'll give you another chance.
Oh, my God.
I'll answer.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Mike and Jack are splashing to the lake to learn how to swim.
That's right.
Seriously?
If you don't trust me,
you can fight with my dad.
Do you want to?
No.
You're the one who's in charge of our school.
Why do you want to do this to us?
Ask him.
Don't you dare.
I'll ask him.
There must be something between Tommy and you.
If you tell me something that you don't like,
I'll tell you.
I agree.
Let's go.
[TOMMY & JACK ARE GOING TO THE LAKE]
They're so fast.
They're really fast.
[TOMMY & JACK ARE GOING TO THE LAKE]
Why is it getting dark?
The sky is full of stars.
Let's run.
Hi, Putri Duyung.
Do you know where Isana Duyung is?
I don't know.
We want to ask her about the will.
Yes.
It's for the school.
You're in the wrong.
Our precious will has been stolen.
Stolen?
Do you know who stole it?
Not yet.
That's why I'm here.
Whoever finds it,
will get a very precious gift.
I'm so dizzy.
I've been looking for it for a long time.
What's in the will?
This is a painting of our legacy.
It looks like my mother.
No, it's not.
It's not.
It's similar.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so pale?
Are you sick?
No, I'm fine.
I'm working.
Let's go home.
We'll tell our friends.
Okay.
Putri Duyung, we're going home.
Be careful.
Bye, Putri Duyung.
No.
Help me, Jack.
Thank you.
We're lucky we didn't get eaten.
My back.
We're going to lose our track.
We can get scolded by the boss.
He's not that strong.
He can't handle the darkness.
Let's go home.
I'm scared.
It's still hot.
Let's go.
"The next day"
I'm looking for Putri Duyung's legacy.
A ring.
Whoever finds it, will get a prize.
Whoever finds it...
...will get a prize.
It's so cool, Jack.
It's so shiny.
Let's find it.
We'll get a prize.
We can't be careless.
We should go first.
We should go now.
We're all scared.
Let's go.
"The next day"
I know.
I'll change my hair style.
I'll get my hair done.
"The next day"
I'll change it.
I'll get my hair done.
"The next day"
Don't be like this.
I'll change it.
I'll get my hair done.
It's better like this.
Thank you for taking me here.
Yes.
You're welcome.
It's done.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Why are you giving me a gift?
This garden has a lot of beautiful memories.
For me.
Because this is where I first met you.
Agila.
You're right, Purwa.
A lot of beautiful things happened in this garden.
This garden...
has a lot of beautiful memories for me.
"The next day"
You also invited me here?
Purwa, who are you?
I'm Purwa.
Why are you alone? Can I join you?
Sure.
I'll sit here.
"The next day"
Purwa?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
We should go back.
Before they find us.
Okay.
What?
The Duyung library was stolen?
Yes.
And we don't know who did it.
Poor Duyung. They're confused.
Yes, they're confused.
Because whoever finds the book...
will get a lot of prizes.
If that's the case,
we need the help of Professor Yasmin.
So, we can find out where the book is.
Let's go.
"The next day"
Yasmin.
What's wrong?
Be careful.
The thief...
is very smart, Prof.
And I can't get through him.
Because I can see...
the fog is very thick.
And I can only see...
the hands of a little boy who took the book.
A little boy?
Yes.
"The next day"
A little boy?
Could he be the one who stole the book?
The fog is very thick.
It feels like...
deja vu.
What's deja vu?
Deja vu...
feels like something unfamiliar.
Like something that never happened before.
Maybe...
he's the one who tried to scare us.
Maybe he's the one.
The boy is the same.
But why did he steal Duyung's book?
That's what I don't know.
Let's think about it later.
Now, we should be careful.
He must be waiting for us.
Yes, let's go.
Where is it?
I can't find it.
Let's look for another book.
I'll just...
read another book.
This is...
a great book.
It's called...
Madame Gemini.
It can read...
100% accurate.
I want to meet her.
Why do we have to meet her?
She's a good teacher.
She can help us with our exams.
She can be our future teacher.
She's my future teacher.
She's good.
Okay, I agree.
This is what we're looking for.
Madame Gemini.
But, what's the book for?
What's the book for?
We're looking for...
the thief of Duyung's book.
It's written here.
If we're lucky,
we won't get lost.
I'll read it.
This is the code.
1000 kilometers from this school...
to there.
So, we can leave tonight.
We can arrive tomorrow morning.
Where?
There?
They're looking for a thief...
to steal Duyung's book.
We have to follow them.
We have to get Duyung's book.
If we get it, we're in trouble.
Guys, what's the matter?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
Nothing?
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to bed.
I'm sleepy too.
It's only this late,
and I'm already sleepy.
There must be something.
I'm a thief.
You're not that far, Gembro.
You're not like us.
What's your plan?
Listen to me.
If we report this to the police,
because the police...
said that we're looking for him,
we'll get 2 books.
And we can give them...
a reward.
We'll get a gift from Duyung.
Great!
That's a great idea.
Who's going first?
That's fun.
I can meet...
Pramal.
I can also ask for a ride.
I agree.
It hurts.
Here, take this.
I thought you're going to do it.
You're being a jerk.
I'm talking about the soul stone.
Not the soul.
The value.
Learn it.
I know.
I'm a good student.
The soul stone is the ring I'm wearing.
What should I do?
If I take off the ring,
my father will sleep again.
What?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just thinking.
What are you thinking?
About Pramal.
Should I go with her?
I'm confused.
I'm confused too.
I'll think about it later.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
I'll be back.
Why is Alfa so weird?
This is so funny.
It's normal for her to be the worst.
She's a soul stone.
Why is she like this?
I'm curious.
I think Alfa is playing with her body.
Or,
she's hiding something.
Let's go.
Did you lose it?
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Who dares to take the ring?
It's not me.
But, sir.
Just go to the beach.
We'll find the ring for you.
Wait.
Where are your friends?
Oh, Gembrot.
I mean, Boss.
Are you sick?
Yes, sir.
He's actually tired.
He's so weak.
So, let's do it.
So, we can continue the mission.
Okay, sir.
I'll give you a task.
To find the ring.
Yes, sir.
Teleportation.
And you, Garam.
Go to the beach.
Find the one who can do it.
Yes, sir.
[Gembrot]
I found it.
You found it?
Where?
Your book is in the magic school.
In this building.
How come our book is in the magic school?
So, they took it.
We have to get our book back.
Let's go there.
That's weird.
Why is our book in the magic school?
Who took it?
Purwa.
Where are you taking me?
I just...
I just took Akila out.
[Purwa]
Purwa.
Are you pretending to be stupid?
Or are you really stupid?
What if someone sees us?
Hey, I'm not that kind of guy.
You're talking about Akila, right?
Not a girlfriend.
I just want to win her heart.
It's hard for you to say that.
You're saying that I'm stupid or what?
Yes, you're stupid.
You're stupid.
Look at me.
Purwa.
Panji.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you shouting?
It's nothing.
Excuse me.
Um...
Alfa.
How's your assignment from Professor Aldebaran?
Is it done?
This is your inheritance.
[Alfa]
Merik.
This ring is really similar to the one in the dune.
Alfa.
What are you thinking?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going, ma'am.
Where are you going?
It's late.
I'm looking for the missing white sandal.
So, my friends and I are going to a funeral home.
It's called Madame Gemini.
So, you're leaving your mom again?
I don't think so.
I really want to be with my mom.
Do you want to come with me?
[To be continued...]
Feel it, Tommy.
That's why you should not be a coward.
[We can do this!]
Alfa looks like Professor Purwa.
Yes, she does.
Since when did she become Professor Purwa's student?
There's Paji, too.
Usually, they're in the kitchen.
How could that be?
Then, who's that girl?
What are you doing here?
Agu Hila, wear your Jubah Jeb.
Come on.
Jubah.
Mom.
Now, answer my question.
Why did you peep into my house?
Answer.
Yes, sir. We just want to follow Alfa.
For what?
Answer my question.
Yes, sir.
We want to steal.
A man.
A man can't lose.
We won't have a boyfriend.
You're so mean.
You peeped into my house.
You'll get your punishment.
You'll see.
Calm down, sir.
I'm just here to see Paji.
Don't worry. I still have business with Professor Purwa.
And I'll decide...
if I'll come with you to Madam Gemini's house.
Yes.
Where are you going?
You want to skip school again?
We have an important task, sir.
So, we're leaving tonight.
So, we'll be back tomorrow morning.
Yes, sir.
That's right, sir.
Goodbye, Professor.
Goodbye, Paji.
I have to find Alfa again.
I have to find information about the soul stone.
"The soul stone is in the basement."
Where are Rih and Tole?
They should be back at the dormitory.
That's weird.
Mike and Jack are not here.
This is so annoying.
Why can't I get any information?
Here.
I have a headache.
I'm going to ask Julia.
I'm afraid I'll get a cold when I fly.
Me too.
I'll wait here.
I have to get my motorcycle ready.
Alfa.
I can't wait.
I think our trip will be fun.
I'm glad if you're happy.
What if the spirit says...
the soul stone is in your hand?
What should I do?
What's wrong?
Why are you so tense?
I promise I won't make you uncomfortable.
Calm down.
I remember your father used to be adventurous like you.
They like to travel.
Just like you.
Don't be so loud.
You'll get caught.
Let's try to hide.
So, it won't be seen.
That's Alfa.
Where is she going?
She's carrying a backpack.
I think she's going far.
I have to find out.
Who is that?
Why is Alfa's child peeping?
Alfa.
Your child is peeping.
It's behind the pillar.
It must be Tommy.
If he's in, this plan will be a mess.
I'm going.
Don't show up.
Where are you going?
I'm going to meet my friends.
I'll wait for Alfa outside.
Where is Alfa?
She's running so fast.
I have to find her.
But, where is she going?
I'll go there.
I knew it.
That's why I'm not a good person.
I'll go back to the corridor.
"I'm going to meet my friends."
Feel it, Tommy.
That's why I'm not a good person.
I'll go back to the corridor.
Where is the toilet?
I haven't gone back yet.
That's weird.
Ma'am, did you see Ray and Tole?
Ma'am?
Ray, who were you talking to?
Ray, Tole.
I wasn't talking to anyone.
I think I heard you talking to someone.
That's Tommy.
He wanted to follow me.
That's why I'm following him.
So, he won't go.
Let's go.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Let's go.
Where is he?
He's not here.
Come on.
Let's go.
Putri Duyung.
What are you doing here?
Aldebaran.
The heirloom of the Kamiblon kingdom.
According to the Power Sakti fish,
the heirloom is in one of the buildings in the school.
How is it possible that the heirloom is here?
The Power Sakti fish can't be wrong.
So, we'll start to investigate.
Everyone, go.
Wait.
Okay.
I'll let you investigate this school.
But, I have to go.
To keep an eye on him.
He's just arrived.
He's so slow.
He's tired.
I don't know.
We're going to the toilet.
Let's go.
What?
Why didn't you say anything?
Where's your brother?
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
That's Alfa.
Luckily, he's not here.
Why is it so heavy?
What's heavy?
Well...
Nothing.
Mom.
Why did you make us do this?
Where have you been?
I want to be alone.
Who do you want to be with?
Why didn't you tell me?
You're ready, right?
We're ready, Miss.
Hold it tight.
Alfa.
If we don't hold it tight, we'll fall.
I know.
That's right.
Let's go.
Alfa is so weird today.
She's not focused.
Why is she so weird?
I don't know.
Let's count down.
We'll fly.
No need to count.
One, two, three.
Let's fly.
Let's go.
I know that Madan...
loves Dangdut song.
What?
We can do it.
I think it's done.
One more.
The soy sauce.
Let's go.
It's so good.
Akilah will love this.
Akilah.
Lunch is served.
Why did you call me?
It looks good.
For me?
I'm calling Akilah...
for lunch.
Not because I'm hungry.
Why are you laughing?
What's so funny?
It's been a long time.
Since we were in school.
I never forget it.
I always miss you.
What's the news?
Akilah has left.
Akilah has left?
Yes.
I'm going to cook.
I'm going to...
What's going on?
Tuyuk.
What are they doing here?
They're here to raid your house.
Raid my house?
For what?
According to the power source.
The lost King of Duyung's book is here.
Duyung's book?
Don't mess with my stuff.
What?
Is it true?
Don't.
Professor Odebar.
I know who can do this.
It must be Panji.
Don't you dare to talk back.
Yes.
Panji.
Calm down.
We're sure that it's here.
But it's weird. Why can't we find it?
It means that only one thing.
The power source.
Alright. We'll go.
But we'll find our lost book.
I'll find it.
I must have Panji.
We're here.
Gosh.
The queue is long.
Yes.
It's okay.
Come on.
Only the one who can make me happy.
The one I'm close to.
What?
What's wrong?
I miss you.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking for the lost book.
I must find it.
Who knows the book is in him.
"The lost book"
It's here.
Bargi will always wait for Panji.
"The lost book"
It turns out that you're handsome.
You have a monster's taste.
Cing!
You're always taking people's stuff.
I'm warning you.
Don't ever touch my stuff.
Why?
Are you afraid that I'll take your beloved monster?
I'll take your mouth.
Feel it.
You're so big.
I'll eat you.
Move.
It turns out that you're handsome.
What's wrong?
Hang on.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for the lost book.
"The lost book"
It's here.
It's not here.
Angkara, let us go.
Angkara.
Let me be happy first.
Then, I'll do whatever you want.
Okay.
I'll do it.
In the past, there was a princess...
...who was ugly.
No.
I don't want to tell the story of a princess...
...who was far away from her lover.
I want to tell the story of a princess who was far away from her lover.
I'm bored, Mbak Mbirbi.
I know how to do it.
Get the tarot card.
What's wrong with you?
You're so rude.
I don't want to be rude to you.
Don't be rude.
It's hard to be with her.
I don't want to do anything.
I think I know her.
What's wrong with you?
...one in a million.
So, if someone needs help, there's only one condition.
Dance in front of him.
Alfa.
I know how to make him happy.
You have to dance in front of him.
Dangdut?
Yes, Dangdut.
I know him, Alfa.
He's my teacher.
Madam, can you give me another chance?
We'll think about how to make you happy.
Okay.
One more time.
Okay, let's go out.
Madam, we'll go out first.
Let's go.
I know you like Dangdut song.
Huh? Dangdut?
That's why we have to practice it first.
I don't know how to make him happy.
Do you know where it's from?
Did you read it from a book?
I don't think so.
If we make a mistake, he might get angry.
And he won't practice it.
That's impossible.
I'm sure someone will tell me that he likes Dangdut.
That's why we have to dance in front of him.
I want to go home.
We can do this!
Can you do it?
Shut up!
Don't follow me!
You're following me!
That's it.
What?
If you keep doing this, we'll never pass.
Yes, that's right.
Then, what should we do?
How about this?
Hurry up.
Bite this rope until it's loose.
Why do I have to bite this rope?
This is so complicated.
I have an idea.
So, I'll be the first one to do it.
Hurry up.
Just do it.
When I'm free, I'll let you do it.
Come on.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Don't move.
What the heck?
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
I can't control myself.
I had to throw it.
Hurry up.
Let go of this.
It's still smelly.
Just blow it.
Let the smell go.
Hurry up.
You're so slow.
Don't move.
Don't ever touch my stuff again.
Remember that.
Okay.
By the way, we have to do it properly.
I'm afraid that we'll be chased.
Yes.
Luckily, you're not in danger.
What?
My rope.
Hurry up.
Don't touch it.
No.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Sir.
Wait.
Wait for a minute.
Okay.
Wait.
What's wrong?
It's neat.
Be patient.
Okay.
Let's go.
Fly.
I'm very smart.
I'll fly.
Fly?
Yes.
Let's go.
I'm very smart.
They must think that I'm gone.
Now, I just have to follow them...
...to find out where Alfa is.
Fly.
I'm a recorder type.
You're smart.
But, how do you dance?
Maybe, I'll show you later.
I'll show you.
What's that sound?
Stop it!
I want to go to the toilet!
What's wrong?
Why is the police so troublesome?
What if our mission fails?
I don't know.
What if the dark lord is angry with us?
We'll tell him, "What are you doing?"
So, you're accusing me?
And this is against me?
Don't use me in all kinds of ways.
Okay, okay.
I'm a coward.
Coward?
Let's focus.
So, our movement will be better.
Okay.
Who's that?
Hello, everyone.
Who are you?
I saw you from there.
You're practicing dancing, right?
It's good, but it's not compact enough.
How about I help you practice...
...dancing together, but it has to be compact.
Really?
But, you won't pay me, right?
Of course not.
Just relax.
It's all free.
Yes!
Okay.
Music.
Put your thumbs up.
Move your shoulders.
Bye.
I hope they'll be challenged by Professor Aldebaran...
...so that they'll be expelled from this school.
We can do it.
is it okay?
[music]
yeah, you're all great
you're all smart kids
you can do everything
who's the teacher?
aunt
yes
but, what if we don't know her?
it's okay, you can call her aunt
now, you can continue your work
thank you, aunt
we're going to meet Dili
you're welcome
bye, aunt
thank you, aunt
you're welcome
bye
[music]
you're great
let's go
[music]
good afternoon, kids
good afternoon, teacher
where's Alfa, Vega, Rey, Tole, and Plita?
I can't see Jack and Mac
they're not here
not here?
yes, teacher
Alfa, Vega, Rey, Tole, and Plita are not here
where are they?
I don't know
if they come back, we'll be punished
[music]
kids, read page 88
read the recovery plan
I want to go out
[music]
yes
I hope they're admitted to Aldebaran
so, they can be expelled from this school
[music]
have you found a way to make me happy?
yes, we have
promise me, if you're happy, you'll take care of us
don't worry, I never break my promise
show me
one, two, three
[music]
I'm falling
where?
it hurts
[laugh]
you're smart
you can make me happy
[cheering]
what should I do?
I want you to check the missing white paper
do you know where it is?
[music]
dear, teacher
please, give me a clue
where is Putri Diyung?
[music]
the ring
a woman
[music]
the ring is in a woman
long hair, white skin
and the woman is here
where?
you're lying
she's our friend
the crystal ball is not a lie
the woman is here
but we can't see her
we don't understand
it's a bad omen
you're talking nonsense
Madam never make a mistake
and all of her prophecy is not wrong
you're the one who make a mistake
you
be careful
you dare to Madam
what Madam Gemini meant is me
but how can I use the crystal ball?
because I haven't seen them for a long time
what's the meaning of this?
[music]
are you done?
yes, sir
I'm not strong enough
get down
Madam Gemini said that the crystal ball is in a woman's hand
what do you mean?
we don't know
I don't like you
you're making a hypothesis
I can't believe it
[music]
show your spirit, get ready to find your friends
run, jump, and climb the crystal
dare, don't know, say, give up
chase your hope and dream
go, go, go, achieve all your dream
go, go, go, don't ever stop
go, go, go, fight with your heart
go, go, go, make yourself proud
go, go, go, let's dream
go, go, go, we must