Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
From today, I'm the head of the school
You're so embarrassing
You better tell me where is Professor Naldebaran
Let me go, I'm being chased
Let me go, let me go, let me go
Tommy, do it quickly
You're a vixen
Run, run, run
Help me, Tommy
Help me
Help, I'm being chased, help
Don't be a vixen
Or do you want to suffer more?
Let Tommy go, quickly
Let him go
That's it, hold on
Hold on
Help me, help me
You're a vixen
Demet, what kind of man are you?
Help me, help
You're a vixen
You're a man but you don't want to be loved
And you, Tommy
Because you've been devoted to me
You've got the highest grade in this school
Yes, yes, yes
I'm a vixen
Wake up, Angka
Angka, Angka, Angka, wake up
You're a vixen
You've never loved anyone else
Agni
I didn't expect to see you here
Finally we can meet
Now is not the time to be in a hurry
I have to go to the bathroom
Don't be a vixen
We have to be careful because Angka has confessed to Professor Aldebaran
You? Because of Aldebaran?
Yes
And it's all thanks to the help of the Dark Lord
So, from now on, everything will be easier
My hair is black
I have an idea
What is it?
But I'm asking you
Don't tell Purwari
He can't be trusted
Panji, Panji
You two have been together since school until now
What's the enemy?
Now everything is in the hands of Professor Gitan
Give me a smile
Professor Agni
I'm in
If it's about being naughty, being naughty, being naughty
That's my hobby
You know it yourself, right?
That's good, Professor
Come on, get ready
This duricatus must be removed immediately
If not, it's dangerous
You can get a hangover for the rest of your life
Come on, get ready
Hurry up
Panji, Panji
I'm bleeding
It hurts, it hurts
Not yet, Nik
I'm bleeding
Not yet, take a deep breath
Slowly, slowly
They say the army of the West
Just got hit by a duricatus and already screaming
Shame on you
Where is Gitan?
We have to go to the village immediately
Come on, prepare your lollipop
Come on
Wait, wait
The lollipop is destroyed by that cactus
We just take a break
While we think of finding a way out
To be able to go there
Can, can
What's wrong?
Get up, get up
What's wrong, soldier?
What's wrong?
So many duricatus
I was so happy just now
Because I got to be in Alfa's session
You're so good
Now everyone can see
That I'm better than Alfa
Wait, wait
Wait
I want to see Alfa's session
Who's the best
I'm sorry, I'm against you
I'm so proud of you
I'm proud of you
I'm sorry, I'm against you
Come on
She's just a little bit naughty
She's naughty
I won
I'm proud of you
Tommy
Follow me to the room
Okay, sir
Alfa
Alfa is better
Tommy
I have an important task for you now
Starting today
You will monitor every move of Alfa
Starting from who she goes with
Who she meets
Or anything
How about it?
Are you ready?
I'm ready, sir
Good
Very good, Tommy
You're better with me
Because if you're with Aldebaran
You can't be the number one student
Because he's too biased to Alfa
But if you're biased to me
You can be the number one student in this magic school
Alfa
Okay, finish
You have to rest first
When you're healthy
You can come back to the dorm
Okay, Alfa?
Thank you, Mrs. Pertiwi
You're welcome, handsome
Okay, I'm going now
Bye-bye
Alfa
Are you okay now?
No, I'm just a bit dizzy
We have to be more careful
With Tommy
Yes, Alfa
Just now
Tommy was called by Professor Ankara
He must be trying to say something bad
Yes
Our school is going to be scary
Not like before
Yes
It's so scary
In a black jet
Yes
I miss the Professor Libaran
Now
Where is Professor Libaran?
Mr. Adi
Alfa
You just get well
It's okay, sir
Mr. Panji
Please change to Blacky
I really miss Blacky
Yes, sir
I can't
I change
If I'm only in the first month
It's a day off
Mr. Panji
Now we're all confused
How
How to face Professor Ankara
Because
He threatened us
He's going to hurt Professor Libaran
If we don't fight back
Yes, sir
For that matter
You just calm down
I already have a plan
How?
What is it?
Okay
It's safe
Now
It's time for us to take action
Ready
One, two, three
Three
Go
I'll be caught
Okay
I'll take Jubba first
Jubba
This is Jubba
Okay, let's go
I want to talk
Tomorrow I'll teach the black magic to the children
I think
I hear a voice
Go
Why are you in jail?
It's a long story
I'm here
To protect my grandson
His name is Leon
What's wrong with your grandson?
Leon
Has the ability
To control fire
Because of that
The Dark Lord
Was after him
We
Had to hide
We moved
From one place to another
But
Finally, the Dark Lord
Was able to find us
And save us
From the Dark Lord
I'm scared
(The Dark Lord is here)
Don't ask me
Why I'm here
I'm here to ask you
If you want to fight me
You will have to fight me
I
Will show you
(The Dark Lord is here)
Impossible
Angkar
Calm down, Angkar
Even if you're here
I can still defeat you
Yes
I'm here
(The Dark Lord is here)
Zell
I think I'm too tired now
It's better to find fresh air first
I'm scared
Don't be like that, Zell
I'm ready
Let's go
(The Dark Lord is here)
I challenge you, Angkar
You're crazy
How dare you challenge me
I'll show you your true self now
Panji
You're dead but you're still pathetic
You can still disturb people
Show me your true self now, Panji
Hurry
Weird
This is really weird and it doesn't make sense
Even though I'm dead
I can still disturb people
But I don't care
Whether it's a person or a ghost
I'm still invincible
Let's go
What's that?
Panji
Get out, Panji
I'll destroy this room
What's that?
I'm so mad
Calm down, Angkar
It's better if I walk straight ahead
I want to drink hot chocolate
After that, I'll feel better
Let's go back there
But Prof. Titan is still not here
We have to find a time until Prof. Titan finishes his assignment
But what should we do?
Let's just follow him
Yes
Give me a smile
It's safe
The situation is under control
Eight, six
I can imagine
If Angkara sees this
He'll be terrified
He'll scream
One by one
Angkara is here
[Angkara]
Tentara
How's it going?
Is it still a long way to go?
Yes, Tentara
If we use lollipop
It won't take a day
We've arrived at Melayu Village
But if we walk
It'll take two more days
Two days?
How long?
Two days
More than two weeks
Two weeks is too long, Tentara
Even so, if we walk
It won't take two weeks to stop
Not to rest
Not to eat
Not to go to the toilet
It'll take two weeks to walk
Tentara, this joke is not funny
Tentara
Enough
Don't make it harder
How about we call lollipop from school?
Wait, I'll try
Davatang
It can't be
The magic mantra Davatang
We can use it
If the distance from school is only 10 km
While our distance from school is thousands of km
So the magic mantra Davatang won't work here
Now it's time for us to eat
Take out your lollipop
And share the rest with me
Let's go
We're almost out of food, Tentara
That's right, Tentara
Where is it?
How about we try first?
Wait
Davatang
Food
Why is there sand?
There's a lot of sand
This is a sand field
Not a house for eating
There's no food
No lollipop
No water
What should we do, Tentara?
We might die of hunger here
This is it
What's up, Tentara?
We have an idea
My favorite bicycle
Bicycle?
We can eat a bicycle
You're kidding
Hey
My bicycle
Don't underestimate it
It's not just a bicycle
It can bring lollipop here
And food
And drink
We still have a chance
Hurry up, Tentara
It's not easy to call it
It's a bit difficult
This is how you call it
Test, test, test
One, two, three, test
Ontel
Tell Alfa
Alfa, please prepare
Five lollipops
Food and drink
Send it to the sand hill
We're all waiting there
Hurry up
Don't take too long
Okay
Thank you, Ontel
What do you think, Tentara?
It's more peaceful here
There won't be any problem
[music]
Hey, what are you doing?
Ancik
Get out
Where are you going?
I want you to send it to the sand hill
It's close
It's done
I'll destroy your bike
Ready
Go
You're kidding me
How can a military bike follow a forest?
It's a forest
Does it know our plan?
Maybe it heard us
Maybe it didn't hear us
After that, we'll go to the sand hill
And it'll follow us
Our bike is out of the sand hill
We'll be in trouble
If we get hit, we'll get out of the forest
We'll get hit by the sand hill
What should we do?
There's one solution
What is it?
We run
Run
Inspiration
Look
Starting tomorrow, I'll make a rule
The bike that's in the school must be removed
It seems like the other 300 are gone
I'm sure it's afraid of my threat
But if it's really you
Why did it follow me?
Or
Is it still alive?
We're here
Yes, professor?
I want to ask you
You have to answer honestly
If not, I'll punish you
I'll answer honestly, professor
Answer
Is it true that I'm still alive?
Or is it really dead?
Answer
Is it true that I'm still alive?
Professor is evil
Why did you ask that?
You want to make me sad again?
You're all dust now
Professor is evil
So it's really dead
So it was really a ghost
People are right
If a person is evil, it means he's evil
But still
Even if he's not dead, he's still a ghost
Professor is evil
Shut up
To be continued
We can do this
Let's go to the restaurant
Let's go
Professor is chasing us
We have to go
Why don't we just go with him?
We can do it
I'm tired of running
I'm tired of being chased
I'm scared
Let's just play
Sit, rest, sleep
We can play like friends
Like friends?
I'm scared
Who threw trash in my room?
You're too much
Today, I will finish you
Get ready
Don't come in, I'm not sleepy
Get in
I'll go this way
Be careful, Gara
It's been a decade
It turns out that the science of the universe is not the same as the one in the world
Come here, Gara
Finish him, Gara
You're such a bad guy
Until when?
The number can't beat him
And if it can, he will disappear
And make the number feel
What are you doing here?
Professor, hurry up
We're doing nothing
Excuse me, Professor Purwa
I'm preparing the rehearsal for tomorrow
You're smiling
Professor Purwa
I also have to prepare the rehearsal for tomorrow
Me too, Professor
Wait
You're not teaching
What are you preparing?
I mean, I'm preparing the medicine
Who knows, someone got hurt after fighting inside
Someone got hurt?
What's this?
Adi
What are you doing here?
Answer me!
[The number can't beat him]
What's that?
Jip Jip Jip Jip Jip Jip
There's another guy
[The number can't beat him]
The girl is scared
I got it
[The number can't beat him]
It's just a ball monster
I thought it was a flood
Angkara
It turns out that you're afraid of me
It's really sad
I'm more afraid of you than of a girl
I'm going to school
Shut up!
[The number can't beat him]
Where are you?
It's raining
[The number can't beat him]
Help!
What are you?
You told me to go up there?
What are you doing?
I'm going to jump like this
Help!
[The number can't beat him]
[We can do it]
What are you doing?
If you see this door, I'll be mad
So, I want to pay you back
I know
So, you want me to open this door?
Okay, jump
I told you
[The number can't beat him]
Bicycle?
What do you want?
[The number can't beat him]
This bicycle is so weird
Maybe the army asked this bicycle to do something
Like that
What are you looking for?
[The number can't beat him]
So, you're looking for lollipop?
This is so weird
We already have our own lollipop
How many do you want?
One?
Why are you sleeping?
Why?
You want more?
Tell me
This much?
Four is enough?
Five?
This bicycle is so weird
[The number can't beat him]
Wait!
So, you want food too?
You've been gone for a while
[The number can't beat him]
Be careful
I'll send you my greetings
Tell the army, Nick and the others
Tell them
They have to go home safely
Bye, bicycle!
[The number can't beat him]
Where are you? I can find you
I've run so far
He can't catch me
I've told you so many times
Wherever you go
I can find you
So, you better not reject me
You're my student
So, you'll be a great sniper
A strong sniper
And you'll have a lot of followers
[The number can't beat him]
The army is coming
I'm scared
I'm scared too
You all have to be patient
Be patient
Wait
I heard a poem
Eat in front of the soldiers
If we're hungry
We better drink first
Oh, no
What about the army?
We've run out of drinks
Yes, the army
I'm so thirsty
I'm thirsty
There's no army in the desert
There's no army drink
Wait
I just remembered
We can chant the water of the phoenix
Which was taught by Prof. Titan
You still remember, right?
So, we're still close
That's it
What if I try?
What?
The water of the phoenix
The water of the phoenix is useless here
It's broken
Oh, no
Hey, listen
We're in the desert
Even though the water of the phoenix is powerful
But the water of the phoenix can't create water
The water of the phoenix can only move water
From the water source around us
If the water of the phoenix doesn't work
It means there's no water source around here
I'm so thirsty
What?
It's really cool
Where's the water?
I can't see it
What's wrong?
The army is taking one of the 12 soul stones
One of the soul stones?
What's a soul stone, Prof?
It's a part of the black magic
Black magic?
In the past
There was a sorcerer named Sergius
Sergius?
Dive in and around the chicken.
All you need to do is concentrate on the chicken.
[music]
He's not a normal human.
And his power is very sadistic.
Let's get out of here.
Is that all you got?
In the old times,
there was a evil sorcerer named Cerberus.
It turned out that Cerberus used a soul stone to protect his power.
And he divided his soul into 12 parts.
[music]
That's why he can't be defeated.
And every time someone tries to kill him,
his soul will be revived.
And that will bring him back to life.
The evil of Cerberus kept happening.
That's what made all the good sorcerers unite to try to defeat him.
[music]
And after the 12 soul stones were destroyed,
Cerberus was defeated.
[music]
There are two sets of soul stones in this world.
One of them was used by Cerberus.
The other was kept by Professor Aldebaran.
But without anyone's knowledge,
the Dark Lord managed to take the soul stone from Professor Aldebaran.
And he used the soul stone to protect his power.
Are you ready for me to enter the magical world to be the chosen one?
[music]
What's wrong, Yaya? Are you afraid of him?
No, I'm not willing to work with you.
[music]
Leon, all decisions are in your hands.
So you have to think carefully.
If you refuse me,
it's the same.
You will be separated from your family forever.
[music]
Leon, no.
Please don't.
Don't, Leon.
Maybe you've never heard of my prison.
So, there's nothing wrong with it.
I'm just a little afraid of you.
The fire prison is a prison surrounded by many people.
And the guards are very cruel.
If we make a little mistake,
we will be stabbed with a sharp sword.
Try to imagine that.
Think about it.
[music]
Wait.
[laughing]
Good, good.
[music]
No.
Don't.
Please don't.
Don't, Leon.
[music]
Sir.
What's wrong, sir?
My grandson...
has become...
a dark man.
[music]
If so,
we have to find a way out of here.
Leon.
Welcome to the palace.
Dafatang Juba.
Leon.
Now, you use it.
Why?
This juba indicates how deep your knowledge is.
If this juba turns black,
then,
your knowledge will be deeper.
Let's eat.
Dafatang, food.
[laughing]
You can finish it all.
Come on.
[music]
There's one thing you don't know, Leon.
That juba is the mirror of your heart.
Juba budi.
It means your heart is still clean.
The darker the juba is,
the darker and evil your heart is.
When the juba changes color to red,
that's when your heart changes to black and evil.
And at that time,
you're ready for me to enter the magic room
to be the chosen one.
[laughing]
So, where is the King of the Wild now?
We don't know yet.
We've tried to force Professor Angkara to tell us where Professor Aldebaran is.
But until now,
he's still keeping it a secret.
Wow.
So, Professor Angkara deliberately kept it a secret from us?
Yes, Alfa.
But don't worry.
We're still trying to investigate him and find out where Professor Aldebaran is.
Hmm.
I have a better idea.
What is it, Alfa?
Just leave it to us.
It's morning already.
Hey, wake up. It's morning.
Acting like an intel agent.
Eating two jellies at a time.
Where is that jelly?
Why isn't it here yet?
Oh, no. This is dangerous.
I have to call him again.
Why is he calling me?
Maybe he's not connected.
Test, test, one, two, three.
Test, test.
Check, check. Test, one, two, three.
Ontel?
Do you hear me?
Roger?
What's in the coffee, Ontel?
Oh, no.
I hope he doesn't wake up.
What should I do?
I can't even crawl.
I don't know why I'm in this situation.
It's not a jelly.
Hey, wake up.
It's morning already.
Intara, where are you?
Did you get the jellies?
There are fruits,
feeding the animals,
the stroller,
the blanket,
the fire,
the children,
and Ontel hasn't come yet.
Intara, we could die of hunger here.
Yes, Intara.
Intara, I'll join you.
I'm so weak, Intara.
What should I do?
Me too, Intara.
Kids, today we're going to learn...
how to turn ordinary water...
into grape juice.
Now, pay attention...
and listen to the mantra.
Javadi.
Good morning.
I'm the one who will lead you to teach.
Angkara.
I mean, Professor Angkara.
Please don't disturb my lesson, Professor.
You're so rude, Agni.
How dare you forbid me?
Have you forgotten who I am?
I'm the head of the school here.
Professor Angkara.
Agni, I didn't forbid you.
Get out of my way.
Now, kids.
Whoever succeeds in following my instructions...
will get a prize.
Come on.
Who wants to go first?
I want to talk.
Oh, it's you, Tommy.
The smart kid.
Come on.
Go ahead, Tommy.
Go ahead.
Tommy.
Now, follow my mantra.
Javadi Rajo.
Javadi Rajo?
Did I succeed, Professor?
Where's the prize?
Not yet, Tommy.
Because I have to prove it first.
Is this water...
really poisoned?
How?
The way is...
one of your classmates...
must drink this water.
Angkara. / Agni.
Please don't hurt my son.
If you disturb me again,
I'll have another lesson from you.
(The mantra is very powerful.)
(Whoever gets affected by this mantra...)
(will die.)
(We can do it.)
Come on.
Who wants to taste this water?
Please be my opponent.
Come on, kids.
Go ahead.
Professor, I'm an opponent.
So, you're Vega.
It seems like you're suitable to be my opponent.
Please go ahead.
Vega, go ahead.
Or I'll give you a punishment.
Professor Angkara, please.
Don't hurt my kids. / Hurry.
Vega, go ahead.
Don't, Vega.
Don't.
Vega.
Professor Angkara, don't hurt my kids.
Quiet.
Vega.
(The mantra is very powerful.)
(Whoever gets affected by this mantra...)
(will die.)
Guys.
Give them this water.
Yes, Professor.
If they're separated,
you'll get a reward.
Yes.
Yes, Professor.
Drink it.
Hurry.
Yes, Vega.
Drink it.
So, I'll get the reward.
Hurry.
Drink it.
Vega.
Drink it, Vega.
(The mantra is very powerful.)
(Whoever gets affected by this mantra...)
(will die.)
You're not funny.
Follow me.
Professor Angkara, wait.
Professor.
Vega.
Stand here and raise one of your legs.
Hurry.
Today,
I'll punish you.
Stand here and raise one of your legs until the afternoon.
You're not allowed to eat or drink.
How long will you run away from here?
Vega, wait.
Oh, my goodness.
It's so big, Vega.
Let's help Vega.
Let's go.
Don't you dare to help him.
If you dare to help him,
you'll be punished severely.
Guys, don't worry.
I'll teach him well.
Agni.
Teach him again.
-I'm sorry, Vega. -This is an order.
(The mantra is very powerful.)
Agni.
Hey, wait.
Let's go.
Guys.
You're hungry, right?
How about we try to find food,
drink, or anything...
so we won't die here?
Where are we going, Nick?
My body is so weak. I can't walk.
Yes, Nick.
At least, we try.
At least, we won't starve.
If we starve, we'll try.
I remember I read a book.
In the forest,
sometimes, there's a spring called...
oasis.
It means we still have hope.
Do you want to join us?
No.
-No. -No.
I can't stand it anymore, Nick.
-I'm so tired. -Alright, Nick.
I'll join you.
Instead of starving to death here.
I won't join you.
I can't stand it.
I'll try to find food.
Hey.
Wait.
You're just a kid.
Where are you going?
We're looking for water, soldier.
Yes, soldier.
Anything. Hamptons can eat.
No.
Don't.
Come here.
Go back.
This is a desert, bro.
Don't play in the desert.
It's dangerous.
There are many wild animals.
Many weird animals.
If you're eaten, it'll be a disaster.
Come here. Go back.
Be patient.
Soon, my bike...
will come here.
Bike again.
Dream.
How long do we have to wait?
Since yesterday, there's no bike, soldier.
Do you want us to starve to death here?
Soldier.
If you don't want to go,
if you don't want us to starve,
we have to fight to find food and drink.
Yes, soldier.
We don't want to die here.
We'd better die when we're looking for water...
than die here.
That's right.
Okay, let's go.
I'm with them.
But what about them?
I'm worried.
A rat.
There.
So, you've met your trial rat.
Trial rat?
What do you mean, sir?
This rat...
will help you learn mantra.
Because I'll teach you...
a lot of mantras.
Mantra?
What mantra, sir?
Look.
This mantra is very powerful.
It will make you scream.
Just like that rat.
Stop.
Now, do what I've done.
That rat's mantra.
Before this bell rings.
(The trial rat)
Sir, I have to torture this rat.
No. I don't want this rat to get hurt.
If you refuse, your brother will suffer.
And if you obey all his orders,
your brother will get happiness.
He will get food in prison.
All decisions are up to you.
Listen.
If you refuse,
your brother will be stabbed by a knife.
Guys.
We have to run.
Why?
Why, Feca?
There's a rat.
I'm here because I want to quit.
Lies.
You're lying.
You're definitely lying.
Are you sure...
you want to quit being a teacher here?
Say it.
Show your spirit, get ready to find your friends
Run, jump, and chase the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your might
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we will