This story is purely fictional. If there are similarities in names, characters/figures, and places in this show, it is merely a coincidence without any element of intentionality.
MDentertainment presents
🎵 "Show your spirit, get your friends ready" 🎵
🎵 "Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars" 🎵
🎵 "Be brave, don't give up" 🎵
🎵 "Chase your dreams and hopes" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, never stop" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, fight with all your heart" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, make yourself proud" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, let's dream" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, we can do it" 🎵
🎵 "We can do it!" 🎵
We're not done, Megantar
We still have to close the cave with a mantra
So that the spirit will not appear again forever
I only had a father when I was a kid
Now my father is gone
I'm alone
Melinta, you're not alone
We're still here, just us
You joined us to school
Now you're free
You're not a servant of anyone
Free?
I'm free!
I have to get that life fluid
I have to lose everything so I can live again
And remember, that life fluid is very rare
Only one person can get that very rare life fluid
No one can beat Raya
He's so beautiful
I'm not afraid of you
I'm so mad
He's so clingy
Just admit it, I'm going to make him lose
I have to win, I have to
What's wrong, Pegah?
I don't know
Guys, Pegah
You've been in the toilet for so long
I'm sorry, I met a ghost
A ghost?
That's scary
It's not scary anymore
But it's annoying
It's annoying, and it sings
It's on purpose, it's scaring the participants
So that they fail
Oh yeah, there were a few kids who gave up
And threw away the white flag
And then they were returned
That's why we have to be careful
And remember, we can't give up
Let's go
Ray, don't
Don't
Ray, did you hear the jury?
We can't eat this
If we eat it, we'll fail
No way
But I really want to
It looks good
I'm hungry
Ray, you're going to fail
I don't think so
Let's go
I'm hungry
I have to seduce them
So that they want to eat
If I do this, I'll be like a normal kid
This is good
Hi, do you want some?
Just eat it
It's really good
But they said you can't eat it
Who said that?
Just eat it
Just a little
I won't be caught by the jury
Come on, eat it
Ray, don't
I'm going to be caught
Hi
I'm Ray
The ice cream you saw is really good
It looks good
Just eat it
If I eat it later
I'm going to fail
Who said that?
I've tried it
You've run
Really? Just eat it
Come on, you'll regret it
I'm going to fail
[The judge is very nervous]
[The judges are very nervous]
Just eat it
I'm going to fail
What are you doing?
[The judges are very nervous]
What are you doing here?
You made me lose
So what?
I'm sorry
Listen, I'm a candidate for the winner
I'm going to get the life-saving potion
So, you're a candidate for the contestant too?
We're also a candidate for the winner
We're going to win against you
So, are you going to win against me?
Just give up
I'm going to win, I'm not giving up
Yes
But it's up to you
If you lose, don't cry
What are you doing?
We're doing our homework
Let's play
No, we don't want to play
We're doing our homework
Let's play
I'm not confident
You're the one who's not confident
Come on
I'm sorry
I'm going to call Vega
Let's do it
No
Just do it
Let's go
Why are you wasting our time?
Vega doesn't care about me
He cares about you
I'm sorry
I miss you, dad
I'm alone
I'm lonely, dad
A rat?
What should I do?
I'm getting more scared
I'm scared
Don't
Just a little
I can't
Just a little, don't be scared
I'm scared
Alfa, wake up!
What did I do?
You bit my hand
Oh my god
I'm sorry, Rey
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay
It hurts a little
Don't be scared, Rey
I can eat this
We're here to win the match
For Alfa
I feel sorry for Rey and Vega
Because of me
They're in trouble
Let's go
To save the life
Rita
Don't
Don't touch me
What's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
Come here, I'll help you
No, I'm okay
Let's go
There are many candies in this park
Your task is to collect 100 candies in 30 minutes
In a bucket
The one who succeed will be sent to the next round
The one who fail will be eliminated and sent home
Get ready
Start
Go, go, go
Remember
The candies you collect
Can't be eaten
If you eat it, you'll be sent home
The candies that fall from the bucket
Will not be counted
I got it
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with all your might
Make your dream come true
Go, go, go
Let's dream
We can do it
Go, go, go
Show your spirit
Get ready to find your friends
Go, Raya
Why are you so slow? I'm first
You're the first one
Raya
Watch out, Raya
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with all your might
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
4, 5 too
4, 5
Fight with all your might
Go, go, go
Look at this, I got 20 candies
You're so slow, you're so arrogant
Never stop
I got it, let's go
Let's look for more
Go, go, go
Fight with all your might
Achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go
Raya
Oops, sorry
I did it on purpose
Watch out
Raya
Miss, miss
Watch out
You're so slow
Enough
It's better to collect your candies
You're cheating
How come?
Rayga
I just remembered
Maybe we can find the jury
If the candies are not there
Does that mean
It's because of Raya
Yay, Raya
Rayga, Ray
Calm down
There's still time
To exchange
What? There's no time
There's only 5 minutes left
Where are you going?
Rayga and I will be executed
No, not him
If we lose because of him
I won't forgive him
Where's your camera?
Where's my camera?
Here it is
Let me try
It's not broken
There's two
Try again
Here
We're not finished yet
Let's try again
Try again
You win
Yes
Friends forever
Yeah
I think they're the heaviest
I have to beat them
And win their trust
Because that's the only way I can live again
You lose
You win
Hello
Alpha
I'm coming
Hello, I'm coming
Where are you?
I'm coming
I'm coming to meet my friend
Why are you calling me?
I'm a handsome guy
If you call me again
I'll make you a boy
I'm coming
Okay, where are you?
I want to meet you
I'm looking for medicine
With Vega
Alpha is sick
They're looking for medicine
Why are you not invited?
I'm not invited
What is that?
A new mantra?
I don't know
That means I don't know
That's a fairy
I'd rather talk to pretty people
Than talk to ugly people
I'm coming
Hello, Pelita
You still remember me, right?
I'm the handsome guy, Alpha's friend
Yes, I still remember
You don't want to accept my handshake?
I'm sorry, I can't
Why?
You're not polite
Leave me alone, I want to be alone
Because I'm ugly
You don't want to shake my hand?
You're arrogant
No, I'm not
I'm not arrogant
I still have self-worth as a cat
I feel like I'm being stepped on by you
You have to shake my hand
No, you have to leave
Leave, I'm not arrogant
I'll force you
I'm sorry, I can't
Popo!
No one can know about this
If they find out, I'll be expelled from school
Pelita!
We can do this!
Thank you, Popo
I'm sorry, Popo
I've been hiding you here
I'm sorry, I'm late
What's that?
It's a key
How can you do this?
This is the key
No, there's another attack
We have to report this to the professor
Okay
This is weird
I feel like the weather is changing
A few hours ago, the temperature was 30 degrees
Now it's 17 degrees
Yes, you're right
How can this school be attacked again?
I don't feel any negative energy from this
I feel like it's an attack
What is this, Professor?
This is a special power
that one of the students in this school has
Who is he?
He's a student of Professor Mokyam
I don't know
But we have to find him
If this power is not controlled, it can be dangerous
Now I'm wearing gloves
If my friends touch me
I'll be in trouble
Dita!
Dita, come here
No, I don't want to
You're wearing gloves
But I don't want to
He's so rude
He's just like his friends, Alfa, Vega, and Ray
They're both rude
Don't call them Alfa, Vega, and Ray
They're good friends
Really?
The best friends in the world?
I'm the best
Help!
What's going on?
He's a monster!
What are you doing?
I'm not a professor
I don't know what's going on
He's lying!
I saw him with my own eyes
Throw him out of the school!
Or just kick him out!
I'm not wrong
Don't kick me out of the school
Because I don't have anyone else
He's a monster!
Don't be close to him!
Don't kick him out of the school!
Throw him out!
Maybe Tommy was right
I can't be here
Because I can hurt people who are innocent
Like Popo
Nurita!
I didn't mean to
Now you have to walk through that bridge
You have to use your own power
No magic
No flying
Don't forget, you have to be careful
Because if you fall, you can be carried by the smoke
I'm sorry
If I can fly, I will be number one.
But I can't. I can't let other kids fall.
But, the camera is for photography.
Then, what is this cover for?
Let's try it.
I have to win. I can't lose.
That's the sound of the wind.
Apparently, this thing can hear people's heart.
Later, when it passes, I will send Go Vega, Ava, and Ray.
Let them fall and then bring smoke.
Just watch. I will make them lose.
Wait, friends. Do you know how to use it?
I know. It can hear people's heart.
I heard Raya was trying to attack us.
Are you serious?
We have to be careful. Raya is behind us.
Okay.
[Scream]
I can't fall. If I fall, I will fail.
What should I do? I can't fly. If I fly, I will fail.
Friends, let's just leave him.
Let's just throw him.
But, poor Vega. What if he really falls?
Poor him. He's already a ghost.
He's gone, Alfa. It's useless to help him.
Yes, if he falls, he won't die again.
But we can't just stay still. We have to help him.
Let's go.
No, Vega. We have to help him.
Wait here. I won't be long.
Alfa. / Raya.
Come on, Raya. Hold my hand.
You are my brother.
Yes, we are rivals.
That's fair.
Come on, hold my hand.
Thank you, Alfa. If you don't help me, I will fail.
You're welcome, Raya.
Alfa, what's wrong?
Alfa.
It's because of you, Raya.
What should we do?
In the next five minutes, you have to arrive at the next destination.
The one who arrives late will be sent back to the flight attendant.
What should we do?
Oh my God.
So, this is what the girl named Pelita did?
I've heard a power that changes everything into ice.
Freezing.
Even a small child can't handle it.
And make this school freeze.
Ice.
And she can freeze herself.
I can speed up. Dangerous.
You three can continue to the next flight.
Yes.
Thank you, Ray, for helping me.
Now we're in the first flight.
And there's one more flight left that we have to pass.
I want to tell Pelita that we're on a adventure today.
Here.
Eh, the light is on.
Maybe Pelita is calling me again.
What happened?
Pelita.
Pelita, are you calling me?
Answer me, Pelita.
Answer me.
[Crying]
My friend.
My friend, let's go.
Why are you wasting time with him?
If my brother saw my hand like this,
he would be afraid to be friends with me.
We can't give up.
Ray has already fallen.
So we have to hold on.
All of this is because of one thing.
My strength is normal.
Sir.
Sir, help me.
[Screaming]
Where did you come from, Angkara?
Why can't you come back to this world?
All of this is because of Ullah Aldebaran.
He always blocks me.
And all my plans failed because of him, sir.
If so, I have to surrender.
But sir, your strength hasn't recovered yet.
You won't be able to fight Aldebaran.
But now I have a great weapon that can defeat Aldebaran.
And I will get my chosen child.
[Laughter]
Nede, why can't you answer?
Maybe he's playing with his friends.
It's possible.
Okay, I'll tell him later.
It's better if we continue our journey.
Okay, let's go.
Welcome back, children.
I wish you all the best.
Because you have passed the first gate,
which is the gate of dreams.
This second gate is called the gate of patience.
As the name implies,
in this gate you will be tested for your patience.
In this gate, you can't be angry,
can't be selfish,
and can't force your own will.
Do you understand?
That's right, this is the canteen.
Now you can eat first.
Yes, yes, I didn't think we could eat.
Yes, yes, yes.
Surely the food is better than the first room.
That's right.
Yes, there must be a grill.
Where is the food?
Wow.
Congratulations.
This must be delicious food.
Food.
Let's open it.
One, two, three.
Ta-da.
Wow, the food is like this.
The food is like this.
It's really delicious.
Vegetables.
Because I don't like vegetables.
I want to eat.
Me too.
I really want to eat vegetables.
I'm not a goat, I eat vegetables.
Rih.
As I said earlier.
This place is to test and practice patience.
You have to finish the vegetables and you can't be angry.
If you are angry or give up, you will return to the first flight.
And if you finish eating, you are considered to have fallen and returned to the first flight.
Oh my God.
We can't give up.
Rih has already fallen.
So we have to hold on.
Yes, we have to be patient.
Even though I don't like tomatoes, but I have to hold on.
I have to eat this tomato.
As long as I have the nature of a snake in my body, I want to eat meat.
Especially this.
We have to be patient, Fah.
You have to control your emotions.
Because we have to go through all this.
Yes, Vega.
There is no other way.
Only the fire of the firefly can warm this room.
I emphasize once again.
If the power owned by this snake is very dangerous.
It can endanger the magic school and students.
And the temperature in the room is already below 20 degrees, Professor.
This is dangerous.
Let's check the children.
You concentrate and read body warming mantras.
So that your condition remains stable.
Oh my God.
They must be cold and faint.
It's better to lift them up with a pole.
It's broken.
Why is the magic useless?
Magic can't work.
Because the air here is too cold.
Now, how can we save them?
We lift them one by one.
It's bad, Professor.
Jack and Hit are weakening.
Mike too.
This child too, Professor.
We have to hurry.
If we are late, these children can die.
Wow.
Ray, you're out too?
Yes.
I don't want to eat vegetables.
Don't want to eat vegetables?
Vegetables are good for your health.
Is it because of your vegetables?
It's not good.
Ray.
How about Alfa?
Alfa has been in a coma twice.
It's still that long?
It's better if you're exciting, Dep.
I'm sure I win.
This is called winning in a battle.
I'm excited.
What if we become friends?
But, are you afraid of me?
I have a strange power.
I can make everyone freeze.
Now the school is frozen.
But who did it, Professor?
The one who did it is Prita.
Prita?