To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Thank you.
This firecracker is really useful.
But we can't continue like this, Professor.
We have to find the sorcerer
and stop him before he freezes this school.
I want to have a strange power.
I can make everyone freeze.
Since we're friends,
I'll tell you my secret.
I also have a strange power.
I can't freeze.
Alva is safe,
even though his face is a little wounded.
The bad news is,
the Dark Lord has taken the news away.
We give time until tomorrow morning.
If our Kris doesn't come back,
and our servants are no longer normal,
we will attack the sorcerer school.
And your teacher,
your teacher will not be able to be able to be a normal person.
Your teacher will not come back.
How is this possible?
We can't give Kris the fire.
If we give Kris the fire,
the children can die of cold.
[The Dark Lord has taken the news away]
Plita must be lonely.
Poor Plita.
I can't leave Plita alone.
I have to help Plita.
[The Dark Lord has taken the news away]
We have to help them.
I'm worried they will be defeated.
But I'm sure that Professor Purwa can handle it.
Because he has a high level of knowledge.
So, Professor Purwa can take care of himself.
We have no other choice, Prof.
Whether we want to or not, we have to fight them.
This is all for the sake of the children and the school.
[The Dark Lord has taken the news away]
Oh no, Professor Purwa has been kidnapped.
What about Plita? Who will look for her?
[The Dark Lord has taken the news away]
It's safe. We can open it.
Oh no, it's you guys.
You scared me.
You're so lucky. You didn't ask us to come.
We can't sleep either.
I'm worried about Plita.
I'm worried about her too.
Poor her. She must be lonely.
Let's go find Plita.
We have to take responsibility.
We're the ones who brought her here.
Yes, that's right.
Okay.
It's so cold. My hands are freezing.
It's cold.
Alva, try to find her using the telescope.
Where is she now?
There she is.
She's finally taken to the train.
Where are we going to take her?
But how?
She's frozen again.
We have to help her.
We can't give up.
Okay, let's go.
I can't do this anymore.
It's so cold.
Vega!
What do we do?
I can't do this anymore.
Rih!
What do we do?
Rih, help me.
Don't be a coward, Rih.
Rih!
What do we do?
Help me.
Rih!
"The most dangerous place in Indonesia"
They think I'm an ordinary person.
Where are you going, sir?
Eka, Tri, Cato. Let me face him.
"The most dangerous place in Indonesia"
Kara, nice to meet you again, Purwoh.
You've seen it yourself
The proof is not only the ice in the school's school yard
And that is a very clear proof
And all of this is a fabrication from him
Along with all the lies in the magic school
He's lying!
We didn't do that!
We didn't steal the firecrackers!
He's a traitor!
He's the one who did all of this!
What else can you prove, Purwa?
Everything is clear
The Satria Chatur has seen for himself
How stupid he is now
And you have no use for shouting like this now
You're done for, Garap
You're done for!
"The most dangerous place in Indonesia"
Where are my phone and the car?
Where are they?
Why did I get left behind?
Alva!
Vega!
Why did I get left behind?
This hole!
This hole is the only thing I want!
I want to see Alva and Vega
Where are they?
"The most dangerous place in Indonesia"
Alva!
Vega!
So, you guys helped us
Thank you
You're so kind
You're welcome
You're our friend, Vega
Vega, where's Ray?
Why isn't he here?
Where is he?
We helped you
Why did you guys do that?
I feel sorry for Ray
I feel sorry for him
I know
We also had to help you, Alva
We also helped you because we had to, Alva
If it wasn't for the girl who asked for it
We wouldn't have helped the guy
Right, girls?
That's right!
Where are they?
We have to find Ray
What do we do?
Hi!
"The most dangerous place in Indonesia"
Hi, Alva! Vega!
Hi, Angsa!
I'm so lucky
I was in a relationship with a girl
If it wasn't for her, I would have been a bad person
How did you know we're here?
Rayna
Ray...
Rayna!
How did you know we're here?
What are you doing here?
How do you know?
Because of this
Thank you
We're sorry for the school
Because the weather is so extreme
We have to help her
We have to find her
She's a bad person
Girls!
Yippie!
Lotion!
Cold water!
You'll use this
What's this for?
The lotion will help you stay cool
So you can stay strong in the snow
Wow! That's so cool!
Thank you!
You're welcome, Vega!
Let's go!
Where is your friend?
Wait, I'll look for her
Ray, where are you?
There she is!
She's not here
I'm sure she's not here
Her name is...
The Black Mountain
Do you know where it is?
I know where it is
How can we get there?
We'll take you there
That's so cool!
Girls!
We're in the Yippie!
You guys go up now
That's so cool!
Yes
Girls!
Pelita
You have to be able to keep your emotions
You can't be afraid
And you can't care about others
If you care
You'll be disappointed
And you'll be hurt
I'm sure everything will be better
It's so fun to ride a kite
Yes, it's so different from a lollipop
By the way, where did you get this kite?
I was going to the hill
I thought if I don't have a boyfriend
I don't like men
So I got this kite
Where did you get it?
I got it from them
It's so fun!
This is so fun!
What's that?
Help!
Yippie!
It's not over yet
I'm going to ride a kite
I followed you to the hill
I thought if I don't have a boyfriend
I don't like men
That's so funny
I'm so funny
You're so smart
It's fun
To be continued...
Have all the kids eaten?
Yes, sir
Looks like professor Andebar is stressed
Because he's thinking about the other soldiers
And I have to keep Ray, Vega, and Alva safe
Megantara, call Agni and Yasmin
We have to get out of here
Because soon, the elves will come
Yes, sir
Andebaran!
Get out!
Get out, all of you!
Give them a fire crisis
I'll count to ten
If you don't give them a fire crisis
We'll attack
They're seriously attacking us
We have to fight
If not, our school will be destroyed
That's right, professor
And the students will be the victims
Listen up
We're peacekeepers
We don't want a war
But we won't stay quiet
If there's a side that's threatening us
We'll use our abilities
To protect the kids
Let's go
We'll unite
To protect this school and the kids
For the sake of all of us
Get out, boss! Our squad is under attack!
What? Attack?
What are you doing?
I'll kill you!
I'll take your crisis!
Where's the crisis?
We've decided to fight
And defend the crisis
Attack!
We won't stop until we get that crisis
As long as we're united
United?
What's wrong, Aldibaran?
Are you afraid of losing?
You don't know how I use my power
You're all cowards
Who do you think we're losing to?
Professor Aldibaran's abilities
Are far superior to yours
I'm not happy with this
You see, everything's frozen
We can't be active
And we need the crisis
To handle the kids
If they can make it
Okay
I'll go
We've released your teacher
Thank you
Now, let's find that kid named Plita
Yasmin, take care of the kids
Don't let them leave the building
Before it gets cold again
Yes, Professor
Damn it, they're all united
We can't let this happen
I have to fight them
Thank you, Miss Sangsah
You're so kind to help us
You're welcome, Plita
Yippie, yippie, yay!
Rega, if you need anything
Just call us
We'll help you
Girls
Thank you, bye
Bye
Bye, Plita
I'm so tired
I'm so tired of being a girl
Plita, I want to fight you
Don't touch me
What's wrong? Are you mad?
I'm sorry, we left you yesterday
But, we're back now
Yes
You should go back to school with us
Do you want to?
Because everyone is asking about you
Yes, we're all so mad at you
Plita, we'll play together again
I promise I won't leave you
I promise
You have to forget them all
Who's that? Why is he bringing Plita here?
Plita, you have to make a decision
Do you want to stay here with me
Or do you want to go with them?
I'm going to go with them
Plita, don't you forget?
We promised to be together
Plita, you have to focus on your recovery
Don't go with him
You have to kick him out of this school
We have to go with him
Let's go
Why are you wasting time with him?
You guys go from here
Why are you kicking us out?
I want to stay here
You guys go
I want to take you home
Don't you dare to leave
Plita, your hand
Come here, I want to see
Don't touch me
Plita, are you okay?
Plita, you're so brave
Do you know?
Only bad people dare to attack their own friends
Ali is a bad person
We all came here because he's a bad person
He's not a bad person
He just can't control himself
He's like my brother
So, I want to protect him
Plita, let's go home
Let's go back to school
Plita
If you want to go with them
You have to kick him out
Easter egg, what should we do?
Easter egg, take them away from here
Plita, don't
It's a monster
You have to think for yourself
And you have to let go of your love for others
Because that feeling can destroy you
We can do it
Let go of me
What you're doing now is right
You have to train yourself so you can be cured
Goodbye, Vega, Alva, and Kare
A year later
Why are we still here?
We came all the way here just to be kicked out by Plita
Let's go home
Yes, let's go home
Vega
Stay here, I want to meet Plita
Stop it!
Hold your emotions
I can heal Agni
This is all a misunderstanding
We should be united
One
It hurts!
I'm tired, I want to go home
Yeah, let's go home
Where are you going?
Let me go!
I want to take Plita home
Vega, don't be like that
That monster has hit you
What if we go there again?
Let's go home
I want to try
I'm sure Plita is a good girl
She has a kind heart
I want to talk to her
What's the relationship between you two?
I'm sure Plita will be affected
I agree with you
Best friend forever
Havancur
Plita, let's go
Plita, wait for me
(Groaning)
(Banging)
Serba !
(Groaning)
Hey !
You should run !
(Groaning)
Where are we ?
We're here !
Do you want to play ?
Brita !
Come here !
Let's play !
Come on Brita !
Or else,
we'll go the wrong way !
(Bang)
Come here !
Turntable !
Yes !
Number 6 !
6 !
I'll go again !
Turntable !
Yes !
4 !
Number 10 !
Now, you Brita !
Yes !
5 !
Yeah !
Are you happy playing this ?
I'm so happy !
Especially,
if you play this at school, Brita !
It'll be more fun !
There are many kids playing this !
Yes !
That's why,
you should go home, Brita !
We can play together again !
You should go home, Brita !
Please !
We've promised
to be friends !
Besides,
you're not lonely here, right ?
You should go home !
Please !
We'll play together again !
Okay, let's go !
So, you want to go with Vega ?
Yes,
it's all up to you.
But, you should remember my words.
You shouldn't use your feelings.
Because, feelings
will only hurt you.
And you shouldn't care about others.
Because, caring about others
will only make you sad.
I'm sorry, Sir.
But, I can't leave Vega.
It's okay.
You should use this.
If you need my help,
you should use this.
I'll come to help you,
wherever you are.
Thank you, Sir.
Audrey !
Let me go !
I beg you !
I'm sorry !
Audrey !
Are you okay ?
I'm okay, Sir.
I just got hit by a car.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Sir,
now, we're going home together.
Wow, that's great !
But, don't touch me.
You'll get cold.
Yes,
when we get there,
we'll meet the Eid Professor.
I'm sure,
the Eid Professor
can cure you.
Let's go home.
Let's go !
I'm so happy to be with you.
Me too.
Especially me.
Sir,
come here.
Can I ask for a favor ?
Sure, what is it ?
Can you find the Eid Professor ?
Later.
You tell him,
if we're together,
we'll be able to solve the Eid problem.
If we're together,
we'll be on the way home.
Okay.
Thank you, Sir.
You're welcome, Alpha.
There's a message from Alpha.
Alpha is on the way home with Felita.
Megantam,
why is Alpha outside the school ?
Actually,
I wanted to tell you this morning.
But,
the Eid Professor hasn't come yet.
So,
I forgot.
Tell Alpha,
I'll be waiting for him,
in this bamboo forest.
Okay, Sir.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Sir.
We should rest here,
while waiting for Alpha and Felita.
Megantam,
next time,
you have to tell me everything.
Okay.
Cook it in the stove,
so it won't get dirty.
I'll always report to the Professor.
[Megantam, thank you for coming!]
[Alpha, thank you for coming!]
You must have poisoned the food,
right?
No, I didn't put anything in the food.
Don't be reckless.
Professor Agni won't do that.
Shut up!
Wait!
Be patient.
Let me help you cure him.
No need.
Let me do it.
You want revenge, right?
Hey,
go to Gandaria,
buy a light sharp sword.
Ksatria,
remember,
slander is more cruel than murder.
You can see for yourself,
that this is a statement,
not a slander.
Alright,
let's go our separate ways.
We will use our own way.
Wait,
Professor!
Just leave it.
No need to be restrained.
For what?
We should all be united,
not separated like this.
I don't agree.
Well,
they are the ones who are looking for trouble.
Where is he?
He's so thin.
He might attack us.
You guys go first.
Alright.
Let's go, Prita.
Alva?
Oh no,
where is Alva?
the ghost is gone.
Alva is attacked.
What should we do?
Prita,
you stay here.
I will look for Rey and Alva.
Alva!
Rey!
Where are you guys?
Alva!
Rey!
Where are you guys?
Who are you?
Don't move.
Don't make any noise.
Where is the cafe?
It's been a long time.
[Ghost]
Let me go!
Help!
Shut up!
If you call them,
they will come to your house.
Maybe this is a trap.
Vega,
Rey,
and Alva
work with these people.
Why are they with me?
I trust Vega.
Vega!
[Ghost]
Finally, you called them.
Help, Sir!
Pelita,
you have to gather your power
and attack them.
Now, throw your sick people.
Hurry!
She is so brave.
She made Vega become like this.
I told you,
she is a monster.
That's why we have to stay away from her.
[Ghost]
Go! Go! Go!
Fight with the power of your heart
Make yourself proud
Go! Go! Go!
Let's dream
We will win