To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Your power is not comparable to mine
You come with me
Let me go, let me go, you're evil
The power of the star girl is at night
You can burn with her light
So?
We wait until tomorrow
Tomorrow morning, I will get the power of the star girl
So it's true, the fallen star girl is the one who will be the one to destroy the world
The fallen star girl is in our school
Yes, professor
I asked her to stay at the school tower
But because of professor Angkara, she was kidnapped
We have to go there immediately
Before Angkara takes the power of the fallen star girl
Yes, professor
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Now, it's time for me to take the power of the fallen star girl
I will destroy you
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Who are you?
Come out
That person is...
The star girl, our teacher
Come out
It turns out that he is the one behind all this
He wants to take Selena's heart
I have to stop him
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Wake up! You have to get out of here!
Star fairy!
Star fairy, wake up!
You have to get out of here!
Star fairy!
Star fairy! Wake up!
Alva, I'm with your mother. I'm so scared.
But we have to get out of here.
Alva, my hair! My hair is cut!
Yes, your eyelashes are also squeezed.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Wait a minute.
In a moment you will see my father's power.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
I have to get rid of her eyelashes and hair now.
After that, I will become a star.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Alva, you have to protect him.
Don't let him drink the eye drops that have been mixed with my hair.
Because it can cure all his diseases.
And he will be stronger.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
I'm going to cut your eyelashes.
It's not as easy as you think.
The basics can be disturbing.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Give me the eye drops.
I've cut your eyelashes.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Alva!
He's drinking my eye drops!
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Alva!
What are you attacking?
I'm stronger now.
Your eye drops will never be able to hurt me.
Alva, it's broken!
Now, it's time for me to take the star girl's heart.
With my power, my power will never be limited.
It's broken!
[The power of the fallen star girl]
I have to find a way to differentiate the real and cloned Rion.
I'm sorry, Zai!
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Megantara.
Remember, Ankara will never appear in the mirror.
Once we see the real Ankara, we attack together.
Watch this!
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Lightning!
Megantara, let's go.
Let's find Ava.
Let's go.
Please, please, Daniel.
I want to go back to the past.
I'm not ready to be a great leader in Jogja.
Zai!
[The power of the fallen star girl]
What's going on?
My body is getting thinner.
Ava!
Where are you, Ava?
We have to get out of here.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Professor, the army is here.
Ava, Ava!
You met the fallen star girl.
Yes, Professor.
Let's get out of here.
Wait, soldier.
We have to save Jebi.
Because the dark energy is getting stronger.
She has managed to cut off Selena's hair.
And she has managed to suck out Selena's tears.
It's okay.
Let's get Selena out of here.
Let's go.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
We're here.
Thank you, Alva.
You fulfilled your promise.
So I can go back to space.
And thank you, Megantara, for your help.
Goodbye, Alva.
Don't forget to send my regards to Vega, Ray, and Plita.
I'm so happy to be able to meet you.
Yes, goodbye.
I'll be back soon.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Let's go back to school.
Alva, Professor Ade is hurt.
Hurry, take her to the school.
Megantara.
I'll face this darkness.
Hurry, Alva.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
I'm sorry, everyone.
It's not good, Sir.
The army is coming.
They're so strong.
Alva, watch out.
He's running away.
Don't let him get away.
Professor Ade.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Watch out.
It's useless to fight him.
You'll never win.
Alva, let's go.
We're almost there.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Good.
Let's go, Vega.
Ray, Melita.
Keep attacking.
Megantara.
Alva.
Keep attacking.
What do we do now, Sir?
What do we do?
Don't be fooled.
There's a very important task for you.
What task, Megantara?
Let's go.
Save the girl.
[The power of the fallen star girl]
Professor Ade.
Professor Ade is bleeding.
What happened to him?
He has a bad face.
Yes.
He was attacked.
We have to take him to the clinic.
Hurry.
Let's check with Dr. Pertiwi.
Come on.
Hurry.
Professor Ade.
Let's go to Dr. Pertiwi's clinic.
Hurry.
Let's go.
Angga.
It's like the voice of the God.
I'm coming, Sir.
Hang in there.
It's bad.
It seems like Professor Ade is too weak to walk.
Vega, prepare the pole.
Okay, Sir.
Ready.
Fire.
Angga.
Prepare the food.
What happened, Sir?
The mutant has returned to its original form.
But I managed to locate Aldebaran.
I'm sure,
he will die soon.
I have a task for you.
Yes, Sir.
I will do it.
Professor Aldebaran.
What happened?
We can do it.
S5.
Young coconut.
Let's go.
What is that light?
It's bright.
What kind of light is that?
OMG.
Amazing.
This is mushroom centurion tea.
It's a very rare mushroom.
It can cure all diseases.
All diseases.
But why is it here?
Isn't it in the cradle?
Let's go.
It's moving.
Hey, mushroom centurion.
Don't go.
Don't go with me.
It's gone.
OMG.
Oh, no.
Hello, Ibu.
I have a request for you.
And you have to do as I command.
[Music]
Damn it.
The data.
Hurry up.
Okay.
[Music]
Sir, we need help.
Let's go.
Don't go.
Professor Aldebaran.
What happened?
Professor Aldebaran was attacked.
Professor Aldebaran is very well-educated.
And if someone can beat him,
it means that person is very well-educated.
We'll talk about it later.
Now we have to treat Professor Aldebaran.
Let's go to the cradle.
[Music]
Where is the cradle?
It's not here.
You even use vegetables.
When you're in need,
you use the cradle.
Okay, let me find it.
Cradle,
where did you get it?
OMG.
Professor Aldebaran is old.
Why?
Don't ask too much.
Immediately perform a sedative on Professor Aldebaran.
[Music]
Oh my God.
This wound is very bad.
Very, very bad.
And must be treated immediately with energy transfer.
Pedang Kramat Purnama.
Pedang Kramat Purnama?
So, where is Pedang Kramat Purnama?
Alva,
Pedang Kramat Purnama is in an old castle in the forest at the end of the school.
[Music]
Ask Alva to take the Pedang Pusaka Purnama.
Remember,
only Alva.
No teacher can accompany her.
Do you understand?
[Music]
Alva,
you better look for it,
so that Professor Aldebaran can be treated immediately.
Alva,
the Purnama castle is a very dangerous place.
There are many traps there.
Let me go.
Don, don't go.
You teachers must stay here,
meditate.
Okay.
If so,
I'm the one who needs to go.
Don't, Megantara.
You must stay here.
Okay,
I'm not going.
Okay, we too.
Alva,
Professor Aldebaran.
Prof,
you don't go, Alva.
But, Prof,
No, sir.
You don't have to go.
It's dangerous for you.
Megantara,
if so, let me teach you to ask for help.
No, Prof.
I already know,
when I was kidnapped.
Okay,
so,
we're going just the two of us.
There's me.
[Music]
Where are you?
Here.
Let's go.
[Music]
Guys,
we have to hurry.
Yes.
Hurry.
[Music]
That's the castle.
Come on, guys.
Let's go there.
Let's go.
[Music]
Why are those kids coming?
Why not Alva?
Alva should be there.
The Fatak Centurion.
[Music]
What should I do,
Duran?
Stop those kids.
Don't let them in the castle.
[Music]
What are you doing?
Stop them.
That's...
You haven't read the book, right?
That's Centaurus.
Yes, this is Centaurus.
He's our hero.
Watch out.
[Music]
Come here.
He's going to attack us.
[Music]
Help me, Turi.
Hurry.
[Music]
I'm on the police car.
Why are you attacking him with a spell?
What spell are you using?
What do you know?
I don't know.
What spell are you using?
[Music]
Help me.
What should we do?
Yes, what should we do?
Everyone is in trouble.
Don't laugh.
Yes.
Come here.
[Music]
Help me.
My body hurts.
[Music]
Ray, Tuli.
You guys, watch him.
I'm going to look for him in the book.
How to find him?
But, how?
Okay.
Hold me, Tuli.
[Music]
Come on, Tuli.
Attack him.
Come here.
Come on, Tuli.
Come on.
What should we do?
[Music]
Where is he?
I don't know.
[Music]
Where is he?
I don't know.
[Music]
Help me, Tuli.
Hurry up.
Oh, no.
Ray, I'm going to die.
You're going to die.
Be patient.
[Music]
Ray.
Here he is.
Yes, I know how to get rid of him.
[Music]
I'm going to kill you.
Yes.
Centaurus, come here.
Attack me if you dare.
Come here.
Come here, Centaurus.
Come here, fight me.
[Music]
Take this, Centaurus.
Yes, it's delicious.
Hurray.
Ouch.
It hurts.
[Music]
Come here.
Ouch.
It hurts.
[Music]
Yes, I did it.
You're a fool, Centaurus.
[Music]
I'm going to make the children regret it.
You're done, Centaurus.
[Music]
Destroy them all.
Come on, hurry up.
Yes.
We have to find the sword.
So that the professor can recover quickly.
Yes.
[Music]
What is this castle?
The forest is in a mess.
There must be something.
This is hard.
This.
[Music]
Look, now you guys distract him.
So I can read the book.
How do we defeat him?
So we don't become a burden.
Shh.
They think we're worms.
I don't know.
Don't talk too much.
You don't want the professor to recover together, do you?
Yes.
[Music]
Eat this.
My meat is the best.
[Music]
What is this?
Take it.
[Music]
Where is it?
[Screaming]
[Music]
Yes, I did it.
Come here.
[Music]
Hurry up, I want to take a picture.
Okay.
Come on.
[Music]
[Screaming]
Men are always like this.
There's no other way.
[Music]
You're right.
There's no other way.
Even if the professor is with me.
[Music]
Come on.
Come here.
[Music]
[Screaming]
Fire.
[Music]
Yes.
It worked.
[Music]
All my monsters are destroyed.
The kids are too smart.
I have to make a stronger monster.
[Music]
[Screaming]
Get the fire.
[Music]
I am...
...Burned.
[Music]
Destroy them all.
Don't let them enter the castle.
[Music]
I am...
...Burned.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Maybe...
...they'll all be destroyed.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Rey, wake up.
Rey.
What should I do?
[Music]
Rey, wake up.
Monsters.
What happened to my monsters?
[Music]
Hit them.
[Grunts]
[Music]
[Roar]
[Grunts]
[Music]
I am...
...Dead.
[Music]
Thank you.
[Roar]
[Music]
I am...
I can't run anymore.
I need help.
[Music]
I am being ordered.
Help.
[Music]
Professor Ragni.
Hold on.
You have to be strong.
[Music]
Come on.
We have to hold on.
Stay together.
Don't let the energy transfer be released.
Because it can be a threat to the monster.
[Music]
Good evening, Professor.
Good evening, Felita.
I asked Koki...
...to cook for the professor.
Koki said this food...
...can make the professor's power come back.
But how do we eat it, Felita?
I can't let go of this.
Okay.
I'll help you, Professor.
[Music]
Come on, Felita.
Give it a big bite.
[Groan]
Again.
Felita.
Where is Professor Atomi?
I'm worried.
I'm walking around.
I don't know what to do.
Where is he?
They failed.
I have to help them.
[Music]
Professor has changed.
He's huge.
[Music]
This is...
...aquafl...
Calm down.
I want to feed you.
Let me.
[Music]
I'm Megantara.
Yes.
Megantara.
I need your help.
Can I?
[Music]
Let me go.
Vega.
Vega, wake up.
[Music]
Wake up, Vega.
Vega.
Where is Rey and Tole?
[Music]
Rey and Tole are there.
Rey, Tole.
[Music]
Wake up, Rey.
Rey, Tole.
Wake up.
Rey, wake up.
[Music]
Alpha.
I'm here.
Go home.
[Music]
Help me.
Hurry up.
Why are we going up?
Seriously, Alpha.
You have to go home.
No.
I don't want you to be a victim.
I don't want to leave you.
[Music]
Naga.
Take them to school.
[Music]
Good, Alpha.
You're getting closer.
[Music]
Finally.
The special kid is here.
You're showing your true power, Alpha.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Roar]
What's that?
[Music]
[Roar]
Why is he showing us the way?
Vega said,
The monster is dangerous.
But I don't think it's dangerous.
Or maybe it's a trap.
Let's try.
[Music]
[Roar]
Why am I brought here?
I am...
Varga.
I...
Want to be remembered, Alpha.
Remembered?
Yes.
Remembered, Alpha.
[Music]
Let me go.
Where are you taking me?
[Music]
Let me go.
I...
Want to be remembered, Alpha.
What does he want?
Why is he holding me?
Monster!
[Laughter]
Yesterday, I've found the power of the fallen star.
And now,
I will find the power of the chosen one.
[Music]
[Laughter]
That way, I will be a great warrior.
And my power is unlimited.
[Laughter]
Anggar.
It's up to you to do what I want.
To destroy Albaran.
[Music]
[Laughter]
*laughing*
[music]