To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, jump, jump, we are the champions
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
To be continued...
This is our heritage
Why is it used by you?
No, it's impossible
It must be similar
Aldebaran, our kingdom's heirloom
And according to the power of the gods, the heirloom is in one of the buildings of this school
How is it possible that the heirloom is here?
The heirloom is in a woman with long hair, fair skin
And the woman is here
What she meant was me
But how is it possible that I'm wearing a heirloom?
I haven't seen them for a long time
What is this?
I'm confused
What does this mean?
Don't you know?
Me neither
Are you done?
Yes, professor
That's it? You're not strong enough?
You're a coward
Then, let's go down
Let's go down
Come on
You almost stepped on me
How is it?
The heirloom can't be seen by the woman
Then, how?
I don't know
Just think about it, Rick
You're a coward
So, Alva and her friends didn't go to class
Where are they?
I don't know, professor
Tommy said they were not here last night
So, I came to the professor
I think the professor knows where they are
Usually, I know
But this time, they didn't say anything about me
And I haven't heard about them
[The professor is looking for the heirloom]
I'm sorry, professor
Did you see professor Purwa?
Purwa?
So, professor Purwa is not here
I've been looking for him
But I haven't found him yet
Where are they?
[The professor is looking for the heirloom]
We can escape if we have the heirloom
If not, we'll be kidnapped by the witch
I'm still confused about what the heirloom means
Alva, do you understand?
No
I don't understand
I don't understand either
What's wrong with him?
Kids
Mr. Panji, why are you here?
We've been following you
So, have you found the heirloom?
Not yet
The witch said that the heirloom is a woman's hand
So, we're confused
Maybe the witch is a witch
Okay
Now, let's go back to school
I'll punish you because you're lazy
Do you understand?
We're lazy?
So, the professor is also lazy
The professor is here, right?
Right?
Yes
Professor is lazy
Shut up!
You guys
Now, take out your lollipop
Come on
But, professor
No buts
Come on
The Witch's Hand
Everyone, on the count of three
One, two, three
Fly!
Alva
What's wrong?
Why don't you fly?
Nothing
Nothing?
Mr. Panji
Alva
Yes, ma'am
What's wrong?
Do you still remember what the witch said?
Of course
What's wrong?
Nothing, ma'am
I just feel like
She meant you
Maybe the lollipop you're wearing
Is the witch's hand
Impossible, ma'am
The witch's hand can't be mine
Enough, ma'am
I don't want to think about it anymore
Go!
I can't tell you
If the witch's hand is really the witch's hand
I want to find the evidence
Professor is inside
Sorry, we're not allowed to go to school
Without permission from the professor
You don't have to apologize
I'm glad you can take the kids home safely
You two, please come in
I want to talk to the kids
Yes, professor
Where did you go last night?
We're looking for information about the lollipop
Professor, the witch said
The lollipop is in the hand of a woman
What do you mean?
That's why we don't know
Alva, you don't know either?
No, professor
Sorry, professor
Okay, you can go back to your class
Do you think Alva is suspicious?
Yes, she's been quiet
Maybe she's hiding something
What if she's with someone?
How?
You've managed to get the lollipop
Not yet, sir
How come?
According to the witch, the lollipop is with a woman
But the woman is not visible
Do you know who she is?
What's wrong with you?
You're the one who told us to investigate
Why did you ask?
You're a witch
I'm not a witch
You're useless
Thank you, sir
Go back to your class
Find the lollipop
Yes, sir
Teleportation
Congratulations
Thank God, I'm not punished
Congratulations for what?
Oh, the boss
No, it's nothing
Where is he from?
He's from here
He's sleeping here
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, sir
Sit here
Hurry up
I'm doing it
What are you doing?
I don't trust you
Go back
Boss
What's wrong?
I won't let you do this
I'm not a witch
Help me
Hurry up
[Music]
Wake up
I thought I was dreaming
What are you doing?
I'm sorry
Come on
Let's go
[Music]
Who is it?
A woman who was kidnapped by a witch
She said she didn't see me
But I'm here
Where did you get the ring?
I don't remember
I just realized that I was wearing a ring
Is the woman I'm talking about a witch?
Witch
You can't scare people
Why are you blaming me?
You're the one who's confused
I'm thinking about the princess's jewelry
I suspect
That thing is in a place we don't expect
This is what I don't like about you
Too confident
Like a princess
Just imagine
I'm sorry
I can't tell you
If the ring is in my hand
It's a curse
[Music]
[the next day]
I can't do this anymore
I don't want to
[the next day]
How can I feel like someone is coming?
But who?
What are you doing?
What? What are you doing?
You don't like to play...
from behind
You're not happy?
Is this how you play?
From behind?
You're not happy?
I've been here, you've been there
You can't push me
I can, but you can't use your legs
or your arms
You can't do that
My legs are strong
You're weak, you like to jump
You can be a stuntman, a top boy
I think I'm going crazy
Enough, get in
Where is he?
I thought he was in the closet
I thought I saw him earlier
and I saw him, who is he?
[the next day]
What are you doing?
You're talking to me?
I'm talking to you
Shut up
I'm just making sure
I'm not in the closet
You're lying
You're a liar
Don't talk to me
I'm not talking to you
You're a liar
Tanji, Purwa
Agila
Aguila
Did you see Alva come in?
I felt something weird
I felt someone holding my hand
I felt out of breath
But when I woke up, there was no one in the room
Yes, maybe it's true
Alva just came in
But why did he come to his mother in silence?
Did Alva realize that the ring in Aguila's hand is a gift?
Mom!
[music]
Why did this have to happen to me?
Why?
I can't
I can't live without you
[music]
This is the end of PHASE 2!
And that's the conclusion of this episode
Let's meet again in PHASE 3!
PHASE 3
Alpha, where are you from?
What are you doing here?
Yaffa, why did you go out?
You're not even in your room
I had to wake up at night
I was so worried about you
What are you hiding from us?
I'll tell you what I'm hiding
Good evening, students
Good evening
Headmaster, what are you doing here?
I'm here to see what your real business is
What business?
What? Your mom is alive?
Alpha, how is it possible?
You must be lying
Don't exaggerate
We lost the game
You said your mom is alive?
You're lying
But how?
You told us to wake up at 8 AM to wake your parents up
I don't believe you
But there's a power that can wake my mom up
We can't meet her
We want to meet her
Okay, but tomorrow
My mom is still sleeping in the old hospital
Okay, but promise me
But, I'll tell you the truth
So, the soul stone is gone
And you two followed Alpha to find the soul stone
Where is the soul stone?
I don't know
Don't lie
I'll look for it
The food is gone
The soul stone is in the girl's hand
But I can't see the girl
I can't see the girl
You two must be lying
It's true
Why would we lie?
I can't see her
It's weird
Why is there a girl?
That's professor Aldebaran
Where is he?
He's not here
Let's look for him
Let me go
How can we follow him?
We can't
I'll let you go
Hurry up
It's taking too long
Let's go
Hurry up
You're taking too long
We're in trouble
I know this
Who is this guy?
I don't know
Why are you guys hiding?
There was a professor Aldebaran
He was killed
So we followed him
Aldebaran?
Okay, I'll come with you
Let's go
Good morning, sir
Professor Aldebaran
Professor
What is it, professor?
Where is he?
He's still sleeping in his room
I'm sorry, everyone
I have to go
What do you need, professor?
This is about the missing ring
The ring is very similar to the ring that Aldebaran used
To be honest
Since last night
I've been thinking about this
I've been thinking since madam Gemini told me
That the ring was in the hands of a man
Wait
There's something strange, professor
If the ring is in the hands of a man
Shouldn't the child have seen it?
Alpha should have told us
Right?
You're right, professor
Alpha knows
I'm worried
He's hiding it
This was done to protect me from you
Panji, you're close to Alpha
I want you to talk to him
You decide what to do
Okay
What are they talking about?
It's so loud
We're so close
What's that sound?
I think there's someone here
Don't tell me
Alde is following us
Sorry, sir
Sorry
I'll go check
If you're late
You'll be kicked out of the school
I'm sorry, sir
I'll go check
I'll be kicked out of the school
I'm sorry
I have a good idea
What are you whispering about?
We're just saying
We have a good idea
Let's go over there
So we can hear it better
Okay, let's go
What should I do now?
I don't want to lose you
Alpha
Mom?
I think I hear her voice
Alpha, I'm here
Mom?
Why are you here?
I have something important to tell you
Let's talk somewhere else
How about here?
Let's talk in the school yard
I have something to tell you
Let's go
Okay
What are you doing?
You're so smelly
Yes, professor
I'm also a teacher
This means there's someone around here
Who's trying to...
Kill us
Where?
I'm getting more and more nervous
Let's run away
Now!
You're so mean
You traitor!
You're the traitor
How dare you
You're following us
What do you want?
Alpha
I have a question for you
But answer me honestly
What is it?
Did you come to the professor's office last night?
Even though I'm sleeping
I can feel your presence
Yes, mom
I went there last night
Then why are you so quiet?
Why didn't you wake me up?
Alpha
Why are you crying?
What's wrong?
Mom, I have a favor to ask
What favor?
I...
Want...
What?
I want to introduce you to my friends
You want to introduce me to your friends?
Isn't that dangerous?
Calm down, mom
My friends are nice
They can keep secrets
You want that, right?
Because they want to get to know you
Alright
If that's what you want
I'm okay with it
Then, I'll get married first
So I can be pretty
What's wrong with that?
I want to be a rich girl
So, you're getting married?
Yes
Okay, I'll help you
Hey!
Show your spirit, get ready to find your friends
Run, jump, jump, chase the stars
Dare to say no
Chase your dream
How was it?
It was so cool
I think there's something missing
What?
You have to change your clothes
Let me see
Gavanti Bafajuh
It's so pretty
What else?
I think there's something missing
One more thing
What?
You have to wear a glove
Glove?
What for?
So you can be prettier
Do you want it?
Okay, I'll do it
What's wrong with you?
Come here
Listen to me
You can't see
If I'm wearing a ring like before
I'm sorry, guys
I have to do this
Because I still want to be with you
Forever
Don't forget, I'm still here
I'm not a Teguh Skut
I'm a hamster
Okay, get ready
[Gunshots]
Where's the other one?
I don't know
[Gunshots]
Where are you going?
Open it
I'll kill you
[Gunshots]
You want some?
Let me go
You won't get away
Ouch
[Grunts]
I'm here, Alva
Mom
Hello
Hi, auntie
I'm happy to be with you
Usually, I'm a bit late
Me too
I want to ask you
Why are you wearing a ring like this?
I'm sorry, guys
I have to do this
Because I don't want to know
If mom is alive again
I'm sorry for you guys
Keep it a secret
Okay
Thank you
I'm happy that you have a good friend like us
You're all good kids
Thank you, auntie
Let's sit down
[Music]
Good morning, professor
I'll send Ankara to your place
You take care of him
Put him in a cell and keep him isolated
Yes, professor
One more thing, Agri
You have to be careful
Because Ankara can turn into a T-Rex
Don't let him get away
Yes, sir
I'm not a T-Rex
I'm a little bit bigger
Hamster
Move him to the cage
Welcome, Ankara
You're all rude
Now, Ankara's problem is solved
We just have to talk to Alva
About Jiva's stone
Professor Alva
If the ring is released from Akila
Isn't it dangerous?
The ring is the source of Ankara's power
If the ring is released
It seems like Akila will fall asleep again
[Music]
That's the ring from Durium
No
[Music]
Aquila
This is Aldebaran
Professor Aldebaran
It seems like Akila is still unconscious
You'd better not disturb her
Urwa
We have to talk about this
With Akila
Akila
Here, Ani
Akila should be listening
Don't
Move
Akila is not there
Where is she?
Don't
Alva has taken Akila away from here
We have to find her
Professor Aldebaran, wait
Ouch
I think I have to go back
Wait
What's this?
This is a mess
Let's let the professor find her
No, wait
I want to find Akila too
I'll go with you, but don't leave me
Just one minute
Okay, wait
Hurry up
This is my chance
I have to find Akila and Alva
And save them
Report
Akila
She's not here either
Alva must have tried to hide Akila
Where is she?
I have to find her
Teleportation
Alva
Akila
She's not here
Professor Purwadeng, what are you doing here?
You must be looking for a beautiful woman like me
Who are you?
Come here, this is a women's toilet
I don't care
I'm so tired
Professor Purwadeng, why are you in a women's toilet?
Oh my God
I feel so good
Alva
Akila
She's not here either
Teleportation
Don't be too aggressive
You'll hurt yourself
Guys
Let's talk while eating
Okay, let's eat pizza
That's right, pizza
Pizza
Let's eat
Let go of me
Wait
Sometimes, we have to drink when we eat
That's right
Let's use syrup
Okay, I'll get the syrup
Wait
What is it?
Let's prepare the food for auntie first
Then we'll eat
Come on, auntie
Thank you, beautiful girl
Okay
Let's eat
We have to feed Alva
Sorry, ma'am
I'm sorry, auntie
I didn't mean to throw it
It's okay
Let's put our hands on our stomachs
So that she won't be sticky
Don't!
That's the ring from Duyul
No
That's right, professor Aldebaran
The ring has a soul stone that belongs to the eighth dimension
What?
The soul stone
That's so long, professor
What is he doing in the toilet?
He's a baby, right?
You try to call him
Okay
Professor?
What is it?
Professor, hurry!
I'm sorry, professor
Open it!
Professor, we're lying
What do you mean?
Professor is not in the toilet
He lied to us
Yes
Where did he go?
Why did he lie to us?
That's what we have to figure out, professor
Don't
The priest doesn't agree with our action
You remember
The priest always performs the ritual of the world
Yes
It's true, professor
He deliberately lured us here
So he can lure us to the world
Let's find him
Teleportation!
How can your mother use that ring, Alva?
I don't know, dear
Suddenly, after I woke up from a long sleep
I found this ring in my hand
We have to let it go
Because we have to destroy the soul stone, right?
Yes
Don't!
Why not, Alva?
The soul stone contains the power of darkness
So we have to destroy it
So the power of darkness will be reduced
Yes, Alva
You're right, dear
Besides, this ring doesn't belong to me
But, dear, don't
Dear, this is the source of my power
If I let go of this ring
I'll fall asleep again
So the ring stone gives power
Send it to Aqilah, so she can be revived
So you're all here
Good
Professor, what are you doing here?
I'm here to find your mother, Alva
Professor, don't
Don't take that ring
Don't, Professor
Your mother will wake up
So she can die
Don't, Professor
What are you talking about, Alva?
I'm here
To help your mother
Before Professor Aldebaran
Or when I came here
To take that ring from your mother, Alva
So, Professor is defending my mother?
Yes
They already know about this
So you should leave now
Let's go to the school
Let's go
Rey, are you defending my mother?
Of course, Sir
You should meet your mother, Alva
I don't want to, I'm afraid of my aunt
Let's go, Jorim
Yes, Sir
We don't want to make you sad
I'll do anything to save your mother, Alva
[The school is in chaos]
Why is Professor Purwa like that?
Maybe he likes Danta Aquila
[The school is in chaos]
Shut up
You don't have to explain
But, I heard that Professor Purwa is heartbroken
Yes, he's been rejected
Really?
Shut up
You don't have to make a scene now
You'd better take your mother away from here
Before Professor Aldebaran or I come back
Okay
But, I'm not sure if what we're doing is right
Aquila, this is all for Alva
Please
Let's go, what are you waiting for?
Let's go, hurry up
Hurry up
Alva, take your mother away
Let's go
I don't want to leave you, honey
[We can do this]
Alva and her mother are gone
Where are they?
I think Alva is trying to hide her child
We should chase her, so we can get there faster
Okay, I agree
We'll kill each other when we find one
Okay
Teleportation
The children are not here
Alva and her child are not here
There's another one
What are you doing here?
Teleportation
Where is he?
He's gone
Why do you always peek at me?
I'm going to find him
Food delivery
I think Alva and her child are here
[We can do this]
Where are they?
Professor, I think they were here
Where are they now?
We have to get out of here, hurry up
Hurry up
But, where are we going?
There's a cave nearby
We can hide there until the situation is safe
Let's go
Sir, I can't use this ring
If this ring is a stone, we have to destroy it
I'm willing to die, as long as I can destroy the darkness
Agela, what are you talking about?
Don't you think Alva can lose you?
I'm begging you, don't leave me
I want to be with you
We don't want to lose you either
I don't want to leave you either
Yes, I'm sorry
Don't leave me
[Alva's mother is in danger]
But, we have to let this ring go
I'm sorry, Mom
I don't want to leave you again
I don't want to leave you
[Alva's mother is in danger]
Alva, you have to listen to me
I can't use this ring
But, Mom
No, Alva
You can't be stubborn
You have to let this ring go
You have to listen to me
But, Mom
Don't, Dad
Mom, don't
You have to listen to me
Dad, I heard something
Yes, I heard Alva's voice too
That's them, let's go there
What's wrong, Dad?
You can't use this ring
But, you have to let this ring go
You have to listen to me
Yes, we don't want to lose you either
Alva, I'm sorry
Alva is crying
Don't make me angry
I don't want to leave you either
[Alva's mother is in danger]
But, you have to
Where are you going?
Professor Gemar
I'm not a traitor
Purwa has changed
He's a traitor
I'm not a traitor
Then, what are you?
If you're not a traitor
I'm just doing
The right thing, in my opinion
A man shouldn't be like this
He deserves to live
A man shouldn't live
Just because he got a ring
He deserves to live
Where is he?
Professor Purwa is right
He's right
Yes, Professor Purwa is right
Enough, Cun
Enough
The Dark Lord is evil
He wants to rule the world
That's why
Whether he wants to or not
The Soul Stone must be destroyed
But, Professor
There are 12 Soul Stones
We should find the fourth one first
He's right
I agree
Yes, Professor
If we find the fourth one
And the twelfth one
Then, we destroy the third one
Yes, Professor
We should find the eighth one first
Mom
Let's write it to dad
Right, mom?
So, mom and dad can wake up soon
The Dark Lord is evil
Kids
Unfortunately, it's impossible to do
There are steps
If we don't destroy the fifth one
Then, the fourth, fifth and the rest can't be destroyed
And that means
The Dark Lord is getting more and more evil
What do you all want?
If the Dark Lord wants to rule the world
What do you want?
So, I agree
If we don't destroy it, we'll sleep again
Do you really have no feelings?
Yes, I do
Yes, sir
Imagine
If Bargi can't live without the Ring Stone
Can you imagine?
Don't you have feelings?
Enough, enough
Enough
Alva
I know this is hard for you
But all decisions are in your hands
Think about it carefully
I won't force you
But, Professor
But, Alva
There's one thing you have to remember
If you want to keep the Ring Stone
Your life will never be peaceful
Because the danger that the Dark Lord brings
Not only for you
But also for your parents
[The Dark Lord's Ring Stone]
Children
Let's get out of here
Alva
Take your mother
Wait
Don't do this again
Sir
It's urgent
Let the children go
Come on, Nara
I'm sorry, Professor
Come on, everyone
Wait, Alva
Alva
Mother
Come on, mother
[The Dark Lord's Ring Stone]
Professor
School Principal
I think you're in there
[We can do it]
Why is your house in the middle of the road?
Jafatang
Follow me
What's going on?
Anggara
Where are you now?
Why haven't you returned to the castle?
Sir
You must remember
Where I am now, sir
You're in the gang
Who's Anggara?
How could this happen?
I was arrested
By Aldebaran
Sir
Aldebaran?
You're an idiot
Sir
Please listen to my explanation
Actually
I almost got the soul stone, sir
But
Mike, Jack, and Tommy
Betrayed me, sir
You're really an idiot, Anggara
You lost to a kid
I'm sorry, sir
I was careless, sir
But
I got valuable information, sir
It seems
Aldebaran and Mewa
Already know
Where the gang is, sir
Are you sure?
It seems so, sir
Because I saw them whispering, sir
Alright
I'll investigate further
Then
Tommy, Mike, and Jack
What now, sir?
If they're really betraying me
I'll investigate further
Who are you?
I'm Pangen Redilang
I want to tell you
That I know where your gang is
Don't lie
I'm not lying
If you really know
Where is it?
Aldebaran
The leader of Sekolah Segeri
Your gang is there
You've come to Sekolah Segeri
We've even explored
The hideouts we suspected
But
We didn't find anything
They've hidden it
So you can't take this gang
Alright
Then
We have to go back and look for it
We have to unite our strength
To defeat Aldebaran
We agree
We work together
To defeat Aldebaran
Good
[Chuckles]
If it's like this
I'm easier to defeat Aldebaran
Let's go
We have to go
The hideout must be found
Wait
What now?
Search for it
What do you want to do with our gang?
[Chuckles]
That's a protection spell
From now on
You can't be attacked by Irfan's spell
Let's go
Aldebaran
[Music]
Who's the traitor?
Everyone
What do you think?
Here
In this cave
We can stay for a while
Wait
This is wrong, Purwa
This is not right
You're an adult
And you're a teacher
Please think rationally
Don't support them
What did I say?
With mom?
You want to leave me?
I'm sorry
I miss you too, son
I want to be with you forever
But we can't be selfish
We can't be selfish
As long as the 8th prince is still in power
It's dangerous
Everything can be destroyed
Irfan
[Music]
Wake up
Tamdun
[Music]
[Laughs]
Now Aldebaran is trapped
Alapak
You have to be strong
You can do it
[Sighs]
[Laughs]
Finally
He brought his soul here
[Laughs]
[Music]
[BREAKING NEWS]