Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Oh my God, this wound is very bad
And must be treated immediately with energy transfer
The sword of the savior
The sword of the savior?
Defatambarga
Destroy them all, Bar
Don't let them enter the castle
Let me go
I want to remember Alfa
Vega, Ray, Soleh, have you got the sword?
Not yet, bro, now Alfa is the one who is wrong to be the sword
Alfa?
They will definitely meet
If the dark lord will catch and finish Alfa
I will finish them all
The head of the headless school, Aldubaran
But don't worry for me
I will infuse Aldubaran, I will help you
Just that, what I will infuse is not the dragon to Alubaran
But poison
Poison, poison, where is the poison?
I need help
Where is the poison?
Alfa, wake up Alfa
Alfa, wake up
You are the one who has been missing for two years
Why do you come to my dream?
Alfa, do you know who that kid is?
Who?
That kid is you
Alfa, you are the one who has been missing for two years
You and my father, right?
That's right
If they are my father's servants
If I am not taken care of
Then where are they now?
Of course they don't take care of you
Because they are old
They are not your children
Even if they don't take care of you
Because they are both dead
Dead?
Why is the rain so heavy?
Ketomi, please, sir
Professor Ankara is attacking Professor Alubaran
What?
Kau Vega, Kare, and Katole are fighting him
But I don't know if they are strong enough or not
We have to do something
Jack, wait for the kids
We have to save Professor Alubaran
Okay, sir
Thank you, Ketomi
Guys!
We have to help Professor Alubaran
He is fighting Professor Ankara
Let's go
Boss!
Have you got it?
Yes, I have
Let's find the other eggs
What's wrong?
It's a monster!
Run!
What's wrong?
It's a monster!
Run!
Ankara!
Kids!
Stop them!
Say it!
Feel it!
Dad!
Why are you here?
We want to help you
Guys, let's get ready
Hey!
Do you think you can defeat me?
You underestimated me
Even though you have 1.000
You still can't defeat me
Professor Ankara, don't be too cocky
Yes, we are special
Do you want to know why they died?
Guys!
Don't hurt them
Let them go
Guys!
Let's go
A drop of water from a chosen child
Can bring back my power
Mr. Bonda!
Let me go!
Mr. Hipok, the teeth can kill
But you can kill it through the teeth
The string is his weakness
Yes
What?
What did I teach you?
You've killed your monster
Now listen to me
Boku!
Kids, you're all great
Going to Egypt to buy turtles
The magic children are really great
Yeah!
Only your blood status left
Then my power is perfect
Because your blood status
Can bring back my power
No, I don't give up
I don't give up
My blood is for a monster like you
I fight to the death
So you can't
Take my blood anymore
Who do you think you are?
Do you know who you're facing?
I'm the Dark Lord
Your power
Can't beat mine
And I don't need your permission
I will take your blood
For real
Take his blood!
Watch out!
No!
Soon, the power that you've been hiding
Will be back
And it's all because of you, Alfa
Please go home, Alfa
Because your job is done
I won't let the Dark Lord
Come back!
You've made me so angry, Alfa
Feel this
(Music)
Do you know what this means?
That is the torture mantra
(Laugh)
After you enter this room
You will feel our torture
Very amazing
And you will ask your parents
(Laugh)
Dad, Mom
What is this time I met you?
(Laugh)
(Evil laugh)
(elloquial voice)
Alpha
Bro
Mom
Now
I know who you are
Dad
Mom
I've been fighting
But I lost
Like this
I will meet you both
No, Ango
You can't give up
Yes, Ang. There will be a time when we meet again.
You must defeat the darkness.
You are our only hope.
How?
He's so strong. He has the power of a star.
Only with the determination and love that's in you can you defeat all evil, Alpha.
You must believe in yourself. You can do it.
(Epic music)
Okay
I won't give up.
Be patient, Alpha. There will be a time when we meet again.
(Epic music)
I can't give up. If the darkness gets my blood, it will get stronger. It will hurt a lot of people.
I must resist. For Sega, for Ray, for the stars, and for Tenara.
Megazord
Red Bird, help me.
(Scream)
We can do it
[Beep]
[music]
why weird, why can he suddenly disappear?
even though he followed
so our effort is in vain
hey
don't say in vain
there is a white chicken climbing a tree
don't be sad
because you have defeated Ankara
right, Ankara has escaped
you all managed to save professor Aldebaran
[music]
now
it's better for you to find and save Alfa
Vega
Ray
Tole
you save Alfa
you go, save Alfa
and you can also bring the head of the dragon
yes, sir
[music]
wow, this is a big dragon
wow, it's so big
Vega
next time
we will go to the forest
I'm not afraid
[music]
wow
wow, it's so big
it's so big
[music]
[whistle]
!@#$%^&*(
(trying to protect his feet)
What happened to me?
Why am I here?
I thought I was swimming in the nature?
I'm confused!
Thank you, Garuda bird!
I'm gone!
I have to find the sword
and go back to school.
Why did you come here, Alfa?
Are you looking for the sword?
Yes.
The sword is not here.
It's my plan to trap you.
But...
Doctor Pertiwi said that...
Doctor Pertiwi?
He's been affected by hypnotism.
He will talk to you as I want.
You're a bad person!
Enough, Alfa!
It's better...
if you join me...
than you die in vain.
You can be my guardian.
And we will rule this world!
No, I don't want to work with you!
You're a bad person!
You're a murderer!
You're so rude, Alfa!
How dare you to come to the dark side!
I'm focused!
Ankara...
failed to get your blood.
But not with the help of darkness.
[laughing]
It hurts!
I'm Alfa.
You're Bil.
You want to be my guardian?
No!
I won't give up!
It hurts!
Help!
I think I hear Alfa's voice.
Alfa, please show yourself to me.
Alfa?
Enough, Alfa!
It's useless to fight!
You're sick!
Bite him!
Let him go!
[music]
My dear daughter.
Why are you here?
You want to give me your heart?
Right?
[laughing]
Open your eyes, Alfa.
I'm talking through your heart.
Because only you can hear it.
Come on, open your eyes.
Pangeran.
Do you know what the task of a star is?
The task of a star is to increase my power!
Wrong.
The task of a star is...
to shine!
[music]
My eyes!
Alfa, let's get out of here.
Run!
[music]
Alfa!
The darkness wants to sweat, tears, and my blood.
We can do it!
It's Alfa!
Alfa!
Alfa, fly!
[music]
Up!
Fly, fly!
[music]
[screaming]
How dare you!
I can't even use my power!
[screaming]
Thank you, Celena!
Yes, just take it as my reward.
Because you helped me to go back to the sky.
Yes, you're welcome!
Come with me.
Come on, friends.
Wow.
Goodbye, Alfa.
Goodbye, Vega and Ray.
[music]
I know Vega and Alfa, Ray.
Who are they?
They're beautiful.
Let's go back to the school.
[music]
[screaming]
The dust is separated by the sun.
Thank God, Alfa is safe now.
How are the kids?
Did you get the sword?
There's no sword.
This is just a trick.
This is a trap.
The Dark Lord just wants to sweat, tears, and my blood.
Dr. Pertiwi can't be lying.
Dr. Pertiwi is not lying.
He was just hypnotized by Professor Angkara.
It's true, guys.
It's true.
I was looking for Mushroom.
Then I met Professor Angkara.
I was hypnotized.
It's scary.
Now, Pertiwi, how do we save Professor Aldebaran?
This kind of energy transmission is the best.
Now, Professor Aldebaran can rest in the clinic.
In 1x24 hours, Professor Aldebaran will be back.
Isn't it amazing?
Thank God.
[music]
Wait.
For the sake of Professor Aldebaran's safety,
I will enchant this door.
So that only the master can enter.
Good idea, Professor Purwa.
Good.
Lock the door.
While I was on an adventure,
I met Centaurus.
It's a human head.
But it has a horse's body.
[music]
Can you defeat it?
Of course.
I, Reng Vega, can defeat it.
Of course, I'm the strongest.
But there's more.
Centaurus has a white tiger.
Its body is huge.
I almost got kicked.
Why are you quiet?
I'm the strongest.
You're so strong.
You can defeat Centaurus by yourself.
How can you defeat Centaurus by yourself?
Tell me.
[music]
Please, wake up.
I'm so tired.
Why does he always come to me?
Alfa, do you know who that baby is?
Who?
That baby is you.
[music]
Why are you crying?
Alfa, what's wrong?
Come on.
Tell me.
Tell us.
Why?
I'm scared.
He's evil.
He killed my parents.
First, my father was attacked.
Then he was burned.
Then my mother was attacked.
Because of him, I became a orphan.
Because of him, I don't know who my parents are.
I don't know why there's an evil person in this world.
[music]
Alfa, not everything in this world can be understood.
But one thing is clear.
No matter how strong the evil is,
at some point, it will be destroyed by good.
Because in the end, the good will win.
[music]
You're rude.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't know if the chosen one can use his power to summon Pegasus.
Angara, we don't have time.
Before there's a unique item, we must get that baby.
But how, sir?
[music]
Wake up, Varga!
Sir, do you want to use Varga again?
It's useless, sir.
Because Alfa knows how to defeat Varga.
I will make Varga again.
[music]
Varga!
Take this!
With this ring, you will not be defeated.
Your only weakness is if the ring is detached from you.
Now, destroy that skull.
Bring Aldebaran here.
Hurry!
By defeating Aldebaran,
the baby will be defeated by us.
[music]
Today, we will learn the Batu Mantra.
A mantra that you can use to defend yourself.
The mantra is...
...Divinjo.
This mantra...
...implies the power that comes from within you.
Imagine...
...the person you love...
...is sick.
You want to protect him.
You want to do something.
The greater your power,
the greater your ability to protect the person you love,
the greater the power of this mantra.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Now, pay attention.
Divinjo!
Now, we will practice the mantra.
[music]
Reka, it's your turn.
Divinjo!
Next,
Toli.
Divinjo!
That's enough.
We have to practice more.
Zuladiam.
Tobi.
[music]
Divinjo!
[laughing]
Alfa,
it's your turn.
Create your feeling.
Imagine the person you love.
Then, memorize the mantra.
[music]
Divinjo!
[explosion]
[cheering]
[music]
Very good, Alfa.
What do you imagine
so that you can
give that much power?
Both of my parents are...
[music]
DON'T MISS THE NEXT EPISODE
[MUSIC]
[GROWLING]
We have to find him.
Alfa, Alfa, where are you going? Sit down.
Sit down. Where are you going?
I want to fight Barga, Prof.
No, you stay here.
But, Prof.
No, I won't let the kids get hurt.
You stay here.
Let the teachers face you. Understand?
Prof.
What else?
His weakness is his fangs.
If you take off his fangs, he will be a robber.
[EVIL LAUGH]
[GROWLING]
Everyone.
You attack Barga.
I will try to break his fangs.
Because Barga's weakness is his fangs.
Let's go.
Prof. Fadlif.
[EVIL LAUGH]
[GROWLING]
He's getting up again.
He's coming here again.
What should we do, Top?
I think there's something that makes him strong.
Let's go there.
Let's go.
[GROWLING]
Let's go back.
[EVIL LAUGH]
[GROWLING]
I feel weird.
I feel like I'm going to faint.
Don't do that.
[GROWLING]
What's that?
He's so strong.
I don't know.
He's attacking the other one.
What should we do?
Let me help.
Let's faint.
[GROWLING]
Yes!
You're the best, Belba.
What's that?
Try me.
I'm going to faint.
[EVIL LAUGH]
[GROWLING]
You can't beat Barga, Alfa.
Barga is stronger now.
Barga will not be defeated.
[EVIL LAUGH]
Good, Barga.
Keep going.
[EVIL LAUGH]
You're not good.
Let's go.
[EVIL LAUGH]
What are we doing?
Let's go.
[GROWLING]
Ouch.
Okay, now.
Now, we're going to count to three.
We're going to fight him.
Okay?
One.
Two.
Three.
Attack!
[EVIL LAUGH]
[GROWLING]
Wake up.
You're okay.
[GROWLING]
We should leave.
We'll lure him out of the school.
If we stay here, the kids will be hurt.
The school will be destroyed.
We attack him.
One, two, three.
[GROWLING]
[BARKING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[EVIL LAUGH]
[SCREAMING]
[GROWLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
[GROWLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Rika.
Wake up, Rika.
[INAUDIBLE]
[GROWLING]
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
That's Garak Clinic.
He's going to attack Professor Bar--
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
What happened?
I don't know.
[INAUDIBLE]
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
OMG.
This must be Garak's doing.
He's training.
Watch out.
I'll stab you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROWLING]
[INAUDIBLE]
Professor.
Wake up, Professor.
Wake up.
Professor, wake up.
I'll get you out of here.
Wake up, Professor.
[SCREAMING]
Professor.
Wake up, Professor.
Wake up.
Professor.
[GROWLING]
Professor, wake up.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Professor.
Wake up.
[SCREAMING]
[GROWLING]
Professor.
[LAUGHTER]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROWLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
Where's Alfa?
Alfa.
Alfa, where are you?
Alfa is near the other team.
It's heavier.
Don't gather in a row.
[INAUDIBLE]
Let's go this way.
Alfa.
[GUNSHOT]
[INAUDIBLE]
[SPEAKING INDONESIAN]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOT]
Alfa.
[SPEAKING INDONESIAN]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHTER]
[SPEAKING INDONESIAN]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHTER]
[SPEAKING INDONESIAN]
[GASPING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPEAKING INDONESIAN]
Show your spirit, get your friend ready
Run, jump, jump, the blunt
Brave, a never-ending word
Chase your hopes and dreams
Go, go, go, achieve all dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we will
[music]