Show your spirit, prepare it, friends
Run, run, jump, climb, we
Dare, don't know, say, give up
Chase, hope, and dreams
Go, go, go, achieve all dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with the power of the heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Participants must dive to the bottom of the lake
When they arrive at the bottom of the lake, they must take a net that has been guarded by their tail
Favorite, give it to me
It means that for this first match, the winner is Alfa
I have to think about how I can beat Alfa
If necessary, he can't participate in the next match
I know how
Help
The sound is around here
But where?
Help
Hey
Where are you?
Open it
Kids, the match will start in 15 minutes
For the participants, gather at the school's playground as soon as possible
Where is Alfa? Why is he missing?
Where is Alfa? It's been a long time
He must be eliminated, Alfa
If Alfa doesn't come, what should I do?
Alfa must come
Hey, I'll look for Alfa for a moment
Where is Alfa?
I want to fight him
The most dangerous
Why is there no one?
He's here
Where is he?
He's almost there
Damn it
I'm your friend
Calm down
Don't you touch me
Sleep
I'm your friend
If you want to attack again, I can attack you back
Look at this
I'm your friend
You're my friend
Don't
Tindara
What's wrong?
Why can't I?
Don't try to go inside
It's dangerous
Because there's a reptile inside
Reptile?
How can a reptile be in school?
Yes
This reptile
Actually, I caught it from the forest
So, it's still wild
It's very dangerous
Calm down
I heard a scary sound
I heard a reptile inside
It's scary
Listen
The problem is
I'm preparing a cage for the reptile
So, I'll put it in the cage for a while
Anyway
Stay away from the cage
Don't get close, it's dangerous
This is the food
Really?
That's why
We should go to the competition
Okay
It's starting
Let's go
No
Help
Where are you?
Help, don't eat me
Alfa will be eliminated
Because she's late
Professor Aldebaran
It's time
Okay
We'll start now
Kids
The competition will start in five minutes
For the participants who are not here yet
The participants will be eliminated
Professor
I was playing in the dark
In the dark?
Really?
Yes, I'm not lying
I saw it in the mirror
I looked for it, but I couldn't find it
You're a coward
Don't be a coward
You're dreaming
It's true
I'm not a coward
I'm not dreaming
I'm not lying
I'm not a coward
I'm just kidding
Don't be mad
Vega
Maybe you're still traumatized by the dark
So, keep thinking
What are you talking about?
You're stressed
Instead of thinking about it
You should ask Alfa
So, you'll be calm
And happy
And feel comfortable
And feel strong
Okay
Let's go
Help
Someone's coming
Hey, Alfa
Professor Titan
Why are you so stupid?
Like a cow eating a rice cake
Go away
Professor, I don't want to be helped
It's dangerous
This kind of problem is so boring
Go away
You're going to join the competition, right?
Yes
I want to win
Wait
You need this
To win the competition
For my feet?
Yes
For what?
You'll understand the benefits
Okay, professor
Thank you
Thank you, professor
He's not here
Where is he?
This is weird
Where is Alfa?
He's scared
Yes, he's scared
He's a king before the war
Kids
Now
I'll start the countdown
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Hurray, Alfa is here
Thank you, professor
Finally, you're here
Where have you been?
I've been everywhere
But, I'm tired
I have something to do
Kids
The competition will start soon
The rule is
Every participant
Can get three feathers
From the queen
Queen feather?
How can I get it?
She doesn't like men
Alfa, hold the door
It's stinging
Kids
This is the magic door
Every participant
Who get in the magic door
Will go to the queen's house
Let's start
With the first participant
Please, Rey
Thank you, Rey
Two
Thank you
You must be the queen
The queen
That's her
How can I get the feather?
Where is it?
I know
I got it
It's so hard
To get the feather
I want
The strawberry
The red one
The second participant
The queen
The third participant
I'm going to be a woman
I got it
I did it
I'm the queen
Who are you?
I'm Rey
Don't say that
I'm Reyina
You don't remember me
I'm the one from that time
Then, what are you doing here?
I got lost
I can't go back to school
If I get it, I'll get 30 angsa
Poor you
What should we do?
We don't want to give our feathers
Right?
Yes
What should we do?
We can give it
But, only for people
Who can understand us
But, how?
That's the secret
Right, girls?
That's great
I'm so happy
I got it
We got it
We'll eat the vegetables
Why do we have to eat vegetables?
We don't like it
We're not ordinary
Right?
Right
Girls
We got it
Why did you do that?
How was it, Rey?
It's disgusting
I got bit
Calm down
Because you didn't get the feather
You're disqualified
Alfa, you have to succeed
But, you have to trust us
Right, Alfa?
You can't lose
If you get disqualified, I'll get it
Rey and Alfa know that I like angsa
If I knew it, I would have told Papi
I'll win this time
Now, it's the next contestant's turn
Tommy, please
Boss, we're going to get beaten
There's a man
Attack!
Wait
I have something for you
Here
Wait
If you want to get the red flower
You have to give three pieces of your angsa feather
Three pieces of angsa feather
Give me
Yeah!
How was it, teachers?
Is it real?
How was it, Professor Agni?
Can you guarantee the authenticity?
It's real, Megantara
It's real, Professor
It's real, what should we do?
You have to be able to do it
Alfa, you have to win
You can't lose to Tommy
Now, it's the next contestant's turn
Alfa, please
Be careful, Alfa
I heard it
Hi, everyone
Lucky!
That's Alfa
Are you here to ask for our feather, too?
Like your friend
Yes
Can I have it?
Thank you, Mugtiara
Give me
Our feather is very precious
Don't just give it away
But I know you want to help her
Sure
As long as she can pay with something worth it
To win the contest
I have something
We won!
But Alfa, can you give us more?
We still don't have enough
We have 10
I know
I got it
This is a double camera
If you take a picture, you'll get a lot of money
Do you believe me?
Okay, I'll try
We won!
Here you go
We have 10
We won!
Alfa
Hello
Why are there so many balloons?
I only said 3
Alfa, this is a bonus for you
Because you made us happy
Right, girls?
Right!
Okay
Thank you
Why isn't Alfa here yet?
It's been so long
I'm worried
I know, it's been so long
Wait, Alfa will be here soon
Alfa is great
She'll succeed
Trust me
Alfa won't win this time
Yes, she'll be the one to win
We won!
How was it, Alfa?
I didn't get it, Prof
See, Alfa didn't do anything
Right
You failed
But
I have something
Here's the proof
To prove the authenticity
We'll give it to Prof. Akli
Akli will investigate which one is fake and which one is real
Please
Alfa! Alfa! Alfa!
How was it, Prof. Agni?
The real Megatron
The real one?
And the number is bigger than Tommy's
And the number is bigger
If that's the case
For the second match
The winner is
Alfa!
Listen up, kids
The third match
Will be held in three days
So, to the contestants
Alfa and Tommy
Get ready
Yes, sir
Prof. Alfara, why are you here?
We can do it
That's right
Your opponent is me
Prof. Alfa
Die!
This laptop
Will be your son
I will make good use of it
Get the
Stamper
The stamper is your proof
That you're mine
Or not?
I'm the one who will take it
How do you know which one is the real one?
Is it Joker or Bunga?
I don't know
I want to give it to Prof. Titan
Wow, that's cheating
Why is it cheating?
It's cheating
Prof. Titan gave you a stamp
He didn't give me a stamp
He only gave me a chocolate and a stamp
He said it will be useful
It's the same
Prof. Titan knows how to do it
I'm tired of knowing
Vega
Don't be like that
Prof. Titan is a good man
He's my teacher
You too
I was saved when I met Monster Raptor
Monster Raptor?
He's in the warehouse
Yes
I was trapped there
Luckily Prof. Titan was there
Or else
I would have been a fool
Alfa
Come here
I'm suspicious of Prof. Titan
Why does he help Alfa all the time?
What does he mean?
Alfa was helped by Prof. Titan
To get the chocolate and the flower
Cheating!
I know
I have to make Alfa fight with Prof. Titan
Then
Alfa will get mad at Prof. Titan
And then
Alfa will be disqualified
I will win
Yes
What are you doing?
You're the one who broke my heart
What are you doing in my room?
I'm in the toilet
What about you?
I'm in the bathroom
I'm going to get hit by a tree
Prof. Prof. Prof.
Wait
Tommy
Someone wants to talk to me about Alfa
What is it that you want to tell me?
It's very important
I promise
Prof. Krua and Prof. Aldebaran
Will get mad
Tell me
What is it?
Yesterday
During a competition
I was in the toilet
What's wrong with Alfa, Tommy?
Tommy
Tell me
What's wrong with Alfa?
Why is my voice like this?
I'll explain it
Using sign language
(Alfa is trying to say something)
I remind you, Tommy
Don't play around
Enough
You're wasting my time
If you do this again
You will get punishment
Understand?
You're wasting my time
Why is my voice weird?
Hello?
Hi
I forgot that Tommy is here
Hi handsome
I have a gift for you
It's done
Chocolate
Tommy, there's chocolate from me
Why did you reject me?
I know why you rejected me
Because of your teeth
God
You're unfair
You're cheating
You helped Alfa
I'll tell Alfa and you to Albaran
Wait
Before we go
I'll show you something
Come on, Tommy
Tell me how to get rid of your teeth
Come on
Tommy
I told you before
Why are you telling me now?
Think about it
Tell me, P!
If you don't tell me, I'll scream
Don't be noisy
That's why I'm telling you
But
I'll scream
Okay
I'll tell you
I'll bring you a rose
And a heart-shaped chocolate
Give it to the girl
Give it to her
Okay
Look at me
You don't have enough evidence
If I gave you a rose and a chocolate
But if I showed you a picture of me to Aldebaran
You'll be disqualified
Don't tell Aldebaran, please
Okay, Tommy
I won't tell you
But you have to stay still
And we don't have to explain anything
Just concentrate on the third test
Okay, handsome?
Damn it
[Titan's room]
That's Professor Titan
Why is he standing in front of the warehouse?
Yes, sir
Professor, why are you here?
Ouch, it hurts
Give him a lesson
[Titan's room]
Oh my god, my dream is so scary
But I'm getting more and more suspicious of Professor Titan
Maybe he's related to the eighth dimension
If he uses a dream to change reality
He'll change soon
[Titan's room]
So, what now?
I'll lose
If I lose, I'll be his opponent
Tommy, don't be so harsh
If people find out, it'll be dangerous
But, I'm a puppy
If I join the competition, I'll have a hard time winning
Yes, I'm confused too
Your friend, Alfa, must be very smart
You often give him a slip-up
But you never win
No, Alfa is not smart
Alfa is a coward
He can't keep losing
So, I have to win this time
If not, I'll be a loser for a week
Shh, don't do that
Your puppy will get stressed
That's why I have to win
What's the punishment?
I don't know
Oh, so you want me to lose?
It's okay, I'll feed you and drink you too
Don't do that
But, promise me
If I tell you, you have to win
Okay?
Okay, I'll tell you
Huh? A ghost?
Professor Tim?
It's Professor Tim in the dark
I'll be attacked
What? I just woke up from my dream
Why are you laughing?
I think my dream is a clue for me
Oh, you're dreaming
Don't be involved with real life
Yes, I'm a slanderer
I often give him lollipop and chocolate
I have a lot
Hey, listen
Don't believe what people say
Remember this, Professor Angkara
Professor Angkara?
He's nice to us
Very nice
But, he's a slanderer
He's a slanderer, so he's a bad person
So, I think
Professor Tim has a connection with the ghost
You're exaggerating
There's no good person like him
What's that? Slander?
No
Professor Tim is a good person
Right, Rik?
Yes
Okay, if you don't believe me
I'll prove my words
What's that?
Good morning, kids
Good morning, Sir
Why are you so down?
Good morning, kids
Good morning, Sir
Okay
Today's lesson is
History of Magic
We're going to learn
About the magic of changing without knowing
This magic is one of the highest black magic
And
It's not time to be mastered by you
What's the great thing about this magic?
This magic can change someone's existence
Into another person's existence
The great thing about this magic
Not only can it change another person's existence
But it can also change the nature of the person
That's why this magic is perfect for slander
And it can last up to a year
Sir
Is there any weakness in this magic?
Yes
Of course there is
Then what is it?
The weakness of this magic is
Maybe some of you know what the weakness of this magic is
Someone has to answer
I don't know
Where's Vega?
He usually knows the answer
Vega, what do you think the answer is?
Look
Where's Vega?
He's not here
We're confused
I'm going to expose him
Because I have to prove that
Professor Titan is evil
Hey
What are you doing?
No, Vega
Why did you capture Professor Titan?
No
Sorry, Professor
I didn't mean to
If he uses a magic to change the world
He'll change in a second
What's going on?
Vega
What are we looking for?
Why did you capture Professor Titan?
Professor is scared, Vega
Sorry, Professor
It's okay
It's okay, Professor
You're smiling
Professor, I have a gift for you
A Lollipop!
Vega
This is a sweet Lollipop
For you, sweet Vega
Thank you, Professor
Professor, I'm going
He didn't change
Did I get it wrong?
A Lollipop!
But, where is Professor?
Mom
It's scary, someone's at the door
We can do it
Okay
Since Vega is not here
And none of you can answer
This magic weakness
I'll tell you
This magic that changes the world
The weakness is
A mirror
Oh, a mirror
Why is the weakness a mirror, soldier?
Because of the way it changes the world
But without using magic
Vega
What's wrong?
What?
You're such a good friend, but you didn't come in
You're such a bad friend
The lesson was so fun
We were taught a magic that changes the world
I'm sure you're upset that I didn't come in
Stop it, you're so noisy
I'm reading a magazine, don't disturb me
Okay, let's read somewhere else
You're so noisy
That person is so weird
Maybe he's crazy
He's so sensitive
He's right, the ancient wizard said
If it's a girl
She's the most difficult creature to understand
No wonder
Her name is girl
What?
What's wrong, Captain?
Can you come to my room after lunch?
The professor will give you a private lesson
For free
How's that?
I want to, sir
You're so cute
The professor has a gift for you
A chocolate
This is a chocolate from the professor for you
And for you, Rey
Thank you, sir
You're so kind
You're welcome
I told you, I have a gift
I can't let you take it away
Raptor
This is your favorite food
Come out
Raptor
This is an example of a cheap food
Come on, Raptor
Don't hide
Come out
Hi, Raptor
Eat all you want, Raptor
But remember, Raptor
I have a mission for you tomorrow
Raptor
Come on, eat
I can't wait to read the book
I'm going to the room
The professor is leaving
Yes, someone's here
I'm going to check the room
What's that?
What's in there?
Why is it locked?
I'll just open it
I'm going to the room
Mom
There's someone at the door
Oh, Alfa's here
She thought I was Professor Titan
I'll just go out
I'd better not go out
She'll be mad if she finds out I'm studying her favorite book
Alfa saw Mari too
I'm sure Alfa will suspect Mari's secret
Be patient, B. B. Centaurus
You'll be expelled
If you're expelled, Professor Titan will be finished
Be patient, B. B. Centaurus
There's a kid in this room
I have to tell her
I know you must be bored there
Right?
Be patient, B. You'll be expelled
Be patient
Hey, Alfa
Professor
What are you doing here?
Professor, B. B. Centaurus is making a fuss
He's making a fuss
Or maybe he wants to be expelled
He's bored
Don't worry, Alfa
I'll take B. B. Centaurus out to play
Play?
Now, I'll give you a magic spell
It's useful to catch ghosts
Ghosts?
Have you ever seen a ghost?
Are you scared?
No, I've seen one
Great, Alfa!
You can catch ghosts?
Yes, Professor. Ghosts are transparent
I can catch them when they're dense
That's right, Alfa
So, Professor will teach you this dense magic
Alfa, look at this ghost
Now, Professor will catch it
Power of the Dark!
Alfa, look
I've caught the ghost
Now, you can try
[Dense Magic]
Alfa, look
Sorry, Professor
I didn't mean to
I must free myself
Since there's a kid in this room
It's okay, Alfa
Now, you can try again
No, Professor
He's kind
He even taught me a new magic spell
So, I was wrong
[Dense Magic]
A, B, C!
What's that noise?
[We can do it]
Professor
I did it!
Good job, Alfa
Thank you, Professor
You're welcome
Help!
I'm the real Professor Tita
[Dense Magic]
We're in the wrong house
You're evil!
You're cunning!
Let me go!
A, B, C!
What's that noise?
It's from Professor Tita's room
Maybe he's training with Miss Sentaurus
I'm going with you, Miss
I'm in a hurry
[Dense Magic]
Kids
It's time for the final match
Between Alfa and Tommy
Alfa! Tommy! Alfa!
Calm down, kids
Wait a minute
Alfa and Tommy
You have to ride your bike into the forest
And you have to catch a ghost
A ghost?
That's scary!
After you catch the ghost
You have to bring it to the finish line
And when you get there
You have to run and get the prize
The first one to get the prize
Will be the winner
Alfa and Tommy, are you ready?
Yes, Professor
One
Two
Three!
Where is he?
He wants to catch us
It's been a while
I'm on standby, I can catch him
Where is he?
There he is
He can't catch me
I'm a coward
That's Alfa
Yes, that's Alfa
She's the one who made me lose my faith in life
I will make her lose
Guys
You better hide
Don't show up in front of the magic school kid
His name is Alfa
Don't we have to show up?
What should we do?
One more is okay
But the one named Alfa
Can't be there, got it?
But?
No buts
Just follow me
No, we don't want to
We want to see Alfa
That's it
Over there, at the bar
Over there
You're done, Alfa
You won't get the ghost
And you will lose
Alfa, I'll go right, you go left
Let's see who gets the ghost first
You're not watching the competition?
There's something more important than the competition
What is it?
I'm going to the gym
There's something more important than the competition
What is it, Vega?
Professor Titan
What about him?
Professor Titan, who's been in our school
He's a fake
Bye, Alfa
Don't come in
You're done, Alfa
The ghost is already hiding
You won't get the ghost
I'm going to the gym
Show your spirit, get ready
Find your friends
Run, jump, and climb
Beat the beat
Be brave
Don't give up
Chase your dreams
[Go, go, go, get all of your dreams]
[Go, go, go, never stop]
[Go, go, go, fight with your heart]
[Go, go, go, make yourself proud]
[Go, go, go, let's dream]
[Go! Go! Go! We will win!]