This story is purely fictional. If there are similarities in names, characters/figures, and places in this show, it is merely a coincidence without any element of intentionality.
MDentertainment presents
🎵 "Show your spirit, get your friends ready" 🎵
🎵 "Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars" 🎵
🎵 "Be brave, don't give up" 🎵
🎵 "Chase your dreams and hopes" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, never stop" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, fight with all your heart" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, make yourself proud" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, let's dream" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, we can do it" 🎵
🎵 "We can do it!" 🎵
We don't have much time
We have to destroy the crystal ball
Because if the crystal ball is full, it means the children's energy has been taken
And the children can die
Mutyara!
This is all because of the curse of the 8th prince
Mutyara has leaked where the children are now
Starting tomorrow, you will have a mid-semester vacation
And you will do a field trip to the magic village not far from the school
I just got news that the children from the magic school will be conducting a tour to the magic village
And I think we can attack Alfa there
This time I don't want to fail again
It turns out that the prophecy is true
The plan has come
We will all be affected by the curse of the legendary monster
He's right
The curse of the legendary monster
What did those people mean?
What is the legendary monster?
Go back, go back
Be quiet
As students of the magic school
You all can't be afraid
What if we become a stone?
Calm down, kids
We will definitely find out what has happened
Megantara, it's better if you take the children out of here now
And don't let a single child fly
Okay
Defend
Move
Kids
Let's go to the magic village
We must always be together
And don't let anything go
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
Let's go
Alfa, the legendary monster
We must tell Professor Aldebaran about this
Yes, sir
Good afternoon, Professor Aldebaran
Something terrible has happened here
When Nick wanted to report to the galaxy village
Suddenly, he turned into a stone
Nick turned into a stone?
Who did that?
We don't know, Professor
It all happened so suddenly
But now all the children have been taken to a safe place
Okay, you all keep an eye on the students
And take care of them
I will go there with the chief to take care of Nick
Yes, sir
Stop
Why did you stop?
What's the problem?
Is it painful?
We can't enter this village
What?
Is there something that can stop us?
Oh no
Luckily I didn't go there
If I didn't, I would have been burnt
What really happened to this village?
[The story of the children who experienced this]
Mr. Lura
For a child who experienced this
What should we do?
In this village
There is a lake that can cure all kinds of diseases
Who knows
It can cure this curse
Okay
Thank you, Mr. Lura
I will go to the lake right away
Please
Keep an eye on the children
Okay
Be careful, Tara
Be careful
There is a lightning
Coming from the sky
Don't worry
Megantara
Will come back
[The story of the children who experienced this]
Stop, Megantara
Megantara
Don't go through this gate
Professor Aldebaran
Concentrate, Megantara
Look slowly
Professor
Who installed the horrible magic in this gate?
I don't know, Megantara
Obviously
You can't leave this village
And we can't enter the village
But, Professor Aldebaran
I have to look for a lake outside this village
Because the water of the lake
Can restore Nick as he lost
There is another way, Megantara
In this village forest
There is still a mushroom that can cure the curse
Look for that mushroom now
If in three hours
The child can't find the mushroom
Then he will be a stone forever
Doctor Kutip
There are millions of mushroom in the forest
Which mushroom can cure Nick's curse?
That mushroom
Different from the others
The head is down
The position is tilting back
Fast
Okay
I will look for that mushroom
By using the mantra
Dafatang
Wait, wait, wait
You can't do that
Don't use magic
The power of the mushroom will be reduced
It's better to use
Your hand
Remember
Don't use magic
You know?
And one more thing, Megantara
You have to stay calm
Don't show your competition to the children
If they are afraid
They will run to this gate
And it's dangerous for them
Yes, professor
Soldier
Where is the soldier?
Yes
That's a medicine for Nick
I just
Met professor Aldebaran
And
Professor Aldebaran
Apologize
He can't
Gather with you
Because he has something to do
What should I do?
I want to go home
Yes, bro
How can we go home?
We want to go home, too
Children
Professor Aldebaran
Messages you
So you can help me
To find
The forest mushroom
Mushroom?
Yes, the forest mushroom
Because according to professor
This forest mushroom can cure Nick
But this is not just a mushroom
This mushroom grows in a different way
The umbrella is below
The mushroom stalk is above
And
Notice
This is the most important
This mushroom can't be taken
By using a manual
Professor Aldebaran also
Messages you all
When in the forest
Please
You have to focus
Don't play around
Don't look left and right
And hold something unimportant
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
Okay
Now you can get ready
I
Want to talk to
Professor Purwa first
In the classroom
Megantara
Is there a problem?
No
The village gate
Is given a very strong mantra
That's
What makes people here
Can't get out
And can't get in
Because of that
Professor Aldebaran
Can't come here
Professor Aldebaran orders
So that we can protect
And protect the children
Don't let
A child dare
To break the gate
Because this will be very dangerous for them
Wait
I will
Help you
To find the forest mushroom
Children
Before we enter the magic forest
To find the forest mushroom
I will
Divide you into groups
One group
Five people
Davatang
Pluid
Now
You are divided into groups
One by one
If one of you
Has found the mushroom
You just have to make the noise
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
And if there is a danger
That approaches you
You just have to make the noise
Davatang
Pluid
Professor
Why is Tintara alone?
Because she is Megantara, Alfa
She is a very strong and tough person
But you
You can't be alone
You still need an assistant
Come on
[music]
But it's so small
Romi
What are you doing?
Focus on finding the mushroom that grows upside down
Do you understand?
I understand, professor
Don't touch anything in this forest
Okay, sir
Hurry up
Go back to your friends
[music]
[howling]
Srigala
I'm Megantara
A beggar
Can I?
[howling]
[music]
There is a slender man
Hit by a tree on a iron bridge
Smart boy
Megantara
Excuse me
[music]
A bug
[laughing]
[music]
Wow, so cool
Oh, yeah
Professor Aldebaran's book
I'm sorry
I can't touch anything
And I can't see anything
I'd better find more mushrooms
[music]
[howling]
[laughing]
[music]
The mushroom
What is it?
I can use a mantra
How?
I'll try
[music]
It's impossible
I swear
[music]
I can't reach it
Wow, so cool
[whistling]
How, Vega?
Have you got the mushroom?
Yes, ma'am
But it's there
I can't get it
Don't worry
Leave it to me
[music]
Thank you, ma'am
You're so kind, professor
You'd better whistle
So the other kids will know
We've got the mushroom
Yes, ma'am
[music]
The mushroom is found
So we can get it
Let's go there
Let's go
[music]
I'm so happy, sir
Help!
[music]
The mushroom is found
So lucky
Let's go
[music]
The mushroom is found
Why is it so quiet?
[music]
Don't, sir
Sir
Sir, where are you?
It's useless to call him
Maybe he's a stone
Yes, he's a stone
Let's go
Don't come near me
Sir
Don't be angry
Let's go
Let's look for Alko
Alko
[music]
Where is he?
Help
[music]
My arm
Help
Let me go
Don't be noisy
[music]
God, let me go
I want to go back to the group
They will definitely find me
Help
It's good to be called
Who are you?
Huh?
Popo
Hmm
Gaaah
[music]
God of power
[laugh]
You have to join the dark lord
The dark lord
Help
[music]
You want to be a god?
Hmm
I don't know
I thought you wanted to attack Popo
Quietly
I thought you wanted to be fooled
But it's okay
Better
We have the power
Let's go
Come on
Oh my God
[music]
The dark lord is here
[laugh]
Come on
Attack
The dark lord is here
[laugh]
[music]
Popo
[laugh]
Hmm
There are many
Fried
Still hot
Gaaah
[music]
[laugh]
Not bad
[music]
A rat like you
[laugh]
[music]
Now
You know
The real power of Popo
[laugh]
Now
You
Take your magic staff
Then
Popo counts to ten
If you don't take your magic staff
Hmm
Tomorrow morning
You will be the breakfast
Of the dark lord
[laugh]
Come on
One
Two
[music]
Three
Why are you just standing there?
I'm just kidding
This is serious
You can't see
This is a serious Popo
Hmm
Take your magic staff
Four
Five
Six
[laugh]
Seven
Come on
Keep going
You can do it
Eight
Nine
[music]
[laugh]
Come on
My turn again
Attack
Hmm
What's wrong with you?
Oh yeah
I know how to beat him
[music]
Move to
Advance
[music]
Eh
Popo is here
[music]
Why are you attacking there?
Wow
There are so many
Fried
And soy sauce
[laugh]
[music]
Pretty girl
There are so many
[laugh]
Tiara
From Saksa
I know
You don't like men
But now
You help me
Malak is evil
He wants to take me to hell gate 8
Girls
Alpha is kind
He helped me
So
We have to help him
Come on girls
We help him
Shot
[music]
You're so annoying
You don't know who we are
You dare to play with me
Hmm
Now
Feel this
[music]
You can't
You're not a girl
Girls
[music]
Yeah
[laugh]
Help
Alpha
You should go
Everyone is looking for you
Poor him
He can't swim
He will drown
If he drown
He will die
Popo
Just let him die
He's not a man
So we hate men
Come on girls
Come on
[music]
Help
Popo
[music]
Help
Thank God
[music]
You saved Popo
[scream]
You're a bad guy
Popo
Why?
Because you saved Popo
Now
You want to be beaten
No
Now
I have to go back to the group
Eh
Wait
Do you think I like it?
I have to
Okay
If you have to
I don't want it
I don't ask for it
Oh
Not like that
Who saved Popo's life
It will be my duty
If not
Popo will die
[music]
I still see Popo as a spy
So, you have to save Popo now
So
Yes
Popo will be your servant
[music]
But I have to go to the village
I have to find many people there
Just say it
I'm your servant
[music]
You're right
Let's go there
Eh
Go
Yes
Just say it
If you don't go there
You will be eaten
It's scary
If I don't go there
What will I wear?
[music]
So
Who is this, Alfa?
Eh
Why are you asking?
I'm going to sleep
[music]
The doctor said
After they're buried
They will recover in 48 hours
I hope
They will be fine
[music]
Prof
How is Netoloso and Kanik?
Don't worry, Vega
They will recover in 48 hours
[music]
Mosquitoes are very venomous
So they will recover
[music]
[scream]
Dad, help
Dad, help me
Don't be noisy
Dad, help
[scream]
Why did you make me mad?
I never do that
[laugh]
Dad
Don't be like that
Don't be mad
Poor him
I'm looking for him
Dad, help
Dad
[music]
Dad, those kids
Came in from our roof
[explosion]
What?
[music]
What's that?
Alfa, thank God
It's okay, honey
Don't be afraid
Alfa is your friend
Alfa, where have you been?
I'm worried about you
I thought you were a rock
You've been lying to me
I'm not lying
I'm not
Don't fight
Alfa is safe now
I see
It's not easy to be a rock
I'm not a rock
I'm a man
Then
Who is Alfa?
Um
Why are you asking?
I'm a rock
[music]
Popo
Don't be rude
[music]
You know me, right?
Popo, yes
[music]
Where do you live?
I don't know
[music]
Popo, with Alfa
Because Alfa has been kind enough to help me
[music]
Popo, I'm a rock
I live in a rock
I don't have a place to live
Can I live with you?
You don't have to
You can't do that
You have to be polite
[music]
Popo, you can live here
Okay, then
It's time to eat
You must be hungry, right?
Yes
Let's go
[music]
[screaming]
Please enjoy
[music]
Don't be so rude
I'm forced
If you're forced, don't do it
[music]
Alfa, why did you bring him here?
He looks scary, you can't trust him
He looks scary
He's ugly
[music]
Look at him
Sorry, boss
[music]
We're trapped here
Don't be so harsh, Professor Purwa
We have to cover this up
Don't make them panic
Yes
Poor them
We brought them here to do field trip
To have fun
But in fact
We're trapped here
I have an idea
There's a crow
It's been brought here
It's been stabbed in the back
Don't worry, professors
Tomorrow
We'll ask them to do something fun
[music]
Rita
What's wrong?
Why are you so nervous?
I'm scared, Vega
Why?
What happened today
It's like what the legend said
Legend?
What legend?
[music]
Why are you crying?
We told you to come here
But why did you refuse?
This place is dangerous for you
Who are you?
Why do you always appear in my dream?
I'm Gamar
I'm Queen
We're two
You're so beautiful
Now you have to remember, Alpha
Don't look at me like that
Remember, don't ever look at me like that
What do you mean?
[music]
Gamar, I'm Queen
Gamar
[music]
Why did you wake up?
Why did you dream?
I couldn't sleep
Why?
I don't know
But I think I feel something
I think the teachers are hiding something from us
Hiding something?
Two kids have been killed
But we can't go home yet
And the professor
He said he would come
But he hasn't come yet
[music]
If this legend is true
It means the monster is gone
And later we have to find out who the real Bima is
[music]
What are you doing here?
I have a clue about this
Come here
Here's the book
100 years ago
The people of Sihir village lived in peace
Until one day
A disaster came to the village
[music]
The disaster was like a curse
The village was in chaos
And many people turned into stone
Help me
[music]
It's so scary
The only hope of the village was
A great sorcerer named Bima Sakti
[music]
The villagers were still afraid
They couldn't trust anyone
Even a good sorcerer like you
[music]
What's wrong?
Help me
Save this village, Bima Sakti
[music]
Look
This village is like dead
No one dares to leave the house
Because they're afraid of being cursed
[monster cry]
Why are you pale?
My family is cursed by the monster
Finally, Bima Sakti faced the monster
[music]
I'm going to kill you
Bima Sakti defeated the monster
And locked it in the cave
No one knows where the monster is
But the spell doesn't last forever
So the monster can be released
[music]
Only the fifth generation can open it
If this legend is true
The monster is released
We have to find out who Bima Sakti is
Who can lock the monster in the cave
Who is he?
[music]
All the disciples and teachers in the village are in the cave
How can I get in there and help them?
[music]
Children, even though we're on vacation
We still have to learn magic
[music]
Children
Now I'm going to teach you a magic
This magic can neutralize the enemy's attack
Which makes you powerless
Makes you stiff
And you can't do anything
But if you use this magic
You will be free
And will be normal
Yes, great
I have to be able to do this
Teach me
Okay, get ready
We will make you stiff and powerless
[music]
Kavaku Wada
Concentrate
Now I will teach you a magic
Which will free you from this helplessness
The magic is
Free from murder
[music]
Come on, children
Concentrate
Who can be free first
You can take the chocolate on the table
[music]
And if you can't free yourself
You will be punished
[music]
[scream]
Be free, be free
Don't
[music]
Don't disturb us
Who disturb me?
But he didn't mean to
He was really scared
He mispronounced the mantra and he got you
Forgive him
[music]
Be free, be free
Children, I will help you
[music]
What's wrong?
Wait, come here
I'm surprised
How can a snake talk to you?
I'm also surprised
But I used to talk to a snake
Huh?
When?
When I lived with my uncle and aunt
[music]
Is it weird that I can talk to a snake?
Wait, wait
You can talk to a snake in the kitchen
Then what animal can you talk to?
[music]
You're lying
The teeth can kill
But you can kill it through the teeth
You're so smart
Maybe I'm a descendant of the devil
[music]
How can we get rid of this?
And we can't go home
Because the village gate is haunted by a very powerful magic
We're all trapped here
Now we know that the monster likes chocolate
So we have to trick our friends to drink chocolate
I agree
So that the monster won't be harmed
Let's go
[music]
Opo, my dear
Do you want to help me do my job?
[music]
Show your spirit, get ready to chase your friends
Run, jump, jump, chase the stars
Dare, don't know, say, give up
Chase your hopes and dreams
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go! Go! Go!
Let's do it together!