To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all the dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your might
Go, go, go, be proud of yourself
Go, go, go, let's dream
We can do it!
The Hamster
That hamster!
Yes, I know that hamster!
That's Ryo's car!
Or maybe it's just a coincidence
Sir, our plan is going very well
All the magic school students are influenced by the love spell
So, they all follow all the words from Ryo
What are you doing?
Hi, Ranggara
Alva!
How dare you play with me?
Take this!
Sir, I understand you now
So, you're looking for the 8th prince and you're giving it to me?
Yes, sir
Please, write it down
I'm sorry, prince
But, your plan has failed
Leon knows everything
And the kids are back to normal
That's enough!
Prince, you have to be careful with Aldebaran
He's smarter than you think
I can't lose to Professor Aldebaran
Hello, sir
How are you?
Anggar, I'm here
Anggar, is it true what you said?
Our plan has failed?
Yes, sir
I'm lucky that I managed to escape
That's enough
My plan has been ruined by Alva and Aldebaran
Prince, you should be more careful with him
Because, he's in love with Alva
I can't believe it
Anggar is a trustworthy person
What should I do?
He told me that he's not a trustworthy person
Why are you so jealous?
Jealous?
He doesn't know that he's a trustworthy person
But, he's not a bad person
He's just like you
Finally, we're here
Now, I'm going to prove who's the real Professor Ragni
Or Prince Aldebaran
The Prince
Hey, kid! Why are you here?
Get out! This is not a playground!
I'm here to beat my uncle
Get out!
Ouch!
Timidus!
Hey, who are you? Don't come in!
Tornado!
Timidus!
Don't come in!
Timidus! There's a video!
Uncle! Where are you?
This is Leon!
Let's go back to my room
Let's go
Guys! This is our friend!
We're friends!
Why are you all tied up?
It's all because of the soldiers
They did this to us
Help us, Prof! Let us go!
Let go of me!
Thank you, Prof!
Who tied you up?
Since the soldiers used the Rathovenus's soul stone
Their attitude has changed
We're confused, Prof
We're all confused
Where's Megantara?
Megantara is at the clinic, Prof
She's been injected with the virus
I'll talk to her
I'll go with you, Prof
Let's go to the lab
Let's go
[What happened?]
Thank you, Megantara.
You've realized it.
And good.
You've managed to get the soul stone.
It's not even Eid yet, and you're already wearing a dress of Alibaba.
Alibara!
Why are you here?
In Batinbah?
Are you trying to surprise me?
Megantara, you're so fierce.
This must be the influence of the soul stone.
Now give me the soul stone.
You're so reckless, Aldebaran.
You're just asking for it.
To get this soul stone, I have to fight every day.
I even have to face the devil cactus.
You're just asking for it. You can't do it.
Megantara, give me the stone.
Come on, quick.
What if I say no?
Megantara, give me the stone.
Aldebaran, you're challenging me?
You dare to challenge me?
If you dare, let's have a match.
What style do you want?
Do you want kung fu?
Where are you going?
Alva, quick.
Open the cage.
Yes.
Give it back.
Open the cage.
Yes.
Professor.
Aldebaran.
Why am I tired?
What did you do?
You fought with Professor Aldebaran.
Fight? Don't be ridiculous.
You even challenged him to a duel.
I challenged him to a duel?
Who challenged him?
Impossible.
Don't be ridiculous.
This will affect your soul stone.
Affect?
So, I'm a part of the evil soul?
I really wanted to challenge him.
I'm sorry, Professor Aldebaran.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay, Megatara.
You didn't realize it.
Good.
Now, we have the first soul stone.
I'll continue with the sword.
Yes, Professor.
Let's go.
I challenged Aldebaran.
Grandpa.
Leon.
Leon, wake up.
Grandpa.
Where are you?
It's true.
You're still alive.
Leon, don't.
It's dangerous.
Grandpa.
What should I do?
The fire is getting bigger.
Grandpa.
Leon, stop.
You have to get out of here.
It's dangerous.
Grandpa.
I want to free him.
Please, get out of here.
Hey.
Don't do that.
Don't hurt him.
Let him go.
He's just a kid.
Don't hurt him.
Please, don't hurt him.
Leon.
Grandpa.
This is a punishment for the intruder.
I want to free him.
Adam.
Leon, Orion's grandson tried to break into our fire prison.
What?
What are you doing?
Why did a kid like you get into the prison?
We're sorry, sir.
Then, did he meet Orion?
No, sir.
We managed to catch Leon.
Good.
From now on,
be careful.
Don't let Orion and Leon get away.
Yes, sir.
Am I right, sir?
We've lost.
And Leon knows everything.
We have to be more careful with Ankara.
This is useless.
If this continues, I'll run out of energy.
I have to come up with a strategy.
He...
He has to be trapped.
The Power Barrier.
Catch that shadow.
Catch the shadow.
Good.
The power of the power.
Where is it?
Calome.
I'm here.
This heart...
...is not mine.
Hold this.
Call Alva.
Yes, sir.
Finally, I managed to catch this annoying creature.
Okay.
I have to go see him.
I'm here.
Hide.
And the last one is...
...the black owl.
What is this?
This creature...
...will make the 8th Pingisan's king.
I can take his legs.
What are you doing?
Sir.
You scared me.
What are you doing?
Sir.
This...
I'm making a potion to increase stamina.
I made it especially for you.
Why?
It doesn't smell good.
It's called Jahamut.
Nothing smells good, sir.
Sir.
Why did you destroy it?
You, Fik.
I don't know what I'm going to do with you.
You want to give me up, right?
Sir.
Don't judge me like that.
You got it wrong.
I'm going to destroy you.
So, you can't go back to school.
And tell everyone that Alva is a traitor.
Get ready.
JAHAMUT
TRIO
ALVA
JAHAMUT
TRIO
ALVA
JAHAMUT
TRIO
ALVA
JAHAMUT
TRIO
Try to break the sword.
What do you mean, sir?
What did you say?
Now.
You push the sword to the soul stone.
I tried it, but it didn't work.
Why me, sir?
If the prince can't do it, why me?
Alva.
Your destiny is tied to the eighth hand.
Since you were born, you've made the eighth prince lose his power.
Because of that, I'm sure...
...only you can destroy the eighth prince's soul stone.
Let's go, Alva.
ALVA
JAHAMUT
TRIO
ALVA
JAHAMUT
TRIO
What are you doing, Alva?
JAHAMUT
TRIO
Yes!
Alva.
Sir.
Sir, wake up.
Sir, what's wrong?
Sir.
Wow, you're awake.
You didn't even sleep.
The eighth prince can't do it.
Let's go.
Sir.
Sir, you can't do it.
Wake up.
Sir.
So, I can take your leg?
Yes.
Very good.
We've destroyed the first soul stone.
Yes.
Hey.
Jambu Batu, Fruit Pineapple.
Destroyed one.
There are still 11.
We're still in the middle.
Wow, that's beautiful.
Our journey is still long.
Kids, we can't give up.
Now, it's time to find the second soul stone.
Where is the second soul stone, sir?
The second soul stone...
is controlled by a creature...
named Bati.
It's a dragon.
It's a dragon, Ben.
It's not a dragon.
It's a serpent.
Enough.
Don't joke.
This is a serious matter.
Help!
What's going on?
A bomb.
Help!
Sir!
What's going on?
There's a bomb.
Help!
Who's that?
I'm hungry.
Help!
A dragon?
I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
Sir.
He's a female demon.
His brother is Barga.
That's scary.
Barga is a male demon.
While Barga is a female demon.
It's easier for a woman to be a demon, right?
Yes.
So, it's weaker.
Wait.
Barga is more fierce than Barga.
And he's 10 times stronger than Barga.
I'm hungry.
You're a slug.
Where is he now?
Where is Barga now?
It's huge.
Is that a big slug or a small slug?
It can be a slug.
Yes, especially a slug.
It's a holiday.
Do you see that?
It's a slug.
What's in it?
Oh my God.
He's in danger. We have to help him.
I'm scared.
He's a slug.
We have to go there.
Professor, let me accompany the kid.
Kids, get ready.
Let's go.
Leon, Leon.
I'm okay.
Leon, my grandson.
Leon.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, is this really you?
Yes, it's me.
I'm dreaming, right?
No, you're not dreaming.
You're in the same prison as me.
In the fire prison.
Grandpa.
Leon, my grandson.
I miss you, Leon.
I miss you, Grandpa.
Grandpa. / Yes.
Forgive me.
I can't help you.
No, I'm the one who should apologize to you.
Because you're suffering in this prison.
It's okay, Grandpa.
I'm happy wherever I am.
As long as you're here.
I want to be with you, Leon.
Grandpa.
You promised that we can get out of here.
Yes, we have to get out.
Grandpa.
Kids, are you ready to fly?
Yes.
Get your lollipop ready.
We're going to fight against the Bargi monster.
Okay. / Ready?
One, two, three.
Three, two, one.
Let's count to three and fly.
One, two, three.
Now!
That feeling.
I saw a ghost.
What if it's just a dream?
But it hurts so much.
A ghost.
So, this is not a dream.
You're my future husband.
My future husband.
This is the power of Megatron.
I don't understand what you mean.
Calm down.
Let me read your mind.
Don't hurt her.
Don't hurt her. Let her go.
She's just a kid.
Don't hurt her.
Leon.
Leon is in danger.
I have to go there.
Bargi headquarters?
Professor Rita.
Professor Libaran.
Hi.
You're smiling, Professor Aldebaran.
I'm sorry.
I got hurt because of my children.
They're in love.
So, I was attacked by my own magic.
Okay.
Take Titan to the clinic.
I have to go.
Where are you going, Professor Aldebaran?
I'm going to the fire prison.
The fire prison?
Why are you going there?
I have to save Leon.
He's in the fire prison...
...because he tried to save his leg.
Professor Aldebaran.
I can't just sit here.
While Scorsese is being attacked, I'm going to help.
Don't, Professor. This is dangerous.
Because this is dangerous, I'm going to accompany you.
Okay, then.
Titan, Yasmin, you take care of the school.
Okay, Professor.
Professor Aldebaran, we should go.
I'm going to use the lollipop.
Don't, Purwa.
We can't use the lollipop.
Why, Professor?
Because the fire guard can sense our arrival.
What should we do now?
The fire guard can't see.
He can only sense our presence.
We have to turn ourselves into animals.
Animals?
My husband's candidate.
My husband's candidate?
What kind of dream is this?
I can't believe I'm meeting you like this.
Where is he going?
That's not important.
What's important is that I have to leave this place.
But how?
I'm going to use the magic of the place's divinity.
The divinity...
of my husband.
Where is my husband?
Where is he?
He's my husband.
Finally.
Okay, I have to take him.
I'm going to make it this time.
Eat this.
I'm sorry.
I'm not hungry.
Eat this.
I said I'm not hungry. I want to go home.
It hurts.
What's that monster?
Do you want to be my husband?
Do you want to marry me?
Marry?
Where is the monster? I want to see him.
Eat vinegar and tofu.
I don't know either.
Guys, let's go to my house.
Who knows, my husband might run away...
and come back to his house.
Okay? -Okay.
Also, check on my condition and your condition.
Is there anyone who can help me?
I'm going to be left behind.
Mr. Panji!
There's no one here.
I think there's no one here.
Wait.
Be quiet.
I think it's from that way.
I heard a music.
Music from that room.
That's my room.
Where is it?
It's from that room.
Let's go.
Why not?
That's my uncle's dirty clothes.
That's right. It stinks.
Let's wear our clothes and go there.
My dirty clothes?
It stinks?
Instead of throwing up, we can throw up.
How can I be that dirty?
I thought I'm the only one who's dirty.
Let's go there.
Wait for me here.
If you're angry, eat this.
Hurry up. Don't use your hands.
I'm sorry, sir.
We have to lie to you.
Because Mr. Panji told us to keep this a secret from anyone.
For the sake of my mother and father.
What's wrong?
Let's go, sir.
Why is it like this?
Oh no.
Music from that room.
The infusion is always active.
What infusion?
There's an infusion that always makes my parents angry.
I thought the person is a criminal.
But, the professor is on our side.
But, he's not the one who infuses the medicine.
That's right.
Who else could it be?
Why does it take so long for Alva and Vega to come?
They said it's only a short time.
Is it really in the place where I keep my dirty clothes?
Yes.
It smells.
Can we throw up?
Yes.
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
I know.
Don't eat meat with me.
Don't be a coward, Megantara.
You're such a coward.
How dare you call Megantara a coward.
Who's a coward?
What's next?
It's so sour.
Why does it take so long for Alva and Vega to come?
Can we throw up?
I mean, can we drink coffee?
Can we eat meat?
Can we?
Here, wear the glasses.
It's so hard to wear the glasses now.
The glasses are from the 8th floor.
We have to wear the glasses so we can know...
...that there's a sorcerer who wants to infiltrate our prison.
That's the prison.
Remember, never change into a human.
If you do, the guards will arrest us.
Daniel, what he's doing is too much.
He's bothering your powerless parents.
Yes, that's why I'm so mad at him.
And I have to find the sorcerer.
"The Sorcerer"
Who's that?
Why is no one here?
"The Sorcerer"
What's that?
It's a letter.
Let me see.
"The Sorcerer"
The headquarters of the Barji...
According to our rules, the loser...
...has to follow the winner's wishes.
"The Sorcerer"
Let's go inside.
Get ready, Professor.
There's an intruder!
Let's attack!
"The Sorcerer"
This is a good chance.
Since the Dark Lord is unconscious, I have to get rid of him.
Nara.
What are you doing?
Agni.
Don't tell me you're going to make a mistake again.
I'm currently curing the Dark Lord.
Who knows, he might faint because he's tired.
I'll cure his legs.
Yes, get in.
Yes.
Thank you.
Ankara!
Attack!
What's wrong, sir?
Nothing, sir.
I'll take care of it.
I'm a sorcerer.
I won't let you pass.
Now, sir.
Here I come!
"The Sorcerer"
Merik!
No.
Don't.
We still need them.
I have a better idea.
What is it, Professor?
I agree, Professor.
Let's bring them.
Come on.
"The Sorcerer"
Did you meet your parents?
Yes, I did.
They're okay.
But, there's a snitch.
A snitch?
Listen.
What are you talking about?
Stop whining.
I'm not invited.
Bye, sir.
You can invite us if you want.
I want to know.
I'm tired.
Where did you get the clue?
A snitch came into the room.
I found this map on the snitch.
What does this map say?
It's morning.
Let's go there.
Okay.
Wait.
Think.
This could be a trap.
"The Sorcerer"
What if it's not a trap?
That's right.
I think we should follow him.
We don't know where the base is.
We have to save him.
That's right.
We have to go there.
Wait.
Let's think.
Let's go to the school.
Okay.
But, remember.
We have to be careful.
Okay.
Let's go.
Kneel.
It seems safe.
Now, we have to go out.
"The Sorcerer"
We did it.
Let's go in.
Let's go in now.
Okay.
We're here.
Where is the base?
Let's go around.
If the map is correct, we're not far from here.
Okay.
I'll go first.
You guys, follow me.
I'm confused.
Who is the sorcerer?
I think...
...he's our age.
What?
Our age?
He's still a kid.
Yes.
I heard a voice in my parents' room.
It can't be a kid.
He's so strong.
He can destroy the ground.
Mr. Panji, where is he?
I don't know.
Here.
What?
What can't you do?
You guys are always noisy.
I'm not asking you to do anything.
What can't you do?
We're confused.
You said you're confused.
What can't you do?
You're so slow.
Let's go.
Come on, girls.
I'm a sorcerer.
That's...
That's Mr. Bargi.
He's in the headquarters.
Did you hear that?
There's a sorcerer.
He's a coward.
He's so strong.
Don't be afraid.
Who's afraid?
We're not afraid.
Maybe your soldiers are afraid.
You're a kid.
You're the one who's afraid.
There's Mr. Bargi.
Bye.
The headquarters is near.
You're kidding, right?
Bargi is getting married.
Okay.
Let go of my hand.
Here's the thing.
I want to tell you that getting married is a hassle.
Because we have to prepare a lot of things.
For example, we have to have a wedding.
We have to prepare a wedding.
We have to prepare a wedding dress.
We have to save a lot of money.
And one more thing.
We have to do the job.
I'm a waitress.
I don't have a job.
So, don't worry about me.
Bargi is getting married.
Okay.
Agni.
Why did you take my daughter?
What weapon did you use?
What weapon?
Don't lie.
Agni.
Agni, click.
What is this?
That's...
a foot-puller.
You're going to take the blood of the 8th prince with this, right?
Right?
Why?
Agni.
A foot-puller.
To take the blood of the 8th prince.
How could you?
You're a teacher, but how?
I don't trust you.
Don't lie.
Agni.
As long as you know...
I used that...
to take the hair of the 8th prince.
There are a lot of hair.
Who knows that's what makes him weak.
He easily faints.
There are a lot of bacteria in his hair.
We have to take it off.
Liar.
I don't trust you.
So, you're the one who's going to fight.
Alright.
How about we make a rule?
The one who wins...
will follow the rule.
How?
Who's scared?
Hey, you guys.
Now it's your turn to guard here.
Alright.
I'm heading there.
Yes.
Alright.
You guys guard here.
We'll follow the rule.
Alright.
We'll guard here.
Professor.
I thought we knew each other.
Don't lie.
We'll keep on walking.
What's this?
You lost, Agni.
According to our rule...
the loser...
has to follow the winner's will.
Alright.
Now...
what do I have to do?
Hi Hi Hi Hi
depth of consciousness
Beware guys, Vega!
Vega, you're okay right?
yes, Vega, are you okay?
what's wrong, papa?
you've saved me
no, I haven't
you haven't done anything
yes, that's right
it's not Alva who saved you, Vega
but, but who?
I don't know either
but if I look closely
the light is coming from those bushes
beware, Vega
attack!
Leo, bring the other team, quick!
yes!
open the cell
for what?
we will bring Orion and Leon to the 8th prince
because they will get the death sentence tonight
right
this is the direct order from the 8th prince
yes, sir
what should we do, Kate?
we will be sentenced to death
Leon, you have to run
so that grandpa will be punished
no, I don't want to leave him
I want to be here with him
what's wrong with me?
good evening, prince
how can I sleep here?
yes, you fainted
now, I want to do a cleansing ritual for you
are you ready?
let's start
I will give you a cleansing ritual
are you ready?
let's start
what are you doing?
you fainted, right?
it's because of the bacteria on your feet
so that you won't faint easily
I will cleanse you
are you ready?
take a deep breath
hold it
let's start
the other foot
right
one
two
three
wait, it's not done yet
again
let him finish it
it hurts
finally, it's done
I got the eight-legged owl
yes
what's wrong?
hello
yes, it's true
there's someone there
and he saved me
don't tell me that person is the same person
who gave the map of the bargy headquarters
but we still have to be careful
who knows
that person has evil intentions
hold it
give me the stone
I will check this stone
scanning the stone
it's safe
this stone is just a normal stone
there's no magic in it
then, can I keep it for later?
hello
is there anyone?
hey, come out
don't hide, come out, good person
even though you're a good person, you have to make it beautiful
come with us
let us go
calm down, Orion
this is me, Aldebaran
Aldebaran?
yes, this is me, Aldebaran
and that's Professor Tumba
we will set you free
but you have to calm down
don't panic
we will catch you
understand?
let's go
that looks like a magician
what are you doing?
I'm sorry for disturbing you
what's wrong?
I want to ask
did you order the two supervisors to release Orion and Lel?
don't joke
I never ordered that
but the two supervisors told me
there must be a magician
hurry, catch the magician
yes, sir
hey, Mr. Niran
now, Mr. Niran's leg
ready
one, two, three
Professor, it seems like they are suspicious of us
stay alert
yes, sir
come with me
it seems like they are suspicious of us
they are hiding
you go and check the stables
let's go
Lel, take your leg
hurry
hurry, protect Orion and Lel
yes, sir
you guys stay here
what's that sound?
maybe he's about to be eaten
we can do it
according to the map
it's true
this cave is not wrong
no
what's that sound?
maybe he's about to be eaten
I don't want to
don't force me
I don't want to marry you
you have to want to marry me
I like you
I said no
I don't want to marry you
I don't like you
what's that, Nara?
wait
don't be panic
it's dangerous
we better think of a strategy
soldier
don't think of a strategy
we can be late
what if we die?
listen
Merpati bird
it's too late
I'm too nervous
I'm concentrating
I'm about to be eaten
I know
yes, that's right
Alva
let's go
Merpati bird
[music]
Good, Leon. Let's go before they come back.
Let's go.
Don't fall, okay?
It hurts here.
Then?
Why?
Why are you like this?
No, actually, you're healthier now.
Because all the bacteria are gone.
Now I want to throw it away, okay?
We will trade souls again with these officers.
Leon, please wait a moment.
Before our exchange is perfect.
Yes, sir.
[music]
Trade souls.
What should we do, Kik?
There are so many of them.
I'll calm you down, Leon.
Okay, Kik.
Wind, throw it.
[music]
We're being attacked.
Leon, it's getting stronger.
You have to hold on, Leon.
[music]
What are you doing?
Professor.
Now is the time.
Okay, Professor.
[whistle]
You guys are in danger.
[music]
Dad.
I don't want to marry this monster.
I have to get out of here.
Use it.
No.
That's the name of the pig.
It's so scary.
I have to help him.
He's turning.
[screaming]
Alva.
It's true, Professor Albaran.
He's so strong.
[screaming]
The enemy is gone.
Alva.
[music]
The enemy is gone.
Do you want to drink?
No.
Alva will be mad at me if I put her in the dark room.
Drink.
No.
[music]
Run.
Don't go.
Who are you?
[screaming]
[music]
Go! Go! Kita Pasti!