To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, don't ever stop
Go, go, go, be brave with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
I need your help
You're looking for Edward, right?
Because I'm sure he can help you defeat the Dark Lord
Yes, I'm looking for him
And you know why the Dark Lord can't kill you when you're still a baby?
Because you're Alfa's chosen child
No!
Yes! I got the book!
Finally we got this famous "Escape" sword
Get down, get down!
Before I find a way to break this sword
I will plant the sun flower
How's it going, guys? Have you found anything?
We've been looking for everywhere and found nothing, Prof
Yes, Prof, our eyes were even blinded
But it's the same, there's no black smoke, Prof
Yes, Prof, we've been looking everywhere but there's nothing
That's weird, why is there nothing?
What's possible? Yasmin is wrong
Professor Aldebaran
Agni, what's waiting for me?
The sword, the sword is gone, Prof
My sword? How can it be gone?
I don't know, Prof
The professor's room is also messy
It's like someone just came in from here
That's weird
Agni, where's Yasmin? I want to talk to her
Yasmin is in her room, Prof
She was injured because she was attacked by a unicorn in the forest
Agni, Yasmin is not the same person who was in the forest
That's right, Prof
But she was in my room
That's impossible, Prof, that's impossible
Yasmin was with us, we were in the forest looking for the angel fruit
That's weird, that means the one who met me was not Yasmin
Someone is playing with me
(music intensifies)
GO IN.
Why haven't you waited for me?
(music intensifies)
GO IN.
(grunt)
(music intensifies)
Come on girls, let's find the flower seeds of that day.
Come on.
(music intensifies)
The seeds are not growing.
What should we do?
Girls, calm down.
The seeds won't grow unless we plant them ourselves.
Wow, this must be the work of that unicorn.
We have to lure him here.
Yes, even if he comes here,
can we beat him?
(music intensifies)
You guys just passed out
because you were attacked by a unicorn.
Right?
Now all of you say thank you to Alfa
because he has helped and fought for his soul and body.
He brought Fruit Angel here.
(grunt)
Alfa!
We have to find Alfa.
(music intensifies)
How is it?
Any news?
The girls and the students have recovered, Professor.
But we have a new problem.
What is it?
You said just the name of the flower that was lost.
There's more, Professor.
(music intensifies)
Ankara has managed to escape from the prison of the devil.
Hi, Ketri and Samsa.
Hello, Vega.
(music intensifies)
There she is, Alfa.
Wow, she's also with Ketri.
Samsa!
Samsa, why are you here?
You said you don't like men.
Yeah, right.
Then, don't fight with men.
So we can't hide.
I do hate men.
But I need Alfa.
(music intensifies)
What's the matter?
Alfa, I heard you can beat the unicorn.
So I came here to ask for your help to catch the unicorn.
To take the key to our sun.
Sorry, Garis Putriangsa.
We're not here to help you.
We have other problems.
We're looking for the unicorn.
That's right.
We still have a lot of...
...missions.
Go away!
(music intensifies)
If you want to help us...
...to get the key to our sun...
...we'll help you to get the unicorn.
What do you want to get?
(music intensifies)
So...
...the sunflower seeds can only be found by the big guys.
(music intensifies)
I have to find them all.
There's another one!
Help!
(music intensifies)
(whistles)
The unicorn!
(music intensifies)
(screams)
Help!
(music intensifies)
(screams)
Let go of me!
Let go!
You're so mean!
(music intensifies)
Okay, we'll help you.
Okay, let's go.
I want to come with you.
Me too.
You can't come with us.
Only Alfa, Vega, and this little girl can come with us.
Go!
(whines)
(music intensifies)
Okay, let's go.
I want to come with you!
I can't wait.
I want to come with you.
(music intensifies)
(laughs)
Mr. Pancik, I'm hungry.
What?
Mr. Pancik?
What's that?
My name is...
Professor Silita's daughter.
She looks just like you.
Pretty Silita.
Pretty girl.
Who are you? I forgot.
(music intensifies)
Pretty girl.
Can I come with you?
Can I?
Okay.
(music intensifies)
(laughs)
You're funny.
You're funny, honey.
(laughs)
(music intensifies)
Why is it so quiet here?
Yeah, it's so messy.
Maybe...
(music intensifies)
(coughs)
I'm a stone.
Yeah, maybe I was attacked.
(music intensifies)
Wow, this must be a unicorn.
It must be here to talk to us.
(music intensifies)
Girl!
Where are you?
(music intensifies)
(laughs)
Welcome to the Dark Castle.
You evil.
Why did you arrest us?
Quiet!
(music intensifies)
This is your bed, right?
I want...
(music intensifies)
You to plant it here.
Girls, what do you say?
No way!
(laughs)
Okay.
If you don't want to...
(music intensifies)
(whistles)
(screams)
(music intensifies)
It was a unicorn yesterday.
If you don't want to...
you will be teased by our unicorn.
Go.
What do you say, girls?
Let's just plant it.
OK. We'll do it.
Good.
Now, you just have to plant it.
Let's do it!
[Tempe, Indonesia]
Why hasn't it grown yet?
Answer me!
It's useless to catch us.
We're not enough.
This seedling won't grow.
This seedling will grow if we have more.
While, there's no such thing as a pure seedling.
Right, girls?
Yes!
Shut up!
I won't give up.
I'll tear you apart.
You're so mean.
[The next day]
Where are you going, my brothers?
Run, Riga!
[The next day]
Brother!
Alfa, you're great!
Is that a new trick?
Yes.
You can run like a horse.
You're great, Alfa.
The horse can't get up.
The horse is losing.
Everyone, we have to get out of here.
We have to save the horse first.
Heron!
What's wrong with him?
We're eating.
How do you know?
Shut up!
I made the rules here.
So, I can take you anytime.
I have a mission for you.
Alfa and her friends have kidnapped Ansa...
and brought her to Sihin School.
So, your mission now is...
to find Ansa and bring her here.
Don't fail.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
You should ask him.
You should.
Why?
You're the boss.
I'm not.
I don't want to.
You're dreaming.
Don't be noisy!
What's wrong?
Well...
Well, Heron.
If we succeed...
we will be...
I mean, we'll be free.
I mean, Heron.
Her hand...
Her tattoo will be gone.
Yes, Heron.
It's painful.
If you call us, it's always painful.
Yes, Heron.
The pain is here.
Yes.
It's here, Heron.
Alright.
But, after the mission,
do you understand?
Yes, sir.
We're free.
Yes!
Don't jump!
I'll do it.
Ready to attack.
Teleportation.
I'm leaving.
We're free.
Don't run.
Where's your husband?
Don't run. We'll attack him.
I'll attack him.
Come on, Nik.
Divinju!
What's this?
I'm a fan.
Divinju!
Don't attack him.
What's this?
I'm a fan.
Don't attack him.
It's painful.
No.
Sorry.
Where's your husband?
Get up.
Ray, Tol.
There's a big female monster outside.
Very big.
Ouch.
Ray.
A female monster.
Don't be afraid.
Let's go.
Nik.
You're smiling.
There's a monster.
Where's that big creature from, Professor?
Maybe...
the monster is the dark wizard.
I'll attack him.
Let's go, Prof.
BoBoBop!
Be careful, Prof.
It didn't work.
Let me try.
What's wrong, Tol?
Divinju!
Professor, the monster is very strong.
You'd better ask for help.
It's dangerous.
Come here, Prof.
Okay, Prof.
Attack him again.
Airborne!
Beeping Shot!
Divinju!
BoBoBop!
Airborne!
Divinju!
Why did you attack my friend?
I don't know.
Why did you attack another friend?
That's my girlfriend.
What?
Girlfriend?
What's wrong with her?
Where's my husband?
Buy the ribbon.
Buy the jiruji.
They're right.
The monster is my girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
Bargi?
Husband?
Who's that?
This is...
Angsa's daughter.
Who?
This is Angsa's daughter who's injured.
Yes.
We just saved her.
She's not my girlfriend.
Calm down, Bargi.
What are you doing here?
I told you to stay home.
Let's go to the clinic.
Okay.
Husband!
Wait!
So, the seeds of the sun...
can only be planted by Angsa's daughters.
Hold this.
Professor.
The kids want to talk to you.
What's wrong?
So, this is it.
The unicorn is the monster of the eighth prince.
First,
it took the flowers.
And then,
it kidnapped Angsa.
Oh my God.
They kidnapped everyone?
Yes, Professor.
Only Angsa's daughter managed to save us.
From now on,
the eighth prince will not be left alone.
In my opinion,
he knows that the soul stone is in the sun flower.
And the seeds of the sun flower can only be planted by Angsa's daughters.
The sun flower is a very strong flower.
Once it's planted,
it will never wither.
And it will never die.
Even if it's destroyed.
That's why,
the eighth prince...
wants the seeds of the sun flower...
to grow into a sun flower.
So, the unicorn's stone in the sun flower...
will never be destroyed.
That means,
we have to protect Angsa's daughter.
And we can't be kidnapped by the eighth prince.
Yes, Alfa.
We protect each other.
Are you ready?
I'm ready, Professor.
And one more thing.
You, Alfa, Vega, and Purita.
Now you have to continue your studies.
Even though you've helped a lot in finding the soul stone,
but you have to remember,
education is number one.
That's right.
Yes, Professor.
Where am I?
There's a man!
This is for you.
Of course.
Thank you.
The flower is beautiful.
The chocolate.
The chocolate makes me want to swim.
I really like this chocolate.
If you want to join us again,
there are so many places outside the classroom.
Really?
Yes.
Let's go.
Come on.
My husband's hair.
Why is it so far?
We're almost there.
There are a lot of flowers and chocolates for you.
You must be bored.
Okay, be patient.
Okay, let's go.
Wow, there are so many.
You're so kind.
Thank you.
(The flower is beautiful.)
(The chocolate makes me want to swim.)
You're as bad as ever.
Don't run.
I'll get mad.
Class!
Help!
Don't run!
Oh, no.
You made me panic.
It's not Mr. M58.
It's Bargi.
Bargi.
I'm mad at you.
I'm so mad.
Why did you scare Putri Angsa?
You hate her?
Bad girl.
No, Bargi.
She's beautiful.
Bad.
Beautiful.
Ouch.
I...
I'm mad.
Hi, Bargi.
I'm Angkara.
I don't know you.
You may not know me, Bargi.
But you must know the 8th Prince.
Listen, Bargi.
The 8th Prince wants to make a promise with you.
What promise?
He will take away the curse on you.
And you will be a beautiful princess again.
Bargi.
A beautiful princess?
But there's a condition, Bargi.
What's the condition?
You must catch and hand over Putri Angsa to the 8th Prince.
What do you think, Bargi?
Do you agree?
Liar.
I don't believe you.
You must hand over the 8th Prince to the 8th Prince.
And he can do whatever he wants.
And remember, Bargi.
If you become a beautiful princess again...
...I will automatically choose you from Putri Angsa.
Forgive me, Bargi.
Forgive me for having betrayed you.
Now...
Will you marry me?
Bargi is happy.
What?
Answer me, Bargi.
Don't just smile.
I'm ready, Bargi.
I'm ready.
Hazil!
Uncle, it's Bargi!
Watch out, Bargi.
If you touch Putri Angsa's wound...
...we can...
It's already late.
You should sleep.
I want to rest.
No.
I want to leave this place.
This place is not safe.
Don't go.
It's more dangerous.
Putri Angsa.
What if you get caught by the Unicorn or the Fire Guard?
Who knows?
The prisoner was mean.
He tried to catch me.
Putri Angsa.
Calm down.
Bargi is a good person.
Bargi is just a friend of yours.
You are so beautiful.
So, calm down.
We'll tell Bargi.
Just tell Bargi.
I hate men.
Especially, Panji.
We'll tell him.
What if I'm safe here?
I know.
Alarang Fang.
Vega, Prita, and Rafa.
What's this?
It's an alarm to keep you safe.
So, only me, Prita, and Alfa can get in.
Besides, this alarm will make a loud noise.
Yes.
If we get caught, we'll tell them.
We'll go out now.
Okay.
Bye.
"The Alarm"
I can feel it.
Help!
Let me go!
It's dangerous.
Vega and Prita.
If they set an alarm, they'll be caught.
Yes.
The alarm.
The water is loud but not deep.
I can feel someone is hitting me.
That's Alarang.
That's bad.
Rih!
Rih, wake up!
Wake up!
The alarm is loud.
Rih!
I'm still sleepy.
I can't sleep.
There's one.
What?
It's dangerous.
Let's go there.
Help!
Everyone, hurry up.
We have to find Putri Angsa.
Let me go!
Sir, that's Bargi.
He's taking Putri Angsa.
Be careful, Bargi.
If you touch her, you'll get hurt.
Everyone, get ready.
Sir, what should we do?
Hurry up.
Everyone, get ready.
One, two, three.
Let me go!
Vega! Alpha!
Help me!
I'll be a princess soon.
If I become a princess again,
Panji will be happy.
Bargi!
Let Putri Angsa go!
Husband?
Bargi!
I'm begging you.
Let her go. She's not at fault.
I don't want to.
What are you going to do with her?
Where are you taking her?
To the Dark Palace.
Bargi!
Don't do that!
Putri Angsa is in need of magic.
Don't hurt her.
Bargi is more important.
She's more important.
Bargi!
Don't take Putri Angsa, Bargi!
( Epic Music)
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Release!!!
(Epic Music) Release meee!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Release meeee!
(Epic Music) Release meee!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Margi!!
(Epic Music) Release the adult!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) You can't be like that!!
(Epic Music) I don't want to!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Yes Margi!!
(Epic Music) Don't be selfish!!
(Epic Music) It's said that adult shouldn't choose their love!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) See, it's true!!
(Epic Music) Shut up!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Ouchh!!
(Epic Music) Hold it!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Margi!!
(Epic Music) You can't be selfish!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) For the adult is the happiest person!!
(Epic Music) Who can be loved by others!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Shut up!!
(Epic Music) You have to be honest!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) The honest person won't be happy!!
(Epic Music) About the suffering of others!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Go!!
(Epic Music) If the honest person is going to be defeated!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Shut up!!
(Epic Music) Ouch!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Bargi!!
(Epic Music) Stop!!
(Epic Music) Let me go!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) We'll be there soon!!
(Epic Music) Bargi!!
(Epic Music) Let me go!!
(Epic Music) I don't want to be taken to the dark side!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Bargi!!
(Epic Music) My daughter is a student of Seir Bargi!!
(Epic Music) Don't hurt her!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) You can't be selfish!!
(Epic Music) The best part is the person who is happy and can be loved by others!!
(Epic Music) Bargi!!
(Epic Music) You have to be honest!!
(Epic Music) The honest person will not be happy!!
(Epic Music) On top of the suffering of others!!
(Epic Music) The honest person is a coward!!
(Epic Music) Hmm.. Alfa is right!!
(Epic Music) Bargi doesn't want to be selfish!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Bargi bring her back!!
(Epic Music) You want to bring me back??
(Epic Music) Yes!!
(Epic Music) Bargi is good!!
(Epic Music) Bargi is honest!!
(Epic Music) Okay, let's go!!
(Epic Music) Hurry up!!
(Epic Music) Yes!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Mom!! Help!!
(Epic Music) Let me go!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Hello Bargi!!
(Epic Music) Thank you for bringing me Putri Angsa!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Putri Angsa!!
(Epic Music) Now you get out of the way!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Hurry!!
(Epic Music) Don't!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) How dare you!!
(Epic Music) How dare you to challenge me!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) I will kill you!!
(Epic Music) What is that??
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Why my mantra is not working??
(Epic Music) You are free!!
(Epic Music) Run!!
(Epic Music) Hurry!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Thank you Bargi!!
(Epic Music) Hurry!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Hey!!
(Epic Music) How dare you to challenge me!!
(Epic Music) Monster!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Put it in!!
(Epic Music) Unicorn Gun!!
(Epic Music) Chase that animal!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Bargi!!
(Epic Music) Now I will challenge you!!
(Epic Music)
What is good??
(Epic Music) Huh??
(Epic Music) What is bad??
(Epic Music) You just stole my princess!!
(Epic Music) Bargi is still good!!
(Epic Music)
Taste this!!
Sivirza!!
(Epic Music)
(Epic Music) Huh??
(Epic Music) (Coughing)
(Epic Music) What are you doing??
(Epic Music) Why I don't feel anything??
(Epic Music) (Coughing)
(Epic Music)
Sivir!!
(Epic Music) (Coughing)
(Epic Music) What is that??
(Epic Music) It looks like I'm being cheated!!
hahaha
why is my mantra really not working with her?
Feel it!
feel it!
uncle cantan...
uncle cantan, are you okay?
yeah, i'm fine
i'm okay, i'm okay
okay
let's chase bargy again, and this time we will use violence
bargy is happy!
why is bargy's mantra here?
let's go!
panji!
stop!
don't come any closer!
bargy is nice, bargy is honest!
what is nice? huh? what is honest?
you just stole my princess!
bargy is still nice, bargy is nice!
that's enough bargy!
i want you to release my princess right now!
but...
bargy is already...
already what?
you already gave my princess to the dark side, right?
bargy, you are evil!
you are naughty, you don't know yourself!
but...
enough! enough! i said enough!
i don't want to deal with you anymore, bargy!
i want my princess!
get out!
fly, fang!
bargy is nice, bargy is honest, but i hate bargy!
*sobbing*
bargy is sad!
bargy is nice!
bargy has released his princess!
*sobbing*
bargy, are you serious?
bargy, i don't want to be selfish!
i want to be nice!
wait a minute, bargy!
if you release the princess, where is the princess?
i don't see her!
i don't know!
princess, go first!
guys, let's find the princess!
let's go, sirva!
bargy, come with us!
sirva!
thank god, i quickly escaped from the fire department!
i have to go now!
where is she?
guys, be quiet!
the princess has been released!
be quiet!
bargy must not be with us!
let's go find her!
unicorn!
stop the fish!
release the princess!
unicorn!
watch out!
wait for me!
be careful!
*screaming*
thank you, bargy!
*growling*
let's use the rocket launcher!
the princess will be angry if we let her go!
ready!
what's wrong?
we can do it!
you're so weak!
how dare you throw me into the fire!
where is the princess?
i'm done with the darkness!
unicorn!
you got the princess!
unicorn, you're so good!
now, we bring the princess to the 8th department!
princess!
come here!
feel this, bargy!
bargy!
where are you going?
here!
don't hurt me!
you're so weak!
unicorn, attack them!
*growling*
congratulations!
now, i have to bring the princess to the 8th department!
bye!
unicorn!
face them, bargy!
*growling*
bargy!
princess!
now, you're in the cage!
Angarang, give the princess to them!
yes, sir!
here, sir!
plant it!
yes, sir!
you'll be sucked by the unicorn!
we can't do this anymore!
let's just drop it!
*the unicorn is attacking the princess*
enough!
we've done the task
here, sir!
why is it only a flower?
wait until the sun is shining
because the sun flower will bloom when the sun is shining
it's still a thousand o'clock
so...
there's still one hour left
let's go!
wait! wait!
I thought...
it can bloom right away
but it has to wait for one hour
okay
I'll wait for you
it's here! let's go!
unicorn!
you're evil!
you're cheating! you're a traitor!
what's that?
what's going on?
help!
sir!
*the unicorn is attacking the princess*
I can't do it anymore!
get up!
*the unicorn is attacking the princess*
mom!
what's wrong?
I forgot
the unicorn is so strong
Akara!
what's that?
there's a fight with Panji
but don't worry
the unicorn will take care of them
let's grow fast!
soon
you'll be immortal
attack that face!
you're too late!
*we can do it*
I'm sure there's something wrong with that face
including that unicorn
I'll look for it
*we can do it*
here it is!
so that the weak unicorn
can see the crying unicorn
what's wrong?
a bomb!
*we can do it*
why is it crying?
the unicorn is not attacking
let's go!
you have to save everyone
*we can do it*
we did it!
we're the
Zing! Zing! Zing!
let's grow fast!
attack that face!
you're too late!
only 10 seconds left
the baby will be born
and you
will never be able to destroy my soul, Alfa
feel this, Alfa
*we can do it*
this is a very special time, Alfa
if you turn your finger
you can advance the time
as much as you turn
if you turn your finger back
you can turn back the time
if you turn off the time
you can stop the time
*we can do it*
stop!
you have 60 seconds
to turn back the time
I need to find a way to save him
open the door!
*we can do it*
don't tell me that the first one is in this box
let me open it
I can't
I'll open the box!
*we can do it*
I can't open it
I'll open it!
*we can do it*
Alfa!
ready!
yes, we did it!
the time is up
it's time to turn back the time
the sword is still here
Alvintar!
Alfa!
Alfara!
*we can do it*
kids
today, Sihir School will give a prize
to 5 brave students
and 1 brave guest
they are
Vega, Plita, Alfa, Rey, and Tole
and one more person
Panji
*we can do it*
I can do it too
me too
*we can do it*
thank you Alfa and everyone
thank you Sihir School
you're welcome
we want to give a prize
that is very valuable
to a brave person
*we can do it*
I'm sure I'm the one who's meant for this
for Bargi
Bargi is here
just stay there
everyone, go!
thank you
Bargi is beautiful
Bargi is happy
*we can do it*
Bargi! Bargi! Bargi!
dare to say no
chase your dreams
go go go
achieve all your dreams
never stop
go go go
strive with your heart
make yourself proud
go go go
let's dream
we can do it
show your spirit
prepare your spirit, my friend
Run, jump, jump, get angry...