To be continued...
Show your spirit, get your friends ready
Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your hopes and dreams
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
I was accepted to a magic school
Three days until the full moon
And if in the full moon, the dark lord gets the stone of eternity
He will get unlimited power and will destroy the whole world
I will prove that I'm right
Just wait and see
I won't let anyone disturb my mission
To take the stone of eternity
And from now on, the school has decided
If Alva is not expelled from the school
Good bye
Let's eat together
Let's eat
Okay
You eat, don't be a spoiled kid
Why are you shaking?
I'm afraid of getting a cold
If you're cold, just do it
I'm afraid my food will be eaten by the drought
No, just do it
Really?
Yes, it will be cold there, hurry up
Hey, you're still down there
I'm going to die
I'm going to die, I'm going to die
I want to meet the guards
Albert!
Let me go!
You will regret it because you have caught me
And don't you think that the dark prince won't wake up
Because you have caught me
The terror won't end here
And in the end, you will lose
This school will be destroyed!
Let me go!
Watch him
Don't let the students hear his scream
Yes, professor
Let me go!
Albert!
Students, now I will teach you how to use the enemy's weapon
Pay attention, okay?
Weapon's ready!
Now it's time for you to practice
Try Ray and...
Where is Tole?
I haven't seen Tole since yesterday
I don't know where Tole is
What should we do?
Professor Adni, I'm sorry, I'll cut the line
Students, I've told you a thousand times
Gorilla, dream of a giraffe
If you want to be a child, don't be a coward
Throw the leftovers in the trash
Who is this?
Huh?
It's a cockroach
Who is it?
Hey, don't be a coward!
Hey, don't tell me that's Metal
Yes, he's a chicken now
He's afraid of me
Megantara, where did you get the chicken?
Near the lake
He ate it and then he ate my food
Albert, that's a big cockroach
Here, Garip
This is a gift for your birthday
Why is it only for flowers?
Here, Garip
For you
For me?
Be careful, Nick!
You too, Garip
Nick, Nick!
Why are you shaking?
I'm not shaking
Nick, Nick!
Why are you shaking?
I don't know either
[Music]
Garip!
Professor!
Garip, the tank has been kidnapped
[Music]
How did it go?
So we ran away to the lake and
There are some dogs following us
And then Karin just disappeared
Oh, how?
It's so scary
Calm down, kids
Megantara
It's better if you take the kids back to school
And tell the others
Don't leave the school until it's safe
Yes, professor
Let's go to the lake, follow me
[Music]
I want to go back to the lake
Who knows if I save Tole
I can be a hero like Alva
Hey, there's a robber
Come back to my friends
[Music]
One by one, don't be late
You guys
[Music]
Come on, come on, guys
Come on, come on
Help me
[Music]
And this is our savior this time
Rey
Who saved Tole and Karin from the attack
[Music]
[Applause]
Ouch
[Music]
Rey
Hold it
Where's Rey?
Rey
Where is she?
That's Rey
Why is she there?
Why isn't she far away?
Wait, wait
I think there's something wrong
It's actually Rey, not like this
Come on, let's follow her
Maybe she has an idea that's not finished
Come on
[Music]
I can't be afraid
Because I'm going to be a hero
[Music]
But
I don't know what the enemy is like
What if the dog is fierce?
What if I get bitten?
[Music]
[Scream]
Tommy
What are you doing here?
We're going to the lake
We're going to beat the dog that stole your friend
Tole
That's a good friend
Good
Sorry
We're not good
We just want to be heroes
It's a waste of your friend's fate
Tole
Don't be like me
I also want to be a hero
What if we go there together?
[Music]
Come on
Where is it?
Where?
Don't be like that
He's in the lake
We have to find him
Come on
Okay, let's go
Where are you going?
[Music]
All students are ordered to stay silent in their respective dormitories
The question is where are you going?
[Music]
Come back
Or I will give you punishment
[Music]
What are you doing in the middle of the hill?
B U B U K A K B U K
Why do you have so many questions?
[Music]
K K Karin
I'm in the lake
My proof
[Music]
Karin
Karin, wake up
Hey
Wake up
[Music]
Where am I?
I don't know either
We must be rescued here by the eagle
[Music]
Mom, Dad
I'm a kid
Help
[Music]
Eh, where are you?
Sorry, Tom, I'm scared
Tom, it's really scary
Where are you? Who are you looking for?
We're all alone
You all scared me
If the eagle doesn't show up
We'll fish for it to show up
Then we catch it
How, Tom? The eagle is here
Yes, Tom
Someone must swim
[Music]
Please, Tom
I can't swim
You know I can't swim
Don't tempt me
[Cough]
I don't feel good, Tom
Yes, Tom
You all are so annoying
That's it
You're all stupid
If you want to lose, you have to swim to the middle
[Music]
Yes
The eagle is here
Hurry up, stupid
[Cough]
[Music]
I'll follow you
If I get caught
I can't be angry
You want to be expelled from this school?
Huh?
Yes, Tom
Om Pimpa Layum Gambreng
[Cheering]
[Music]
It means one of you has to swim
Come on, swim again
Om Pimpa Layum Gambreng
Yes
Two more
It means you and Ray have to swim
Whoever loses has to swim to the middle
Yes, Kong
It should be him
Jack can't swim
He's already drenched before he gets to the middle
Don't waste time
Hurry up, stupid
[Music]
Yes
[Cow mooing]
You have to swim to the middle
Now I have to swim to the middle
You want to be an expert, right?
[Cow mooing]
The horse is coming
Come on, Ray
Come on
[Music]
You can't be fast
You lose
Hurry up, Ray
You're going to lose again
[Music]
Come on, hurry up
Don't be far
To the middle, Ray
I'm already in the middle
You're going to be in the middle
You said you wanted to be an expert
Come on, what are you going to do?
[Music]
Come on, guys
Come on
[Music]
Help
Help me first
[Music]
You think
It's easy to beat the ducklings
[Music]
You think you're all great
The result is very bad
For some students
Must be treated in a treatment clinic
[Music]
If there is a serious problem
This school can be closed
What do you want?
No, Prof
[Music]
Now
You all go back to the dormitory
And no one can leave school
Without any reason
And without exception
Understand?
Understand, Prof
You all I order to clean the school toilet
Without magic
[Music]
What are you doing?
Have you changed there?
[Music]
Now I want to talk to Professor Alubaran
I'm with the professor
[Music]
I'm sure
The ducklings are only in war
It seems there is a greater power
That controls them
I agree
The ducklings are good
Good
They kidnap students
And hurt students
True, Professor
Nine people were injured
And three were missing
And if the parents of the students know
This school can be closed
[Music]
In my opinion
We must take action
To the ducklings
I disagree
[Music]
The ducklings are good
If we don't take action
To the ducklings
More victims will fall
We must take action
Now
Agree
[Music]
Get the doll
Get the broom
[Music]
Bro
We attack
Yes
Attack
[Music]
Stop the attack
They can hurt the children
[Music]
The ducklings should be able to defeat us
But we can't do anything
They attack Karin, Tole and Rey
[Music]
Really
Bro
Rey was kidnapped by the ducklings
We have to help her
[Music]
Basics
Head-strong teachers
I told you
They don't want to hear
[Music]
The ducklings are good
There must be a reason
[Music]
Soldier
Why must be surprised
What is it
Sorry soldier
Do you know if Rey was kidnapped by the ducklings
Yes
I know
We want to free Rey
Do you know what the ducklings' weakness is
[Music]
I don't know
But the ducklings may know
[Music]
Come on
Hey
What
Where are you going
We want to find the ducklings
Yes
Come on
Ouch
[Music]
Alpha
I will call the ducklings
And you hide
Because the ducklings don't like men
[Music]
Watch out Alpha
What's up Vega
Is there anything we can help
Here's the girl from the army
The ducklings attacked us
And my friends were attacked by the ducklings
I want to help the ducklings
Weird
As far as I know, the ducklings are good
Really
But why did they attack my friends
I don't know
But as far as I know, the ducklings don't like to attack people
They prefer to mate
And if they mate, it can last for hours
Is that right, girls
That's right
[Music]
We got the weakness, Vega
The ducklings like to watch
So we have to make them reflect
[Music]
There's another one
Run
[Music]
Ouch Alpha
The ducklings are out
She's going to attack another one
[Music]
The ducklings are so fierce
Vega, don't be sad anymore
We're almost there
[Music]
Come on, Vega
We got the weakness
[Music]
Finger snap
You guys are so stubborn
[Music]
If you want to be free
Answer my question first
You're our friends
Why do you have to be alone with them
[Music]
It's so late, Vega
We'll ask him again tomorrow
[Music]
What's that sound
Let's go up there
[Music]
A duck
Yes
Let's go
Are you ready?
Yes
[Music]
This is perfect, Mike
If we bring this duck to our tent
We can be hunters
Yes, bro
We can be famous than Tommy
That's right
Let's go
[Music]
It's so heavy
Mike, come here
[Music]
Just shut up
It's heavy
[Music]
Where is he, Jack?
Hurry up
[Music]
Hey
Why are you two being chased by the devil
No, boss
We're just chasing the duck
Are you two crazy?
The duck is in the back of the school
Are you serious?
Yes, boss
That's why it's so dangerous
We have to get out of this school
I'll call my dad first
[Music]
Where are they going?
There must be something
[Music]
Mega
He's bleeding, Mega
We have to help him
[Music]
Why did he run away?
I don't know
Maybe he's afraid of us
Okay, Mega
Give him a mirror
To calm him down
Here
Mirror
[Music]
Here's the medicine
Here, Mega
[Music]
That's not fair
They're friends with the duck
Maybe
They're the ones who planned the terror in the school
I have to report this
[Music]
He's smiling
That means he's not angry anymore
Yes
Maybe he's aware
If we treat his face
[Music]
Maybe he wants to kiss you
[Laugh]
[Music]
Um
Duck
Now we're friends, right?
[Squeak]
Answer me
Where are my friends now?
[Music]
Oh
The lake
[Squeak]
[Music]
What's this for?
To eat
[Music]
What's this, Mega?
I read in a book
If the mirror is far from the duck
It can make the person who eats it
Breathe in the water
Wow
That's cool
[Music]
Mega
It feels weird
[Music]
Yes
But
We can breathe in the water now
Right?
[Music]
Show your spirit
Get ready to find friends
[Music]
Running, jumping, jumping
Star
[Music]
Brave
Unknown words
Surrender
[Music]
Chase
Hope and dreams
Go, go, go
Until everyone
[Music]
You're in jail
They're in the water
[Music]
Don't
You guys
Attack my friends because you're forced
[Music]
So
Where are our friends?
[Music]
You don't want to tell me
Hey
Where are you taking us?
[Music]
Don't do it
Don't
You guys are forced
Don't do it
[Music]
You're in jail
Briga
[Music]
Briga, wake up, Briga
Briga
[Music]
Buy soap using a table
Just play with your eyes
[Music]
Because of you
Bro
[Music]
It's better now we take Vega to the clinic
Hurry up, Megantara
Come on
[Music]
Huh
Doctor
Where's the doctor?
[Music]
Doctor
Why are you here?
I need a doctor
Doctor ran away
Why did you run away?
Professor Adebaran asked him to go to the village across
To treat people
So I'm the one who's in charge
Okay, okay, that's enough
Now, please, please, Vega
He's been possessed by Professor Purwa
Oh, that's a bad kid, Purwa
Wow, that's a bad omen, it can't be
I mean Professor Purwa
Yes, wait
Mom
Do you need to call 10 girls?
Like when you cure Ray
Uh, I don't think so
This seems to be worse
Uh, worse
[Music]
So what?
He must use the water of the butterfly
Now the butterfly has run away
What should we do?
[Music]
Vega
You wait
I will definitely find the water of the butterfly for you
[Music]
Quiet
The point is, me and my husband
Don't want to hear any excuses
And now I will bring my beloved son Tommy
To the village
Because in my opinion, it's not safe here
Right, daddy?
Right, honey?
Uncle
Mike and I want to go with you
Come on, uncle
We ride, uncle
Oh, sure
Uncle has prepared the ship, we go home
Daddy, you can't invite your father
I will not stop my father and mother
If you want to bring your son and mother home from this school
And I, after I become the head of the school
Apologize
For all the inconveniences that my parents have experienced
And I will try to solve this problem as soon as possible
[Music]
Think you
Think
Vega
[Music]
Sorry, professor, I didn't mean to
It's okay, Alva
How's Vega?
That's right, professor
I want to tell you, professor
The only way to save Vega
Use the Eremata Duyung
Eremata Duyung
Okay, Alva
Let's go now
Look for Eremata Duyung
So Vega can be saved quickly
[Music]
Alva, let me call the Duyung
Don't, professor
Later the Duyung is afraid
Let me call
[Music]
Putri Duyung, where are you?
Putri Duyung, I need your help
Putri Duyung
[Music]
Until now, Vega is still unconscious
Because of the magic of the ancient professor
He said the offer is your Eremata
Can I ask for your Eremata for Vega?
[Music]
Daffa, hold on tight
Alva, put it here
[Music]
Thank you Putri Duyung
You're so kind
[Music]
Duyung
Who did that?
I did it
[Music]
What do you want?
It's none of your business
You better go now
Bring the Eremata and save your friend
Hurry
Alva, you better bring the Eremata now
Poor Vega
[Music]
I will make sure Putri Duyung will be fine
Hurry up
I'm sorry Putri Duyung
I have to go
But I will help you
Daffa, hold on tight
[Music]
Vega, you're cured
You're cured
I was bewitched by Professor Purwa
What about Duyung?
He ran away
Thank God
But he came back
Why?
Because the only way to make you realize
That's Eremata Duyung
[Music]
He came back just to help me?
Yes, because he's back
He was caught by Professor Purwa
We have to help him
I don't want him to get hurt
Let's go
I have caught Duyung
And now we can interrogate him
To find out where the students are being held
Let me show you
[Music]
It's so delicious
Let's go home
Luckily, you came here quickly
Or else we could have kidnapped Duyung
Right?
Of course, who's first?
Tommy
Alva and Vega will be kidnapped by Duyung
That's right
What's going on?
Tommy, help me
Tommy
Help me
[Music]
[Screaming]
Tommy, help me
Tommy
[Music]
Tommy, help me
Tommy
[Music]
What's going on?
What's that?
Tommy
Why is he here?
I don't know
[Screaming]
Open the door
He's been kidnapped
Open the door, it's so heavy
[Screaming]
Give me back my brother!
Brother!
Help!
Two more children.
Then your task will be done.
And I will give you back your voice.
Remember.
One of those children...
must be named Alva.
Alva.
I know that voice.
Yes, I feel like I know him too.
But who?
Yes, it's so weird.
Why does that person know Alva?
Who is he?
Alva.
You're wrong if you think I'm going to lose.
I will never lose, Alvaro.
I will never lose.
Alvaro's voice.
Where is he?
Alvaro.
The terror will continue.
Until I get that chosen child.
Take him to the lake.
Everyone will attack the castle first.
We can do it.
Now tell me where the students are hiding.
Answer me.
Don't be ridiculous.
I will kill you.
Calm down.
Come in.
Get out, professor.
Get out.
Come on.
Tommy.
Tommy, wake up.
Help me.
I'm going to kill you.
What happened?
We were walking.
There was a big wave.
Then the students appeared.
They pulled Tommy and his friends to the sea.
Tommy.
That's why we're here.
To ask for your help.
We have to find the students and destroy the castle.
I agree.
We attack the students.
They are too much.
I disagree.
Is Duyung really a good person?
Megatara is right.
He wants to give his power to Vega.
If Duyung is a good person, why did they kidnap the students?
I agree.
I will help them.
There must be something that forces them to do that.
Megatara.
If you're afraid, you can stay here.
But don't be too hasty.
Everyone, get ready.
We go to the castle first.
Your friends have kidnapped the students.
We will attack your castle to free the students.
Megatara, do you see where they are?
They are going to attack the castle.
Alva, let's go to the lake.
Okay.
Alva.
Megatara.
Why are our students in danger?
Wait.
You're wrong.
Duyung is a good person.
They are bad people.
Professor Purwoh.
Did you hear what Alva said?
Yes.
I think we should stop this attack.
Instead of doing stupid things and endangering people.
No.
I have to find my daughter, Tobi.
And I have to take revenge on Duyung.
Because he has ruined my life.
Alva must have been brainwashed by Duyung.
What should we do?
We're late.
Let's just follow them.
Okay.
Alva.
Vega.
What are you doing?
You can swim.
You can attack.
Palm trees.
Turquoise trees.
You can't attack.
You can only attack.
We have no other choice.
We don't want to hurt Duyung.
We will use this method.
This is the method.
Daffatang.
Bufa Bajo.
Bufa Renang.
Wow.
That's cool.
By using this method.
We can breathe.
And talk inside.
Okay.
Ready.
One.
Two.
Three.
That's where Duyung's palace is.
Let's call them.
Hey, Duyung.
Come out.
We have captured one of your friends.
If you don't come out and surrender.
We will punish your friend.
Why aren't they coming out?
Be patient.
We will wait a little longer.
They will come out to kill him.
Be patient.
You are a swine.
Alva, it's dangerous.
We have no other choice.
No, Mama.
I'm scared.
We are all scared.
And hungry.
Karim.
Bufa.
Shut up.
Remember.
If you dare to do anything.
I will make you become a swine.
To be continued...
(Preview of the previous episode)
(Preview of the next episode)