Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Where are you?
I can find you
So, it's better if you don't reject my offer
You are my student
So, you will be a great sniper
The dark night took the soul stone from Prof. Alibara
And...
His wife used the soul stone to protect her strength
I want to torture him
No, I don't want to
If you want to, I will stab you with my first sword
Come on, do it quickly
Good, come on, keep doing it
If you stop this torture, I will...
Torture you
Come on, keep doing it
Don't stop
Before the target stops appearing
Hahahahaha
Baku
Aryan
That's food for you
I don't want to accept that evil food
Take that food out
You don't know yourself
Taste this
Hey, enough
Stop it
Taste this
It's okay, it's okay
It's okay, Mr. Alibara
I just can't see that food
Because that food is a curse
A curse from the dark night
Because my grandson has fulfilled his wish
Mr. Alibara
I swear
I will never let them steal my grandson's heart
Never
Aryan, what's taking him so long?
He said he went to the toilet
But it's been so long
I'll just make it myself
Let's go
[Suspense Music]
I want to change
I've changed into the darkest night
Yes, yes, yes
Actually, I hate it when people change into the darkest night
Because they are evil
But I'm doing this for Mr. Alibara
[Suspense Music]
Aryan, are you hungry?
I'm hungry
[Suspense Music]
You're not your usual self, are you?
I'll help you
[Suspense Music]
Thank God you can stand up again
That's all yours
[Suspense Music]
This is for me
Thank you
[Suspense Music]
See you again
This is the second lesson for you
Don't help anyone
Or anyone
Because helping others
Only makes your heart hurt
[Suspense Music]
Nick, stop it
I can't walk anymore
Men, you have to be strong
We can find the eyes of the monster
No, Nick
I can't do it anymore, Nick
I swear
I won't give up
[Suspense Music]
That's it
I found it
We found it
Nick
It's true, Nick
Those are the eyes
I'm sorry
I'll go first, Nick
[Suspense Music]
It's true, Nick
That's it
I'm sorry
[Suspense Music]
Now
It's time for action
Yes
[Suspense Music]
Sir
Eh
Professor Ankara
Tumben
Sir called me professor
I'm surprised
You came in
Without knocking the door first
Yes
I'm sorry, sir
Because I thought
There's no one here
Oh yeah
What's up, sir?
Eh
I came here
To scold you
Scold me?
What did I do wrong, sir?
A lot of things wrong with you
Since you came to this school
You punish your students
Those are kids you punish outside
In the field
That's wrong, you know?
But
He's very smart, sir
He's a traitor
I don't care
The point is
I want you to free them all
And then you apologize
Free them, sir?
Yes, and don't forget
You give them chocolate and candy
Give them candy?
Yes, as a way to make them feel
You're wrong with them
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to
I taught them well
Before they were like that
Why
Now I'm the one
Who apologize to them
What?
They became my followers?
Yes, sir
Why are you surprised?
No
Who's surprised?
I'm not surprised
I just don't like your way
Your way is wrong
If you're like this
How can they become my followers?
They'll be the one who's going to be the back up
Do you understand?
Yes, I'm sorry, sir
Okay, it's okay
You're my student too
Okay, sir
Yes
Vega
I brought you a drink
How much is it?
Later
Professor Ragni will be punished by Professor Angkara
Okay, Vega, just drink it
You better not be weak
Even if Professor Angkara punish you
Let him be
Yes, Vega
Professor Ragni is right
You better drink it
Now
Instead of being caught by Professor Angkara
We'll be punished
I don't want to be punished
Yes, Vega
I'll keep an eye on you
If there's Professor Angkara
I'll tell him
Listen to your friend
Now, drink it
So you won't be weak
Ragni
I told you not to help him
Angkara
Poor Vega, he's weak
If you want to punish him, just do it
You better release him, Vega
Enough
I don't want to talk about this anymore
Vega
Your sentence is over
Seriously?
I never lie
About what I said
Thank you, Professor
Vega, come back here
Vega
Professor
I
I'm sorry
For all my actions
I
I'll get a permit
Permit?
Thank you, Professor
Thank you
I'm going
I'm sorry
For the Professor
And this
Give all these permits to your students
As a request from me
Thank you, Professor
Let's go, Vega
I'm sorry
Why?
Angkara is a good guy now
Lucky
The punishment
Is not stopped
He gave me a permit
I'm so lucky
But
Don't you feel bad for Professor Angkara?
Why did he suddenly
Do that to us?
He freed me from the punishment
And apologized to all of us
After that
He gave me a permit
Why is he like Professor Titan?
Why is he laughing?
And then?
I'll clean this up
I'm so lucky
Sir
Have you done your job?
Yes, sir
I've freed all the punishment
Yes
Sir
Are you okay?
I think something is wrong with you
I'm okay
What's our next plan?
Our next plan?
Yes
I'll be a good son
What's our next plan?
I...
I have a plan
What is it?
But
Before that
I want to know
Where is Professor Aldo Baran?
Didn't you already know?
Yes, but
I didn't ask you to tell me
Yes, I know
You're the one who told me
To find out where Professor Aldo Baran is
Sir
Sir, please be nice
What?
I'm being nice?
Yes, sir
I'm sorry, sir
I think something is wrong with you
Are you trying to steal from me?
No, sir
I just...
That's enough
I'm leaving
I have other things to do
I'm sorry, sir
I think something is wrong with you
In the dark world
We're not so sure
If we meet someone
We don't know if that person is the real one
So
The enemy is coming
No, no
Someone is trying to steal from me
Where are you going?
Wait
Rey, wait
You look like the dark one
You're not going to tell Rey?
I'm sure I ran away
I'm sure
I was right
All of these are
The naughty kids
This is too much
How dare they
Call me the dark one
Guys
We have to run
What for?
There's a terrorist
Run
Wait and see
Where are they?
That was fast
I'm going to get them
This time they succeeded in kidnapping me
But next time
I won't be fooled
By those naughty kids
Watch out
I think it's safe
We have to tell the others
Wait
Why?
You always use water
Because it's scary
Let's go
Soldiers
We found it
The source of the water
We're great, right?
You're great
It's not a waste
You're chosen as the Aldebaran soldiers
You can find drinking water
Cool
Thank you
Look at our faces
We brought it for you
Thank you
You're welcome
I want to drink it first
Give it to me
Let's do a sweet
Me?
Me
I'll drink it first
Stop
Soldiers
We're thirsty
Don't drink that water
Stop
Nick
They're poisoned
So you used the source of the water
To make the anchor
You're so brave
Give me a smile
You're smart
I admire your bravery
But when are we going to call the soldiers
From the fire prison?
Alfa
The fire prison is far away
Whoever goes there
Will never come back
We can't give up yet
We have to find a way
To get the professor out
How?
Don't worry, leave it to me
I'll find a way to get the professor out
Give me a smile
Sorry
I'm flustered
It's okay
Give me a smile
Professor Agni
How are you going to get out of here?
The anchor will come for you
Don't worry
I'll think of something
Give me a smile
Thank you, professor Agni
You're great
Look
If I see them again
I'll sue you
Why are you still here?
Someone wants to talk to you
Enough
I know who you are
Stop pretending
You can either do it or I'll sue you
What do you mean?
Stop pretending
I could be fooled
But now
I can't anymore
You better confess
Or I'll sue you
You're rude
You dare to deceive the head of the school
Don't make me angry
Fine
I'll sue you
Why didn't you say anything?
What do you mean?
Why did you insult me?
I'm sorry
I thought it was my students
Because one of them
Wanted to be a teacher
And he sued me
So, you should be a teacher
Don't be stupid
You have to be strong
Even though you hurt the students
Especially you
I'll give you one more chance
You destroy the school
Don't let it fail
I'll sue you
I'll wait for your answer
You can do it
You're professor Agni
Why did you come to my class?
Do you finally want to admit
That I'm the head of the school
And I'm the head of the school
But it's the opposite
I'm here because I want to quit
You're lying
Are you sure?
You want to quit the school?
That's your dream
I know that
My decision is final
I can't be changed
Agni!
I'm sorry
Call me
Call you?
I'm sorry
Call you
You asked me to do it
I'm sorry
I thought you're still in front of me
What did you call me?
I'm sorry
You're fired
You're safe now
Let's go
That's the thief
I was with my friends
And we found the thief
That's creepy
We have to tell professor Angkara
So we can get the prize
Okay
Professor Angkara!
Professor!
We want to tell you something important
What is it?
Professor, you scared us
We want to tell you something important
What is it?
The thief
You're so loud
How can I hear you?
You're confusing me
Speak one by one
You!
Enough!
You must be quiet
I don't have much time
The thief that was here yesterday
He's in this school
He's friends with Alfa
His friends
Friends with Alfa?
Yes
He's a student
His name is Panji
Not Panji
Panji!
His real name is
Panji
Panji?
He's in the school's next door
So, the real Panji
The thief that was here yesterday
He's a student
Where are you going?
Where's our gift?
Maybe he's not here
Let's follow him
The first plan has succeeded
Now, it's time for me to free Prof. Alfara
My dear Otel!
He's here!
We can do it!
Look
I've prepared all of that for you
What is it, Sir?
Why are you asking again?
It's all for you to practice
The magic
Can I practice without hurting anyone?
I don't want to, Sir
If you don't practice with this animal
How can you be strong?
Do you want to be weak?
That's it
Now, you have to free the animal one by one
What is it?
Leo
Leo, you can do it
The magic
Vika
Good, Sir
Look, the cat is angry
People who do evil
Must be punished
Natural punishment
Shut up, Leon
Don't teach me
Do it, I said
Keep on doing it
Come on
What is this?
Keep on doing it
Come on
Keep on doing it, Leon
Good
What is it, Sir?
Their power is getting weaker
They are hungry
They are thirsty
What should we do?
We are just like this
What if we become three?
We will die
Shout, shout
Calm down, please
Our friend is like this
How can we calm down?
How can we cure them?
We have the antidote
You are right, Pijat
The antidote
We are now for the antidote
To cure them
You must bring
The book about the antidote
Just bring it
In your bag
Try it
Tentara, this is the book
Yes, Tentara
I have read
About the antidote
For poison
If our body is poisoned
By the water of padang burung
Wait a minute
The antidote
For poison
By the water of padang burung
Here it is
The antidote to cure
The person whose body
Is poisoned by the water of padang burung
Can be cured
By using
The flower of the devil cactus
Praise the lord
For the success of yesterday
Yes
They can be cured by the flower of the devil cactus
That we faced yesterday
Come on, what are you waiting for?
Let's go
Why are you quiet?
You four
Have passed the test
Chosen as the brave soldiers
Don't be a coward
You can't face the devil cactus
You don't deserve to be brave
The soldiers are brave
To fight the cactus
No
Therefore
To fight the devil cactus
I need your help
If we work together
We can
Defeat it
Oh my
Soldiers
We are not strong anymore
We are weak
We haven't drunk or eaten
What else to eat?
Let's fight the cactus
We have lost
Go home
Eat a lot
If only
The food falls from the sky
Wow
Food
Soldiers
Pray to the lord
The cactus is really cool
Really
The food falls from the sky
Wow
Since when
I read
The cactus can be this powerful
My cactus
He's here
Hotel
Go to the hotel
Bring the kite
Buy the kite
And the fish
My dear hotel
I miss you
Let's see
Did you bring my order?
Bring a lot of food
Complete everything
Good hotel
This is a bad hotel
Why did you just come?
I'm hungry
Oh my god
You're not as strong as before
You didn't come since yesterday
You're stupid
I'm hungry
So
Don't you dare
To insult my bike
Now feel the consequences
This is a bike
You can be angry
Feel it
For now
You can stay here
There's no army
Okay
Thank you
It's okay
Sir
Where's the man?
Man?
You mean the professor?
Don't be stupid
I know you know a man
Called Panji
No
We don't know him
We saw him
He's coming here
Don't be stupid
Shut up
I'm just asking you to be honest
If not
You and all your friends
Will be punished severely
Does the professor
Have proof that I'm lying?
Don't lie to me
I know the proof
I know you're drinking Ramuan
To change your face
And you're changing yourself
To a dark hero
Right?
So now
I'm asking you
To tell me where Panji is
I told you
I don't know him
He's lying
Shut up
Okay then
Now I'm going to punish you
And all your friends
Tommy, Mike, Jack
Get them
I'm sorry
Don't punish my friends
Punish me
Get them
Your request was late
So now
I'm going to punish you
Professor is a bad person
Shut up
Because soon
The sun will rise
And you'll be the victims
Get them
Eat it
I'm Panji
I won't die easily
Because of a coward like you
We can do it
If I'm really here
He won't be able to see
A tragedy like this
And when he's here
To help Alfa and his friends
That's when I'll finish him
You're a bad person
You think I'll just stay quiet
And watch everything happen?
Okay
Mufundur Harimau
Why is Harimau back?
He's angry
Who did this?
Who?
Come with me
Professor's power is not strong enough
Don't you dare insult me
Who did this?
Mufundur Harimau
He's going to explode
Mufundur
Mufundur Harimau
Who did this?
Is this your power?
It's not us
It's him
Who?
We're enemies
Don't hurt us
Shut up
This is what I'm doing
Come on
Get out
Don't be a coward
Show your face
Get out
He knows I'm here
But I'll stay hidden in this cave
I'll let him find me
I'll do it my way
Get out
Help
And then, suddenly...
I get it!
A firefly?
Huh? a firefly?
that... is the firefly
[music]
Erik, Fija, we are full and drunk and have enough rest
Now, it's time for us to take action
Are you ready?
Ready, sir!
Okay, what we will do to attack this giant cactus
We have to use tactics
And the tactics we use is guerilla tactics
What is guerilla tactics, sir?
Guerilla tactics is...
One person will go forward fishing as a bait
So that later it will be attacked by the cactus
When the cactus attacks, the others are ready to attack and attack
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Okay
Now, there must be one person who is fishing as a bait
This is a very dangerous task
Who will be the bait?
The soldier!
Huh?
Why me?
Oh, mama...
Everyone knows the soldier
The oldest here is a soldier
How about that?
And also, Purcha is the fattest, right?
Yes, Purcha
The most flexible, like a buffalo
I know
Enough, you young people
Your life is hard
Okay, now let's start
Ready, sir!
Now, we attack!
Eric!
You're just a little kid
But you're still alive!
I'm Panji
It's not easy for me to die in the hands of a trickster like you, Kahra
Zal!
Panji, you have to win, okay?
I hope you win
Yes
Panji! Panji!
Come on, Panji!
Come on!
Hey, you didn't pay for my hug!
You hugged us!
Yes, so I'm the first one to get stung
I'm the first one to get stung
I remind you all
If you lie to me again
I will give you to the family
Yeah!
Yeah, Panji won!
Yes!
Now, you go there
You free the body and the friends
Hey, Srigala
Don't expect me to obey your will
If that's what you want
Now I will also find the 8th prince
You
Find the 8th prince?
Yes
I'm afraid of being killed
[Laughter]
What are you laughing at?
I found the 8th prince
To prove that I'm still alive
So he knows
That his poor fruit child
Has killed him
Hmm?
You think I don't want to threaten your peanuts?
Okay, if you're not afraid
Now put down your staff
Or do you regret it?
Put it down!
If you're not afraid
Now I will also find the 8th prince
See you
Wait!
Okay
I will obey your will
Hurry up!
You've been like this for a while
Now hurry
You go there
You free them
Come on
Come on, hurry
[Laughter]
You're a fool
You're afraid of that?
I don't know where the 8th prince is
Vivilla!
I warn you all
If you lie to me again
I will give you to Barga
And Barga will eat you
Barga?
Not Barga?
I'm going to destroy you, sir!
Shut up, you fool!
Enough!
Follow my order!
Sir!
Thank you
Now we're free
Yes!
We're free!
The punishment is over
It's not fun
[Cheering]
You missed!
You're a coward!
Come on, attack me
You missed!
You're a coward!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Eric!
Are you okay?
What should we do, soldier?
I fell down, it hurts so much
Come on, cheer up!
Our job is not done yet
We have to get that cactus flower
We got the flower
You're great!
Good
We did it, Jack!
You're a coward!
Let's run!
Dad!
I miss you so much
You're so kind
You're so kind, Opa
We miss you too
How?
Have you got the cactus flower?
I'm sorry, Dad
I haven't got the cactus flower yet
I heard that I have to burn 12 stones first
So the cactus flower can die
Opa
To help us, you don't have to be a murderer
Because to make us aware
You only need a drop of blood of the 8th prince
Only a drop of blood
A drop of blood?
Only a drop of blood of the 8th prince
So that's how it is
Rai, Rai, Rai
Wake up, Rai
Wake up
Rai, Rai, Rai
What's wrong, Dad?
Wake up, Rai
What's wrong, Rai?
I don't know
What's wrong, Dad?
Why are you still sleeping?
It's not important what I'm talking about
What's important, Dad?
Yes, I'm dreaming about eating delicious food
Until I'm not hungry anymore
I'm sorry to wake you up
But there's something important I want to talk about
What is it, Dad?
What's important?
It's about my parents
Let's go find Mr. Panji
Let's go
Don't go back on your word
What should we do?
This is a collection of the remains of the Raksasa cactus
That will heal their wounds
Tentara
Why is there no reaction?
It's been a long time
I went to the market to buy some vegetables
Be patient and wait
Oh, no
Nik, you're awake
Wake up
(Grunting)
I'm sorry
What did we do?
What's wrong?
You two fainted
You drank too much
Luckily, there's a soldier
He saved you two
He brought you some medicine
Thank you, soldier
Thank you, too
This is a lesson for all of us
As members of the magic school
We have to help each other
Listen up
Make a sound
Then, you can do the magic
The break is over
It's time to continue
Yes, sir
So, we're going to the army?
Yes, right now
What are you waiting for?
Look, my dear hotel
Not only food and drinks
He brought lollipop for you four
We have to respect the hotel
Respect for the hotel
Yes, sir
Wow
It's new
Thank you, sir
This is a new lollipop for you
Thank you, soldier
Let's go
Okay
Ready?
Ready, soldier
One, two, three
Break!
That's the place
I have to get inside
Meteor, fire!
What's that?
Let's see
Let's go
Where is professor Aldemar?
The sorcerer is here
Catch him!
Stop!
Where is he?
Over there!
Don't close the door
What should we do?
[The sorcerer is here]
The sorcerer's aroma is gone
Where is he?
They can't see
They can only sense
That's why I turned into a cat
So they don't realize
That's what my parents said in my dream
Ufa, are we going to fight the dark?
Are you kidding?
You're crazy
We're just being chased
We're already in trouble
But I don't want to fight
I just want to take his blood
What should we do?
Alfa, what should we do?
If we want to get the dark's blood
We have to fight him first
What should we do?
I don't know
We're just seeing his face
We don't have to be afraid
I'm scared
I think I can get the dark
That's the person we can trust
The person we can trust?
It must be Angkara
That's right!
I'm going to be Angkara's professor
That's good
What's next?
Are you going to use the magic potion again?
I think we shouldn't be afraid
We should not be reminded
Angkara's professor has a plan
He must be aware of us
That's right
Have you forgotten?
We've been taught to change our minds
We always feel like we're old
We're going to be the new generation
What's going on?
Stop!
The army is here!
It looks like we're going to be there soon
Finally, the army is here
Wait!
We can't work like that anymore
The plane is too fast
It's going to take off
Let's use the magic potion
(Credits)
Let's make sure
you