To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Go, go, go, never stop
The prison of fire is very far away
And whoever goes there, will never return
Panji, we can't give up yet
We still have to try to find a way to get Professor Aldebaran out
Where do you think Professor Aldebaran is?
There's a snitch coming here, catch him!
Catch him!
The snitch is gone, where is he?
They can't see, they can only sense, that's why I turned into a cat
Don't be afraid, don't be fooled
Professor Ankara has a plan
He must have been in contact with us
Have you forgotten? We've been taught to change our souls
The soul is the key to change the body
The mantra we're going to learn today is the body changing mantra
I finda jiwa
Yes, I think that's a very good idea
Panji, where's my body?
Of course, Alva
Here
Okay, I'll go first
Alva
Be careful
We're coming too
I'm coming too
Remember, after Professor Ankara appears, we'll start the action
Okay
I think he's not at the door
Why is there someone there?
The soul is here!
What?
Vega, calm down
That's Professor Ankara
He's only gone for a while
So, Alva has entered Professor Ankara's body?
Yes, I'm inside now
Let's continue our other plans
Okay, I'll go first
Now, please take care of Professor Ankara
Okay
Crazy!
Don't be so fast, that's still my body
My body will get sick
Yes, sir
But, we're going to discuss about that later
Okay?
Yes, Re
Okay, I'll go now
Okay, sir
The world's first telecommunication network in Indonesia.
To the next generation.
And the future.
Does romance exist?
With "Happy Together".
But now, "Hopefully Together".
"Surely Together".
"Together, Never Alone".
Yes! Now I'm a professor of physics.
But how do I call the 8th dimension?
Let's just try it.
Who knows, maybe the 8th dimension will really come.
It worked! Yes!
One, two, three, sling, dos, cedar!
Why are you so excited, Angkara?
No, sir. I'm just warming up, sir.
Yes, yes, yes. That's it, sir.
Oh, yes, sir. Come here, sir.
Come here?
Yes, sir. I'm in front of you, sir.
You come here. I have a lot of things to do, Angkara.
I can't go there.
I don't know where the place is.
If I ask, it must be in the middle of the 8th dimension.
What is this?
No, sir.
Sir, I'm now the head of the school.
And I have to take care of all the students in the school.
All the students will be your followers.
Right, sir?
Okay, sir. Come here, sir.
Be careful on the road, sir. Bye.
Why is Angkara so naughty now?
And who is the real master?
Me or Angkara?
(The King of Angkara)
I was so nervous.
I felt like I was going to be kicked out.
I'm the king now.
You just guard the door so no one can come in.
Okay, sir. I'll go out and hide.
I'll hide inside.
I'll hide.
Here, a girl.
She's so pretty.
What should we do?
If she wakes up, we'll be caught.
Wait.
Oh, right. The TV is on.
What?
I'm so hungry.
I'm almost full.
Let's go inside.
Yes.
Toilet.
Let's go inside.
Let's go.
Okay.
(The King of Angkara)
What's going on here?
Why is it so scary when I come in?
(The King of Angkara)
What's going on?
Sir, you scared me.
Please sit down.
Sir, when did this happen?
Don't talk too much.
What did you talk to the king?
Look, sir.
I'm not a spy.
It's a big story.
I managed to punish Ava.
What did you punish her?
Wait, sir.
Good, Angkara.
Taste this.
What are you doing?
Nothing, sir.
I'm just relaxing, sir.
It's good, sir.
It's not that, sir.
Angkara, I still want to see.
It's okay, sir.
It's not important.
Let's just finish this.
Sir, I want to discuss something with you.
What do you want to discuss?
It's okay.
Let's go.
What's going on?
A snake!
It's so close.
Vega, let's go.
Let's go get some food.
Okay.
Syair!
It's so close.
Just a little bit more.
If not, Ava will be angry.
Because her body is burning.
Let's go.
Let's go, sir.
Sir, before we start,
please have a drink.
Here, I made a drink, sir.
What is this, Angkara?
Give this drink to him.
He will be satisfied.
Here.
What is that, sir?
I don't know what it is.
It's coffee, sir.
I know it's Angkara coffee.
But since when did you drink coffee?
Sir, this is a sign of our success.
We've punished Alva.
And also,
the adults said...
coffee is a friend of a person who is having an affair.
A person who is having an affair.
This is his friend.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome, sir.
This is what happened, sir.
Sir.
Sir, what's wrong?
Why am I sleepy?
Are you sleepy, sir?
Sir.
You better go to sleep, sir.
No.
I'm a dark wizard.
If it's just a matter of day,
I can do it.
Yes, I did it.
What do you think?
Dark wizard.
I'll give you some blood.
It doesn't hurt.
It feels like...
I'm being bitten by a mosquito.
[The Dark Wizard]
I'm going to sleep.
Bye.
[The Dark Wizard]
Rasker Adebaran!
It looks like...
we're going to reach our destination soon.
We're finally here, soldier.
Ready.
We're landing soon.
Prepare for landing.
Let's go.
[The Dark Wizard]
Soldier.
Is this the right place?
I don't know, soldier.
There's no name tag.
I'm sure.
This is the place we're going to.
[The Dark Wizard]
I think you're not going to sleep here.
What are you doing here?
My love.
I'm here...
if it's my luck.
I'm not going anywhere.
I agree with you, soldier.
The animals here...
are all beautiful.
Oh, my.
My body is stiff.
I'm so refreshed.
I see beautiful animals like this.
You guys are embarrassing us.
Watch your manners.
Don't be rude.
When we're with women,
we shouldn't underestimate ourselves as men.
You're embarrassing us by flirting.
Watch your mouth.
Let the man ask.
[The Dark Wizard]
You want to be a man?
But who's going to be your man?
Excuse me, sir.
I want to ask you something.
What?
Is it true...
that this village is called...
the fishing village?
Yes, it's true.
If so,
allow us to meet...
your leader.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
What is this?
No one's coming.
Guys.
What's up, sir?
Did you succeed?
Of course.
Look.
I got the Dark Wizard's blood.
Here, Vega.
You're great, sir.
Let's go to your parents' house.
Let's go.
I'll go first.
What are we going to do?
Oh, right.
Sorry, guys.
I forgot that my soul is still in Professor Angkara's body.
Let's go back a little.
Move, soul!
Help me.
Hurry.
Here.
The door is locked.
Hurry.
(The Dark Wizard's blood)
I'm sleeping here.
No.
Something's happening.
How can I sleep here?
Where's Angkara?
It's useless to have a fruit kid.
You're not supposed to sleep here.
You're not allowed to sleep here.
What's wrong?
My finger is hurt.
Who did this?
Why did I sleep outside?
Angkara!
Sir.
Why are you here?
Angkara.
What did you do when I was eating?
I'm sorry, sir.
What do you mean?
Don't lie to me.
You let me sleep here...
and you hurt my finger to take my blood.
The holy blood.
Sir, I really don't understand.
If it wasn't you, who would dare to take my blood?
Sir, I couldn't do it.
Sir, I'm confused now.
Why did I sleep outside?
Someone must have done this to you.
He hurt my finger to take my blood.
I won't let this go.
I'll take your blood.
Sir, I'll help you find him.
Shut up, you bastard.
This is all because of you.
But, sir... / Shut up!
You're here because I'm going to give you a hard punishment.
What's going on?
I'm really confused.
(The King's Palace)
Please come in. The King is waiting for you inside.
Thank you.
Your Highness, there's a traveler looking for you.
Greetings, Your Highness.
(The King's Palace)
See, Nik? I told you.
The people here are beautiful.
Especially the queen.
I swear, I'll die here.
Eda, especially me.
My eyes are fresh.
What are you looking for?
Let me introduce you, Your Highness.
My name is Megantara.
And they are students from the magic school.
Our purpose of coming here is...
to find a stone.
A stone? What stone?
(The King's Palace)
Nik.
What's that?
I don't know, Tengkara.
But it looks like a stone.
(The King's Palace)
Tengkara, that's...
What's that?
That's the soul of the stone.
What are you doing?
Don't you dare to touch my king.
(The King's Palace)
Forgive us for our previous plans.
Why are you playing with the stone?
Don't be ridiculous.
You want to be punished in someone's village?
I'm not playing with the stone, Tengkara.
I'm taking the stone.
What stone?
You don't know, Megantara?
The detector is pointing to the stone.
It means that the stone is inside the queen's chest.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with my chest?
Your Highness.
As we have said.
We came here to look for the stone.
But not just any stone.
We're looking for the soul of the stone.
And...
It seems...
The soul of the stone that we're looking for...
The queen is holding it.
This is my grandmother's legacy.
The legacy of my ancestors.
King.
Who dares to take my blood?
Get out!
Kelembu.
Show me who dares to take my blood.
And where is my blood?
There it is.
That child.
It's Alva who dares to take my blood.
Teach him a lesson.
I'll let you do it, Alva.
I didn't expect that I managed to get the queen's blood in the dark.
I can't wait to see my mom and dad...
Awake from their long sleep.
To be continued...
Dad.
Mom.
Alva.
It's not morning yet.
We're going to wake up early.
Yes, sir.
Let's fly.
To be continued...
What's wrong?
Why are you doing this to yourself?
What's wrong? -I don't know.
That's Alva.
Wait!
Look.
There!
Aido.
There's blood!
Wait!
Let's help Alva.
Let's go.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Wait!
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
I'm dizzy.
I'm tired. -I'm hungry.
I want to go to the car with gasoline.
Ouch.
What's wrong?
My butt hurts.
Don't fight in this situation.
One, two, three.
Wait.
What's that?
What's that? -It's in front of you.
It's here. -What's that?
What's that? -There's blood.
Yes.
It's bleeding. My butt hurts.
It's bleeding.
I'm going to the car.
Don't fight.
Don't go.
Hurry up.
What's that?
Wait.
We can't do that anymore.
It flies so fast.
It's going to be high.
Let's use a remote control.
Now, it's time...
to draw the blood.
To be continued...
We can do it.
Come on, sir.
I'm coming.
Hurry up.
Come on, sir.
To be continued...
Blood!
Come to me!
Come on, sir.
To be continued...
Finally.
The holy blood is back.
To be continued...
Be patient, sir.
We'll use another way.
Sir.
Don't give up.
Now,
no one can defeat me.
Or take my holy blood.
Anak Wilian!
Sir.
Eat this chocolate.
Thank you.
I'm not hungry.
You haven't eaten for days.
If you keep doing this,
you'll get sick.
I don't care.
I'm living for free.
If my grandson is taken by the 8th prince.
Even though,
I've been surviving all this time.
For my grandson.
Agni.
Professor Aldebaran.
I finally found you, professor.
How did you get here?
It's a long story, professor.
I came here to save you.
Let's go, professor.
We have to go now.
That's impossible, Agni.
I can't leave this place.
Of course you can, professor.
You can use the magic to turn a seed into a bird, right?
Do it, professor.
Are you sure?
Yes, professor.
It turns out,
the guardians are blind.
They can only see through the people around them.
Come on, professor.
What are we waiting for?
Let's turn the seed into a bird.
And we'll leave this place right away.
Wait.
Go.
You have the right to be free.
Sir.
I can't leave you like this.
If you're worried about me,
I beg you.
Please save my grandson.
That way, I'll be fine.
I have high hopes for you.
Please save my grandson.
Where's the seed?
Let's go now.
Before the guardians get here.
Come on.
Go.
Now,
the holy blood has returned to me.
I won't let you come back.
Never again.
I'm in front of you.
Listen to me.
Leon.
Wake up, Leon.
Wake up.
What's wrong, sir?
I'm still sleepy.
You have to wake up.
Because,
I know how to set you free.
And he's waiting for you outside.
He's going to set me free?
Sir.
Leon.
My grandson.
I miss you, Leon.
I miss you.
You can't get close to your grandpa.
Who are you?
Then, why can't I get close to my grandpa?
Sir.
Sir, please help.
Wake up, sir.
Why are you hurting this old man?
Leon.
You attacked him.
Because he's hurting your grandpa.
He's hurting you?
No.
He's hurting me.
I'm going to kill you.
What's wrong?
Wake up, sir.
What happened?
He's just like you.
So, this is all a lie?
This is all a trick.
So, your power will increase.
You're so good.
You're evil.
I'm not the one who's evil.
But you are.
Because you attacked a human.
I'm going to be your teacher.
You better be careful.
You better give up.
Because soon...
Your grandfather will be here.
Maybe I'm difficult to change.
But I'm doing this for my grandfather.
Remember, you've done the right thing.
You've done the right thing.
I'm sorry.
Finally, I'm free from the fire.
Why did I get angry?
I don't understand what's happening.
Why did I have to do this?
Who's coffee is this?
Or maybe...
It's the dark wizard's?
But how come the dark wizard likes coffee?
I'll go check.
Angkara!
Wake up!
Useless!
I've been working and you're just sleeping.
Angkara, wake up!
Alright.
You have to kill me.
You're dead!
Get up!
Angkara!
Wake up!
Who are you?
Get up.
Follow me.
You're so rude to my son.
I told you to walk, but you're still sleeping.
Angkara.
This is nothing.
I'll make you pay for this.
You'll regret this.
We can't help you.
Get the blood.
Yes, but don't worry.
We'll help you if you need our help.
It's okay.
You've tried.
Goodbye, my friends.
That's the dark wizard.
He's been pulled around Angkara.
There.
Don't.
He'll be punished if he does it.
I can feel it.
Professor.
What?
Why are you helping him?
I don't want to.
What's wrong with you?
You're so mean to us.
Why are you helping him?
What happened tonight was my fault.
I wanted to be Angkara's professor.
It's not his fault.
I have to help him.
What are you doing?
Why are you helping him?
I don't want to.
I want to.
It's okay if you don't want to.
I'll do it.
Me too.
Why are you helping him?
He's right.
Angkara's professor is not wrong.
We have to help him.
Alva, Lita, let's go.
Don't go.
Let's go.
If you come with me,
please save my grandson.
Please.
I have high hopes for you.
That's what I want right now.
Let's go.
Okay, sir.
I'll...
Hey.
Why are you so noisy?
Let's go.
It's time for you to go.
Go.
I want you to go.
It's time for you to go.
Let's go, professor.
What are you waiting for?
[The smell of death]
What is this?
It smells like a bird.
[The smell of death]
What is this?
It smells like a cat.
Why are these animals...
...behaving like this?
[The smell of death]
Finally,
I can be free from the fire.
Professor, I'm sorry.
We shouldn't have gone to Gabah.
Gabah?
What do you mean?
If the professor comes back as a bird,
it's dangerous if our real identity is exposed.
You're right.
Because the fire police...
...can sense and sense our departure.
Come on, Mie.
Get on my back...
...so our journey is faster and safer.
Angkara!
Wake up, Angkara!
Wake up!
I'll punish you, Angkara.
Did I do something wrong...
...that I have to be punished?
Sir.
Why are we in the forest?
Why is my hand in the bag?
Sir!
Sir, what are you doing?
Sir.
Why did you throw my bag?
Shut up!
What's wrong?
It hurts.
You'll die in there.
You'll be eaten by the monsters.
Why is he so mean?
He's the professor of Angkara.
How could he be punished like that?
That's why...
...we have to help him.
Let him be punished for our mistake.
Then, what should we do?
Let's get closer to the hole...
...and think of a way.
While the professor is leaving.
Sir.
I don't have the strength.
Get away!
Sir.
I don't have the strength.
Get away!
Don't eat me!
Sir!
Ouch!
What's wrong?
The children must be happy to see the professor.
Where are you taking me?
Sir!
We can do it.
Why can't the professor see...
...what's going on with them?
What do you think they're doing?
Okay.
Tell me.
They're being asked to do something important.
From the professor.
The professor of Agni.
I see.
Okay.
Alright.
You're smiling.
My children.
Since there's no professor of Angkara.
That's why I asked you to go out of the class.
Because I feel...
...so bored in the classroom.
Because everything is so messy.
It's like we're always...
...at night.
What do you think, children?
Right.
We're out of class.
Well.
The professor will teach you...
...a very useful...
...and useful mantra for you.
This mantra is called...
...Bovobovom.
There's a bomb, professor.
Are we going to make a bomb?
Yes, that's right.
More precisely.
This mantra is useful for creating explosions.
And it can also be used to shock the enemy.
Do you want to?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Now, I'll show you an example.
My children, pay attention.
Okay.
Pay attention, professor.
Bovobo...
What's that, professor?
A bomb, professor.
A bomb, professor?
Yes.
Bomb!
Wow.
That's what a titan, professor.
The bomb is used as an explosion controller.
And it can be exploded anytime.
It can be controlled like a bomb.
Give it a smile.
Okay? / Yes.
Now, you go forward.
Yes.
You just practiced the mantra.
Bovobo...
The bomb is back.
You're right.
The professor is right.
The bomb is back.
We've arrived at the school.
Hold on tight.
I'll be right there.
All the children will be happy to see you, professor.
Where are you going, professor?
Bovobo...
Where are my children?
Come on.
Go back to the classroom.
Give it a smile.
I miss you, but don't hit me, professor.
Professor Ranggarbaran.
It's not fun to have professor Ranggarbaran.
I can't be a student of your favorite school anymore.
I'm also happy to be able to go back to school.
And I'm sorry...
for all the things that happened lately.
But I promise you.
I'll go back to school as always.
Okay.
Let's go.
We're back to school.
Yes.
That's enough, children.
Now, professor Aldebaran will go back to work.
Come on, professor.
Professor Tita, please continue your lesson.
Thank you, professor Aldebaran.
Give it a smile, children.
Now, we're back to the professor's lesson.
Do you understand?
Now, continue your lesson.
Yes.
Don't forget.
Why did you do this to me?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
You're so slow.
I'm so glad that I don't have your strength.
Bang Heran!
Please, Bang Heran!
Oh, my God!
Bang Heran!
Bang Heran, I'm begging you!
How dare you eat me?
Watch out.
I'm a fast learner.
But, he doesn't want to.
Watch out!
Don't eat me!
You're so slow.
You're sick, but you still make me sick.
Don't eat me!
Watch out!
The professor is so mean.
He's so mean.
What should we do?
You go and look for the professor.
I'll help you.
You untie the rope.
Okay, Karva.
Bang Heran!
We're going to the North.
Be careful.
You too.
Come here, you slowpoke!
Come here, you coward!
You slowpoke!
To be continued...
Let's go!
We can do it!
Come here, you slowpoke!
Come here!
Why are you here?
The professor is angry.
So, I'm here to help.
You can't help me.
I'm the head of the school.
You stay here.
So, I can open the door.
What's wrong with this kid?
He's so arrogant.
You're so mean, professor.
Just leave him be.
I'm the head of the school.
That's weird.
So weird.
Queen Venus said...
that the necklace belongs to her.
It's been more than 1,500 years.
Are you sure?
We're 100% sure.
Yes, sir.
Because I saw a black smoke...
in the soul stone.
You're right, sir.
It's not here.
I didn't see it.
What's wrong with you?
You're so arrogant.
You can't see the soldier...
because he's an adult.
He has a lot of sins.
That's why you can't see him.
You're so arrogant.
You said he has a lot of sins.
What's the relation between my sins...
and the stone he's wearing?
You forgot.
The soldier is an adult.
And an adult can't see the soul stone.
The soul stone can only be seen by children.
We can't see it.
But why is it...
why is the shape...
is like that?
The soldier also forgot...
what the professor said.
Remember, Negantara.
Nick, Fija, Eric, and Oktav.
The soul stone...
can't only be seen by adults.
But it can also be seen in another form.
For example?
Usually, the soul stone...
will be sucked into ancient objects.
Antique and very valuable.
And there, it will find a safe house.
Because the owner...
will take good care of it.
And will never give it to anyone.
(The soldier is an adult)
How is it? Is it true, soldier?
The rainbow is colorful.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
That's unusual.
Alright then.
We'll act.
And we have to take...
the soul stone from Queen Venus.
Yes, soldier!
(The soldier is an adult)
Bring the rainbow to Surabaya.
Dear beautiful queen.
Give me the soul stone.
Wait.
Don't be rude to our queen.
You can take our queen's soul stone.
But you have to step on my body first.
How can I step on your body?
You're not even a body yet.
Soldier, the rainbow is not dead yet.
Hurry up and bring it back.
Bring it back.
Calm down, Men.
The rainbow weapon...
hasn't been brought out yet.
Kincir-kincir, fly to the clouds.
Don't worry, dear queen who looks like a cloud.
Dear queen.
I won't take the soul stone from the queen.
But I will buy it.
Calm down, Boy.
Bro, just relax.
Big burger.
What is this?
Nick, Eric.
Please open the box.
The content of this box...
will make the queen happy and the palace full.
This is real.
Not fake.
You think we're carrying a fake item?
You call this fake?
Queen.
All of these diamonds and gold...
are the work of a magic school student.
So, I'm sure that it's real.
Come here!
Men, let's go!
It's broken!
I can do it.
Yes!
Let me do it.
Let go, Ali!
The King of the Jungle
What did you say?
Thank you? / Shut up!
I'm the head of this school.
How dare you!
Just say thank you.
I don't want to.
Shut up!
Sir.
Let's go back to school.
I can do it.
The King of the Jungle
I can do it!
Thank you, Frita.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Come on, Bro.
Shut up!
I can do it.
You're so arrogant.
Okay.
See you later.
The King of the Jungle
Yes!
This is the professor.
The room.
The King of the Jungle
Yes! I did it!
What are you waiting for?
The King of the Jungle
The King of the Jungle?
Sir.
So, this is how it is.
You're in cahoots with all of them.
You're a traitor!
Sir, you're misunderstanding.
I'm not asking for their help.
They're the ones who helped me.
I'll destroy the lollipop.
The lollipop?
What are we going to use it for?
Sir.
Anghara.
You've been pretending to be my follower.
But you're in cahoots with all of them.
No, sir.
Sir, don't get me wrong.
You're wrong.
This is the proof.
You're in cahoots with them.
I'm going to kill you.
I'll make you angry.
You're a traitor.
You're so mean.
Shut up.
Or maybe you're helping me...
because you're the ones who are betraying me.
Right?
Yes.
You're so rude.
You're angry.
But you're helping me.
Thank you.
What's that?
He's confused.
He's so smart.
Shut up.
How dare you.
I'm going to kill you all.
(The next day)
Wake up.
Get out of my way.
I was killed in the middle of the night.
It's okay. I'm dead.
How can a person be dead?
I don't know.
Because this school is a mantra school.
So, the evil spirit can't enter.
Shut up.
Who's the evil spirit?
It's me.
To be continued...
(Preview of the next episode)
(Thank you for watching)