To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Leon, this is the school you have to destroy
You will join this school as one of its students
And you will change your identity
Your name is not Leon anymore
But Rio, Leon, do you understand?
I understand, so this is the person who has betrayed my grandfather
I will destroy you both
Come on, say goodbye to him
Goodbye
Ah, how cute with a smile
Professor Andepanat, I feel so relieved
With this dust
Our school is now secure and safe
Without any disturbance from the Angkara
Not only that, Professor
But in all the rooms in this school
I have put a sign
If there is danger, a monster or an enemy comes
The alarm will sound
So there is no more story
There are students or teachers who suddenly disappeared
That's very good, Professor
What is that sound, Professor?
That's a sign of danger, I mean
In the Purnama dormitory
Come on, let's go there now
Come on
Look at your left
Professor Andepanat
I thought the scariest thing was the family
It's him
Where is he?
Who?
I think we can't get out anymore
If so, we have to attack more
Let's go
[Music]
[Screaming]
Purnama dormitory
What's going on, Professor?
Why is it not open yet?
What's going on?
They are smiling
Kids, calm down
The teachers are here
The teachers will definitely save you, kids
Professor, let's open it with magic
Open it
Weird, it's still not open yet
It's too late, Professor
Kids
Who attacked you?
Karang?
I'm not Karang
I'm Professor Andepanat
[Screaming]
Calm down, kids
We will definitely save you
Calm down
Hang in there
[Screaming]
Once the sword is sharpened
The goat's body will fly
Dear Queen Venus
My students
Prepare for the match tomorrow morning
Okay, sir
See you tomorrow
That's all, sir?
The goat is not dead, sir
Yes, sir
It's too ordinary
The goat's body is not good, sir
It's not sharp, sir
Is there anything else you want to say?
There's no queen
That's all, sir
Thank you
Let's go
[Phone ringing]
If I lose
I have to give this box to them
But am I willing to?
[Lightning]
Queen Venus
I am Batu Jiwa
I remind you
This box is very precious
You can't give it to them
You are...
Batu Jiwa's spirit?
That's right
I am
Batu Jiwa's spirit
Who broke this box?
Today
I will be the judge
I'm so lucky
[Lightning]
Whose footprints are these?
These footprints lead me to the lost body
[Lightning]
Oh my God
The horse's footprints are gone
Banana!
We are wrong, sir
We are not the one who broke the box
We are the one who broke the box
Don't be afraid
We will save him
Get up!
One, two, three
We are not afraid
[Lightning]
Let me try the meteorphone's spell, sir
Meteorphone!
I'll take it
You better take it, sir
Let me go first
Bomb! Bomb! Bomb!
[Evil Laugh]
This is still a success, sir
We are not the one who broke the box
How is it, sir?
What's going on?
The door can't be opened
It seems like there's a power inside
That's right
Let's go, guys!
We are broken!
[Screaming]
What?
Our friends are fainted!
Let's blow their noses
So they can breathe
Rika!
Get her!
Lita, get her!
Hurry!
Rika!
BoBoiBoy Reset!
[Lightning]
What should we do?
What if the monster is not in there?
[Lightning]
No!
What's that?
[Screaming]
Let's go!
That's a black ghost!
Why is it so powerful?
Oh, no!
Why is it so powerful to attack the monster?
[Groaning]
What's wrong?
The monster is gone
It seems like they are attacked
Let's attack the monster together
Don't let it get away
Yes, sir
Power of the Five!
[Lightning]
What's that?
Rio!
Professor, why is there a monster here?
Yes, professor
She's poisoned
Poisoned?
Alva, what happened?
We are attacked by monsters
We are all attacked by the monster
By the monster
Alva!
I'm going!
Thank God, it's okay
But...
Whose footprints are these?
Who's in here?
It's okay, what matters is you and me
Me?
What's happening?
I'm going to be chased!
Whoever it is, it managed to beat my horse
And that means...
It has a very high HP
Even the prey managed to beat it
Who is it?
I have to be careful
[Lightning]
Dr. Pertiwi must be shocked to see so many patients
Ah, hi! You're smiling
That's right, Professor Agni
I think we should immediately tighten security
So that this disaster doesn't happen again
Okay, then we'll bring the kids to the clinic
Yes, professor
[Music]
Pertiwi!
Oh my God!
OMG!
Oh no, no, no, no
What, what, what the...
These are all tests, victims!
Pertiwi, quickly treat them!
Yes, professor!
Come on
Teacher, you know that...
This is a serum for recovery
Please, help me!
Help me, pour it into their mouths
Go, go, go, go, go, go
Pertiwi!
Help Rio first, she's the most seriously injured
Oh no, oh my God!
Yes, professor
Oh my goodness!
Oh professor, why is our school always attacked?
Why, professor?
Pertiwi is sad
As you said, it's a disaster
But just now, I realized
And told me
That Rio is the cause of this disaster
[Music]
Sir
How's the mission, sir?
All good?
Mission accomplished, sir
Aldebaran finally believes in Leon
I mean, your prionel, sir
Very good, Aldebaran
Good
Now, your job is to fight the protection prism
But, how, sir?
Every time I change to find myself
I always get stuck, sir
Don't be stupid, Aldebaran
Every mantra, there must be a weak point
You look for a place that is not protected by the dust
But, where, sir?
Where?
You look for it, I have to look for it too
Okay, sir
I want a banana
You're a coward
Who did this?
I want a banana
Banana, banana
Find it yourself
Banana
Painting of a tiger
Good
This is better
Painting of a tiger
Keep this powder well
Don't let it get in there again
Good
Painting of a tiger
Last, Aldebaran
Before we fly
We should do what is called warming up
What is it?
Warming up
Okay, ready
Follow my movement
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Viru Batu Venus
Eat the strawberry, buy it with the jackfruit
Delicious
They are so confident
They don't know who we are
That's right
The match will start soon
Nick from School of Magic versus Viru Batu Venus
Viru Batu Venus
Come on, cheer up for Nick
Long live Nick
Taf, bring out all the bling bling magic
So we can look cool
Okay
Patan, come here
What is this?
A stick
You too?
Oh my
What should we do?
We asked for a stick, but we got a stick
Look, we are being betrayed
Do I have one?
You have one too
You guys
You are so weird sometimes
You are so shy
You are using wrong magic
No formal
Come on
Get ready, Nick
Come on, Nick
Nick
Long live Nick
You are just a kid, what can you do?
Nick and Viru Batu Venus will go around this island three times
The one who reaches the finish line first is the winner
Come on, Nick
Cheer up
You can do it
One
Two
Three
Come on, Nick
Venus
Keep chasing
Hurry up
Come on, Viru Batu
Come on, Nick
Concentrate, Nick
You can do it faster than Viru Batu
That kid is not as strong as he looks
Hurry up
Fly higher
Keep chasing, Nick
Come on, Nick
Keep chasing
You can do it
I'm sure you can win
That's why Viru Batu
Don't underestimate the kids of the magic school
I have to find a way to win
Turns out my kid can't be considered as a queen
Nick
Be careful, Nick
Watch out, Nick
She's so brave
Turns out
Even though the queen has a beautiful face
She's a coward
Venus, back off
I'm sorry
But you can't beat my kid
I have to find a way to win
I'm sorry
But you can't beat my kid
I have to find a way to win
Kids
In an emergency
Actually, lollipop can be made to fly
But
The result can be fatal
Because it can damage your lollipop
That's bad
It's a shame if it's damaged
It's very dangerous
The mantra is
Turbofan
Daft Punk
So fast, Nick
Faster than a rocket
You have to win, Nick
Come on, Nick
Faster than a rocket
Faster
Come on, Nick
You have to win, Nick
Faster
Yeah!
We won!
Great, Nick
Last cut
Adi Arati!
Oh, my
The beautiful Venus Queen
We beg you
Give me that soul
The most beautiful woman in the world
It's okay
I won't give you this
You're so cruel
Please be fair
The boy is in the top
The beautiful queen
Turns out she likes to lie
She's lying
Please be fair
Listen
If you want this necklace
You have to fulfill one more requirement
What is the last requirement that the Venus Queen wants?
Pertiwi
Yes, Prof
How is Rio?
Rio is still out of consciousness
But the others are all awake
Amazing, right, Prof?
Why is Rio the only one who's still unconscious?
Vega
Rio is already poisoned by the laba-laba
When we came in earlier
You were all unconscious
Only Rio can survive
And she defeated the laba-laba
That's great
If you write a new one
Rio will be so great
Looks like the boy has become a hero
Oh my God
So sad
How can I repay you?
I'm happy
I'm tired, I'm dizzy
Good night, Birbi
Agni
Tonight
We'll have a party
For Rio
Yes, Prof
I'm sorry, dear
Just leave us alone
We can do it
This place is so quiet
No one comes here
Maybe the Venus Queen isn't here
No sign of the Venus Queen
Maybe she's in the dark
I did it
The Valdebaran
Is nothing to me
I'm waiting for you
Rio is fighting the laba-laba
With the matrix
Who is she?
Pegasus
Vixor
Where are you, Rio?
I'm so scared
We did it
Thank you, Rio
Thank you for saving us
Thank you
Rio
You did a great job
And you
Will hold an event
To give away medals to you
That's too much
What I did
Was nothing special
Thank you, Rio
Thank you
Say thank you to Rio
Thank you, Rio
Alva
Please take the drinks from that table
Why do I hear a voice?
Alva
Don't
If you look at me again
I'll be
What?
Alva
Why did Alva leave?
Of course
Alva is jealous
Of Rio
Who is now
A total loser
Right?
Of course
Alva
You lost to Rio
Right?
Alva is not that kind of person
She's a good girl
I know
You're so mean, Miri
Enough
Let's go
Let's go to Alva
(Alva is not that kind of person)
Alva
What is she doing?
What are you doing?
Running around the clinic
Don't you know?
Alva looks confused
I know
Did you hear that?
The professor is coming
No
What?
I heard it
You're kidding
Yes
The professor can't come to school
That's why I want to check
If it's true or not
But it's not possible
It's not possible
Alva
Ray
I'm not lying
What are you doing?
I want to find her and meet her
Do you want to come?
If you don't want to come
Go to the clinic
Take care of Rio
Alva
She's so annoying
She's so annoying to Rio
Because she wants to be a hero
I know
Don't you know Alva?
She's your friend
I know
I don't like her
Just kidding
Alva's friend
I heard a voice from here
Where is it?
Maybe it's inside
[Music]
What's wrong with you?
It's just my feeling
[Music]
I think it's a cockroach
I have to find it
[Music]
Just leave us alone
What's wrong with you?
Thank God, there's nothing
[Music]
I'm going to be late again
I failed again
I give up
[Music]
Get out
I'm confused
I heard a voice
I thought it was a cockroach
But there's no one
[Music]
I don't feel good
I feel like I'm missing something
[Music]
But there's no one
Okay
I'll tell you the last condition
[Music]
I want you to make this white cloth
Turn red
If you can
I'll give you
[Music]
The queen's request
Just change this fabric color
To red
[Music]
Okay
The noble queen Venus
We will do
What is the requirement of the queen Venus
If so, do it right away
Hurry
Give it to me when you're done
[Music]
Hey
Is there anyone?
[Music]
Lay the fabric
Prepare the drawing equipment
[Music]
Okay
Now we will start
Nick
You draw first
Okay, sir
[Music]
Eh
Why is it suddenly gone?
It's gone
How could it be?
Maybe this fabric doesn't suit you
I'll try to draw my face
Which is similar to that fabric
Surely this will not refuse
[Music]
Immediately gone
It's gone
Why isn't there?
Oh my God
That's it
Because your face is ugly
Here I try
Try there
Oh my God
[Music]
See
Gone
[Laughter]
Too medical
Wait
Clear
That the fabric given by the queen Venus
This is not a fabric
[Music]
This fabric has been unused for a long time
No one comes
Surely I can make myself a human being here
Ah
Just there
[Music]
If I'm here
I will be a loser again
Just like me in the history of the Alba
[Music]
[Laughter]
Finally found a big place
Bigger than my Alba
Now let me know the situation
[Music]
Sir
You guys are rude
What else?
Sorry sir
I didn't mean to make you fall sir
But
I have good news sir
Good news?
[Music]
I
Can be a human being again in the desert sir
Without being driven away
Just make a festival sir
And do you know sir
I can do this
Because I'm hiding
The ruins are still broken sir
And
Not because of the flood sir
How sir?
I'm smart right?
You're really stupid Angkar
I told you
If that can be done
Enough Angkar
You don't bother me anymore
I'll scream
If Aldebaran hears your voice
I'll be angry
Hey
I want to be
A hero
[Music]
I've been using something
From the toilet
The toilet is broken
Not used anymore
Or maybe
[Music]
Hey
Is there anyone?
[Music]
This cloth is so weird
This cloth is from Queen Venus
Really weird
With all the way
One line
No one sticks to this cloth
Hey
I've brought it
Bad with my father
He's the one I need!
Watch out!
I'll do it!
[chanting]
Finally!
This is so funny!
Who is it?
It's Vega.
I'll go back to the dorm.
It's sick!
He doesn't know what's inside the sim.
I have to go to the toilet.
What should we do?
We've tried everything.
But this cloth doesn't change into red.
It's a waste.
Should we just give up?
No.
If we give up, how are we going to get the box?
Oh, no.
It's so easy.
The queen is so cunning.
Wait.
Where are you going?
I'm going to make a salad.
I'm going to get some inspiration.
Rio! Rio!
Rio, you're done.
I'm proud of you.
He's our leader.
Yes.
Yes, Din.
Get ready for the next lesson.
Rio! Rio!
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Do you like it?
If you like it, you can have it.
I'm fighting against the bad guys.
I'm fighting for our safety.
Not for the medal.
Wow, that's so cute.
We're so proud of you.
It's so hard to make you happy.
Rio, congratulations.
Where did you learn to be a medalist?
This is the medal.
Yes, I saw it.
So, I want to say congratulations.
You're welcome.
Can I say something?
Sure.
Where did you learn to do a magic trick?
Magic trick?
Yes, magic trick.
You beat the bad guys with magic trick, right?
It's black magic.
[The next episode]
Are you sure Rio said the magic trick?
If not, you're dead.
[The next episode]
Inspiration.
Come on, I'm confused.
If there's a magic that can inspire me,
there must be a way out.
To turn the fabric into red, like Queen Venus' wish.
Hi.
Hi, sir.
Why are you calling me sir?
Did you forget who I am?
Yes, I'm Megantara.
Megantara.
Can I give you a hand?
Sure.
There's a beautiful girl,
but she's in a bad mood.
Hi, beautiful girl.
Can you help me?
What do you want me to do?
Let me be clear.
I'm confused.
I'm so confused.
With your queen's challenge,
which is to turn the fabric into red.
Please, help me.
Give me a clue.
How can the fabric turn into red?
Fabric is the queen's wish.
No one has ever turned the fabric into red.
It's our fault.
Just give up.
Because any effort is useless.
Give up?
Useless?
Traveling to the north,
wearing a red hat,
called Megantara.
I don't know what giving up means.
I will keep fighting,
finding a way to turn the fabric into red,
like Queen Venus' wish.
And I will succeed.
I will not give up.
Okay, just try.
Do you want me to try?
I will not give up.
But how?
How?
I thought about it,
now I'm hungry.
But if I'm hungry, there's no food here.
I'm eating while watching the dance.
When I'm hungry, there's durian.
I'm hungry.
Durian!
Eat durian!
There's a goat.
Who is that goat?
Is the goat asking for durian?
Since when does a goat eat durian?
It's really angry.
Be patient.
I want durian. Just eat it.
Eat it.
I want durian.
That goat is really angry.
What are you doing?
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
You're the one who attacked the goat using the mantra.
I heard it.
I didn't say that mantra.
I just learned the mantra from the mantra teacher.
That's all.
Are you sure that he said that mantra?
If not, you're lying.
I'm not lying.
I heard it.
But you were still unconscious.
How could you see it?
I wasn't unconscious.
I heard it.
Alva.
You don't have to be jealous.
You have a lot of power.
Don't be jealous.
I'm jealous.
You're not jealous.
Alva, calm down.
Even though he's great, we're still your friends.
Right?
I'm not jealous.
You don't trust me, right?
Stop fighting.
Alva, don't be jealous.
I didn't mean it.
I don't want to be a hero.
Or anything.
I just want to fight the goats.
So, we can be safe.
If not, we'll die.
I'm so proud of you.
How about we switch partners?
Me and Rio.
You and Alva.
I don't want to.
My sister chose Alva.
I want to be with Rio.
We're twins.
We should share everything.
I agree.
But, I don't think you're that great.
I'm so jealous of you.
Let's find someone else.
Let's go.
"Alva and Rio"
That person again.
Harimau, what happened to you?
I told you to take care of this pig.
Not a date.
He's even more fierce.
You're so mean.
"Alva and Rio"
Alva.
Rio.
"Alva and Rio"
A mask to protect your skin.
Who dares to do this?
Making a mask out of peanuts.
I have an idea.
"Alva and Rio"
Nik, Riceh, Ari, Oktav.
Help me.
What's wrong?
Look for a cloth or a bandage.
He's in so much pain. What's wrong?
I met a goat.
A wild goat that doesn't know how to speak.
It's a basic. It must be at school.
But the goat is okay, right?
Goat?
Hurry up and find a cloth or a bandage.
I almost broke my kid.
Okay, wait.
I'm out of cloth.
Slowly.
Okay.
Thank you, Nik.
You're welcome.
I'm going to rest.
He's out of the house.
He's looking for inspiration.
He met a goat.
It's so good.
It doesn't know how to speak.
It's a bad luck.
What?
What's wrong, soldier?
Where's the cloth?
It's gone.
Where is it?
I don't know.
Why is it gone?
Don't.
Don't say that, soldier.
The cloth is in his hand.
It's true, soldier.
Because he's bleeding, he's changing his color.
It's turning red.
Red?
Yes, red.
It means...
This white cloth...
Can turn red...
If...
It's touched by...
The goat.
We've solved the problem.
We need blood.
If so, just hurt the soldier's hand.
It's true.
It'll turn red.
The soldier is bleeding.
I'm going to die.
Kids.
Today, I'm going to teach you...
How to make a love potion.
But before that, I want to ask you.
Does anyone know what love potion is?
Rio, you answer.
Love potion is...
A magic potion.
So, the person who drinks it...
Will fall in love with the person who gives it to them.
You're so smart, Rio.
Since it's Valentine's Day...
I'm sure there are many kids...
Who want to make a love potion.
I'm here...
To teach you how to make a love potion.
How to make a love potion?
How?
How to turn the white cloth into red using blood?
We've used a lot of soldiers, but it's still not enough.
Even the anime...
We can't make it.
Really?
Made from brown beans.
I have an idea.
Buy cheap clothes in Jeparang.
What's your idea, soldier?
You can help us.
Are you ready?
Come.
Get ready.
The Phantom Camera.
What is that camera for?
For selfie?
It's not the time yet.
You're so slow.
This is not a regular camera.
This is a double camera.
It can double the object in the photo.
Oh, my.
What's the connection with this cloth, soldier?
Do you know what it's called?
You're so slow.
It takes a long time to load.
Look.
It's double.
Wait a minute.
It's triple.
There.
There are many.
Look.
It's red.
The cloth is red.
It's amazing.
All the cloth from Venus.
All of them are red.
It's amazing, soldier.
It's amazing.
You don't know yet.
Megantara is amazing.
Soldier.
The camera is amazing.
Now, the ingredients are in front of you.
The ingredients are paprika.
Centaurus' sweat.
And a bit of turmeric.
Now, if you stir the ingredients three times clockwise.
You will get a pink liquid.
Let's try it.
Pink. Let's try it.
[Pink liquid]
Alva?
You failed. Try again.
Okay.
What did you make?
[Pink liquid]
Vega?
You failed.
Try again.
[Pink liquid]
Rionelo.
You made it.
You're amazing.
Guys.
Rionelo made it.
Let's give him a big hand.
Vega.
Usually, you can make a mess.
Why did you fail this time?
[Pink liquid]
What's that?
What are you doing?
There's no poison.
I'm not doing anything.
You're the one who's bad.
[Pink liquid]
[Go Go Go song]
Remember to look at your promises to the people, not the government.