To be continued...
Show your spirit, get your friends ready
Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your hopes and dreams
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
What is this?
Barga is a monster that is not human
He is a hand and leg monster
That can defeat him
Only the dark lord and a kid
Who is he?
Alpha
Night, Nan
Before the sun sets
You have to go back to the secret room
And get the eternal stone for me
What are you doing out there?
When can I kill you?
Ouch
Ray
How did you know?
You were unconscious
I was unconscious
But because of you
I got this disease
Let me try using a mantra
Dangdut Dapang
Why is it dangdut?
I don't know
Maybe you got the mantra wrong
Yes
Dapat Tangtangdu
This is it
Come on, Ray
It's working
Dapang
I'm sorry, Ray
[music playing]
How do I catch him?
I got you!
[music playing]
Oh my God!
I can't find the antidote!
What kind of poison is this?
This is poison from the Three Heads.
What? Three Heads?
Oh my God!
The Three Heads poison has no antidote.
You better go to Megantara now.
What do you mean?
Captain Megantara.
Because his guardian is Megantara.
Hurry!
Okay, I'll go to Megantara now.
Go!
[music playing]
The body switch is fast.
I have to concentrate.
[music playing]
Now, by doing this, I can know the direction of the movement.
Turbo Volt!
[music playing]
See?
[laughing]
They're beautiful girls now.
Vega, now it's your turn.
You have to approach them.
You have to figure out how to get them to the clinic to get their kidneys treated.
Why me? I already know them. I want to be a soldier.
Here's the problem.
They're not into men.
They're not into men like me.
I'm handsome.
They'll get allergic.
Don't think too much.
Do you want to be a doctor?
Come here.
[music playing]
Hey, who are you?
Did you call us here?
Yes, I did.
I really need your help.
My friend is a third-ranked soldier.
You're the only one who can treat my friend.
Why do we have to help you? We don't even know you.
Why are you saying that? Please, help me.
I promise I'll do everything you want.
Please.
[music playing]
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
Okay, if you want to do what we want, you have to make us happy and laugh.
But how?
Think about it. We haven't laughed in a while. Right, girls?
That's right.
It won't take long. I'll count to three.
Or we'll leave.
How?
One.
Two.
Shh.
Wait.
Follow me. I'll make you laugh.
I can do it. Please, believe me.
Come on.
Let's go.
[clock ticking]
You're quite good at this. One problem solved.
[laughing]
[music playing]
Sorry, soldier.
Oh, no.
It's a man.
I'm not a man. How are you?
You said you're tired of men.
What are you waiting for? Just shoot him.
Friga, don't.
Attack.
[fighting]
[laughing]
Don't.
[music playing]
[laughing]
Yes, yes, yes. We are party.
[cheering]
[laughing]
I made you laugh.
Now, help me.
[cheering]
[music playing]
Yes.
[coughing]
Yes, yes, we are party.
[cheering]
[music playing]
[laughing]
I'm so happy.
Let me see.
[music playing]
So, now, please tell me.
Why are you in that room?
So, it's like this.
Alfa said...
this school is in danger.
And he needs that stone to save this school.
If not, many girls will be threatened.
This is so annoying.
Alfa doesn't need that stone.
What is he doing?
Where is Alfa now?
[music playing]
No, no, no.
I'm going to kill Buca.
Hey.
What are you doing in there?
Alfa.
Ma'am.
How is it, Alfa?
Yes, ma'am. I managed to get the stone.
[music playing]
Excuse me.
I'm going to kill Buca.
[music playing]
For the next two hours, your voice will change into a dog's voice.
[dog barking]
[music playing]
Ma'am.
I've handed over the stone.
So, this school is safe, right?
[music playing]
What do you mean, Alfa?
I managed to get the stone.
And I gave it to the professor, right?
[music playing]
I never asked you to do that.
Alfa.
Why did you take the stone?
Professor Agni asked me to.
Because this school is in danger.
Only that stone can save this school.
Alfa, I never asked you to take that stone.
But yesterday afternoon, Professor Agni asked me to take the Stone of Eternity.
No, Alfa. I never asked you to take that stone.
[music playing]
Professor.
The Stone of Eternity is...
[music playing]
The three heads of the dragon are all fighting.
Alfa.
How did you know all this?
Professor Agni, Professor...
Professor Agni told me.
And Professor Agni also told me about the food of the three heads of the dragon.
Alfa.
I never and never asked you to do all that.
Yes, Professor.
[music playing]
[roar]
Alfa.
Now you should go back to your dormitory.
But, Professor.
I really gave the stone to Professor Agni.
And after that, I don't know what else.
It seems like someone chased me until I fainted.
I never received anything from you, Alfa.
That's impossible, Professor.
I can't be lying.
Here's the thing, Alfa.
The stone can't save this school.
On the contrary,
if the stone falls into the wrong hands,
this school could be in danger.
For example, the 8th Prince.
[roar]
[music playing]
The 8th Prince?
What's going on?
You shouldn't be hearing that name.
And you don't need to know who he is.
Based on your son's behavior,
a thief,
you should have just taught him at school.
Enough.
Now, go back to your dormitory.
Go.
I'm sorry, Professor.
This time, you're really naughty, Alfa.
You went into that room,
and then you took the stone to the abyss.
The stone was gone.
And you lied again when you were asked by Professor Agni.
But, Tentara, I didn't lie.
I don't believe it.
How can you believe it?
Professor Agni has been a teacher at this school for decades, Alfa.
So, it's impossible for him to lie.
But, I'm telling the truth, Tentara.
I'm not lying.
Tentara,
who's that Dark Lord?
That Dark Lord?
You don't know the time yet, Alfa.
What's clear is that this Dark Lord is very dangerous, Alfa.
Not a single person hopes that he will return.
[DARK LORD]
Rey,
you're back!
Rey, I know everything.
If you're not here, I'm not going to be able to save you.
You took the stone to the abyss,
and you lied.
You said Professor Agni asked you to do it.
But, you didn't.
Now, you're denying it.
Is that true or not?
No, Rey.
That's a lie.
I gave the stone to Professor Agni.
And suddenly, someone came after me.
And I don't know what happened.
Oh, really?
But, you don't believe it.
Vega, you don't believe me either.
[DARK LORD]
Alright.
If you don't believe me, it's okay.
I'll prove it to you later.
If what I said is true.
Oh, he's the one who's angry.
I should be the one who's angry.
I've been poisoned.
But, I'm just a victim of a php.
I think he's not wrong, Rey.
What do you mean?
Professor Agni lied?
That's right.
Hey, guys.
You've heard it, right?
Alfa is a thief.
She stole the stone from Mr. Dian.
How could a thief be allowed to enter this school?
Right.
Let's go.
It turns out that Klepto is not only shameless.
He's already a thief.
But, he still dares to show up here.
Guys.
It's not fun if there's a thief in our school.
I have an idea.
We have to make a petition, guys.
What do you think?
Do you agree?
A petition to be banned.
[Petition to be banned]
Petition, it's been canceled.
Wow.
There are so many people.
If this continues, Malik will be expelled from this school.
Right, guys?
Right.
[Petition to be banned]
Alfa.
Come here.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Come here.
You're so annoying, Alfa.
Alfa has betrayed us.
Alfa is a good person.
The proof is that he saved me from the thieves.
A good person like Alfa can't do that.
I'm sure he's being trapped now.
And he's in a trap.
Come on, he's a rat.
Listen.
I don't want to be poisoned anymore.
If you want to help Alfa, go there.
I want to sleep.
Hey.
Alfa said he was trapped in front of the forbidden room.
I think I need to investigate that room.
Just in case there's any evidence left there.
[The forbidden room]
What's that?
Ouch, it hurts.
What's wrong with me?
Hey, don't go there.
[The forbidden room]
Sir.
Why is this room sealed?
It wasn't like this yesterday.
Yes, because Alfa was in this room yesterday.
And this is a very forbidden room.
That's why this room is sealed with a spell.
So, no one can enter.
And you.
Don't you dare to enter this room.
Do you understand?
I'll go first.
If the spell is used to open the door,
then the door can also be opened with a spell.
I have to find a spell to open this door.
[The forbidden room]
Now, no one believes me.
Tentara.
Ray.
And Vega.
They think I'm lying.
But I don't have any evidence.
And I don't know where the body switch is.
Hi, bro.
Why are you smiling?
Do you believe me?
Yes.
Here, a magic spell from me.
Take it.
You take one.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Open it.
Is it good?
I told you it's not good.
You're right.
[The magic spell]
Why is your voice like this?
It's so funny.
I got it.
What Jack gave me is a voice changer.
So, for the next two hours,
your voice will change into an animal's voice.
That's a lesson.
Let's go.
You're expelled from school.
[The magic spell]
Never say a magic spell in front of the mirror.
Because the spell will come back to you.
For that,
there's a magic spell you can use.
You have to say this spell...
before you say the one you want to say.
Repeat after me.
Javangan Pantung.
Once again.
Alfa.
Why don't you repeat your spell?
Do you think you're smart?
Why are you just standing there?
Come on.
Repeat the spell.
You're insulting me, Alfa.
Shut up!
You're too much, Alfa.
For that, you'll be punished.
I'm sorry.
Attention, everyone.
All students, gather in the classroom.
Once again.
Attention, everyone.
All students, gather in the classroom.
Alfa's School
What is the important thing that needs to be discussed...
until I have to leave my class?
What steps should we take against Alfa?
I think that should not be discussed anymore.
Alfa should be expelled.
Alfa's School
Expelling a student from the school...
is not an easy task.
But, Professor.
What Alfa has done...
is beyond the limits.
If we don't expel her...
we can protest against her...
by her parents.
That's right.
Three days until the full moon.
And if in the full moon...
the darkness of darkness gets her stone...
she will get an unlimited power...
that will destroy this world.
And all of that will happen to Alfa.
Professor.
Just now, at the break time...
some students gave me this petition.
The petition states that...
all the students in this school...
agree to expel Alfa from this school.
It seems...
we have no other choice, Professor.
Alfa has to be expelled from this school.
Megantara.
Call Alfa.
Tell her to come here.
Luckily, my voice is back.
If not...
Professor Aldebaran will be angry.
Megantara.
Why did you call me?
Good morning, Professor.
The words you will hear...
will not be pleasant to the ears.
But you have to listen to them.
Why, Professor?
You are expelled from this school.
[The school is in chaos]
Now, prepare your things.
The school's guard will take you to the dana tomorrow.
I'm done talking.
You can go now.
[The school is in chaos]
Professor.
Excuse me.
[The school is in chaos]
Rolf.
Did Alfa...
really take the stone?
No.
The child is innocent.
If it's not Alfa...
it means Professor Agni is lying.
No.
Agni is not lying.
Something has happened.
And we have to find out...
what really happened.
[The school is in chaos]
Rih.
Professor Aldebaran just called me.
You don't know...
what punishment I got from Professor Aldebaran.
It's all my fault.
I was so stupid to be lied to.
Rih!
[The school is in chaos]
Come here.
Help me.
To find the mantra to open the seal.
Hurry up.
It's okay.
Read this.
Just tell me.
I'm here for a refreshing.
Not to read a book.
I don't want to know.
You have to help me.
Dufuduk!
Wow!
Bafacabukuk!
Maximalklahilumpika!
Eda.
Enough.
I'm so sleepy.
Let me go.
You can sleep later.
But I'll find the mantra.
I'm so tired.
I got the mantra.
Yes!
Yay!
I can sleep.
Yes.
I'll let you go.
Amen.
[The school is in chaos]
I just remembered.
The ring.
The ring of the snake.
But it's useless.
You're out.
What's wrong?
[The school is in chaos]
[We can do it]
It's done.
Yes!
I did it.
[The school is in chaos]
Why are you going there?
Because I'm scared.
Yesterday, a kid got bewitched.
And he fainted here.
Don't say that.
My head is spinning.
I'm so scared.
Don't ask anything to my brother.
I don't want to talk to you.
Understand?
But you have to tell me.
Who attacked Ava?
At first, there was Professor Agni.
Professor Agni?
And then, this place was so smoky.
I didn't see who attacked the kid.
But he attacked with magic.
He must have a great power.
I'm going to move to another place.
It's scary here.
At least, now I know.
Ava is not wrong.
Where are we going?
There!
Where's Alfa?
Do you see Alfa?
Alfa was kicked out of the school.
What?
Now, she's at home.
How can she sleep here?
What's wrong?
She's having a nightmare.
[The kids are having a nightmare]
Ri, wake up!
Ri!
What's wrong?
Alfa, Ri!
Alfa was kicked out of the school.
Come on, hurry up!
Alfa was kicked out?
Let's ask the teacher.
Yes.
The news you heard is true.
Alfa is being taken to the lake by the school's police.
I'm the one who's wrong.
I was mean to Alfa.
She told me about the punishment.
But I didn't want to hear it.
You're too much.
You're not sensitive at all.
Everyone says that.
Even if I'm handsome, I'm not sensitive.
Why?
But, Alfa is innocent.
We have to make her go back to school.
But we don't have any evidence.
You're talking nonsense.
We can't make a solid evidence.
But we have to investigate it together.
And Alfa is a soldier's friend.
How can a soldier be so confident...
...to see his own friend who's innocent...
...but being punished so severely?
Alfa, you're in charge now.
This boat will take you back.
I'm going back.
Goodbye, Vega.
Goodbye, Rey.
I'll try to get back to you as soon as possible.
But if I do, they'll be mad at me.
They hate me.
What's going on?
You've been expelled from this school.
Why are you still here?
I know who stole the stone.
Who?
Professor Tuluak.
I'll prove that I'm right.
Just wait and see.
Let's go!
Don't let the stone...
...be given to the 8th Prince.
There are two of them.
Two?
To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready...
...my friend.
Run, jump, and conquer...
...the stars.
Be brave, don't give up.
Chase your dreams.
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams.
Go, go, go, never stop.
Go, go, go, fight with all your might.
Go, go, go, make yourself proud.
Go, go, go, let's dream.
Go, go, go, we'll make it.
D'yiii!