To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
To be continued...
Let us go, let us go
Please, let us go
Fanjul
I told you not to come near the lock
Not to open the door, not to enter the dungeon
But what happened?
You've broken my advice
And you've broken your own promise
Please, please don't kill us
Please don't kill us
Please, I beg you
From now on, if you want to open this door
You have to tell me
Alva
I want to make a revenge
To the people who have destroyed me
And the first person
Panji
Astagfirullahaladzim
Alva
Panji
Stop, Panji
That's enough, let's just go
Panji, we're not going to win
Right? Let's just give up
No, we can't give up
The future of the school is in our hands
We have to unite with that monster
But I'm so scared
The monster is so big and sharp
I'm going to be bitten, it's so sad
Ouch
Just let it be, Cik
Don't let it hurt you like that
You're arrogant
I'm not
Alva, Donya, Cik, Benk
Let's go find another place
Yes
Yes, sir
Let's go
It's so hot, I'm so scared
Let it be, don't think about them
The important thing is we focus on fighting that monster
Until we defeat it, okay?
Let's go
The raptor is different
Where is it going?
[The raptor is going to attack the school]
Let's just stay here
Instead of going to the school
That's so cute, boss
Okay, boss
[The raptor is attacking the school]
What's that sound?
It's so loud, boss
Help!
[The raptor is attacking the school]
It's so loud, boss
Help!
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Sir, I've done some attacks
And I'm sure
People will be more suspicious of you
Very good
Keep an eye on the raptor
And wait
Until it's under my nose
Attack it
Okay
Let's go there
Where is it?
It looks scary
I don't want to look at the telescope anymore
Whatever it takes
We have to go back there and take its heart
Why do you want to be chased again?
Just look at its face
I'm tired of it
We have to make it happy
So it won't be chased
How do we do that?
I know how
What?
We have to feed it
With the food it eats
So it will be kind to us
I want to do that too
Me too
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Come on!
Feed it!
[The raptor is attacking the school]
I want to feed it
For the baby
So we can use the oil
It's attacking me
I'm going to hit it with a stone
We will be punished
I'm going to eat it
Okay
We got the stone
It took so long
Come on!
We got it!
You're so funny
We got the stone
Guys
While the raptor is chasing Mike and Tommy
Let's attack them from the side
Remember
We only have one slogan
One dead, one alive
If you fall, you have to change your clothes
Don't give up
We have to be brave
[The raptor is attacking the school]
We got it!
That's why you don't have to be so patient
Why is it so tight?
It's for the fish
So we can eat it
I want to eat the chicken
But I got hit by the stone
I know
I'm going to hit it from the side
[The raptor is attacking the school]
We got it!
Try to go up a little
Higher
I'm going to hit it
The skin of the raptor
Is not like a human
The skin of the raptor is very hard
So it can't be weakened just by a stone
What should we do?
Tell my students to use the ninja mantra
They have mastered it
Mike! Fight with the ninja mantra!
Yes, sir!
[The raptor is attacking the school]
We did it!
You guys are great!
Megantara!
Yes, sir!
What's wrong with you?
If I can't catch your staff
We're going to be destroyed
Oh my god!
I'm sorry, sir
Take it back
Of course, it's your staff
What else?
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Everyone!
We need to concentrate
Our training is almost over
Yes, sir!
Let's go!
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Our school is back!
It's all because of us
Yes, because we distract the monster
So they chase us
Yes, that's why
Thank you for us
Yes, sir!
Excuse me
[The raptor is attacking the school]
What's up?
We're making food for you
Sir?
Since when did I marry your aunt?
[The raptor is attacking the school]
I'm on a vacation
I don't like chicken
I'm vegetarian
Sir!
Seriously, I'm not going to eat
I'm scared
Hey!
Stop it!
It's for me!
I'm not going to eat
I'm scared
Those naughty kids
They're using the same trick
If you're a vegetarian, it means it's easier to find food
I agree
Here you go
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Turn left!
Turn right!
I'm holding the leaves
No!
I'm going to sleep now
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Sir?
What is it now?
Ta-da!
We're making food for you
We're vegetarian
Do you think I'm going to eat the leaves?
Enough!
Now, all of you, leave!
I'm not hungry!
Understand?
Leave!
[The raptor is attacking the school]
He said he's a vegetarian
I don't want to eat
Let's go home
But I want to win
I just want to go home
If you say you want to go home, I'll turn you into chickens
What should we do?
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Wait!
He said he's a vegetarian
Let's do it another way
What should we do?
Who is it?
Come here
Now, they won't bother me anymore
So, I can sleep peacefully
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Excuse me!
Show your spirit, get ready, my friend
Run, jump, jump, run, we're
Brave, don't give up
Chase your dream
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
How is it, sir?
Are you still sick, sir?
I'm sick of smiling
Kids
Yes, sir?
Don't bother me
Watch out, if they dare to bother me again
[The raptor is attacking the school]
I'm getting hungry because of scolding them
I'm running out of food
Never mind, just go shopping
I haven't gone out for a long time
[The raptor is attacking the school]
This is a good chance
If I reveal who he is
I'm sure he'll be angry and I'll get rid of him
So I don't have to worry about the raptor
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Ray, don't give up
This is for our friend, Alva
I won't give up for Alva
Don't be like that
I know him
What's wrong with him?
Let's help him
He doesn't want to help us
This is for the sake of humanity
We have to help him
Let's go
[The raptor is attacking the school]
I can't change here
Everyone is afraid of me
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Mega, you always bring school
I will kick you out of the school
Just watch
I'm coming, Medi
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Are you okay?
Thank you
You are a good boy
Okay
I will invite you to dinner at my house
And I will fix your telescope
Yes!
Why are they here?
Sia!
Let's go
Uncle, wait
Why are you afraid of the moon?
It's scary
It's scary, but why are you afraid of the moon?
Can you be quiet?
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Okay, everyone stay here
I just remembered
I forgot something
I will help you later
Hey, are you leaving?
Yes
But don't expect us to help you again
We don't like kids who are afraid of the moon
Yes
It's scary
Okay
I will fix your telescope
Really?
Yes!
What are you doing?
Because the raptor is so big
But I have one request
Don't go anywhere
Stay here
And none of you can go to the cave
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Do you understand?
Yes
[The raptor is attacking the school]
Wake up!
I forgot to turn on the light
[The raptor is attacking the school]
We are so scared
The raptor is so scary
It's so big
Don't complain
It's useless
It's better to fix the telescope
It's better than nothing
Yes
Don't complain
Be patient
I'll fix it
I know
[The raptor is attacking the school]
I want to go home
Let's go home
I'm scared
How?
Nothing can't be fixed
It's done
Thank you
You're so kind
I'll excuse myself
Thank you
Opega!
[The raptor is attacking the school]
My friends
Wake up
My friends, wake up
[The raptor is attacking the school]
What's wrong?
The telescope is fixed
I can find Alva
You!
Sorry, I was attacked
The telescope is fixed
Where's Tol?
He's still unconscious
Let's go inside
No
You go alone
I don't want to
I'll go alone
Help!
Ouch!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry
You attacked me again
You want to kill me?
I'm almost dead
I'm not going to die
Don't be mad
Calm down
You're safe
Let's go
Alva is here
She's in the village clinic
I want to see her
Stop fighting
Let's go find Alva
Let's go
It hurts
I'm sure
This is all my doing
I have a monster
Yes, I did it
You don't have any feelings
Let's fix this at my house
I want to see her
Don't go there
You don't have any feelings
You guys
Why are you here?
We're looking for you
Let's go home
Let's go
We can go back to school with this
What's wrong?
I still have something to do
What is it?
I have something to do
Like a police officer
You know?
I want to make my house like yours
Like yours?
Why are you going there?
The house is scary
And scary people
Are you from there?
Yes, we fixed this telescope
That was broken
What are you doing?
She's a ghost
I'm curious who she is
Here, take this
Okay
What is that?
It looks like a monster
Why is it not here yet?
I'll try here
Here, try this
It's broken
Try again
Let's fix this at the police station
Okay, let's fix this at my house
I don't want to
Don't go there
Don't
I don't want to
I'm scared
I know
But
I'm not afraid of the ghost
They always ask for help
I think they are attacked
By the monster
I feel sorry for them
I want to take care of their house
Do you want to come?
If you don't want to come
It's okay, I'll go by myself
Me too
You want to come too, right?
We are friends
Okay
1, 2, 3
Time to
Wash our hands
Why are you so slow?
Why don't you give up?
Why are they there?
I'm going to succeed
What's wrong?
Sir
I'm so sorry
I could have made you
Appear in front of the people
If I had been
They would have been fired
You are stupid
Why did you act
Not according to what I ordered
But sir
Shut up
I don't want all my plans to fail
We wait until the full moon
Because at that time
It's the right time for us to act
Tonight is the night of the full moon
I'm sorry
I have to hide
I can't go out
Because I don't want to hurt anyone
Anyone
I'm sorry
Excuse me
Who is this?
What are you doing here?
Sir
The telescope is broken
Can you fix it?
Here
This is what makes me angry
Wait
Where are you going?
There
Why is it broken?
It's not
It's easy to get in
I can't
Go upstairs
Why is the password?
TETOT
You're wrong
Remember, if you're wrong three times, you'll be blocked
I can't be with you, Mumi
Panji
TETOT
You're wrong again
I'm wrong again
What's the password?
Last chance
15 seconds left
I just saw you here
What's your name?
If you're wrong, you'll be blocked
My name is Alfa
Why is it open?
You said the password is correct
Please come in
So, the password is Alfa
What's wrong?
That's it
This can't be fixed
It's broken
Here
When you get home, I still have a lot of things to do
It hurts
I'm tired
Can I rest here for a while?
My feet hurt
I can't
I can't eat plastic
Let's promise not to eat plastic
It hurts
I'm sorry
Mum
Dad
Mum, wake up
Dad wake up!
Mom, wake up!
Wake up dad!
Mom!
Wake up!
[music]
How can he breathe?
That means they're still alive!
Dad wake up!
Mom, wake up!
[music]
Dad!
That means they're just a residual.
[crying]
Dad, wake up!
We're trapped.
Dad is being punished.
You have to let him go.
Dad!
[music]
Mom, what's wrong?
Dad!
Mom!
[music]
[bell ringing]
We're trapped!
[music]
[bell ringing]
We're trapped.
I'm going to laugh.
Let's hide.
We have to help him.
Come on.
[music]
Mom!
Dad!
Stop!
[music]
What have you done?
You can't free them this way.
But you killed them.
They can't get out of this chain.
I just want to free my parents.
Go.
Go away.
You're a criminal.
You should know.
I'll kill you when you leave.
No.
Who are you?
You stole my parents.
[music]
Parents?
You said parents.
Don't be ridiculous.
No.
You're ridiculous.
I'm Alva.
They're my parents.
[music]
You're Alva.
Yes.
I'm Alva.
They're my parents.
Why did you kidnap them?
[music]
Alva.
You have to help me.
Don't do anything to her.
Wait.
[music]
I'll explain.
Actually....
[music]
Don't be ridiculous.
This is bad.
I'll change.
[music]
Alva.
You go from here.
You too.
Now, you go.
No.
I want to go.
Don't be ridiculous.
You two go from here.
Vipinksan.
Stop.
[music]
Vipinksan.
[screaming]
[music]
Where is Alva?
Oh, yes.
Maybe she went to the mine.
When will it be over?
We're attacked.
Alva, you should let your parents go now.
Don't touch me.
[music]
What if Alva asks?
They fainted.
They can't breathe.
[music]
Let's look for Mr. Anji.
There is the way.
Yes.
And Mr. Anji is there.
[music]
Mr. Anji.
Where is he?
He's not here.
Mr. Anji.
Where is Mr. Anji?
Don't.
He ran away.
What?
Let's go back to school.
We'll tell the teacher about this.
Yes, we'll go there again.
No.
I don't want to go there.
And then, I don't want to lose my parents.
Where is the telescope?
Here.
But, the telescope is broken.
The cable can't be used.
It's totally broken.
So, it can't be fixed.
Maybe there is a clue.
Let's try.
Where?
Mount Surab.
Huh?
Why is there a sound?
I don't know.
Maybe he didn't show us.
Maybe he tried to show us.
That's impossible.
That's a mistake.
The telescope is broken.
It's not his fault.
You know where Mount Surab is.
Yes.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
No.
I'm not scared.
I'm brave.
I'll find my father.
Please, help me.
Please, take care of my parents.
I'll be back.
Don't.
The monster is coming.
Tole.
It hurts.
Be happy.
Don't be sad.
If you're scared, just stay.
I'm scared.
Where is he?
Oh, yeah.
What's going on?
It's from the ground.
Kill them all.
Don't let them escape.
Yes, sir.
We can do this.
To be continued...
Next episode...
Change the target.
Then, attack them all.
Yes, sir.
Kill them all.
Don't let them escape.
Yes, sir.
Hurry.
To be continued...
Help me.
I have to find him.
I have to get the money.
Because...
I have to save them.
There's a monster.
Why is it attacking us?
Professor, it's angry.
I've defeated you.
To be continued...
What?
The child is still alive?
Akara.
Finish the child and the monster.
Hurry.
To be continued...
Why hasn't he come yet?
Don't let him get to me again.
Don't be rude.
Okay.
It's better if you don't come back.
Let's follow the monster.
I'm hungry.
Where should we go?
Don't be mistaken.
The inside is...
Forgive me.
Akara, don't be rude.
Don't be rude.
I'm angry.
Where's the makeup?
Hurry up.
Okay.
Fire!
It's okay.
Now is the time.
Now I can save Mr. Panji.
Where are you, Alva?
Are you scared?
Poor you.
I see.
Because your power is not as good as mine.
Where are you, Alva?
Who's scared?
You're back.
But I have to finish you first, Panji.
She's gone.
You're confused, right?
I'm not angry.
This must be Alva's trick.
Alva, come out!
What's wrong with him?
Akara!
How dare you attack me?
I'm sorry, sir.
Alva and Srika are dead.
But you've ruined them.
Answer me!
Don't be angry, sir.
You'll be in trouble.
Shut up!
You're Akara, right?
Yes.
Yes, I'm Akara.
Answer me!
I was told to shut up.
Alva, come out!
You scared me.
We can do this.
What is it, Professor?
I'm thinking about the eighth wave.
Before it ruins the world...
...we have to fight it.
But how, Professor?
We know that...
...the eighth wave has recovered.
It's even stronger now.
The only way...
...is to find the soul stone.
Find the soul stone.
Okay.
Professor.
Let me go find it.
Don't, Megatara.
This mission is too dangerous.
I don't want to involve the children.
We don't have to involve the children.
It's better if...
...me and the other professors...
...go and complete this mission.
That's the problem, Megatara.
We have to involve the children.
Because the soul stone is filled by the eighth wave.
It can only be seen by the children.
"The eighth wave has recovered. The children are safe."
Where are you going?
Don't touch me!
Let's go.
I'm going to get the soul stone.
That's me.
Don't touch me.
Let go of me!
I don't want to.
I'll kill you.
You're a group again.
I love you.
Let's go.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
You're still alive.
I know you're using the eighth wave.
Alva, where are you?
Alva!
Alva, come out!
You scared me.
I'm going to look for my father.
I'm going home with my doll.
That's not a doll.
That's a lizard.
Alva, why did you bring the lizard here?
Where did it come from?
I saw a raptor attacking the lizard.
A raptor?
Yes, a raptor is a creature from the Angkara province.
It attacked the lizard and fainted.
If the lizard lost, why did you bring it here?
Are you going to cure it?
No, it's not a raptor.
Then?
It's my father.
My father?
Yes, my father is a raptor.
The raptor is so cute.
Don't come near me.
I'll give you a name.
It's Blacky.
Blacky?
Why is it called Blacky?
Come here.
Let's go.
Wake up.
Let's play.
(Blacky's roar)
Sir, I'm sorry.
I promise I'll be a better man.
Sir.
Okay.
I'll give you another chance.
But don't fail.
We don't have much time.
We only have six hours before the sun sets.
And I don't want the lizard to turn into a rat.
Do you understand?
Okay, sir.
I'll try.
(Blacky's roar)
What do you want?
I want you to come to my house.
Don't you dare to attack the kid.
They are evil.
No.
That's a lie.
They are evil.
Dad.
Mom.
(Blacky's roar)