Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
What are you doing?
Get him!
You're playing with fire?
The enemy is gone!
What?
Here, as you requested
The 8th Prince's footwear
Thank you, Your Highness
What is the footwear for?
That's none of your business, Your Highness
What's clear is that you have lost to me
So, you have to follow my orders
But be careful
If you use that to fight the 8th Prince
I will not stay quiet
You just calm down, Your Highness
This is not to harm the 8th Prince
But to harm someone
Alright, I'll go now
Thank you, Your Highness
Goodbye
This is so weird
That's enough
You're a traitor
Watch your mouth
Your Highness must be very happy with me
The 8th Prince?
How dare you betray me?
You stole my footwear
To make a mess, right?
So I can realize
Yes, of course
All of this is because of your orders
Since when did you become a traitor?
I'm a traitor and I bow to you
You're acting weird
Maybe you're already known to the world
You're drunk
Drink it!
Sir, why are we here?
Because of your stupidity
You've drunk the love potion from me
That's why you're a traitor
Sir, please forgive me
I'm sorry, sir
You idiot!
Report, Sir
How is it?
Have you arrested the fugitives?
I'm sorry, Sir
Orion and Leon are both innocent
You idiot!
Anggar!
As a guilty person
You must arrest Orion and Leon
And put them back in jail
Hurry!
Got it!
Arrest them!
Sir!
Oh no
It's so strong
That's Mr. Bargi!
It's a rat!
It's a warm tea
Oh my God
Bargi is so big
There's a smoke on his hair
It means there's a soul stone
But I didn't see it
I saw that his hair was so curly
It's like it's never been shaved since birth
Because the soldier is not a kid anymore
That's enough
Dino!
This is it
It's time to take my revenge
Okay
I did it!
I'm tired, I can't do it anymore
Raw cheese is eaten raw
If Tifinju loses
We'll use the Kivilat Mantra
Let's go!
Kivilat!
It's just a joke
Okay
It's time to get together
Anji!
Hello everyone
Okay everyone
Let's do it together
Using Tavalli Mantra
This is a real monster
It's so big and scary
I've never seen a monster like this
Okay everyone
Let's do it together
Using Tavalli Mantra
1, 2, 3
Tavalli!
We did it!
Why didn't you use Tavalli Mantra earlier?
We can't hold it anymore
Let's eat it!
No!
There's only one way
Let's run!
Don't go!
I'm here
Let's run!
Don't go!
Run!
Who are you?
Don't go!
It's me!
Who are you?
Hurry!
We have to get out of here
Follow me!
Don't go!
I'm here!
Follow me!
Okay
Run!
What are they doing?
They're so strong
Thank you everyone
For being here
We'll set up a strategy first
After that
We'll attack again
Where are you from?
I've been looking for you
You better eat first
So you won't faint again
I faint?
Yes
How can I faint?
I don't know
Earlier, you said you wanted to attack Ankara
When you were about to attack Ankara
You suddenly grabbed me
It hurt
And then you fainted
I don't know why
I'll go get the rest
Listen carefully
If you keep your soul in the soul stone
And if someone wants to destroy the stone
You'll feel a terrible pain
And you won't be able to realize it
What if someone wants to destroy the stone?
That's why I fainted
That's possible
Because at that time
Megantara and the other kids went to destroy the stone
That's enough!
Eat first, Sir
Mr. Oret
Welcome to the school
I'm very grateful
To you
For your hospitality
Because you've freed us from the fire prison
And we don't know how to repay you
You don't have to repay anything
This is my responsibility
Leon is a student in my school
I'll help you
Professor
I'm sorry
I've misunderstood you
Because of the dark side
I've wronged you
It's okay
We've forgiven you
Leon
You're so lucky
To meet good people
Like Professor Adebaran and Professor Kulwa
I'm so happy
By the way
Where's Professor Agni?
I want to apologize to him
Professor Agni is in the dark side
What?
Why?
Is he possessed?
No
Now he's in the dark side
What?
How come?
Because of the dark side
And it has affected me
So he's in the dark side
Professor
Agni
Professor Agni
It's all my fault
I have to be responsible
I'll find Professor Agni
At the 8th building
No, Leon
It's dangerous
Yes, Leon
It's very dangerous
It's a stupid move
To come to the dark side
We have to come up with a strategy
To face the 8th building
The 8th building
Enough
They've destroyed the first soul stone
We can't give up
Now
It's time to find the second soul stone
Where's the second soul stone?
According to my research
The second soul stone
Is controlled by a creature
Called Bardi
And now
They're looking for the second soul stone
Looks like we're safe
From him
Yes
Yes, Professor
Why are you and your son
In that haunted place?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for you
And we're looking for Bardi
Wait
There's a doll
And a paper
Hi, Srigala
Why are you wearing a jacket?
Well, it's all because of that feeling
He...
He wants me to marry him
Hey, kids
Don't tease the parents
By the way
Bardi's taste
Is not bad
Don't make me feel bad
He's my uncle's witness
Why should we fight with him?
I'll just ask him
And he'll give me the soul stone
Right
Wait
You said soul stone?
Yes, soul stone
The first soul stone
Has been obtained by the army
And we're looking for the second soul stone
The second soul stone
Is from Bardi's hair
That's right
Bardi's hair is a bit smokey
So we have to cut his hair
That's right
We're Bardi's hair
There's no other way
Let's just meet him
No, no, no
I don't want to meet him
Wait
Listen to this
Kura-kura is playing in the yard
Good job
Megantara has a great idea
What is it?
How is it?
Have you succeeded in getting the soul stone?
I've got it
I've obtained the soul stone
From the dark spirit
And I've created the spirit
Where is the spirit?
Here, professor
What are we waiting for?
Let's attack the dark spirit together
Okay
Let's do it
The dark spirit is not an easy opponent
But we can't wait, professor
If we wait, the dark spirit will know our plan
And it will fail
But if we get caught
It will be fatal
It's okay, professor
Don't be afraid
There are many teams of professors
Especially Orion and Leon
So we can invite them too
Orion and Leon?
Ankara
How do you know that Orion and Leon are free?
Well
I've just finished the eighth stage of the dark spirit
So I know, professor
Maybe
You've drunk the love potion from the eighth spirit
Where have you been?
Vella, Feli
I'm sorry
Because I've been mean to you
It's okay, Rio
We've forgotten
You're so mean
We're not vengeful
You're right
I'm sorry
Actually, my name is Leon
Not Rio
Mario, Ke
Moe, Leon
The important thing is you're still happy for us
Right, sister?
You're right, sister
Let's go to professor Adebaran's room
Ke, who's that?
I mean, Leon
Yes, you're right
Who's that?
He's my grandfather
Hi, grandpa
Nice to meet you
We'll go now
Let's go
Let's follow him
Uncle
If so
Before we give this potion to him
I want you to try it first
Why should I?
It's not for me
Why?
Are you afraid?
Is it really a good potion?
It's done
You don't need to be afraid
You're not easy to be a fraud
More than this
Uncle
The traitor will never win
What's wrong, Adebaran?
Leon
You're a traitor
Uncle
Let my grandfather go
Don't move
Do you want to hurt him?
Don't hurt my grandfather
Stay where you are
If you want him to be safe
Anggara
Don't take my grandfather, Anggara
Please, Adebaran
Please, save my grandfather
Leon
Calm down
I'll bring him back
I feel sick
Why are you acting like that, Megantara?
Listen, Panci
To get that soul
What if you...
Marry Barji?
No, no, no
I don't want to marry him
I don't want to
Panci
We have to get that soul stone
If you marry Barji
In a marriage
The wife has to obey her husband
When Barji becomes your wife
Barji will obey you
When you ask for his hair
Barji will happily share it
Share his hair
Right?
No, no, no
If you want it, I want it
I don't want to marry that monster
I don't want to
Go to the temple
Yes, sir
Think about it
This is just a joke
Yes, sir
Megantara
This is just a joke
It's a lie
It's true
It's a set up
I don't want to marry him
Panci
What about the blonde girl?
How did you know?
I was just asked
My dream girl
Actually
I want to marry a girl from Putri Angsa
How can you
Marry a girl from Putri Angsa?
The girl from Angsa
Hates men
It's true
In English, it's called impossible
In Arabic, it's called mustahil
I'm so stupid
I think you should marry Barji
It's just a joke
No
Listen
I'd rather be single all my life
It's not funny
Guys
Don't force him
Poor him
He's gone
I have an idea
What is it?
The 8th prince will be happy with me
Because I got the girl from Putri Angsa
Stop
I'm Will
I'm Ferry
We're going to punish you
Help
What are you doing?
Let me go
What is that?
This is the dust of protection
Dear dust of protection
Protect this school
From me
What is that?
This is the dust of protection
Dear dust of protection
Protect this school
From me
What are you doing?
Stop
I'll kill you
Here
Ouch
Stop
You're using dust of protection again
I can get you another chance
Watch out
I'll put it here
This is the right place for you
Stop looking for the dust of soul
We can do this
Leon
Grandpa
Thank God you're awake
Where's Professor Angkara?
He's been expelled from here
He won't come back
And he won't hurt us again
But I can't just stay here
I have to bring him back
To make up for my mistake
Thank God
Everything is over now
We're all going to die
Don't
This is the real thing
I can do this
Don't leave me
You're still here
That means they don't understand my potential
I'm going to get you
I have to stop Alfa and Aldebaran from getting the stone
I want to get married
Go
God
Why did you leave?
I almost got hit by the stone you threw
I'm sorry God
I'm leaving
You're so stubborn
You're just like your father
Bargi
I'm here to tell you
Don't you dare to do anything to anyone
Do you understand?
I understand
And if you do anything to anyone
I will destroy you
And your fate will be the same as Barga's
Okay God
I want to get married
Husband
Okay
The problem with the stone is solved
Now it's time for me to go home
I have to check on Gama and Alvila
Sir
What is it now?
Don't ask me for anything
Because I don't want to
Don't be mad at me
We want to make up with you
Right, Lita?
Yes, we want to give you a massage
Massage?
Yes
You were just kidnapped by Bargi
You must be tired
So we want to give you a massage
Do you want to give us a massage?
It's good
Do you want to?
Yes, I do
Let's go
Give me a massage
You're so nice
Is it good?
It's good, you're good at giving a massage
If you want, we can give you a massage everyday
Of course
But there's a condition
What is it?
You have to marry Bargi
This is it
Just a joke?
No, I knew it
You're nice to me because you want to
You're so curious
Wait, sir
The massage is not done yet, right?
No, I don't want to
Do it
But, sir
It's not going to work
How about it?
Is it going to work?
Yes, is it going to work?
No
No, sir
But, sir, I don't want to marry Bargi
You still don't want to?
Yes
I have a better idea
What is it?
Okay
Let's do it now
Change!
Wow, you're so pretty
But still, you're more beautiful than Bargi
If this is the way, I want to be a servant
What are you talking about?
I'll tell the girl
Hi, everyone
Do I look like Gadis Putri Angsa?
You look exactly like her
I'm such a cat, why do I have to marry a random girl?
Hi, handsome guy
Why are you here?
I'm here because I want to meet you
Are you looking for me?
Do you need me?
For what?
Aren't you the one who hates all men?
Yes, I do hate men
But, I'm not a man
But, if the men are handsome like you, I want to...
Since I'm far away, do you want to do something for me?
What is it?
Marry Bargi
What?
Why did Gadis Putri Angsa ask me to marry Bargi?
Does she know Bargi?
That's weird
Gadis Putri Angsa can't possibly marry someone like this
Or maybe...
Come on, you want to, right?
Please
Irfan!
Why are you hitting me?
Alfa!
How dare you lie to me?
Please
I'm angry
Oh no
There's a mosquito!
There's a cockroach!
It's a cockroach!
It's wet!
What's wrong, Alfa?
My plan failed
What are you doing?
There's sugar!
There's a mosquito!
There's a cockroach!
You're so noisy!
Calm down, Megantara
I'm not here to make a fuss
I'm just reminding you all
Don't bother Bargi
Do you understand?
[The next day]
Why are we here?
This is the right place for all of you
Stop looking for the soul stone
I'm not done yet
One more time!
What should we do?
You can't do it
You're a coward!
Your body is already injured
[The next day]
As you all know
Until now
No one can escape from the aquarium
So, it's better
To say goodbye to the world
Help!
It's a mosquito!
It's a cockroach!
[We can do it]
Alfa is also in the forest with the cockroach
But, it's okay
Just leave it
I will never be persuaded by them
To marry a cockroach
Husband!
[The next day]
Why is it him again?
Husband!
Open it!
Kids, don't be weird
Calm down
Let's focus
Let's destroy it together
Not with the mantra
Let's use the mantra
"Api Vih"
Wait!
I can't do it!
How?
Let's try again
With the mantra "Havancur"
Ready?
"Havancur"
We can do it!
Let's try again with "Vivinjo"
"Vivinjo"
Let's use "Vivinjo"
"Api Vih"
"Havancur"
"Vivinjo"
We can't do it
Let's use the mantra "Vivinjo"
Yes, we can do it
Ready?
Concentrate
"Vivinjo"
Help!
Don't panic!
I'm taller than you
Come on!
Get on my back!
"Vivinjo"
Kids!
Eat the snack
During the picnic
Help!
You have to calm down
Don't panic
Let's just help him!
Yes!
We can't do it
Help!
Don't panic!
Let's just help him!
Husband!
Where is he?
Feel your time
Now
You can't go back
Where is he?
Husband!
I know
This must be Alfa's snake
And his friends
They must be looking for the snake
Husband?
I'm in danger
Husband!
The snake!
Where is he?
Why isn't he coming?
Husband!
He's angry
We can't help him
What should we do?
Husband!
I'm so happy
I can punish Alfa and Alder
Now
I just need to punish Leon
And his brother
Angara!
Where are you?
He should be here
And report the result
Angara!
How dare you come here?
Why?
Because
He failed to get Orion and Leon
And
He can't go back to school
Because Aldebaran has spread
The dust around the school
You're so stupid
He can never be punished
I'm so happy
I almost fell
It's so big
Husband!
He's so close
Where should I hide?
I have an idea
Okay
Thousand Leaf Daffodil
Perfect
Husband!
Family!
Come here!
Husband's voice
Husband!
Come here!
The result
Husband!
Argi!
I'm sorry, Argi
Please, Argi
Husband!
Please, Argi!
This is the result of the eighth Pangeron
Amazing
Please, make a proposal
To give it to Argi
So that Argi can realize it
And come back to us
Give it with a smile
Are you ready, Professor?
Yes, Professor
Okay, Dr. Bertini?
Okay
We'll excuse ourselves, Professor
Excuse me, Professor
Give it with a smile
Okay
Finally
I can be free from that bad feeling
I'm so happy
What's that sound?
Let me check
Help!
Rey! Linda!
Alfa!
Alfa! Li! Linda!
Alfa! I'm sorry, Alfa
Because I thought
The SOS you sent was just a misunderstanding
Help!
Alfa!
Where are you?
I'm Argi
Yes, Argi
You guys stay here
I'll go get help
Stay here
We'll be fine
I'm so lazy to meet him again
Daftang Lollipop
Fly, Fang!
Argi!
My husband!
Don't hug me
You want to get out of here, right?
I'll get you out
Argi!
Hold my lollipop
Hold it
Come on
What did I tell you?
Don't touch me
It's so hard
To bring a secret with lollipop
How do I do it?
I know
I have an idea
Big brother
Lollipop
Perfect
Fly, Fang!
Argi!
You go up
Come on
My husband!
Okay
I'm coming
Jump!
Fang!
Hold it
Wake up
I'll go down
Argi!
Hurry!
Destroy the aquarium
I'm going!
Argi!
Alpha!
Hold on!
Three of you, come here
I want to take a bath
Are you okay?
We're okay
You're all safe
We're all still alive
Argi!
Thank you
Thank you, Argi!
My husband!
No!
It's fun!
Just enjoy it!
This is fate
Just be happy
Let's go!
I'm hungry
Argi, you're so weak!
You saved us
Now we're going to be eaten
We're going to be eaten!
The meat is not good
It's so little
If you want to eat, just eat him
He's still fresh
Like a goat
He's a young goat
It's going to be delicious
What?
You're just a bull
You have more meat
Husband!
Eat him!
I love you, Ngen
What are you doing in there?
It's useless
If you don't go in there
The dark side of the building will be mad at me
What's wrong with you?
Sir!
Why did you go back and forth?
Sir, I'm sorry
I failed to get Orion and Leon
The goods are very cheap now
They have put back the dust
So when I got Leon
I was out of breath
I'm sorry, sir
You're useless!
Sir!
Sir, calm down!
Calm down!
You don't have to be patient with me
I know the right punishment for him
What?
He's going to be a scourge for a month
He's forbidden to serve you
Or help you
That way
He's not considered a human
He's not useful to you
And he's not considered by Aldebaran
Sir, please don't
From now on
You're not allowed to serve him for a month
No!
Sir, please do it
Let me do it
I can't do it
Can you do it?
Yes
From now on
You're the one who's going to do the task
But you can't disappoint me
Yes, sir
I won't let you disobey my orders
I won't let you
Change your position as a trusted person
Let him go!
Good afternoon, children
Good afternoon, sir
Today we're going to learn
Mantra
Yes, sir
What's wrong?
What? The teacher? The principal? The passenger?
They haven't come
It's okay
They've got a special permission
From Professor Aldebaran
Where are they going, sir?
How do I know?
That's why you shouldn't go to the village often
You'll miss the news
Let me go!
Silence!
Good
Now we're going to learn
Teleportation Mantra
Who can explain what teleportation mantra is?
No one?
How disappointing
I'm sure you didn't read the book
Good
Teleportation mantra
Is used
If we want to move from one place
To another
And it can shorten the distance
And time
I'll give you an example
Teleportation
*Music*
What's going on?
I'm here
*Music*
Alright, you all have to remember
If you use this mantra
The further you go, the more energy you will get
One more thing, don't misuse this mantra
Because if you do, you won't get to the place you want
Or you will be in trouble
*Mantra*
Ahoy, with a smile, professor Aldebaran
The mission is ready
Thank you, professor
*Music*
What are we going to do?
*Singing*
I'm scared
*Music*
What is that bread for?
What are you doing?
*Music*
Alfa, Alfa
Alfa, the sword
*Music*
Alfa is put in the middle of the bread
Let Alfa go
Alfa
*Music*
Ah
Alfa
*Music*
No
Stop, stop
Don't, don't touch her
She's our guest
Yes, that's right, we're guests
Yes, we're guests
*Groan*
Yes, yes
You want us to get married, right?
If you want us to get married, don't eat them
Okay?
They're all our guests
They're our wedding guests
*Coughing*
*Music*
So, you want to marry me?
Yes, yes, yes
I want to marry you
So, you love me?
Okay, okay, that's enough
The important thing is you can't eat them
If you eat them, we'll cancel the wedding
*Laughing*
Husband
Guest
*Groaning*
Ouch
Get up, get up
It's okay, let's go
Guest
*Laughing*
*Music*
Now, who wants to try this telephone call?
Me, me, me
Okay
It seems like everyone wants to try, except for Tom
Tom
Tommy, please go to the front
You get the first turn
Are you sure, boss? I'm scared
You're annoying
Come on, Tommy, go to the front
Tommy, if you don't want to, you'll get two points
One
*Music*
Stand on my right
I want you to use teleportation and move to my left
Please
*Music*
Teleportation
Where is the boss?
*Music*
Okay, stay where you are
Tommy's turn
*Music*
Tommy, where did you get the pee?
Shut up
*Music*
Why did I move to the river?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Tommy, I told you not to memorize the dance wrongly
It's lucky that you moved to the river
Try it if you want to swim
You'll get it
*Music*
I didn't expect that I was going to get pee too
I think the sound of pee is starting to come
*Music*
It's so good
Do you know that I'm doing everything for Alfa?
Anyway, I don't want Alfa to be killed by the Dark Lord
Whatever happens, we have to get the Soul Stone
*Music*
I'm sorry, sir
I'm sorry for bothering you
*Music*
It's okay
The important thing now, as you said, is to find the soul stone
*Music*
Wait, wait
I have an idea
I don't think Mr. Panji needs to marry Bargi
You're right, Alfa
Alfa, what are you going to do if Mr. Panji doesn't marry Bargi?
How can we get the soul stone?
I don't care if he marries Alfa
But I have a better idea
*Music*
Your job is to give this love potion to Alfa
It means you have to come to the Panjanggut 8 Palace
I have another idea, sir
You shouldn't make your eyes black
It's not good, sir
You don't look good
As usual, Alfa
Yes, sir
You're the only one who can do it
*Music*