Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Attack!
We won't stop until we get that fire crystal
So we can all unite
Damn, they're all united
We can't let this happen, I have to stop them
Don't touch me!
Rita, you're so brave
You know, only bad people dare to attack their own friends
I'm a bad person
She's not a bad person, she just can't control herself
I'm glad I can help you
But you have to remember, you can't use your feelings
You have to control yourself, think of yourself
And you have to let go of your love for others
Let me go, help!
Shut up!
It's useless to call them, they won't come for you
Finally, the police called me
Ah, I'm so lucky
Oh no, what should I do?
I'm so sleepy
Help!
Rita!
Where are you?
Rita, I'm here!
What should I do? I can't help you like this
I'm stuck here!
Rita!
Help!
I've learned Pegasus' spell
This is good, let me try
Pegasus!
This is so small, how can it help me?
Tell me!
Bulgarda, I need Bulgarda
Bulgarda
Pegasus!
Pegasus
Wow, it's so big
Bulgarda, let go of my rope
Thank you Bulgarda
Tell me!
Rita, Ray, Pegasus, where are you?
Rita, Ray, Pegasus
Ray, Rita, where are you?
Ray, Pegasus, Rita, where are you?
Ray, Pegasus, where are you?
I'll look for Rita
Okay, bye
Let me go!
Help!
Help me, Sir!
Rita, you have to gather your strength and attack them
Pegasus, Ray, Pegasus, where are you?
Now you throw the people who hurt you, hurry up!
Rita, where are you?
Where is Rita?
I don't know, when I got here, Rita was gone
Where is she?
Rita!
Ray, use your thunder
Okay
Sir, Rita is under that man's roof
Stop!
Rita, let's go back to school
Yes, let's go back to school
Don't follow him anymore
Don't be fooled, boy
Do you remember? They've made you sad, they've divorced you
Rita, let's go back to school
We want to play the snake again
Yes
Let's go, Rita
Let's go
Pegasus!
Pegasus, are you okay?
Vega, Vega
Vega, don't force yourself
Just write it down
Pelita is so brave
She made Vega become like this
I told you, she's a monster
That's why we shouldn't get close to her anymore
I'm so sorry for what happened to Vega
I shouldn't have gone
Forgive me, Sir
You don't have to regret
Make this a learning experience for you
You have to remember
I will never leave you in any condition
And this is your place
I'm always by your side
[The Snakes' Claw]
There's a truth
Pelita has a very dangerous power
And we have to be careful to catch her
We have to prepare more to fight that girl
If we can catch her
All the snakes will be gone
Tri, you have to make a new weapon
A very powerful weapon
A weapon that can defeat the girl named Pelita
Alright, we will take them down
[The Snakes' Claw]
Pelita, let's go home
Let's go home
Let's go back to school
Let's play together again
[The Snakes' Claw]
I feel so sorry for Vega
Come on, Pelita
She must be so sad
She must be thinking about us
Let's go home, Pelita
Come on, Pelita
Pelita
Wake up, Pelita
Wake up
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
I'm not sick
I feel so sorry for Vega
Come on, Pelita
Let's go home and play together again
[The Snakes' Claw]
Pelita, let's go home
Tentara, we have to help Vega
We have to take Vega to Pelita's place
Tentara, will you?
I feel sorry for her
Ava, don't be nervous
It's a very far place
It's not only far, it's also dangerous
That's why I need your help
To make me safe
Can you help me?
Please, Tentara
I feel sorry for Vega
Please, I'm begging you
Yes, Ava
We'll go there
What are you wearing?
How about this?
What do you think?
It's a good idea, right?
Buy a card, eh
It's full of coconut
Good idea, eh
It's Alfa's idea
Good, good
Let's go
[The Snakes' Claw]
I am the third head dragon
I bring your favorite food
Please enjoy
Sorry for disturbing your time
I'm sorry
For disturbing your time
Change
[The Snakes' Claw]
Come on, finish it
Eat it
[The Snakes' Claw]
Hold it tight
Hold it
[The Snakes' Claw]
We'll succeed
This arrow is very powerful
Whatever it hits
Will turn into a stone
Good
Let's go
So what should I do now?
We have to defend ourselves
Until I can control the little one
Hi, little one
That's the one who kidnapped me
How did he know you?
Besides, you don't have to worry
I've made a promise with the teachers at the magic school
To fight back against the elf warriors
So they won't disturb our plan now
Good, Angkara
Now your job is to eliminate Ray and Vicky
I'll make the elf warriors destroy your elf
You have to kidnap the elf
Yes, sir
Just a moment
[The Snakes' Claw]
Soon, Alfa will be mine
What's that?
[The Snakes' Claw]
What are you doing?
Stay there
You're a bad guy
I won't let you hurt KvK
Don't run, Kelita
[The Snakes' Claw]
Where are you going?
It's late, go to bed
I'll teach you a new skill tomorrow
I don't want to
I know everything
You're a bad guy
You're friends with the one who kidnapped me
You want to hurt KvK and Alfa
I don't want to be your friend
Good, you're here
Come here
How dare you
[The Snakes' Claw]
Kelita!
Come on
Thank you, Naga
I think the place is near
[The Snakes' Claw]
Kelita!
Kelita, wake up!
Keep going, Naga!
Finish them off!
Wake up!
Wake up, Fega!
Fega!
Wake up!
Wait, Fega!
Wake up, Fega!
[The Snakes' Claw]
Yes! Five!
One, two, three, four, five!
Yeah!
Wake up, Fega!
Wake up!
[The Snakes' Claw]
Fega!
You're alive!
I got you!
Fega!
[The Snakes' Claw]
I'm so glad you're not frozen again.
I'm so happy and proud.
I'm not frozen again because of you.
Because I love you so much.
So, the ice cream melted.
[The Snakes' Claw]
Felita.
From now on, fill your heart with love.
Okay?
And don't hate people.
One more thing.
Don't be afraid to leave.
We'll always be with you.
Okay?
Okay.
[The Snakes' Claw]
It's all trees.
The plants here are my friends.
[The Snakes' Claw]
I'm sorry.
[We can do it!]
Where's Papua?
Kauat, he's after us!
[The Snakes' Claw]
Purwocer!
Look!
The ice is melting!
Everything is back to normal.
This means that the firecrackers will return to us.
[The Snakes' Claw]
It's too late!
We did it!
Yeah!
[The Snakes' Claw]
So, Vega succeeded in making the princess realize the meaning of love and sacrifice.
And finally, all this mess ended.
That's right, Professor.
And you, Megantara.
Why did you let Alfa and Vega run away from school?
You brought the Chief of the Three without reporting to me.
Eating the snake's fish,
and sharing it with the coconut.
I'm sorry.
Again, I forgot.
I failed again.
I thought I could get the power to become a weapon.
So, I don't have to face Aldebaran directly.
Angara!
Yes, sir.
Do you know what you have to do?
The Star of Destiny will appear tomorrow night.
I will get it and give it to you.
So you can get the power from the Star of Destiny.
No.
You have to get it, Angara.
Don't fail.
Yes, sir.
The falling star.
The falling star is...
a falling star...
that falls to the earth.
And when it falls to the earth,
the star changes its form...
and becomes a falling woman.
Then...
Tommy.
Yes, sir.
When will the falling star appear?
I don't know.
Tommy.
Tommy!
When will the falling star appear?
I don't know, sir.
Listen.
Vega knows when the falling star will appear.
The falling star...
fell about a thousand years ago.
Good.
You're right.
Then, the question is...
why are the falling stars...
awaited by the people?
Ray.
Why are the falling stars...
awaited by the people?
Maybe because...
Because what?
Because it's beautiful.
I don't know.
Vega.
Why are the falling stars...
awaited by the people?
Because the falling star gives power.
There's no limit...
to what it can do.
Especially the heart.
Correct.
Give Vega a round of applause.
Why are the falling stars...
awaited by the people?
Because the falling stars...
will be fought by the people...
who are thirsty for power.
Therefore...
Professor Aldebaran has confirmed...
that we are all...
forbidden to catch the falling stars.
[The Falling Stars]
Thank you, Aldebaran.
There's a party.
Party.
I like parties.
Popo.
What?
Don't touch me.
You'll turn into ice.
I'm afraid of the cold.
Don't be afraid, Popo.
I can handle my power.
Forgive me.
I made you freeze.
Really?
You're a jinak.
What am I?
Popo.
Let's go home.
Home?
I'm fine.
I'm free.
I'm not helping anyone.
I'm doing this for Alfa's good.
I don't want to be a jinak.
We're sorry.
We're going to hurt you.
It's okay.
Okay.
We'll go now.
[The Falling Stars]
Let's gather.
There's a firework party.
Yeah!
[The Falling Stars]
That's not a firework.
You better give up.
Before the dark lord comes.
[The Falling Stars]
That's not a firework.
Of course I like fireworks.
I'm with Bambu.
They look happy.
I'll find out.
I was happy with the girl.
This is a trap.
We have to get the falling star.
Let's go.
[The Falling Stars]
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
That's the falling star.
I can't fail this time.
[The Falling Stars]
Hey, get out of here.
You better give up.
Before the 8th prince comes here,
we won't let him go.
Before we get his heart.
Don't dream.
Everyone wants his heart.
But it's not that easy.
Step on my body first.
[The Falling Stars]
It's so heavy.
Here, take a rest.
It's heavy.
You want to take my heart, right?
No, it's not me.
Go away, you're a bad person.
[The Falling Stars]
God, help me.
Alright, I'll help you.
[The Falling Stars]
I'll make you sleep forever.
You're a bad person.
You're rude.
It turns out you can use my magic.
But I won't lose.
[The Falling Stars]
Hey, you!
Thank you for helping me.
I'm sorry, I misjudged you.
I hit you too.
Yes, when you landed, they were fighting for your battle.
So I took you away from there.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so bad.
You want to forgive me, right?
Yes.
[The Falling Stars]
Where's the falling star?
The falling star is gone.
It's all your fault.
You should be punished.
[The Falling Stars]
Listen!
The falling star is mine.
If you meet it, you can't touch it.
Not even see it.
Do you understand?
Good.
Goodbye.
[The Falling Stars]
I think this belongs to the Sido School.
They must have taken the falling star.
Yes, they did.
Let's go there.
My name is Selena.
Alfa, I'm from Sido School.
Alfa, I beg you.
Don't tell anyone that I'm the falling star.
Because they will all fight me.
My hair will be cut.
Because my hair can make any kind of clothes.
And my tears will be squeezed.
Because my tears can create new power.
And can cure any kind of disease.
And my heart.
If my heart is taken and eaten.
It can create unlimited power.
[The Falling Stars]
They will fight to get you.
I'm scared, Alfa.
I want to go back to heaven.
Okay, don't be sad.
I promise I won't tell anyone about you.
And I will help you until you go back to heaven.
Are you serious?
Yes.
You're so kind.
Thank you, Alfa.
Promise.
Don't go anywhere.
Because this place is safe.
I will go back to the party.
Because they are looking for me.
Okay.
If you don't want to tell us where the falling star is.
We will find it ourselves.
[The Falling Stars]
Ali Baran!
Why are you all here?
[The Falling Stars]
Are you the soldiers?
Or the rebels?
Hey, what's the truth?
Where did you hide the falling star?
Hurry, return it. Because it's ours.
[The Falling Stars]
The falling star.
I don't understand.
Don't pretend.
This is the proof.
[The Falling Stars]
We found this brooch at the place where the falling star was.
Calm down.
I'm sure this is all a misunderstanding.
The proof is with us.
And it can't be wrong.
If you don't want to tell us where the falling star is.
We will find it ourselves.
Wait.
I won't let you in without my permission.
Or you have to face me.
[The Falling Stars]
Okay, let's go.
The bottom line is that they are really dead.
But, they were just crushed a little.
And now they are gone.
Professor Nadia Bara.
What do we do now?
This seems like a very serious problem.
I will find out about the falling star.
You stay alert.
I will find the answer.
Agni, bring the kids inside.
Come on, kids.
Alfa, where are you from?
We are looking for the answer.
I can't tell you that I'm a fan of The Falling Stars.
I have promised.
I have a stomachache.
That's why I have been in the toilet.
Alfa has a stomachache.
I will take the medicine at the clinic.
No need.
I'm already well.
Let's go there.
The teachers will look for us.
Let's go.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
What is he doing?
He thinks I'm just singing.
Alfa, where are we?
We're at the toilet.
Toilet?
Why are we at the toilet?
We're at the toilet.
If you're a princess...
Just hold my hand...
Princess...
Alfa?
Selena?
Why is it so crowded here?
What are you doing here?
Do you want to join the dance and sing?
Come on.
No, no, no.
Come here.
I don't want to.
I don't want to dance and sing.
Then, what are you doing here?
I want you to be quiet.
Why should I be quiet?
Because if you dance and sing...
Your voice will be heard by my neighbors.
People will be suspicious.
Then, what should I do?
Just sleep.
It's late now.
Alfa, I'm a star.
My duty is to light up the night.
So, I can't sleep at night.
But you can't be noisy.
If you're caught,
and you're taken by the heart,
what will happen?
You'll be taken by the heart.
That's why...
you can't be noisy.
I'll go now.
Bye.
Idiot.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's all because of me, the Elven warriors.
I don't want to hear your excuses.
Why did you let her go?
I have to get the fallen star.
Help!
The fallen star.
You're great, sir!
How can I be in that cave?
It's so cold.
[music]
Running, sprinting, jumping, galloping
Brave, unfamiliar, confessions
Chase, hope, and dreams
Go, go, go!
Get everywhere dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go!
Fight with the power of your heart
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go!
Let's dream!
We will!