This story is purely fictional. If there are similarities in names, characters/figures, and places in this show, it is merely a coincidence without any element of intentionality.
MDentertainment presents
🎵 "Show your spirit, get your friends ready" 🎵
🎵 "Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars" 🎵
🎵 "Be brave, don't give up" 🎵
🎵 "Chase your dreams and hopes" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, never stop" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, fight with all your heart" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, make yourself proud" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, let's dream" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, we can do it" 🎵
🎵 "We can do it!" 🎵
Mission accomplished, sir
Aldebaran finally believes in Leon
I mean, your brionel, sir
Good
Now, your task is to fight that protective spirit
With a spell of torture
Yes, a spell of torture
You beat the bad guys with a spell of torture, right?
That's black magic, you know?
Vega, usually you can make a spell
Why are you a failure now?
A battle of courage and bravery
Test, one, two, three, sir
Test, Roger, Roger, sir
The result is here, sir
How's Leon's development there?
Wow, it's amazing, sir
Leon is now the smartest kid in the school
He even beat Vega, sir
Hahaha
Good job, sir
But there's only one problem, sir
Alfa stole Leon, sir
I'm worried that Alfa can disrupt our plan, sir
Alfa
What's this, sir?
Hahaha
That's my love potion, sir
Whoever drinks this potion, he will be loyal and be with Leon
Including Alfa
Wow, that's amazing, sir
Hahaha
Vega
Leon
What's wrong with you?
You're still a kid and you're sending letters?
You're so stupid
Shut up
Learn from me, kid
I'll give you a present
I'm not a kid anymore
Hey, there's a Lion
What's up?
Do you miss us?
Yes, we miss you
Can I get closer to you?
Yes, you can
We're going to have a party tonight
Do you want to come?
Yes, we do
Okay, then you can tell the others
Okay, kid
One more thing
Don't tell the teacher
Just a little
If the teacher knows, we'll be scolded
Yes, of course
Okay, just trust us
Okay, thank you
Hello, come here
Come here
Okay, everyone
We're going to have a Valentine's Day party
That's right
But there's one condition
Don't tell the teacher
Okay
Now, we're going to prepare
The Valentine's Day party
But don't tell anyone
Okay
Just trust us
[Valentine's Day]
Did you buy the flowers?
No, I was given them
Who did you give them to?
Maria
She said she's sorry
Because she cheated on me
Oh, Maria
That's so sweet
Maria, come to the party
Come here
Did you know?
She's going to have a midnight class
Today?
It must be fun
Can we join?
Of course
Because she's going to invite all the students
Don't tell the teacher
She might scold us
Okay
[Valentine's Day]
Are you going to the midnight class?
With Rio?
I don't know
I don't feel good with her
Why?
You don't like her?
She's a good girl
Right, Rita?
Yes, she's a good girl
Let's go together
So you can get closer to her
Good afternoon, Your Highness
How is it?
Have you managed to get them?
Of course, Your Highness
[The most beautiful moment]
This is it
This is impossible
How is it impossible?
It's possible
The fabric is already touched by the queen
No one has ever dyed my fabric with blood
And yet
You're still cheating
Wait
Queen
So
The queen wants us to die by dyeing this fabric?
Of course
You all deserve to die
Because you want to get the most valuable treasure in this world
Guys, I can't wait for the midnight class
Me too, Sis
Shh
Don't make a noise, or the teacher will laugh at us
You're my sister
You're so annoying
Now, let's divide the tasks
Rita, Pega
Prepare the food
Yes
We're the sexy decoration
Because we're sexy
Smart, my sister
Okay
Okay, you're the sexy decoration
Ray and I will prepare the drinks
Okay
What are we doing?
You're the satbang
Alpah, your task is to wake up the other students
It's 11 PM
What do you think?
Are you sure that there will be a party at 11 PM?
Of course, Alpah
But Ray, our school was just attacked by the labah-labah
Without the teacher's knowledge
It's very dangerous
What if something happens?
You're paranoid, Alpah
The monster is dead
If it's still there, it's still on the beach
If the monster is still there, it will be still there
That's right
We're still here
Hero is Rio
Rio is my hero
Rio Nelo Hero
What are you doing?
You're a scum
You're a monster
The two of you
You're wearing a skirt
The respected queen
The guardian has left
Watch out
The teacher is here
You missed
There's a stone in the grave
The queen has escaped
Let's go
Wait
It's okay
Mik, the army
We must hold on
Hang in there
Why is the lollipop here?
It's just there
I forgot
This lollipop is broken because I used a magic to open it
I must throw it
The lollipop fell
I'll throw it
The lollipop is holding the queen's lollipop
Good, the lollipop is smart
It can save itself
What are they doing?
I won't let you go
Let me go
If you don't let me go, I'll force you
Try it if you can
All creatures have weak spots
They are in the neck, waist, and feet
The queen is in the neck
The queen is in the head
What are you doing?
Why can't you move?
I'm the queen's guardian
So, I can't move
Why can't the queen's guardian move?
What are you doing here?
The queen is in the neck
What should we do?
Wait
Check, test 1, 2, 3
Hotel?
My dear hotel
The hotel is broken
Hotel, come here right now
Help Nick, don't let him fall
Hurry, help him
Come on, Nick
Don't give up, Nick
My dear hotel
You're safe, Nick
What's going on?
Why can't I move?
Help
Please, don't let me go
If you want to give me the necklace
I'll lock the queen again
I don't want to be taught
What are you doing?
I'll lock the queen so she can't fly
Then, she'll fall down
And her beautiful face will be sucked by the rock
Do you want to be ugly?
No, I don't want to be ugly
Give me the necklace now
Okay
You're so annoying
I'll lock the queen
Please, Nick
I don't want to be taught
I'll lock the queen
That's weird
Why is everyone suspicious of me?
I thought I was the one who's suspicious
I should ask Panji
I'll be in trouble if I tell them
I've been given a present by Panji
Peta, yes
He said it's a gift from God
Let's go
Why is there a school?
It's so crowded
There are so many people walking around the school
I'm so proud
I'm going to the hospital
Why is there a sign saying "Prosangkara"?
Ryo is following me
I don't know where he is
Ryo is following me in the dark
Where is he going?
I have to go there
What are you doing?
This is a gift from God
Ryo, I'm sorry
What's wrong?
Who were you with?
I was with a stranger
I'm alone here
What do you want?
Nothing
I don't need anything
I'm going
I don't feel good
Maybe
Professor Angkari is going to be a good person
Prosangkara is going to be Ryo
I don't think so
I have to give him the top vega and other things
So, they'll be aware
I think Alfa is going to be suspicious
Calm down, Leon
He's going to be the guard of the 8th prince
I'm going to be the guard of the 8th prince
It's good
I'm going to make a cake
Our cake
You can make it
You can choose
Why are you making a surprise?
You must be waiting for someone else
You want to taste our cake
Yes
I have an important news for you
What news?
This news
The guard is coming
We can't tell anyone
There will be a problem
Let's hide
Come here
Hide me first
He's running away
I'm going to be the guard of the 8th prince
It's safe
But I'm curious
Who dares to come in here
And do all of this
Whoever it is
This person is too much
Lack of work
Annoying and useless
He's here
You're under arrest
I'm not
I heard that noise
From here
But it's weird
There's no one here
My food is running out
It's running out
The 8th prince
Or maybe
This is Angkara's doing
He's doing all of this to take revenge on me
I'm going to look for the key
I'm going to the kitchen
This way
Let's go
From here to Angkara
Let's go to the kitchen
Let's go to Angkara
There he is
Weird
But there's a writing in the wall
But he's just acting
So suspicious
He's coming
Wait here
I'll go in
So you can be safe
If I pass by
You tell me
So suspicious
Why did he tell me to watch over there?
What is he doing in there?
Bofo
What's that?
It's safe
It's time for me to wait
What are you doing in there?
Why are you here?
I've been following you
And now I want to know
What are you hiding in there?
I'm not hiding anything
Don't lie
I saw something
And you
You're not hiding anything
I'm not hiding anything
And you
You're hiding something
What is it?
Answer me
I don't understand
What do you mean?
I'll check it myself
Don't
Why not?
Because I didn't put anything in there
I don't believe you
I'll check it myself
Don't
What are you?
What are you doing in there?
Why are you stopping me?
I'm stopping you
Because I'm afraid you'll ruin this drink
Now you better get out
If not, what are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
I'll kill you
Don't drink it
Don't
Rey
Okay
Starting tonight
I'll stay here
I won't sleep
I'll investigate
Who is this person
If that person is you
I'll kill him
Alpha
What are you doing here?
Rey
But Rey
I just want to protect you all
He's evil
He's the one who put the poison in the drink
It's a lie
He's lying
It's true
I'm confused
I just want to protect you all
Because
Rion put the poison in the drink
It's a lie
It's true
If you want to know if it's true or a lie
Try this drink
No Rey
It's a poison
You'll die
Come on Rey
You'll know who's right or wrong
Don't Rey
Don't drink it
Rey
Let me go
What are you doing?
The drink doesn't have poison
I'm fine
You're the one who's evil
You've been eating this
And you
You hurt my friend
My best friend
Rey
Hi everyone
I'm sorry
I think
The party tonight was a failure
Why?
Because
The cake and the drink
Are ruined
Ruined
The party is ruined because of Alfa
She ruined our party
Who's Alfa?
She's a jerk
She'll beat up the kids
Beat up the kids?
Let's make a gang
Rey, do you feel weird?
With Sira
Why?
You don't see it
Usually she's not that angry
With Alfa
I don't know
What's wrong with her?
Why is Rey like that?
It's weird that she's mad at me
It must be because of Sirio
I'll show her
I'll reveal her secret
What's wrong?
Weird
That's a punishment for you Alfa
Because you made a mess
What's going on?
Is this a prank?
We've decided
For a month
We'll be your friends
Why me?
Because you ruined our party
Let's go
Poor Alfa
Actually we don't know
What's wrong
With Alfa or Sirio
Me too
This must be Ryo's doing
Ryo must be
Making them to blame me
Ryo is evil
Evil?
It's hot
Riding a pony and a giraffe
It's obvious
I think
We're going to lose
Don't underestimate us
It's obvious
We're going to lose
You're the one who's been coming
Oh my god
What should we do?
It doesn't mean we're going to lose
Nik
What should we do?
Sorry guys
I failed
All the efforts we've done
It's a waste
I'm sorry
You're being cheated on
Stay calm
I lied
I won
Don't be so arrogant
You're going to ruin the equipment
Don't you believe I won?
You won, Nik
You got a prize
You got it
Yeah
Last star
Alif Ba
Nik, come here
Let me use this
Don't touch it
If it falls
Into the hands of evil people
It can be dangerous
I'd better use it
Sorry, soldier
With all my heart
It's not suitable for a soldier
Right, friend?
It's a girl's dress
But look
It's suitable
Here
I'd better use it
Rather than
Being stolen
It's more dangerous
Than being stolen
Do you understand?
We have to save this
It's hard to get
Finally
We got the soul stone
We got it
You're being cheated on
A lot
Kids
It's time to go home
Okay, soldier
Do you know
You're all
Super stupid
You got
One of these
It's hard to ask for forgiveness
They say, last star is a boy
A magic school kid
Where is it?
Come on
Let's go home
It's getting late
Let's go
Alfa
What?
You want to scold me?
No, we don't
Whatever
We're still friends
But you have to believe
I'm not wrong
Do you believe me?
If you don't, it's okay
Okay
It's okay
I have proof
Riaw is evil
She's in a group with Professor Angkara
The school
What's that?
This is the school map
I gave it to Mr. Panji
That time
Everyone here
Will see it
Let's open it
The map is cool
Cool, right?
Here
I'll tell you where Riaw is
You'll see
She's always with Professor Angkara
Where is it?
Here it is
Where is Professor Angkara?
That's Riaw, Karen, and the others
She's always with Professor Angkara
But she's not here
That's weird
Why is she alone?
Where is Professor Angkara?
Maybe she's tired
She should rest
Maybe she's missing her parents
That's why she's in a bad mood
Maybe she's tired
She should rest
Maybe she's missing her parents
That's why she's in a bad mood
Maybe she's tired
Maybe she's missing her parents
That's why she's in a bad mood
We can do it
To the city of Malang
And then to the city of Perapan
Let's go home
Let's go
You'll get mad
One
Two
Three
This is our last chance
We have to protect her
Don't let her get hurt
We hope we can get to school
So she can go home safely
Amen
You're such a jerk
Let's go home
Let's go
What should we do?
One, two, three, go
To the city of Perapan
Alright
With this coffee
I'll be safe
Until the next three days
So I won't be in Malang
There's no one here
This must be the same person
This is the same person
He's playing with me
Continue drinking your coffee
It's so enjoyable at night
So enjoyable
(Sleeping)
I'm sleepy
Are you sleepy?
No, I'm not
You can't be sleepy
Open your eyes
You can't sleep
Can't sleep
(The next day)
Come on, kids
Let's make the school beautiful
Put the flowers there
How beautiful it is
When the world is full of love
Wow
Love with a smile
My kids
Who likes brown?
Yes
Come on, come here
This is the brown
We'll divide it one by one
The contents
We won't divide it, we'll open it
But we'll give it to the friends
Happy Valentine's Day
I hope our day is filled with love
Open it
Thank you, professor
The brown
Makes us love each other more
Love with a smile
My kids
Thank you, kids
Thank you, professor
Happy Valentine's Day
Sorry
I don't celebrate Valentine's Day
So you just keep your advice
Because it won't be useful for me
Do you understand?
Why don't you celebrate it?
Because professor Purwa is single
Shut up
Where's Alfa?
I don't know, professor
I don't know where Alfa is
Maybe Alfa is single
Because he lost to Ria
Yes, professor
Alfa is just a story
He likes to be single
And he's single
He's single
Is that true?
Yes, it's true
I must have lost to them
That's why I like to think weird
If I meet them
I'll be happy
I need to think about Ria
And my parents
Alright
Now we'll learn Mantra
Mantra
I'll introduce
Mantra Sevenka
Who can answer?
What's the Mantra?
Rio
If you use this Mantra
An enemy will appear
And the enemy will fall
If you don't understand the Mantra
But the answer is easy
Good
Now
We'll try this Mantra together
I must fail to other students
So that Rio will be number one
Lita, Rika
You go first
[Mantra Sevenka]
Please go ahead
I can
I can!
What are you doing to my hair?
Lita
The Mantra is Sevenka
Not Sevenka
Do you understand?
Jack
Ray
Go ahead
Get ready
Who?
Jack
Go back to your seat
Ray
Rio, Tommy
Go ahead
Start
Here's our Jaguar
[Mantra Sevenka]
What's wrong?
I don't know
Are you talking about me?
How dare you talk behind my back?
If you dare, come here
Face the front
You're not soldiers
But you're useless soldiers
Calm down, soldier
Hit their tanks
Come on, hit them
Don't, soldier
The car can be damaged, soldier
Don't, soldier, we'll fall
Hit them harder
Don't, soldier
Run
Professor Aldebaran
I have something to tell you
What is it, Professor?
Alpha has dared to ask me
He's starting to rebel
How?
Today, he's going to take my class
Please
Professor Aldebaran, give him a lesson
I'm not a coward
It's not like usual
Alpha makes a mistake
Unless there's a clear reason
Yes
You should not defend him
Keep your head down
He might grow up
Like Gamma
Professor Purwa, please
When you see Alpha
Don't imagine Gamma
But remember Akilah
Akilah
If you're not married to Gamma
You'll be there
I'm going
Oh my God
The painting is here
Where?
Whose voice is that?
The door is locked
Maybe
This is our parents' voice
Come here
What is he doing?
He usually does this
Why is he doing this now?
I can't see anything
I'm sorry
Because the party
Failed today
It's okay
As a request
I'm sorry
I'll give you a present
[Applause]
Seriously?
Yes
By the way, this is a special gift
A black suit
[Laughter]
Really?
Okay, let's go
I want to ask
Where is Alpha?
Alpha?
How do I know?
I'm not in the wrong
Why?
It's just like that
It's so funny
I know
I'm like that
Confused
I'm dizzy
Where are you going?
You are the descendants of the dead
Let's hurry
Feel this
We play cowboy
[Laughter]
Cowboy dance
One more time
We're going to the airport
Ouch
Why did you get a bird?
It's really annoying
Why flying?
Why are there so many birds?
What should we do?
How do we keep the soldiers from attacking us?
I have an idea
What if we cut the rest?
Agree?
Agree
Bastard
Damn bird
Just destroy it
Make a mess
One two three
What are you doing?
You guys are not teaching
What are you guys?
How dare you touch me?
Hurry up
And you guys
I'll make you fall back
Fall to the sea
Feel this
Torvanado
Where's my Tongsis?
How dare you take my Tongsis?
You guys are not teaching
They are not polite
They are too brave to the soldiers
Watch out
Sorry soldiers
I can't give Tongsis here to the soldiers
The soldiers won't be able to hurt us again
[Laughs]
But he can still be angry
If he's just angry at your mouth
We can still chew it
Slow down
Why is he so like that?
With Alfa
Yes, are you still angry?
With Alfa because of the order
Failed
Why is it just like that?
It's too much
I'm suspicious of him
He's always with Ray
Ray, where are you going?
Ray
Cover me
I'm looking for
Padang rice
Who's that for?
That's Rio's cousin
Poor thing, she's hungry
I'll go first
Ray
Wait
It's dangerous, you know
[Groans]
Got it, Padang rice
Nice, Padang rice
Why is he so angry?
I don't know
Listen
I'll answer your question
What's wrong with you and Alfa?
What do you mean?
You're always angry
Because of the order
You know
I'll go first
Ray, why is he so like that?
What's wrong with him?
He's always angry
Yes, he's not a bad person
But he did it on purpose
To make us look bad
He's been friends with Alfa for a long time
Why is he so like that?
He must be a bad person
I'm confused
Alfa is a good person
As long as you know
Not like Rio
Why is he so like that?
Ray, what's wrong with him?
He's so bad
Alfa is a bad person
But you're right
He's always suspicious of Rio
Even though Rio is a good person
And handsome
Why are you talking like that?
Why?
It's not wrong to talk like that
You're just following him
You said Alfa is a good person
But now you're changing
Rio is a good person
Not like Alfa
You're right
That chocolate
There must be something
In that chocolate
That makes Prika change her mind
Here's your chocolate
Here
What are you doing?
That's my chocolate
I just want to see it
You can't
That's my chocolate
I don't want it
Let me see
Ouch
Let's go
Wait
Why is he like that?
He's so suspicious
Of them
Thank you
You're the one who saved me
Where are you?
I'm suspicious
If all of this is a fabrication
Who did this?
Alfa
I did it
It's okay
I'm sorry
I attacked you
Why did you attack me?
Because I thought you're a spy
A spy?
Yes
For the past few days
There's been
What is this?
There's blood
Flowers
Everywhere
It's too much
Too much
It turns out that person
Still dare to come here
Mr. Paji, actually
Who did this?
I don't know
Before
I already
Wanted to stay here
But I don't know
Why I suddenly fainted
And I fell asleep in the room
I'm surprised
Before
I drank coffee
My favorite coffee, Alfa
But why
I can fall asleep
Alfa, this is a child
A child?
Yes, a child
Impossible
Alfa, because he has
Very high knowledge
Before
He also succeeded in picking up
The password I made to protect this tomb
Alfa, so it's impossible
He did it, or the child did it
I'm suspicious
If all of this
Is a child's doing
Yes, sir
This is also my purpose to come here
Besides I miss
My parents
I want to talk about the prosperity of Angkara
What is it, Alfa?
Did Angkara make a child again from school?
The child is a child
Rio is so cool, she gave us chocolate
It's delicious
Rio is our true leader
Yes, I will follow her forever
Live, Rio
Let's try, Miss
If we
Keep on loving this heart
Yes, our heart will be happy
Always happy
Chocolate makes you happy
Wait a minute
That's smart
Miss, I don't want to
Be friends with Alfa
Rio is our new leader
Because the one who is evil
Is only Rio
That's right
Where is Rio?
Alfa
Where is Alfa?
Classroom is not here
Alfa
I better look here
Where is it?
This is
Why is Rio's name
So similar to Professor Rangkara?
Maybe
Alfa is right
What else can Professor Rangkara and Rio do?
In the toilet
Don't use it
Here, I want to show you
Where is the map?
I left it
I want to show you
Show me what?
Maybe
The map you gave me
Is broken
You mean?
Because there is Professor Rangkara
And he always
Have a fight with his new kid
His name is Rio
That means
There is Rangkara near Rio
There
I'm going to kill you
Rio
What are you doing?
Professor
It's a disaster
Rio, why did you do that?
Show your spirit
Get ready, my friend
Run, jump,
Jump, and get the stars
Be brave
Don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with your heart
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Let's dream
We will