Show your spirit, get your friends ready
Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your hopes and dreams
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Stop, stop
I'm sure the dwarfs are still at war
It seems there is a greater power controlling them
Terror will continue to spread until I get that chosen one
Do you see where the dwarfs are?
They are under the lake, everyone wants to attack the lake
Why aren't they showing up?
Be patient, we'll wait a little longer
They will definitely show up to attack him
Be patient, everyone
Watch out!
They are very agile
Let's hide first, we'll attack once they show up
Agreed
Let's go
Attack!
Now answer my question, where did you hide the dwarfs?
Don't play around, answer my question
Answer my question
Do you think you can play?
I will show you
Attack!
Don't hurt them, they are innocent
Dwarf!
Dwarf, are you okay?
Thank you for saving me with your tears
I promise I will free you from your friends
Vega, attack
Hurry
We are here to save our friends
Good, if so, attack
These dwarfs deserve to be taught
We can't hurt the dwarfs, we have to work with them
You don't know how to teach me
Professor Purwa, it's not our fault, we should try first
We don't have much time
You are lying, you have to endure it
Attack!
It's clear that they are weak
If so, why do we waste our energy just to fight?
That's why we have to listen to their opinions
They are still young, but sometimes they are smarter than adults
Alpha, ask them
Where are your friends?
Please tell me where are our friends that you kidnapped?
What are you doing? Are you playing?
Calm down, professor
The Dwarf Fairy can't talk
Lightning!
It seems like Alpha is right
They are not fake
But they can't talk because of one thing
But how can they be so loud?
Why can't you talk?
Who is he?
You were ordered to do this?
I read your mind
I'm not a fool
Absolutely man?
There is no way.
With those two little fangs,
you are definitely not a successor to the Black Kite.
You are just a mere agent.
He's no other than the Alexander Kvass,
the world's greatest detective.
So, what are you doing here?
It is a mission from all of you.
Help!
A tiger is coming!
So, because of that attack,
you can't talk?
I am...
the decision of the 8th Prince.
I have stolen your voice.
And if you want your voice back,
then...
you have to kidnap 8 children from a magic school.
And one of those children...
must be a boy named Alfa.
Those children...
must be taken to the headquarters of the 8th Prince...
which is located here.
The headquarters is a secret.
So...
you can't tell anyone about it.
And if one of you...
leak it,
then...
you will all be cursed to be a bully!
The 8th Prince said that you have to kidnap 8 children.
How many?
So...
two more children are missing.
And one of them must be me.
Mom!
Dad!
Karim!
What is it, Ren?
Food! Food!
Food, Karim!
Haste makes waste.
Do you have more?
Why do we teach you kids?
We will be bored, sir.
We don't get bored anymore!
I am ready, mom.
I am learning the magic of magic.
So I am sure I can protect myself.
But Alfa is not alone.
I will protect her.
The fruit of the dragon, the fruit of the dragon fruit.
It is dangerous!
Don't worry, Tentarang.
We have already fought the three-headed dragon.
So we are sure.
I think there is no other choice.
I will count to three.
If there is no better idea, we will use Alfa's idea.
Professor Purwa!
One.
Two.
Three.
We will use Alfa's idea.
Dapatang Koveris!
I have installed the protection device and the tracking device on the back.
Alfa, Vega, wait.
Alfa, Vega, you have to be careful.
I promise, I will save you.
Putri Ruyung, let's get through this disaster.
You take us to the eighth dimension.
What should I do? I don't want Alfa to get hurt.
But I can't tell her where it is.
Hurry, Putri Ruyung. We don't have much time.
We have to save my friend.
[The End]
Good, very good.
Finally, I have succeeded in my dream.
Give them to me.
Karim, wait for me.
I'm scared, we're all scared.
And hungry.
Karim, please.
I know, I heard your voice.
I was thinking how to get out of here.
I cried.
I'm so sad.
[To be continued]
What happened?
They must know about the trap.
And they deliberately destroyed it.
If it's not a trap, how can we stop them?
This is all because of Professor Purwa.
Because of you, Purwa.
Now, Ava's life is in danger.
Megantara, what do you mean?
This is not my fault.
But it's true.
You threatened me.
I was trying to save the children.
What?
Megantara!
Enough.
It's no use.
[To be continued]
Remember.
No one can dare to escape.
If you dare to do anything,
I'll turn you into fish.
Don't.
I'm hungry.
What?
We're caught.
It hurts.
Where are we?
We're caught.
Where's our cage?
Oh, right.
Where's my cage?
Maybe, they found it.
If we lose our cage,
the teachers won't know where we are.
We'll be in trouble.
I don't know.
We're trapped.
[To be continued]
I'll open it.
Quiet.
Remember.
If you dare to do anything,
I'll turn you into fish.
[To be continued]
Rangga, put down your weapon.
Now, you can't turn us into fish.
Guys, let's get out of here.
Wait.
[To be continued]
It's not that easy.
Professor Ranggara.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for still recognizing me.
Professor.
Why are you here?
You should be in jail.
You underestimated me.
A prison like that...
is nothing to me.
And you, Alfa.
Don't be happy...
because you took my tongsis.
Because without tongsis,
I can still use my magic.
[To be continued]
You're all dead.
What should I do?
I feel sorry for Alfa and Vega.
They're my friends.
But if I tell them without them knowing...
I...
Shut up, you all!
Shut up!
Vega!
[To be continued]
Rafa, wait!
What's wrong, Professor Ragli?
It's no use fighting.
It's better if we find the children.
But what do we do?
We don't have any other way.
[To be continued]
He told us to follow him.
He knows where the children are.
Let's go!
Wait!
What if we're trapped?
Do you have a better idea?
Hurry!
[To be continued]
What is this place?
This must be a trap.
He told us to press it.
He told you to press the stone.
You lied to us.
You will get your revenge.
To save your friends, you must be ready.
I've destroyed the company.
How do you know?
Let's go.
Let's go in.
Get out of here!
How do we get out?
We have to break the stone.
Let's go.
Let me break it.
[To be continued]
It's getting darker.
We're going to be separated.
Catch that pig!
[To be continued]
Anggara?
There are two ways.
Which one should we take?
We should split up.
Wait.
I think that's smoke.
It's a message from the children.
Let's just follow the smoke.
So, we don't have to split up.
Let's go.
So, Professor Anggara...
ran away from the prison?
Don't you dare.
The dark will not be able to hide.
The dark will not rise again.
You have captured me.
The terror will not end here.
In the end,
you will lose.
The kidnappers...
must be Anggara.
Don't be afraid.
Let me face this.
Everything is ready.
Let's continue our journey.
Let's go.
Don't be afraid.
[To be continued]
We have to use the water.
Let's go.
Help!
[To be continued]
Thank you.
Let's go.
[To be continued]
Anggara?
So, you are the one who set the trap.
Anggara.
You managed to escape from the dungeon.
You underestimate my magic power.
You think...
...I can't escape from a cheap dungeon like that?
Anggara, let me face this.
You guys, get to the water.
Hurry up.
You guys, go.
[To be continued]
The coconut fruit is eaten by the tiger.
Where do you want to go, Anggara?
The door is broken.
Let's go.
Wait.
Isn't this the energy transfer crystal?
This weapon is very dangerous.
This crystal can collect the energy of the people who want it.
And it can absorb the energy until it's exhausted.
We don't have much time.
We have to destroy this crystal ball.
If the crystal ball is full, it means the children's energy is absorbed.
The children can die.
I will destroy it.
Avancur!
Let's attack.
[To be continued]
Avancur!
Good bye, Professor Megantara.
Go to Japan through the north.
It's easy to defeat Megantara.
[To be continued]
Let's destroy it together.
Yes, sir.
Avancur!
[To be continued]
Let's go together.
Tommy.
Are you okay?
It seems that the destruction of the crystal ball destroyed this place.
We have to get out of here.
Come on, hurry up.
Hurry up.
Okay.
[To be continued]
Vega.
Professor!
Megantara is still inside.
Is Centara also with them?
Yes, she's fighting against Ankara.
What about Centara?
Alpha, wait!
Alpha!
Centara!
Megantara, where are you?
Alpha.
I'm here!
I'm here, Megantara.
Megantara!
Megantara.
Alpha.
Professor, I'm here.
Thank you, Professor.
Let's go.
This is Centara.
It's dangerous. All the roads are closed.
What should we do, Professor?
Alpha, Professor.
Look, there's a hole.
It's enough for two people.
Alpha, come on.
Go inside that hole.
Hurry!
Come on, Professor.
Go inside. Follow Alpha.
No, Megantara. You go inside.
You can take care of it later.
Professor, go inside.
Stay in the middle.
Where's Megantara?
What's wrong?
Don't leave me again!
We can do this!
Centara, please.
Centara.
Don't leave me.
Centara, wake up.
You promised me.
Don't leave me, Centara.
Wake up, Centara.
Centara!
Wake up, Centara!
Centara! Wake up!
Centara!
Centara, wake up!
Centara, wake up.
Centara.
Alpha, Megantara, hold on.
Be careful. Don't push me.
I'll smash your head.
Coconut fruit.
Alpha.
Don't cry.
Smile.
I promised you...
...that I'll save you all.
Captain Megantara...
...never breaks his promise.
Okay.
Where's your tuxedo?
(Megantara's tuxedo)
It's okay.
Didiung, you can talk now?
Yes.
It's because the magic has gone.
The place is ruined.
(Megantara's tuxedo)
Thank you, Putih Diung.
I'm so happy that you've saved us.
My name is Tiara.
I'm so happy to meet you.
We'll come back here again.
Right, Alpha?
Yes, I'm happy to meet you too.
You're good kids.
I'm thankful that you saved me.
(Megantara's tuxedo)
Putih Tiara, what's wrong?
Are you sick?
Putih Tiara!
Where are you?
This is all because of the Dark Lord's curse.
Putih Tiara has leaked the kids' whereabouts.
And now, she's being possessed by the magic.
Tiara...
(The Dark Lord's curse)
It's more dangerous than the dark lord.
Let's just play.
How about we go to the lake?
I don't want to go to the lake.
I don't want to go to the lake. I'll remember you.
I don't want to.
He left me.
Fine. If you don't want to play, I'll play.
(The Dark Lord's curse)
No, don't.
It's going to be dark again.
No, don't!
Don't hurt me again.
Don't be afraid.
We're not going to harm humans anymore.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Why are you alone?
What else can I do?
Because Alfa and Vega are still sad.
Because Putih Tiara is possessed.
Don't be like that.
Come here.
I want to talk to you.
What?
(The Dark Lord's curse)
I'm going to be Alfa, Vega.
I'm going to be a witch.
Please, don't go.
Please, Putih Tiara. Don't go.
Putih Tiara, I'm sad.
Go away.
I'm not fit.
Vega.
You're so weird.
I have a new surprise for you.
I'm Jamon.
I'm sure you won't be sad.
No, we're going to the orphanage.
Me too.
It's true.
You don't want to meet Putih Tiara.
Don't lie.
It's true. I'm not lying.
Be careful if you lie.
But on one condition.
Alfa, you have to be a girl.
It's not funny.
It's true.
Just follow me.
Is she a girl?
I don't know.
I'm not comfortable.
Where is Putih Tiara?
If you're lying, I'll tie you up.
Just wait.
They'll come.
What?
They.
Let's go.
Girls.
That's Putih Tiara.
Remember what I said?
I met Putih Duyung.
He told me...
...that if you're a girl, you have to take Putih Tiara's mother.
So, she can live.
And then, she'll be a girl.
Hurry up.
Wait for me.
They don't like men.
Hurry up.
Putih Tiara.
I'm happy to see you again.
Girls.
It's so fun.
There's another man.
Where are you going?
Thank you, Rek.
I'm so happy to meet you, Tiara.
Me too.
It's just for a while.
But I'm happy because he's a good boy.
I know.
But I'm so weak.
Attention, girls.
Starting tomorrow, you'll have a mid-semester vacation.
And you'll do a field trip to a magic village...
...not far from the school.
Yes!
There, you'll stay at a guest house...
...and have a chat with the magic people.
Professor Agni, Purwa, and Megantara...
...will accompany you...
...to watch you...
...so you don't do anything stupid.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
(The Magic Village)
There will be a sports competition in the village.
It will be fun.
There are a lot of food.
We'll eat a lot.
It must be fun.
Yes, I can't wait to go there.
Yes!
We have a result.
I just heard...
...that the kids from the magic school will host a field trip to the magic village.
And I think...
...we can attack Alfa there.
I won't fail this time.
So I can regain my strength.
I must get that kid.
Don't worry, sir.
I'll give you whatever you want.
(The Magic Village)
Alfa!
How did you get in here?
Don't be a spy, Alfa.
Why?
It's dangerous, Alfa.
Please, don't go.
But why?
You said you wanted to join the field trip.
I said no.
The event must be fun.
Okay.
We'll always be there.
Where is he?
It was just a dream.
But...
What does it mean?
Why was I forbidden to join the field trip?
Why?
Those two...
...always appear in my dreams.
And they give me a headache.
Kids.
We'll leave soon.
On the count of three,
we'll say the spell together.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
(The Magic Village)
They're here.
Oh, yes.
As we've predicted,
one of them...
will open the door...
and make chaos in this village.
Nik.
Now, you'll meet the village head, Mr. Galaksi.
Tell him that we're here.
And then,
you'll come back here.
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, kids.
Let's see.
(The Magic Village)
Where did you go?
It's here.
Nik.
Faiqa.
Where are you?
We can't be separated.
We have to be together.
Come on, kids.
Come on, everyone.
Faiqa.
That's the test, Nik.
Yes, it is.
(The Magic Village)
Karnik.
Why did Karnik turn into a rock?
Maybe he's possessed?
Oh, no.
(The Magic Village)
It turns out that the prophecy is true.
The disaster is here.
We will all be possessed by the legendary monster.
Yes, it is.
The legendary monster?
What did that man mean?
What is the legendary monster?
What really happened here?
I don't know.
Don't worry.
Megantara will be back.
Who are you?
I'm a monster.
I'm a powerful monster.
What's going on, Nik and Karnik?
Why are you here?
I have a clue about what happened here.
Come here.
♪ Show your spirit, get ready, my friend ♪
♪ Run, jump, and climb the stars ♪
♪ Be brave, don't give up ♪
♪ Chase your dreams and hope ♪
♪ Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams ♪
♪ Go, go, go, never stop ♪
♪ Go, go, go, fight with all your might ♪
♪ Go, go, go, make yourself proud ♪
♪ Go, go, go, let's dream ♪
Go! Go! Go!