To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
To be continued...
Calm down, kids
We will find out what happened
Megantara, it's better if you take the kids out of here
And don't let a single kid fly
Professor, who installed the horrible magic in this gate?
I don't know either, Megantara
What's clear is that you can't leave this village
And we can't enter the village
You saved my grandpa
Because you saved my grandpa
Now you're going to be my grandpa
The magical beam managed to defeat the monster
And locked it in the cave
No one knows where the cave is
But this magic is not permanent
So the monster can be released
And we have to find out who the descendant of the magical beam is
Who can lock the monster in it
I'm surprised, Dek
How can a snake talk to you?
I'm surprised too
But I used to talk to a snake
Maybe it's the descendant of the magical beam
Nonsense, Dek
I can't be the descendant of the magical beam
I'm new here
Nonsense, Dek
It's possible, if you're the one who did it
How can you lock the monster in the cave?
Did your parents ever tell you about Uncle Wisdom?
I don't know them
I don't even know who they are
My parents said they died a good man
You're so naive
I'll listen to you
We have to break the stone
Or we'll be locked in the cave
I want to learn too
Let's learn together
That monster is too small for me
But it can be released by our teacher
Why is it a snake?
You pretended to be retired
You're exaggerating
I'm not pretending to be retired
It seems like they're more confident now
Because they've got a new mantra
That's good
But we can't give up
We have to keep an eye on these monsters
What about Professor Purwa?
Do you have any clue?
No
The book doesn't mention the type of monster
The shape
And the weakness
How can we defeat it?
And we can't go home
Because the village gate is cursed by a very powerful magic
We're all trapped here
We have to find a way to escape
Alva
It's so scary
Why?
The teacher knows about the monster
But he covered us so we won't be scared
And the door is cursed by a very powerful magic
So the students can't get out
That's why Professor Albaran can't get in
I think someone's watching us
What do we do?
The monster has attacked two students
How long do we have to wait?
Soon, sir
They're trapped in the village
All the students will turn into stone
Including the special students
So you just have to wait
I'm bored here
I want to go back to school
Yes, we can't eat at school
Yes
[The teacher is angry]
Prita, you can eat the chocolate by yourself
Yes, share it with me
If you want
My chocolate! Give it back!
Prita, what's wrong?
My chocolate was taken by Jack and Mike
They ran away
That's a problem
I know, but in this situation, it's still a problem
Prita, don't be sad
I'll go after them
Don't worry, I'll go with you
Ray, don't be late
Smells good
What's wrong?
Why did you stop?
Let's go after Jack and Mike
Okay, let's go
My stomach hurts
Mike, wait for me!
[The teacher is angry]
Mike?
Mike!
That's Jack's voice
Maybe it's another monster
Let's go
Mike!
Help!
I'm scared
Jack saw Mike being attacked
That's why he's still shocked
Okay, let's take them inside
Sorry, Professor Purwa
Let Mike handle it
Okay
Alva, let's listen to this
How?
Let's go inside
Kids
Don't go anywhere
Stay here
And always be careful
[The teacher is angry]
Alva?
Are you okay?
I'm okay
[The teacher is angry]
This is the maximum amount of alcohol
If you drink that, you'll be calm
Now tell me what happened
Just now
I was putting on my shoes
And Mike ran away
And then the monster came
I was so scared
And then he turned into a rock
This is the first time this has happened
Usually, students are attacked when they are happy
Professor Agni
Let's read his mind
Okay, Professor
[The teacher is angry]
My shoes hurt
Mike, wait for me!
Hurry!
[The teacher is angry]
Mike!
I like that monster
It looks like the monster likes chocolate
That's weird
How can a monster as cruel as that like chocolate?
Wait, Professor Purwa
I have to make sure of something
[The teacher is angry]
How is it, Professor Agni?
It seems like it's true
When Tol is attacked
There's chocolate
Yes, sir
And when Nick was attacked
Nick was being tested
He was carrying chocolate
Megantara
Go back to your students
Watch them
Don't let anyone panic
And watch them
Don't let anyone pass through the village
It can be very dangerous for them
Yes, Professor
[The teacher is angry]
How is it, Mr. Agni?
Don't worry
Mr. Agni is resting
He's sleeping
What about Mike?
Mike is being treated
With a medicine
Aren't you afraid?
No, sir
We're not afraid, right?
Yes, sir
Good
Who said we're not afraid?
This place is getting more dangerous
But it's our turn to be the bad guys
Let's run away
Do you agree?
Yes, sir
Now we know the monster likes chocolate
So we have to protect our friends
So they won't eat chocolate
I agree
So they won't be attacked by the monster
Let's go
[The teacher is angry]
Hurry up, Don!
I'm late
[The teacher is angry]
It's dangerous, we have to run
I'll go through the village gate
I have to stop this
The army!
The army is coming!
What should we do?
The army!
Now
It's time for the monster to do its job
[We can do it]
Wait!
You're so slow
You said you're not afraid
But you want to run away?
Come on
You all go back to your house
We want to go home
This place is getting more dangerous
So that's all you have?
Listen
You're special kids
Kids who are spoiled by other kids
If you're afraid
You don't have the courage
What's the difference between you and other kids?
Do you know why you're still asked to come here?
Do you?
Look at this
[The Black Magic]
This cave is haunted by the black magic
If we pass it
You'll all be destroyed
What should we do?
We have to fight it
Remember
You're special kids
Go back to being farmers
Go back to being brave
Agree?
Agree!
Louder!
Brave?
Brave!
That's it
[The Black Magic]
Now you know the situation
But
Don't be shocked by the situation
You have to be calmer
And be ready to face it
Your heart has to be happy
We can't, we're scared
Yes, we're scared
This fear is our enemy's target
If we're scared, the enemy will be happy
But if we're happy
The enemy will feel lonely
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
That's good
I'm sorry, sir
Okay
I'm spinning
[The Black Magic]
One, two, three, four, five
I'm not happy
I want to win
Me too!
If we lose, we're done
Now it's your turn
I'm so happy
Sometimes I play alone
I don't have any friends
But now you're not lonely
Because we're your friends
But if you go home, I'll be lonely
I promise, we'll come here often
Wait a minute
Okay
It seems they're having fun
I'll take advantage of the situation
[The Black Magic]
What are you doing here?
What?
You must be trying to do evil, right?
Exactly
And you
You'll help me do that evil
[The Black Magic]
Opo, my dear
Will you help me do evil?
I...
[The Black Magic]
What's this?
This is a communication mirror
If we use this mirror, we can talk from afar
Cool
Let's try
Can you see me?
Yes, I can
Of course, Vega
Vega, watch out!
Kaka Arya is after you
[The Black Magic]
I know how to make you happy
How, Popo?
How about we make something delicious?
What is it?
Let's go
[The Black Magic]
Good
Very good
Finally, my plan went well
And now
It's time for Monster Legend to do his job
You must destroy all the chocolates in the village
If necessary, destroy all the chocolate trees there
So the villagers can't make chocolates anymore
Yes, sir
And remember, watch out for the children
Their safety is very important
Yes, sir
I will try to find another way to get into the village
[The Black Magic]
Hey, wait for me
Popo, no!
[The Black Magic]
Popo, what are you doing here?
Milk?
What?
Kawat, Kawat!
We're all in danger!
Danger? What do you mean, Popo?
Those stupid children
Popo taught them how to make chocolates
Children? Who are you?
I'm their friend
But they're so stupid
Mega!
Those children are making chocolates
What? Chocolates?
That means...
That means the monster is coming
Yes, we're in danger
We have to stop it
Let's go
It's a monster!
Popo, run!
This looks good
Popo!
Tommy, Tommy! Don't eat the chocolate!
Hurry, throw it away!
We're tired of making chocolates
Then, why did you tell us to throw it away?
We don't know!
Tommy, Jack, this chocolate is dangerous
This chocolate can lure the monster here
Don't lie!
There's no monster that likes chocolate
It's you!
Guys, take care of the chocolate
Don't let Alva eat it
Why? You don't want to tell us?
Go away!
Tendra!
Why is there a smell of chocolate here?
Yes, Tendra, they're making chocolates
What? / Yes
I don't understand
Why is there so much chocolate here?
Tendra told us to have fun
But we're making chocolates
It's delicious
Now, throw all of these chocolates away!
Why are we throwing them away?
The chocolate is delicious!
This chocolate
will make you feel guilty
Do you know, guys?
Mike, Jack, and Tole
Why did they become a band?
Because they ate the chocolate!
If you're still making chocolates,
it means you're ready to be eaten by the monster!
[To be continued]
[Previously]
You're in my way!
Go away!
And bring the food
The chocolate smell is so strong
Do your job
and destroy them!
[To be continued]
This is the only way
for me to enter the station
Davatang Avanza!
[To be continued]
Gili Ipi!
There's another man!
Why is that man calling us?
He must be working for us
Hey, young ladies
I'm here
to invite you to a dance
A dance?
Yes
The loser has to follow the winner's will
How?
Why?
Are you scared?
Just dance!
We're never scared
especially with men
Come on, Gili Ipi!
Gili Ipi Baju!
[To be continued]
Enough!
I admit defeat
You're really great, Putri Angsa
We don't believe in men
Where's the man?
Now, you can punish me
with anything
But please, don't put me in jail
Because I'm most afraid of water
Especially in this lake
There's a hole that can lead to the magic village
Don't take me there
I'm afraid of that place
I'm afraid of that hole
He's afraid of the hole
Let's just take him there
So he won't be afraid
Because you're afraid of water
and the lake
We'll take you to the most secluded place
Come here!
Let's go!
Thank you for showing us the way
to the magic village
[To be continued]
The dragon!
[The dragon]
I'm scared, dad
Zhen, you're a galaxy
You should be quick
Let's go to the magic village
Let's go
[The dragon]
Let's go!
The dragon!
[The dragon]
I'm scared, dad
Now you have to remember, Alva
Don't you ever look at the sparkling eyes
Remember, don't you ever look at the sparkling eyes
Maybe the sparkling eyes are the snake eyes
Guys, don't look at the snake eyes!
[The dragon]
Help!
Wait for me!
[The dragon]
Zhen, don't!
It's dangerous, I have to help them
Don't, it's dangerous
Run!
Don't, dad!
Alva!
Dad, I'm so close!
Yes!
I'm going after the dragon!
You're so close!
Vi!
I'm scared
This is fun
Wake up, Vi!
Alva!
Don't look at the eyes!
Don't look at the snake eyes!
[The dragon]
Zhebata!
Dad!
[The dragon]
I'm going after the dragon!
Happy Eid!
I'm glad I'm not a stone yet, Alva
[The dragon]
Mike!
You!
How did you become a stone?
Anis also became a stone
You!
Hey!
He's already in the cave
Now we attack him
In the village!
[The dragon]
Why are you two here?
Praise be to God!
Normal quest
Normal?
What happened to me?
You were a stone!
Enough!
We don't want to make a scene
Let's get out of here
Let's go!
[The dragon]
Sir, it's amazing!
Don't be happy yet, Ava
The snake doesn't die
It just escapes
So the snake can come back?
It can come back if it smells like chocolate
We should leave this place
Bring the children out of the village
I've found a way to get out of the village
But professor
What about the mantra that's blocking the village?
The mantra is a sign for us
Once we get out
The mantra will disappear
Rey!
Wake up!
Ava
You didn't eat the monster, did you?
No
Let's go
Is everything messed up?
What's going on?
Maybe they're playing war
Hurry!
Look!
Who's playing?
Three!
Rey!
Ava!
Children
Let's go back to school
Professor
How's the monster?
We managed to get rid of the monster
But it's not dead yet
Only escaped
You have to be alert
And now
We have to go back to school
Bring the children to a safer place
But I and the teachers will come back here
To kill the monster
Thank you, professor Ladebaran
Rita
I have to go
You'll come back here, won't you?
Of course
But don't forget
We'll contact you through this channel
To be continued...
This well
Connects to the lake around our school
And we'll go in there one by one
As soon as you get in
You have to swim as fast as you can
To the lake
You'll pair up
And the teachers will help you
To be continued...
Wait!
Don't think you can leave this village so easily
Nice to meet you, Ankara
But unfortunately
We have to say goodbye
Don't be arrogant, Ladebaran
The science I'm in charge of
Is far better than the last time we met
Ankara
Don't talk too much
You're not even willing to defeat me
How can you defeat professor Ladebaran?
Professor
It's better
To bring your children
So that I can face this challenge
To be continued...
That's it, let's go
So that I can face this challenge
Hurry up, give me the children
Hurry up, let's go
To be continued...
I haven't lost yet
And I will never lose
Everything is in vain
I'm not going to lose
Everyone is home
I'm the only one left
Hi, Mahfiz
I don't want people to be in trouble because of me
I have to face this
You guys, don't tell anyone
We can do it
Thank God, there's a crazy person in here
Thank God
Hurry up, there's a crazy person
Hurry up, there's a crazy person in here
Help
Felita, what's wrong?
Help, I'm scared
Hello everyone
Felita is in my hands
And you tell Alva
If Alva still wants this child to live
Then she has to surrender herself
I don't understand
It's up to you to tell Alva
The important thing is you have to find me to Ramadhan
Felita and Antaboga will be waiting for you
Huh? Antaboga?
Your time is only 1x24 hours
If you're late
Then this child will be gone forever
I will return to the magic village
To lock the monster in the cave of Krama
You guys take care of the children
And stay alert
Because Ankara won't give up so easily
He will definitely do everything
I'm sorry, Prof
But the professor can
Because as far as I know
According to the legend
There's a monster in the cave of Krama
Because as far as I know
According to the legend
Only people of the five sacred tribes
Can open and close the cave
I will still try
So that the villagers of the magic village can live in peace
Alva
Don't be stubborn
If you go there alone
You will be attacked by the monsters
Yes, sir
Let's report it to the soldiers and the professor
Yes
They will definitely accompany you
Besides
If you go with the professor
You will be protected
Yes, sir
The professor can turn into a bird
Professor Agni can also turn into a cat
The soldiers can also change
No
I have to help him
Alva
Don't be stubborn
No
I will go back alone
I don't want people to be in danger because of me
I have to be patient
You guys
Don't tell anyone
Alva
I'm so scared
Let's report it to the professor
Let's go
Evil
You left me
I can be miserable
I can be in pain
I can die
Evil
Po
It's not working
What are you doing here?
Po
I'm just sitting here
Why?
Why is Alva back?
I'm looking for the treasure
Do you know where it is?
What?
What are you doing there?
Plit is kidnapped
Plit is captured
I have to help her
Do you know?
I don't know
Good
Walk me there
Oh no
Alva
It's so scary there
There's a ghost
I have a bad experience with a ghost
What kind of experience?
So
That time
I didn't mean to
I fell into the cave
I met a ghost
What?
I'm sorry
I'm so scared
Don't be scared
I'm here
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to
I'm so scared
The spell that was played by the dark lord
Turned Antaboga into a mole
A ghost
And since then
I became a follower of the dark lord
So, Antaboga can be a ghost
If we play the spell
I can play the spell
So, Antaboga likes a special music
If I make a mistake, I can be cursed
I can be cursed by Antaboga
Teach me the spell
How?
I'll think about it
Come on, Popo
Teach me
Please
Okay, I'll teach you
Seriously?
Even though I don't like it
Even though I'm forced to
Thank you, Popo
Please, God
I went back to the village
I was about to be kidnapped by Professor Angkara
And Professor Angkara said
I have to go there
I can't go with him
He has to go alone
Or else, he'll be cursed
I can do it
Yeah, I can do it
Thank you for teaching me
Popo was hugged
Usually, all gods treat Popo with love
Isn't it supposed to be a fun trip?
What do you know, Jani?
Unfortunately, you're too late to know
[Music]
Show your spirit, get ready to find your friends
Run, jump, jump, climb the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we will