To be continued...
Show your spirit, get your friends ready
Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
We can do it
Good afternoon
Do you know why I called you here?
Yes, I know
Soon, Usianya will be 7 years old
And he is not safe in this house
You know what to do
We will take him to the hospital
[Alarm ringing]
My name is...
[Music]
I was accepted in a magic school
Sir!
What?
I was accepted in a magic school
The letter said I can go to a magic school
You are great, Alva
Wait a minute
Mommy!
Yes, Pi?
Alva was accepted in a magic school
Do you want to go to school?
Yes, I do!
Pi, so you mean you want to take him to school?
No
Then?
He's in the toilet
Alva!
I've been taking care of you since you were a kid
I've fed you
Now you want to go to school?
And you think I want to pay for your school?
Don't think you can get out of this house
Especially for school
Throw it away
[Music]
He's coming
Mi!
What's wrong, Pi?
He's coming, Mi!
Pi!
What's wrong, Pi?
Close the door!
Pi!
Pi
How could this happen?
I don't know, Mi
[Singing Happy Birthday]
[Music]
How did it happen?
Let's see
[Music]
Good afternoon
Is there anything I can help you with?
Yes
Let me introduce myself, I'm Megantara
I'm here to pick up Alva
Alva?
Where are you taking Alva?
Wait, where are you from?
I'm from a magic school
Oh, so you're the one from the magic school
Yes, that's right
So, let me take Alva
Who?
Not anyone, Pi
Hey, listen
Alva won't go anywhere
And if she wants to go out, it must be my permission
Now, you better leave
Don't ever think about taking Alva out of here
And one more thing
Stop messing up my house
You keep sending me letters
Now, get out of here
Or else, I'll call the police to get you out of here
Bye
Just lock the door, Mi
Yes
I won't open the door
How to be polite
I can't do it anymore
It means I have to use a less polite way
Alva?
Mommy, wake up
Wake up, Mommy
Grandma!
What are you doing to my grandma?
Hello, Alva
How do you know my name?
You know it, don't you?
Of course, you do
I'm here to pick you up
No, I don't want to go
You're hurting my grandma
I don't want to go
I'm not a bad person
I'm here to take you to the school
The place where I should be
Let's go
I don't want to go
I don't want to leave my grandma
She's right, Alva
Alva, you have to go with me
You want to go to school there, right?
Your grandma doesn't want you to go
But this is the only chance for you
But, Uncle
Hurry, Alva
Before your grandma wakes up
Let's go, Alva
Don't worry
She'll be fine
Grandma, help me
[Holy music from the church]
Thank you, Lord
Is the sorcerer here, soldier?
No, he's not
Alva, before you enter the sorcerer's school
You must have a Tongsis first
Tongsis? The one that makes photos?
No, Tongsis is a short form of Tong
Tongkat
Si is a sorcerer
And Es is the meaning of a deity
So Tongsis is Tongkat, Sihir, and Sakti
Now, go to the fruit shop
And take your Tongsis
Is there really a Tongsis in the fruit shop?
A fish is playing circus
Don't ask too much
Okay, soldier
[Holy music from the church]
Ouch!
Hey, you!
You!
You're finally here
I thought you wouldn't come
How do you know I'm here?
Of course I know
I always know who I am and where I am
People are in a tight spot
You have to find Tongsis
How do you know?
It's not easy
Hey!
This one
That's wrong!
That's not wrong!
Find another one
It's easy
Maybe this one, sir
Maybe this one
You're so annoying
Nothing happened
So this one is the one
That's wrong!
Find another one
This one, sir
Hey!
That's wrong!
Maybe she found Tongsis
Tongsis is amazing
Only old people in the world can do that
Sir!
I found it!
Wow!
Cool!
How's it, Alva?
Did you find Tongsis?
Yes, sir!
Good!
You should get what you should get
Look!
Follow me!
Ready?
One, two, three!
To be continued...
It's here!
Yes, it's here
Over there
There's a special door
To the school
Okay?
Only people like you, Alva
Can enter that special door
Now, find a boat
That can jump into the water
A boat that can jump into the water?
Where is it?
You're so stubborn
You should try first
Okay?
Alva!
This is for you
To be continued...
The army is coming!
Army!
To be continued...
That's the army
Sorry, sorry
It's okay
You have a pen too
So, you're from Siir School, right?
Yes
You too?
I have a friend
I'm Rey
I'm Alva
Let's go in
Let's go
Wait, wait
What is this log?
I don't know
What is this log for?
Okay, let's go
You!
That's for special kids
Not like you
You don't have a seat
So, I'm a special kid
To be continued...
We have a special kid now!
Which one?
Just wait
We're going to die!
No!
Don't go!
Alva!
To be continued...
The river is wet
Yeah
It's going to be cold soon
How do you know?
Have you been here before?
Not yet
Just this time
Do you know where it is?
I don't know
Now, we have to find our treasure
If you're smart, you should know where we should look for it
It must be around here
Where do we look for it?
Just let it flow
Look for it one by one
Okay
Just follow him
Maybe he's right
Okay
I'm left behind
Where is it?
It must be here
That's the balloon
My name is written there
Maybe that's it
That's so cool
Awesome
That's him
He has my name
That's so cool
What?
This place is cool
There are bubbles
Yeah
Bubbles
That's so cool
I'm being followed
What?
You're being followed
No, no, no
Don't touch me, just let me be
Come on
Why did you disappear?
That was fun, right?
Yeah
Oh no
What are you doing?
We're going to school
Oh yeah
I forgot
Let's go
Come on
Stop
Where are we going?
There?
I think
There
Let's go
Come on, hurry
That's so cool
Yeah, the school
Let's go in
Come on
Good afternoon, kids
Why is the hat so cheap?
I don't know
It's so cool
We can do it
What are we doing, Sega?
We're going to school
[Train horn]
[Music]
Welcome, kids
I'm Professor Aldebaran
The head of the school here
You're here because of the special talent you have
That other kids don't have
Now
The new students will be selected
Good afternoon, kids
Why is the hat so cheap?
It's so cool
Are you surprised?
You'll be even more surprised
When I read your mind
I'll determine which ashram you'll go to
Purnama or Gerhana
I'll go to Verga
I'll go to Gerhana
Keep reading
Purnama
I'll go to Verga
I don't want to
[Laughing]
You'll make a mess
But you'll have a great loyalty
Purnama
Tommy
[Music]
Slippery like a snake
Full of tricks
Gerhana
[Music]
Alpha Putra Brahmana
A unique kid
Smart
Has an amazing talent
Kind
Helps others
But
Also full of tricks
You'll be selected in Gerhana
Hey
Why?
Don't you like Gerhana?
It's okay
Oh
You're hiding something
I can read your mind
Come on, tell me
Why don't you like to go to Gerhana?
Come on
Because I came here with Ray and Vega
They're my first friends
And I want to go to the same ashram as them in Purnama
Oh, I see
Okay
Since you're honest
I'll let you in
Purnama
[Applause]
[Music]
What's wrong?
It seems like Guru Yomi is looking at me
[Music]
Now
Say the keyword to enter the cave
Gilau Purnama
Cool, Ray
Yes
Come on
Now you all can enter
Let's go
Wait
Ray
Do you hear that?
What's that?
That's the sound from there
[Music]
What's wrong? I can't hear it
I can't hear it
Tentara
Tentara, do you hear that?
There's a sound from there
The sound from that room
The sound of a triple head
What sound?
No, no
It's not
That's a secret room
Secret room?
You ask too much
No, who said that's a secret?
You all don't go into that room
Okay?
If you go into that room
You'll all be punished by the Guru
Do you understand?
Yes
Good
Let's go
[Music]
Come on
My name is Nick
I'm your classmate here
And today
You'll all learn a new language
Which is flying language
[Music]
And this lollipop
You all have to hold this lollipop
Because this will help you to fly
[Music]
I don't want to fly
Really?
[Music]
Good luck
That's our teacher
Why a cat?
The cat taught us to fly
[Music]
Why are you all quiet?
Tole
Don't you run out of lollipop
If you run out of lollipop
You can't fly
[Music]
Why are you all quiet?
Come on, now try to fly
Using the lollipop
[MUSIC]
Alva, you're right. That's how it is.
Kids, now you swing the lollipop and stretch your arms.
One, two, three.
[MUSIC]
You don't have to be surprised.
As long as you know that my grandpa is the headmaster of this school.
So you don't have to be mad.
I'm a special student.
Tommy.
Now, after the lollipop has grown,
you say the mantra so you can fly.
The mantra is "Fly, Fang".
Ruf, call Professor Aldebaran.
Kids, now you wait here for a moment.
[MUSIC]
Hey, it's a goldfish. A rare animal.
I'll put it in my face so it can be my bedroom.
Professor.
Don't.
It will hurt you.
Why do you hurt it?
You don't have to be involved.
It's my business.
Fly, Fang.
[MUSIC]
Poor goldfish.
Tommy.
You don't have to be involved.
[MUSIC]
Yes, I'll finish you.
Free that goldfish.
[MUSIC]
I just want to pay you for the goldfish.
But you're a fighter.
Just watch.
I'll finish that goldfish.
[MUSIC]
Fang.
Feel it.
That's a secret room.
You'll be scolded by the professor.
[MUSIC]
Tommy, where's Alva?
I just want to go to the pool.
Yes, where's Alva?
I don't know.
Maybe they're afraid of the water.
[MUSIC]
Maybe this is the way out.
It's okay.
Alva, how can you throw this?
You don't wear a helmet.
I don't know.
Alva was smart.
We're all smart.
Not only you.
Don't fight.
Do you know what I saw?
What did you see?
I saw...
That's it.
She didn't see anything.
I'm going there.
Come on.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Don't be a man.
You can't come with us.
Come on.
Why are you so mean to Vega?
Just ignore him.
He's so smart.
I'm tired of him.
What did you see in that room?
I saw a three-headed dragon.
What?
Be quiet.
Slowly.
How come?
I don't know.
I'm scared.
Wait.
Alva.
Do you know there's a three-headed dragon in this school?
Of course I know.
It's my pet.
What?
No.
Alva.
How do you know...
...there's a three-headed dragon?
It means...
You.
Yes, but I didn't mean to go in that secret room.
But why is there a three-headed dragon?
Enough.
Now, go back to the classroom.
But, Tender.
That way.
I want all the doors and windows closed.
And tell everyone.
Prof.
We have a problem.
Yes, I know.
Do it now.
Prof.
I know Alva.
But, I don't know where she is.
I know.
Alva went into the secret room.
And met the three-headed dragon.
What we fear...
...will happen.
Run!
I am...
...Barga.
Run!
Barga is a very strong monster.
He is the arm of the 8th prince.
The only one who can defeat him...
...is the 8th prince...
...and his son.
Run!
Help!
To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready...
...my friend.
Run, jump, and conquer...
...the stars.
Be brave, don't give up.
Chase your dreams and hopes.
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams.
Go, go, go, never stop.
Go, go, go, fight with all your heart.
Go, go, go, make yourself proud.
Go, go, go, let's dream.
Go, go, go, we are sure.