To be continued...
[music]
[whistle]
Show your spirit, get ready to steal your friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stars
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your passion and dreams
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with all your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Alva, why did you take that stone?
Professor Agni asked me to
Because this school is in danger
Only that stone can save this school
In three days, he will gain unlimited power
And will destroy this world
You are expelled from school
What's wrong?
[music]
What's wrong with you?
[music stops]
[music]
[coughing]
Where am I?
[music]
Maybe they want me to follow them
Don't move
[music]
[music stops]
I'm running away
[music]
Why are you here?
Come on, hurry up
[music]
I'm sorry, Alva
I don't trust you anymore
[music]
Okay, if you're still angry
It's fate
Because I was wrong
[music]
No, I'm not angry
Are you serious?
Yes
[music]
You're my friend, Ray
[music stops]
[music]
Alva
We believe you're not wrong
So
We prevent you from leaving
If so
I want to be expelled
So I can go to school, right?
Yeah
Unfortunately, only the three of us
Who believe in you
So
You're still expelled from school
[music]
So we have to do this
We have to clean your name
So you can go to school again
But how?
The way
We have to catch the person who took the stone
That's right
Yes, that's right
The person who slandered you
The Dark Lord, right?
Not the Dark Lord
But the person ordered by the Dark Lord
[music]
This person's magic is very great, Alva
Therefore
I will train the three of you
So you can fight him
Especially
You, Alva
[music]
Expelled
Wow, that's so cool
So cool
Vega
Take the stone
And throw it to me
But
Hurry up
[music]
Throw it as hard as you can
So strong
[music]
Now you try the magic
Okay, Dark Lord
[music]
Expelled
Ray
You throw Alva with the stone
[music]
Is that right, Dark Lord?
Let's go, Ray
We test the ability of Alva's spell
[music]
Alva
The spell you made is still too thin
Not thick enough
You have to concentrate more
In reading this spell
Come on
Try again
[music]
Okay
Expelled
[music]
Throw it as hard as you can
Sorry, bro
[music]
I think
The training is enough here
We will continue later
No, no, no, Dark Lord
I still want to try again
I have to keep practicing until I can
Don't, Alva
You are too tired
If you are forced
It can be dangerous for you
[music]
Come on, Ray
Come on
Where are you going?
Alva
You have to stay here
We have to leave here
Because we will be searched
Okay?
[music]
Alva
If there's anything
Just say my name three times
But if it doesn't show up
Just run away
[music]
At least
There's still someone who believes in me
[music]
Um
So, Dark Lord
Thank you
You have helped me
We are also happy to help you
Right, girls?
Yippie, yippie, yay
[music]
Dragon fruit
Celestial fruit
I also want to say
Thank you
[laugh]
There's another one
[scream]
[laugh]
[music]
[scream]
[sigh]
It's so quiet
Without Vega and Ray
[music]
I have to practice
So I can be like them
[music]
Bafurisai
[hit]
[music]
Ouch
It hurts
I can't give up
[music]
Bafurisai
[hit]
[music]
You guys
Alpha
You have to act faster
Before the moon is full
Don't let the magic stone fall into the dark palace
Yes
I want to find that person
Remember
Don't look for someone who is not in the dark palace
Maybe you can find him in the sea
But in the dark palace
There's no ring
You have to keep an eye on him
[music]
[scream]
Stop
[music]
Why do I keep dreaming about them?
But they're right
I have to prevent the dark palace from getting that stone
I have to practice
[music]
Bafurisai
[cheer]
[music]
Wow, Mr. President
Hooray
Yeah
I did it
You're great, Alpha
Perfect
That means
Now
You can do your research
Yes
Now we have to give it to Niel
I agree
We don't have to find him
You do it, Alpha
Huh?
You will interrogate Professor Agni
By pretending to be Professor Aldebaran
Huh?
[music]
Here's the report
With this report, you can be Professor Aldebaran
Are you sure, Vega?
I'm sure
I've followed everything in the book
Prove it
I want to see the result
Okay, I'll prove it
[music]
Alpha
Now you stand in this room
[music]
Wow
Wow, that's cool
I'm now Professor Aldebaran
[laugh]
What else can we do?
There's only one way
You can't get wet
If you get wet, you'll be the first one
Right, Nendara?
Yes, right
Remember that, Alpha
[music]
Come in
Professor Aldebaran
Good afternoon, ma'am
I mean, professor
What's the matter, professor?
What's the matter that makes you come to my office?
I'm now studying the art of defense
Can you help me attack?
Attack you?
Yes
You can try to attack me with a strong mantra
Until I faint
The mantra is called
The Mantra of Meriamfang
And it's a black magic
I've never learned that magic
And I can't do it
Ouch
My hand suddenly hurts, professor
Try this, professor
Check it
Ouch, it hurts, professor
Try this
There's no ring
Where's the ring, professor?
You don't wear a ring?
I said, I don't wear a ring
I'm sorry, professor
Let me help you
Oh my god
I'm sorry
I can't get wet
I have to get out of here
Professor
I'm sorry
Excuse me
I'm a bit tired
You said you need my help, professor
It's okay
Professor
The Mantra of Meriamfang
Professor Purwok
Wafa
You've been expelled from this school
Why are you still here?
The Moon Ring
So, what did Professor Purwok do?
He's the one who took the ring
How dare you to kill me like that?
Now, you're going to join me
We're going to face Professor Aldebaran
You have to leave this school
Let's go
How dare you to fight me?
Wafa
Professor
Where are you going?
Get out!
Wafa
You can't run away, Wafa
Stay there!
The Mantra of Meriamfang
What's that?
Where is he?
He was here just now
I think Professor Purwok can't see me
Is it because of this test?
Wafa
It's true, he can't see me
The Mantra of Meriamfang
Where have you been?
It's been a long time
I want to sleep
You're so annoying
It hurts
What's wrong, Rey?
You're the one who's annoying
What did I do to you?
Don't play with me
Who's playing with you?
Stop it
You've been fighting and making noise
You should be calm
It's more comfortable and safer
It's more secure
The Mantra of Meriamfang
Oh no
You two are so annoying
How dare you to make noise
This is the soldier
Just move
No, not the soldier
Hey
Stop fighting
Wafa
When did you come?
Because I'm wearing this
The Mantra of Meriamfang
If we wear it, we can't see
This is the Mantra of Meriamfang
Where did you get this?
I got it from the sky
When I was chased by Professor Purwa in the cave
Thanks to this, I'm safe
I know who stole the stone
Who?
Professor Purwa
He's a man wearing a moon ring
He's the one who made me faint
And he took the stone
Are you sure?
Yes
I saw him wearing the ring
I'm sure
He's the one
Don't be so sure
If you don't have any evidence
That's why we have to look for Professor Purwa's office
Who knows the stone is hidden there
[The Mantra of Meriamfang]
We have to hurry
Don't make noise
We can't be caught
[The Mantra of Meriamfang]
Don't make noise
Can we go in?
Yes
Don't make noise
Let's look for it
[The Mantra of Meriamfang]
We walk slowly to the door
And then we run away
Let's go
Run away
Stop
You want to run away?
[The Mantra of Meriamfang]
Where did they go?
Professor Langkara
Thank you for saving us
Kids, now everything is in my room
Is there anything I can talk about?
Yes
From there I already know that Professor Purwa is the perpetrator
He took the medicine
That's why we have to look around the room
Because when the news came out, there was still a room
It was still empty
Kids, what you did was very dangerous
I will try to reverse this
Remember
Next time, you have to be careful
If you want to do research, you have to be prepared
And don't be reckless
Yes, Professor
You can go now
Let's go
[The Mantra of Meriamfang]
What's going on?
Don't pretend
You did it, didn't you?
Answer me
What do you mean, Purwa?
Fine
I will make you understand what I mean
What's this?
It's nothing, Professor
I just want to make sure that Professor Langkara
The enemy is right in front of us
We should be united
Not divided into factions
You're right, Professor
I will prove that I'm right
Just wait and see
Tomorrow is the first day of the month
And we haven't played the game of "Tuka Badian" yet
We have to be very careful with Professor Purwa
Tomorrow, he will go to school
To give the stone to the Dark Lord
So, we have to follow him
Not us, but me
But, it's impossible, Alva
You can't do it alone
Because it's dangerous
Hold on
If you and Rey go with me
The teachers will be suspicious
Only I can escape
Without making anyone suspicious
No, because everyone knows
That I was expelled from school
Alva, wait
We are friends
Whatever happens, we have to be together
Hold on, Rey
I beg you
Please listen to me
You have helped me a lot
And now, I have to solve it myself
This is all my fault
I took the stone
And now, I have to break it again
Alva, stop it
Okay, Rey
[Music]
Professor Agni
Lead all the children to gather at the playground
Tonight, we have to pray for the safety of the school
Hurry up, children
Don't let the stone to the Dark Lord
[Music]
I'm scared
I'm already wet
There's no use hiding anymore
[Music]
Professor Rizal
Why are there two teachers?
[Music]
One of them must be using a magic to change the universe
You can't reach the water
If you don't run away from the water
You will become the universe
Water
I have to find water
Find water
[Music]
That's him
He's coming
[Music]
Alva
Don't push Alva
She's dangerous
What are you talking about, Purwa?
You're the bad guy
I came here to pray for Alva
Alva
What do you think?
Who do you trust the most?
I give you three minutes
To clean the page
I work with the Ankara process
Good, Alva
Now you help me attack him
Let's attack him together
[Music]
You're a coward
You shouldn't be in this school
Alva, help me
Alva, he's over there
Alva
[Music]
I'm sorry, Professor Purwa
But I won't let anyone
To disturb my important mission
To take the stone of eternity
Why are you surprised like that, Alva?
Yes
I'm the culprit
Professor
[Music]
I'm the culprit
I took the stone of eternity
To give it to the 8th prince
So
I hypnotized Professor Agni
By using the body of Professor Purwa
So I can make Alva
Take the stone of eternity
Alva
I protect you
With your friends
So you can trust me
And you can suspect Professor Purwa
I have disguised myself as Professor Agni
To take the stone of eternity easily
And lastly
I used your life again, Purwa
To defeat you
[Music]
I swear
The 8th prince will rise again
His power will recover
And you will all be destroyed
[Music]
The destruction of this school
Will start with you
[Music]
But
The first one I will destroy is you
[Music]
Alva
Are you sure you want to fight me?
The power you have
Is nothing compared to the power I have
I'm a bad person
I won't let anyone hurt you
[Music]
Professor
If he comes
I will destroy you both
[Music]
Professor Alibaran
It's too late, Mr. Diah
[Music]
Forgive me, Professor Purwa
Because I accused you wrongly
Your actions are very reckless, Alva
You could have been killed
[Music]
Attention, everyone
Please listen to this important news
As you know
The Stone of Eternity has been stolen
But now
With a happy heart I inform you that
The thief has been caught
Now
I will call a child
Who has helped us find the thief
Alva
[Music]
[Applause]
And from now on
The school has decided
If Alva
Will not be expelled from the school
And even
The school will give
Alva a medal
For all her services
[Music]
Congratulations
Thank you, Professor
Alva
Bouncing in the dark dreams
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your hope and dream
Go, go, go!
Achieve all your dreams
Never ever stop
Go, go, go!
Fight with all your heart
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go!
Let's dream
We can do it
Go, go, go!
Achieve all your dreams
Never ever stop
Go, go, go!