To be continued...
Show your spirit, prepare it, my friend
Run, jump, jump, we are the champions
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Prince?
What should I do? My power is getting stronger
I think this is an attack
And, professor, what is this?
This is one of the special powers of one of the students in this school
What about Alfa? What about Alfa?
Alfa has been in a coma twice
I was bitten by Alfa
Oh my, oh my, oh my, this is a mess, a mess
Alfa must be in pain
I have to help Alfa
Hey, there's a dragon eating a stone mushroom and a papaya
Guard, open the door for me
Guard, open the door
Open the door for me, quick
I have a dragon that wants to come in
Guard, open the door
I'm suffocating, professor
I'm freezing, I'm cold
I'm freezing to death
Just move, I can't, professor
I have to take the firecracker
But, professor, the firecracker is in the highest tower in the school
And I think I should move
There's no other way, only the firecracker can warm this room
Armi, call Megantara and give her this firecracker
Yes, professor
Dafatang, give me the firecracker
Megantara, come back quickly
The magic school is in trouble
And I've already brought the firecracker back
Because Dana is freezing
Dafatang, explode
I'm burning
Find Megantara and bring her back
Megantara, explode
I'm so full
I'm so hungry, I'm not feeling well
I'm going to finish the firecracker
Thank you for finishing your meal
Now, it's time for you to drink the juice
Yes, drink the juice
Yes
To be continued...
Vega is like that for me
What's wrong, Alva?
Alva?
Oh no, it's terrible
My body is starting to get a rash
What should I do?
Oh no, it's so weird
Every time I send a letter, I have to punch it first
This is the back button of Professor Ardebar
It means there's something very important at school
What should I do?
Oh no, what should I do?
Alva's business is not done yet
There's another problem
Don't write my last sentence
Just write it
Delete it
She's not used to writing
Okay, I'll be right back
But wait until Alva's business is done
Wow, that's so cool
If this is the way, I don't have to work as a teacher anymore
You're just a lazy kid
That's why you have a lot of left overs
Right
Go back to Professor Abdi
What's wrong?
I'm so tired
I'm going to bed
This scratch is amazing
The cold feeling is gone
Now you have to do another test
Which is a board painting competition
You have to do it manually
Without magic, without magic
One child who finishes last
Will be eliminated and can't continue to the next stage
Please go straight to the paint house
Painting is easy
That's my specialty
You two must be lame
Do you know the idiom "Tongkosong Nyaring Bunyinya"
That's a noisy person but no brain
Sorry, if a ghost fights a human
It will definitely defeat the ghost
Who said humans are more noble?
So, humans will always win
Ghost
Human
You have to paint the wall with your name
Do it neatly and quickly
The child who finishes last and is the most messy
Will be eliminated
We will start on the count of three
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Rega
You shouldn't be like this
Because of me, you lost
It's okay
Our goal is to get that violin
So, if one of us loses
What else can we do?
The important thing is you have to continue
You have to win, okay?
Make sure my fight with Ray is not in vain
Thank you, Rega
I'm sorry, Rega
You have to go home now
You have to be able to
Win
You failed too
Rega?
What else can I do?
He's a trap
Afal is really angry
I helped him
And I lost too
Rega, what should you do?
Afal is weak
Why did you let him win?
I suggest you give that violin to Afal
What should I do?
I forgot
I didn't think of that
I just want to try to win
A forester eats a pondo's nest
It's not that he's stupid
He's just nice
Whatever the reason
Fighting and sacrificing for a friend
Won't bring you any results
But, soldier
But, soldier?
You don't have to use that word
It's better for him to fight for a friend
And try hard
Than you
Failed because you don't want to eat vegetables
Vegetable chicken
Huh?
This is the final round
The final round will decide
Who will get the life fluid
You have to run until the finish line
Whoever arrives first is the winner
Remember
You can't use any magic here
I'm so nervous
But I won't give up
I'm happy
I believe in you, Rega
One
Two
Three
Four
Come on, brother!
Hurry up!
I'm nervous
Come on, brother!
It's not that long
You should just run
I'll win for sure
This is called
Winning without any competition
I'm excited
[The final round]
This is awesome
I've been waiting for this
[The final round]
Ava
Ava, wake up
[The final round]
You guys
Wake up, Ava
You can't die
But
I can't take it anymore
My body hurts
Ava
You can't let your friends' struggles get in the way
It's true, Ava
They've sacrificed for you
Don't let them be a burden
Ava, wake up
Ava
[The final round]
This is how it should be
Because of me
You lost
It's okay
You came here to get that award
So, if you lose
What else can we do?
We have to move on
You have to win
Okay?
[The final round]
You're right
I'm not giving up
This is my friends
Good
Now, stand up
And be brave
Be brave, okay?
We'll take care of you
Show your spirit
Get ready, my friend
Run, jump, and be brave
Be brave
Don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Don't give up
I'm not giving up
Surrender with all your might
Now, it's time to say goodbye to the ghost
It's true
We can do it
[The final round]
It's so far, Alva
Go, go, go
Be proud of yourself
Let's dream
Go, go, go
Ibu
Ibu, where's Alva?
How can she run so fast?
Where did she come from?
Oh my God
Show your spirit
Get ready, my friend
Run, jump, and be brave
Be brave
Don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Raya
What?
You think you won?
Wrong
I won, you lost
Fine
Let's see, the judges said
Why are you so confident?
I won, you know
It's up to you
[The final round]
Thank God
This firecracker is really useful
But we can't just let it go, Professor
We have to find the culprit
And stop him before he freezes this school
You're right
We have to find the news
I order all teachers to find the news
Split up to find him
Kids, stay here
Don't go anywhere
Yes, sir
I will leave the firecracker here
So you won't be left behind
[The final round]
Life?
Because you're in the finish line at the same time
You two will take the life liquid
The one who finishes first
Will get the life liquid
One
Two
Three
Start!
[The final round]
Yes, I did it!
I did it!
I'm so sad
You didn't get the life liquid
Even though I've sacrificed a lot for you
Now, it's time for you to leave me
I will be a beautiful human
The bottle
Alva, did you take the bottle?
Give it back!
You're so mean!
I don't know!
Why is it in my hand?
But...
It's gone!
I'm here again
Alva!
What are you doing?
Give it back!
That's my brother's bottle!
I don't know!
Raya, in this competition
The participants must be honest and fair
They can't cheat
What?
You've cheated by pushing Alva
So, you're the loser
And we decided
Alva will win this competition
Yes!
Thank you, jury!
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy!
Flita!
Where are you?
Let's just use my crystal ball
Okay, you find it
Okay
Crystal ball's reception
The ball is in her hand
There she is!
What's wrong with my crystal ball?
I'm so sorry
We'll find out where Flita is soon
My little sister
I'm going to cry
Who are you?
I'm Pangeran from a faraway country
Why are you crying here?
I'm a weirdo
Everyone hates me
I'm not a good person
Then we're the same
What do you mean?
I don't have any friends
Almost everyone in this world hates me
I'm considered a problem
What if we become friends?
But are you afraid of me?
I have a strange power
I can make everyone freeze
Since we're friends
I'll tell you my secret
I also have a strange power
I can't freeze
Are you sure you want to be my friend?
Give me your hand
I'm not afraid of you
You see for yourself
I don't freeze
Professor Aldebaran
I got a message from Professor Agni
That the school is in danger
But who will do it?
We can do it
Who is it?
Where's Alva?
Ri, wake up!
It's morning
What about Alva?
I want to ask her
Alva hasn't come
Where's Alva?
She hasn't come
She hasn't come?
I'm scared
Alva?
Are you okay?
You're okay, right?
Alva?
Are you okay?
I'm scared
What's that?
Watch out!
Alva must have been possessed by a very evil magic
What kind of magic is this?
You're all dead
Alva, you're safe!
You're safe!
Come here
Alva, I'm so relieved
You're safe
This is for you
Thank you
Cintara
Forgive me
But thank you too, Cintara
Cintara
Forgive me
Help!
What's wrong, Cintara?
What's wrong?
I almost forgot
We have to go to school
Why?
This is a letter from Professor Ali Baran
I got a letter from him
He said our school is in danger
Danger? What danger?
So we have to go back to school
This letter will make us
Make us able to go back to school
Come on
Hold this
Ready?
Ready
Welcome, Alfa
I'm happy you're here
Thank you, Professor
Professor Ali Baran
I got a letter from Professor Aki
He said our school is in danger
But who did this, Professor?
He did this
He did this?
But that's impossible
We didn't expect it either
But it turns out
Plita has special powers
But unfortunately
She can't control her powers
So when she's angry
Angry, sad
Feeling lonely, scared
Then the power can come out
And what touches her can freeze
Where's Plita?
We haven't been able to find her
We need a telescope
Ray, telescope
Try using this telescope
Where's Plita?
The food is so good
There's ice cream
Permanent
Bakso
Ray, focus
Find where's Plita
You're the one who's thinking about food
I'm hungry
Plita
Can you find Plita?
That's her
That's Plita
Alva
Plita
She's with a man
He's a criminal
But who is that, Prof?
Or maybe
Professor Angkara
But he looks different
I brought you a warm chocolate
Here, so your body will be warm
He can see everything, how sweet you are, sadness is only a part of your heart.
You only have deep heart, nothing else matters.
You have got my heart, I've got your heart.
And we'll always be together.
You really think I can't go to you?
I'm not afraid of you, I'm afraid of your love.
I'm afraid that you'll leave me.
I'm scared.
Wait!
Who are you?
To be continued...
Bobo?
Alva! Where are you?
Alva!
That's Aldebar's voice.
I can't face him with this power.
Alva!
Alva?
Alva, wake up.
You're a handsome boy, why do you look like this?
Alva, who did this to you?
To be continued...
How is it, Professor?
It's nothing. We should go back inside.
Come on, help Alva.
Megantara's feeling says...
...that Professor Aldebaran is hiding something.
To be continued...
How long are we going to stay here?
I'm getting sick of this.
Be patient.
Professor is trying to make us recover.
We should just wait here.
Because of the monster, we're like this.
This school is so cold, we can't play.
It's so cold, we should go back.
Firecrackers.
So this is how they do the cold.
I know how to use this situation.
To be continued...
If the chair is gone, the fire will be destroyed.
And Aldebaran can't use his magic because it's too cold.
A tree?
To be continued...
Where are you taking me?
I'm taking you to a place that can heal your hand.
I don't want to. I want to go down.
Calm down. I'll stop.
You can go down.
To be continued...
What are you doing?
This is a very rare sight.
He always attacks the tree.
While his friends are at school.
Yes, sir.
I want to go to my own school.
Throw him out of the school.
Or just throw him out.
I'm not wrong, sir.
Don't throw me out of the school.
Because I don't want to see you again.
He's a bad guy.
Don't go with him.
He should be thrown out of this school.
Throw him out.
Let's go.
Don't waste time with him.
Let's go with him.
Let's go.
To be continued...
Calm down, Elf.
I don't mean any harm here.
Why are you here?
I want to tell you a secret.
I have bad news and good news.
What is it, sir?
Alva.
It seems that he has met the eighth prince.
The good news is...
Alva is safe.
Although his face is a little wounded.
The bad news is...
The eighth prince has taken Plita away.
Purwa.
I want you to find Plita's whereabouts.
As soon as you find her, let me know.
Yes, sir.
You all can go back to the clinic.
And stay alert.
I will call Alva.
To train her to be stronger.
Because one day...
She may meet the eighth prince.
Yes, sir.
To be continued...
It's true what he said.
Professor is calling me.
Alva.
I mean to call you here.
Because I want to teach you...
The Pegasus Mantra.
Pegasus Mantra?
What is that, sir?
Pegasus Mantra...
Is a mantra that can create friends when you are alone.
And you have to fight a strong enemy.
Like before.
I will set an example for you.
Pegasus!
So cool!
Alva.
Now, you go to me.
Yes, sir.
Look, Alva.
My friend will protect me until the end.
And I can pull myself away from the enemy.
Or distract the enemy.
Pegasus!
Alva.
What animal do you like the most?
Garuda, sir.
Very good.
Now, you concentrate.
And imagine Garuda's feather on your head.
Then, say the Pegasus Mantra.
Concentrate, Alva.
Yes, sir.
Pegasus!
Why is it a chicken?
Alva.
Your enemy can't scare a chicken.
Come on, try again.
Pegasus!
Wow, it's a duck.
I will be laughed at by the enemy.
Alva.
That's all for today.
Now, you should rest.
We will continue tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
I will go now.
To be continued...
Alva.
What are you doing there?
I was taught a new mantra.
A new mantra?
Yes, so I can be stronger than the enemy.
Who is the enemy you met?
I asked the officer.
He was so worried.
I don't know.
I talked to the officer.
Don't tell anyone.
The eighth god.
Who attacked you?
Tell me.
To be continued...
Satria, Alva.
What's wrong?
It's been a long time, Professor Purwa.
He hasn't told me anything yet.
What's in the letter?
We want to ask one of your teachers...
to meet us in the snowy forest at the end of the forest.
Who is he, Professor?
I don't know.
But I will go there.
I will go with you.
To be continued...
Satria, Alva.
Wait.
Be patient.
We don't want to cause any trouble.
Aldebaran.
Is it true that you stole our firecrackers?
You want to kiss my cheek?
You're too much.
Don't dream.
Professor Aldebaran is not a thief.
Don't lie.
The last person who brought the firecrackers...
was our brother, Pancas.
Yes.
Pancas is my twin brother.
And we heard the news...
that Pancas has passed away.
Popo is missing.
And until now...
we haven't found the firecrackers that Pancas had.
And someone told us...
that the firecrackers are now at the civil school.
And our assistant, Popo...
has been made a spy.
Calm down.
Be patient.
I will tell you what really happened.
A few years ago...
I met Pancas.
At that time...
Pancas was fighting the 8th Prince.
I saw that Pancas was exhausted...
and almost lost.
And when I tried to help him...
his wound was too bad.
I couldn't save him.
[Pancas was attacked by the 8th Prince]
Altebaran, we give you time until tomorrow morning.
If our Kris doesn't come back,
and our servant Pomo is no longer normal,
we will attack the school of magic.
And your teacher...
Your teacher will not come back.
[Pancas was attacked by the 8th Prince]