To be continued...
Show your spirit, prepare your friends
Run, run, jump, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, struggle with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Go, go, go, never stop
Is there any need for me to leave?
This is about the lost compass
The compass is very similar to the ring used by Afyuta
If this ring is really a stone of soul, we have to destroy this ring
Even if I have to die, I'm willing to do it
As long as I can destroy the darkness
I want to tell you that I know where your compass is
If you really know, where?
Aldebaran, the leader of the magic school
Your compass is there
Finish!
Now Aldebaran has been caught
Hahaha
It seems you have realized where you are
Let me go, let me go
Let go
Calm down Aldebaran
I will definitely let you go
But you are far from my question
Where is the stone of the compass?
Hahaha
I have guessed
You will definitely be silent
I will find out for myself, Aldebaran
Hahaha
Havadjur!
Why is it so strong?
The stone of the compass is in the hand of Aldebaran
Your Highness
Now I have caught your favorite professor
Professor Aldebaran
If you want me to release Professor Aldebaran
It's up to you
Don't argue with me
Don't argue?
We don't know anything about it
Why are you looking for us?
Hahaha
Maybe you don't know
So you should ask
Alva or Professor Purno
The eighth day
Why?
We have to ask Alva and Purno
It seems that Alva knows
Because Alva and her friends
Have come to my room with Professor Aldebaran
To ask about the stone of the compass
If so
Let me be the first to go to the eighth day
Draft of paper and pen
Professor Purno
Professor Aldebaran has been caught by the eighth day
And the only way to save him
Is by giving the stone of the compass to the eighth day
Find Professor Purno
And give the paper to him
What is that, professor?
From Professor Rahmi
What are you going to do, professor?
Professor Aldebaran has been caught by the eighth day
And the only way to save him
Is by giving the stone of the compass to the eighth day
You see now, right?
Purno, you see now, right?
This is the result
And this is now Professor Aldebaran
Who's next?
This could be dangerous for everyone
Akhila
Professor Aldebaran is strong
He can definitely pass this
You just calm down
Yes, professor Aldebaran has a high level
So, professor Aldebaran can definitely pass, aunt
You just calm down
No, aunt
Don't worry
Enough!
Alva
Mom, it's true
You can't go to the eighth day
I have to give the stone to him
Are you sure, mom?
Yes
Mom, we have to apologize first
Because I need a life, right?
I'm proud of you, son
You have made the right decision
Let's go, everyone
Let's go
Purno
You're here
I've been looking for you everywhere
I'm so worried
Alva
I understand
This is so hard for you
You don't want to be apart from your mother
I know
But in a time like this
You have to be more determined, Alva
I beg you
Because this is for our own good
And I beg you
Please think about it with a calm mind
And a pure mind
About the world's great master
I'm late, mom
I want to go to the toilet
You want to go?
You've been talking for a while
Yes
You should ask first
Don't give me a sign
I'll go there
I know
Okay
Everyone
Let's go to my house
And use teleportation
One, two, three
Teleportation
So the room you've been hiding
Is where Gama and Akila live
You're still alive, Gama
I want to talk to Alva
Okay, everyone
Let's go
Is there anything I can do for you?
I'm sorry
What is it?
I have a secret, Alva
I've been keeping it for a long time
Even though
Mom and dad are sleeping
Don't worry, honey
Because you're not alone
You have a sister
Sister?
Yes, honey
Her name is Eduardo
She was kidnapped by mom and dad
When she was still a baby
A year before you were born
But I'm sure
Until now
Edo is still alive
But I don't know where he is now
So I want you to help me
Find Edo
Because I'm sure he can help you
Defeat the Dark Lord
Okay, mom
I'll find Edo
And you know
Why the Dark Lord can't kill you
When you're still a baby
Because you're the chosen one, Alva
It's your destiny
If one day
You'll grow up to be a great kid
With extraordinary power
And your dad once said
If there's a mantra
There's a mantra
With great power
If you chant it
Your duty
Your duty now is to find that mantra
Now wipe your tears
You have to be strong, Naya
You can call your friends
Okay, mom
Mom
I'm Purwa
I'm Alva
Please take care of Alva
I'm Purwa
Purwa
[The End]
[Thank you for watching]
I love you, Alva
Alva
You have to be strong
You can do it
Alright, everyone
It's time for us to go back to school
Wait
Who will take care of Aghil?
You're not the one who should be worried
Just calm down
Bargi will take care of them
And also Tirgo
Who will feed them
Get ready for the teleportation spell
Go
Teleportation spell
Civicsa
[Teleportation spell]
We're done
We got hit by the dark wizard's son
What should we do now?
We're being chased by the dark wizard
You're the one who got caught
And we're the one who's in trouble
You're the one who should be the one to help me
You agreed to help me
I'm the one who should be the one to help you
How can I agree to help you?
You're so slow
Let's just make an idea
What should we do?
I don't know
What if we find the dark wizard's son?
We should tell him that he's the one who should be the one to help us
And then we should tell him that he should forgive us
That's a good idea
Let's go
Let's go, Orfah
Now, destroy the magic ring
[Destroy the magic ring]
Alfa, why didn't it work?
According to the prof's law, if we destroy it now,
the dark side will be angry,
and the evil side will be the victim.
So, what do you think we should do?
I have a good idea.
What is it?
Not yet.
[Alfa's plan]
[Destroy the magic ring]
But Alfa, I think it's a very dangerous plan.
I like danger.
I like challenges.
I think I agree with Alfa.
Yes, so do I.
Everyone, we're here!
That's like Alfa's voice.
We want to destroy the soul stone!
Finally, he brought the soul stone here.
[Alfa's plan]
[Destroy the soul stone]
We're here!
[Alfa's plan]
[Destroy the soul stone]
Alfa, it's true!
What is it?
[Alfa's plan]
[Destroy the soul stone]
-Visa! -Rise!
You have to help me.
[Alfa's plan]
[Destroy the soul stone]
He lost!
Yeah!
One, two, three!
Three!
Go!
Professor Aldebaran
Professor, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
You all have helped me.
Professor Aldebaran should thank Alva
because she has been willing to let go of the ring on her mother's finger.
Thank you, Alva.
I'm so proud of you.
You have the courage to make the right decision.
Even though I know it's very hard.
You're welcome, Professor.
Okay then.
Now it's time for us to go home.
Yes!
Let's go!
Why am I still here?
What happened?
Janji!
Watch out, all of you!
I will get my revenge!
Especially you, Alva!
Angkara!
Oh, right.
I forgot.
Angkara is still in the prison at the magic school.
I have to get all the soul stones.
And I have to keep it safe.
And I also have to be able to destroy the Kurnaba Sword
so that Alva can't destroy my soul stones again.
Telur!
Now I'm going to assign you to find the fourth soul stone.
And the fourth soul stone is shaped like a sunflower seed.
Find it right now.
Can we make a surprise for Alva?
Sure.
Let's go!
Who are you?
Girls, today we're going to plant the sunflower seeds.
This flower will be very beautiful.
Yippee!
When this flower is big, it will be the strongest flower
that can't be destroyed by evil hands and face.
Yippee!
What's that?
Girls, that's a unicorn!
Unicorn!
It's so cute!
It's so beautiful!
Hurry up!
Let's go to the infirmary!
Oh no!
The unicorn is very strong.
We should leave here.
Help!
Find the angel fruit.
Angel fruit?
This fruit is small but it has power.
We can do it!
Where are you taking me?
I know where you're taking me.
I'm going to the infirmary.
I'll be waiting for you there.
One, two, three!
Happy birthday to you!
We'll pray for you.
And be happy!
Happy birthday!
It's time for the birthday song.
Let's make a wish.
Make a wish, Alpha.
Happy birthday to you!
I'm scared!
It's a snake!
Help!
Let me do it.
They don't like men.
What's wrong with you?
Our village was attacked.
Our village was destroyed.
A snake.
What snake?
I'll take you to the hospital.
Oh, no, Prof.
This is serious, Prof.
I'm not possessed, Prof.
It's because of the fight.
If so, you should cure them all.
That's right, Prof.
The cure is a bit difficult.
What is the cure?
The cure is Fruit Angel.
Or Fruit Angel.
That's what can cure them, Prof.
But, you know what?
Fruit Angel's cure is in a magical tree.
In the forbidden forest.
Amazing, right, Prof?
Kids.
I have an important task for you.
What is it, Prof?
Find Fruit Angel.
Fruit Angel?
This fruit is small.
But it has wings.
This fruit is in a magical tree.
In the forbidden forest.
Kids.
You don't have to be afraid.
Because, while you're looking for Fruit Angel,
you'll be accompanied by the professors.
The team that finds Fruit Angel first...
should inform the other team.
So, they can help each other.
Because the number of Fruit Angel that you have to take...
is eight.
If you're sure, you should leave as soon as possible.
Yes, Prof.
Everyone, get ready.
On the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three.
You're here, Ndiko.
I accept your formality.
So?
You've got the limit of your eyes.
Good, Ndiko.
Good.
If I give you a chance,
you'll get zero.
Now.
The flower of the sun.
I'll give you a chance.
To be a strong flower tree.
And...
The flower tree won't be destroyed by you.
Pay me back.
You've invited me, Ndiko.
Alright.
Please, go.
Now.
It's time for you to face the truth.
Oh, look, Teng Dara.
The moon is getting darker.
Yes, it's getting scarier.
Teng Dara.
Yes, we're scared, Teng Dara.
You're...
Witches.
Witch school kids.
How come?
You're scared of the forest?
It's scary, Teng Dara.
It's getting darker.
What's the devil doing?
Come on.
Keep going.
Be brave.
Ouch.
What's that?
What's wrong?
Ouch, Teng Dara.
I got a toothache.
Come on, Jack.
Who is it?
It's Tommy.
I'll go first.
See you, Teng Dara.
What's wrong?
How come he got a toothache?
That's weird.
Ouch.
My hand hurts.
It hurts.
Ouch.
I'm getting a toothache.
It's getting darker.
He's calling us.
Let's go there.
Teleportation.
Mr. Jiran, please.
Who will be your teacher?
You'll get a task...
...that will be done by the police.
Okay, sir.
Yes, sir.
We can do it.
Now, we'll do it according to the rules.
Are you ready?
Yes, sir.
Yasmin.
What's wrong? Why are you back?
You're not supposed to be leading the kids.
To find their fruit.
I'm sorry, sir.
I had to come back.
Because I got a clue from the stars in the sky.
The soul stone is in the village of Gadis Angsa.
Is this related to the attack by the Angsa girls?
I think so, sir.
You should leave this place.
Because the dark lord is more alert now.
Because he wants to find the stone.
Okay, I'll leave now.
When the kids are back from finding the fruit,
please tell me where it is.
Yes, sir.
(The Dark Lord)
What's the matter, Professor Aldebaran?
You should go back to school now.
I need your help.
What about the problem of finding the angel fruit?
I can do it myself.
Isn't that right, Panji?
Of course, Professor.
Okay, I'll wait for you at the school.
I'll leave now.
Okay, sir.
What's the matter?
Where is the angel fruit?
What's the matter, sir?
Thank you for coming.
Yes, sir.
Now you have to accompany me to find the angel fruit.
Are you ready?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go.
To the ground!
(The Dark Lord)
Keep looking, kids.
There's only one angel fruit tree in this forest.
What does it look like?
If you see it, you'll know.
The angel fruit tree has a very small fruit,
like this.
But it has wings and can fly.
Come on, keep looking.
(The Dark Lord)
The angel fruit tree! Leon!
Leon, the angel fruit tree!
Guys, come here!
What is it?
Professor, there's a path.
That's right.
The wings are flying.
Good, Alva.
That's the angel fruit tree.
Let's call the others.
Firewall!
(The Dark Lord)
Kids, look at that.
That's a sign that if there's a shadow between us,
someone will get the angel fruit.
We have to go there.
Yes, sir.
Let's use teleportation spell.
On the count of three.
One, two, three.
Teleportation!
Wow, it's so shiny.
It's like a new year.
That means,
they have found the angel fruit.
Now, let's teleport.
On the count of three.
Okay?
One, two, three.
Teleportation!
What are you doing here?
We're in trouble.
Professor Lali Baran asked us to move the guards.
Don't be ridiculous.
I didn't get any order from Professor Aldebaran.
Professor Aldebaran is looking for the stone of soul.
That's why he asked us to move Professor Ankara.
And all the professors in the school are looking for the medicine in the forest.
Hurry up, sir. We don't have much time.
We have to do it now.
Before all the mess gets here,
we have to move Professor Ankara immediately.
Yes, sir. We have to hurry.
Before everything gets more difficult.
Okay.
You guys stay in front of the cell door.
As soon as the door is opened,
you guys keep the guards safe.
Don't let them go.
If you let them go,
they can turn into hamsters.
Let's go.
Follow us.
What's going on?
Come on, Ankara.
Come on, follow us.
Soon, you'll be free, Ankara.
To be continued...
Professor Agni.
Professor Tidak.
I'm glad you're here.
Yes, Professor.
As soon as we see the fire,
we'll come here.
I'm glad too, Purwa.
Where's the others?
Where are you going?
My eyes.
Ouch.
You guys.
How long are you going to use teleportation?
I'm sorry.
Anci.
Where are Nick and his friends?
You're not responsible.
You must have left them.
Right?
What?
You're so reckless, Purwa.
They're back to school.
Aldemaran is calling them.
Okay, guys.
Now, let's prepare our lollipop.
We'll go there to get the angel fruit.
Let's go, Purwa.
Let's go, everyone.
Get ready to fly.
Let's go.
Let's go, Purwa.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Finally.
Got one.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I got one.
Yes.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I got one.
Ouch.
It hurts, Ray.
What's that?
It hurts.
Why did you hit me?
I'm hurt, too.
I don't feel good.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It's a bomb.
It's an angel.
Don't run.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm going to die.
Hey, angel.
Don't run.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Ouch.
I got one.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't see it.
One, two, three.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
Yes.
I did it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHING]
Good job, Alva.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Now we find the bomb.
Good.
Where is it?
Boss, I think it's here.
I opened the closet.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
There it is.
Open it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's look for it.
Book's receipt.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe it's here.
Closet's receipt.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Here it is.
Hurry, Boss.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Finally, we got this bomb.
Sit on the balcony.
Eat the food.
Hi, unicorn.
Let me introduce you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm a bird.
I'm not a bird.
Don't be afraid.
I'm a good boy.
[LAUGHING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow.
He's a strong man.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'd rather eat rice and porridge than be eaten by a bird.
I'd rather run away.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Fly.
Looks like we only got two of them.
Me and Alva.
We can't even succeed.
[SCOFFS]
Professor Agni, you should bring the rest to school.
At least these two girls are aware.
So we can know who's actually attacking them.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Then I'll bring the rest.
And you guys, keep looking for the angel.
Yes.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Fly.
Megantara.
What are you?
You're a monster.
Unicorn.
Oh, that's scary.
Let's go.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Alva.
[THUNDER]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRYING]
Where are we?
Yeah, where are we?
You're at the magic school clinic.
Now, tell me what happened.
We were attacked by a unicorn.
What?
Unicorn?
How come?
Unicorn.
Unicorn is a very rare animal.
And as far as I know, unicorns are good.
They're friends.
We don't know.
This unicorn is very deadly.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]