To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
You are more important than my hair
I'm willing to give my hair to you
So, you want to give your hair to me?
That's a loud thunder, Ci
Don't let something bad take over you
Don't be afraid, I'm here
I'm here
Now, you better be Agni first
Agni who died last in this school
Open your mouth
Agni, wake up
I managed to catch all of them, sir
Including Agni
And I've tied them up very tightly, sir
So, they won't be able to get out of here
And there will be many new students joining you, sir
You've learned teleportation, right?
They've learned it
But, they can't do it
Right?
Professor Purwa, it's not wrong to try it now, right?
Idea
How do we do it, sir?
We tie them up
But, we can't do it, sir
What?
Don't talk nonsense
Now, everyone
Take the torch, come on
Oh, I forgot
Why don't I use my magical power?
Wind
It's because of you
I forgot
Wind, come to me
Take the torch
You're great, Leon
You're smarter than...
You know me, right?
I'm...
The Great...
Tali
Everyone
We'll use teleportation
In three counts
One
Let's go, sir
Two
Three
Teleportation
Where are they?
This must be your mistake
You tied them up
But, you didn't take the torch, right?
Oh, yes, sir
I'm sorry, sir
I forgot, sir
You idiot
You have to accept my power
I'm sorry, sir
We're safe
Finally, we're free from the trap
Yes, my teleportation is successful
I miss this school so much
Agni, you've been leaving the magic school for days
And what you did there
Because you have a dark side
What?
I mean, you're taking care of the dark side of Pangeran's hair
No, I'm not
Finally, sir
Finally, it's clean
There's nothing left of Pangeran's dark side
That's what you should do for the first time
We're here
Oh, yes, sir
Where are Tommy, Mike, and Jack?
I was just about to ask them that
Why did we teleport to the magic school?
Maybe it's a bad omen, sir
Where are they?
I'm so scared
What?
Why are you so annoying?
Sir, help me
Yes, sir
Ouch, my hand is slippery
What did we call it?
Teleportation
Is that right?
Yes, that's right
If it's true, we can't go here
Then, what should we do?
Let's teleport back
So, we go back to Kastilah, to Pangeran, and to Gapun?
Let's do that, instead of being a puppet here
Let's do that
Get ready, everyone
Teleport
Get ready, sir
Don't, sir
Ball, ball
They're here, sir
Good, good
You're a good student
They don't want to
Just finish them
Yes, sir
Let's teleport
Oh, no, sir
Don't kill us
We're the guardians, sir
We're the guardians
Right?
Seriously?
Seriously, sir
You all must be loyal
If you're not loyal,
I won't hesitate to give you a severe punishment
What?
Yes, sir
We won't betray you, sir
Promise?
Promise
Good
My husband
He's awake
Bargi, thank God you're here
Now, it's time for us to go
Let's go
My husband
What is it, Bargi?
Your hair is so smooth
No, I said no
Bargi, don't be silly, okay?
You can't
Poor him
Just hold his hair
Yes, sir
Right?
We got his hair because of you
Yes, that's right
Yes, yes
Go, sweetie
Yes, yes, yes
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Come here
My husband
You're so slow
Run, sir
Sir, help me
Sir
Now
You're the one who's going to die
Come here
Hold on
Hurry up
You must remember
If you dare to betray
Then the mark on your hand
Will turn into poison
That will attack you from the inside
What should we do?
The first task for you
Be careful, Alfa
If Alfa gets the soul stone
You must snatch it
You must protect the soul stone
Don't let Alfa destroy it
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
Where's the professor?
He's gone
You managed to bring Agni home
Good
I'm sure you can do it
Agni
Welcome back to Siheung School
Thank you, professor
But
We both have
A little problem
Problem?
What problem?
Here's the thing, professor
Tommy, Mike, and Jake
Are not back to school yet
Yes
When we were memorizing the teleportation mantra
The kids are wrong
And
They're lost
It's all my fault
I gave them permission
But today
There's a report
And a report from the police
And a meeting between the parents and the students
The kids?
Thank God
They're here
Tommy, Mike, Jake
Where are you from?
We were wrong about the teleportation mantra, professor
So
We're heading to Paris
That's great
The view is so beautiful
It's not bad, professor
We can go around the world for free
Yes, professor
We'll go to the engine
And then we'll see the pyramids
You guys just go ahead
We're all worried about you
Sorry, professor
It's okay
What's important now
You can go back safely
Thank God, we didn't know
I want to tell you a secret
To me and the kids
Because
I've already considered you all as my siblings
What's the secret?
Yes
Actually
I'm a pretty girl
But I was cursed by the evil sorcerer
Really?
Are you sure?
It's hard to imagine you being a pretty girl
That's impossible
I'm just like that
How can I be a girl?
That's right
How can I be a pretty girl?
If you kiss me 12 times
And get married
Then
You'll be a girl again
Bargi
I know
This is one of your tricks
So I'll marry you
If you talk like that
Enough
Let's go home
Listen, Bargi
To get married
You have to have love
Do you understand?
Come on, Om
Just marry me
Kiss me 12 times
Then you'll be a girl
I think that's right
Let's go
Kids
Gather in the classroom
At 6 PM
Because there's an announcement
About the parents' visit tomorrow
To get the papers
It's 5 PM
What should we do?
Let's go back to school
Om Panji
Bargi
We're going now
Wait, I'll go with you
Let's go
Kids
Get married
Oh my God, Bargi
I told you
To get married
You have to have love
Okay?
Bargi
Be patient
Just dream
Bargi's door
Is always open
For me
It's a luxury for me
It's so cute
If I blow
Bargi will come
Wherever I am
Whenever
I want
Bargi knows
You're angry
You're angry too
But
Bargi can definitely
Overcome me
Enough
I'm not only pretty inside
But
I'm also pretty outside
If you don't believe me
Kiss me
And marry me
Yes, marry me
Marry me
Bargi
If you do that
It's good for you
But not for me
Kids, are you ready?
1, 2, 3
Fly
Bye
Bye, Bargi
See you
See you again
Goodbye, Bargi
Bye
Be careful, Bargi
[Bargi's phone rings]
Finally
I'm home
Safe and sound
Who's that?
Letter
What letter is this?
From who?
A letter from a magic school
Who put it here?
Maybe
The thief from that time
Who turned a horse's painting into a monkey's
Yes, Alfa, I think it's him
But he's not caught yet
Not yet, Alfa
He's very smart
[Bargi's phone rings]
Sir
Let's go to the parents' room
Maybe the thief can seduce the parents
Yes, Alfa
Let's go
You guys stay here
[Bargi's phone rings]
Thank God
This time
They didn't steal my painting again
Dad
Mom
I'm here
[Bargi's phone rings]
Mom
Tomorrow
I'll take the report
So all the students
Will come to the parents' room
[Bargi's phone rings]
Mom
I promised you
You'll come back
And you can come to my school
From Marapot
I'll be so happy
Mom
I want to be with you
Like my other friends
Let's go back to school
We're late
You stay here
How about this?
What if I come to your school
To be your parent's representative?
Seriously?
Yes, seriously
Don't joke around
Thank you
You're welcome
Let's go
Okay
How's it going?
I'm not done yet
Let me do it
Wait
You're using your fingers?
You can do it with your mouth
Work, work
Guys, I'm going first
Wait
Where are you going?
I'm in a hurry
What's wrong?
Why are you giving me a report?
My parents are nice
I'll get scolded if I go in
Why are you giving me a report?
It's so boring
So you won't know
If I'm naughty
You'll get mad
You're so naughty
I'm just being nice
Because my parents are nice
What?
I'm sad
Because I can't joke around with my parents
Rita, don't be sad
We still have many friends
And good teachers
Just think of them as your parents
Okay?
We are...
Sahabat
Best friend forever
Forever
Yes!
Sahabat
This is my mother
You're not dreaming
We can definitely do it
Hi
I have a gift for you
What's inside?
It's so big
Just open it if you're curious
What is this?
I'm a lawyer
The red value is 1
I'll hit you once
The red value is 2
I'll hit you twice
I'll hit you three times
What is the value of your red?
Six
Six red?
Rotan, punish him
Rotan, we're going to play a game
Okay
Six red, hit him six times
Peace, okay?
[The game starts]
I'm sorry, Rotan
I'm sorry
Rey
I have a gift for you
What is it?
Here
Open it
What is it?
Is it okay?
What is this?
Why did you give me this?
What is it for?
Do you want to know?
Here
What is it?
This is for you
Here
So you won't talk anymore
What is this?
This is for you
Wow, what is this?
Wow, it's cool
It's a gift for you
It's so cool, who did you get it from?
It's from Salsa
It's so good, it's in Japanese
It's so sweet
I want to try it
Let's try it
Let's try
Breath in Tamago
It works
Wow, it's so cool
It's like a ghost
That's right
It's good
This is for you
Congratulations
Open it
Here
It's a diary book
Thank you
You're welcome
Try it
This heart
I like it
Let's try to read it
Wow, why is it not lost?
This diary book can only be read by you, Blita
Because this book has an anti-spy system
So it can only be read by you
Wow, it's so cool
Thank you
You're welcome
There's one more gift
Because you guys have good grades
This is the gift
Chocolate
This is for you
This is my favorite food
It's so good
How good is it?
It's good
Is it?
Eat it
[music]
The preparation of the gemstone for the Gamadana food is done.
Aquila.
Where's Aquila?
Who took her?
I have to go to Alpha's school.
If I go there, I'll be a bad influence.
[music]
I need money from you.
Yes.
I hope it's useful.
(Whistle)
(Music)
Alfa, we have to be very careful.
Don't let anyone know that your parents are still alive.
(Music)
Mother, don't leave me again, mother.
Thank you for your kindness.
I will never leave you, son.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're a grown up now.
I miss you, Alfa.
(Music)
I love you, I miss you, honey.
But mother, how can I wake up?
I haven't got my eighth birthday present.
(Music)
I don't know, son.
I'm confused too.
This morning, I suddenly opened my eyes.
I can wake up.
(Music)
Gama.
Gama, wake up, Gama.
(Music)
Are these curses over?
Gama.
Gama, wake up.
Why don't you wake up?
(Music)
Panji.
Where is he?
(Music)
Panji.
Where is Panji?
He's not in his room.
(Music)
Magic school?
This must be Alfa's school.
(Music)
But now I'm here, son.
I'm with Alfa.
Yes, mother.
This is the magic.
Maybe God gave a gift for us.
Yes, dear.
A gift for us.
Yes, son.
(Music)
I love you, Alfa.
I love you too, mother.
(Music)
Oh, Alfa.
I have a gift for you.
What is it?
(Music)
It's so cool, mother.
This is a very special watch, Alfa.
If you turn the needle forward...
...you can advance the time as much as you turn.
If you turn the needle backward...
...you can turn back time.
If you turn off the clock...
...you can stop time.
Keep this watch carefully, Alfa.
You have to remember...
...you can only use all of its functions once.
So you have to be careful.
You have to think carefully...
...and consider carefully before you use this watch.
Thank you, mother.
I'm sure you'll need this watch one day.
(Music)
Who's that, Alfa?
It's a girl.
A girl?
Maybe her father.
Let's just keep an eye on her.
Let's follow her.
But don't let her get her soul mate.
Okay.
(Screaming)
Where are you going?
Why are you following her?
You want to run away because of your bad temper?
Right?
Where are you going?
It's so hard to be a child.
You're all red-handed.
(Screaming)
It hurts.
It hurts, sir.
Let's go.
(Music)
Where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom.
You can go first.
Let's go.
(Music)
(Screaming)
What's wrong with you?
Why are you running away?
Mom.
Mom, I'm scared.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Wait, I want to ask you something.
Did you see Alfa?
No, she's in the back room.
I'm going to find out who she is.
(Music)
Mom.
Can you introduce my friends?
Sure.
(Music)
Hello, Panji.
Wilan.
You...
How did you get here?
I don't know.
I'm confused too.
This morning, I suddenly...
I suddenly opened my eyes.
But it was only me.
Gama.
I tried to wake him up, but he...
He couldn't wake up until now.
(Music)
Om.
Why do we have to hide?
But...
The sea is just a place for us to rest.
Alfa.
We have to be very careful.
Don't let anyone know...
If your parents are still alive.
We have to keep this a secret.
Very well.
If it leaks to the dark side...
It can be very dangerous.
(Music)
Okay, Alfa.
Now, give me your Gaebkang Juba.
Give it to your mother.
Don't let anyone see it.
Except Alfa.
That Juba...
I have it.
Each of us has one.
But Gama's had it...
When he was borrowed...
Oh, from Baran.
I used it when I came here.
So, that Gaebkang Juba...
I want to get that magic Juba back.
You don't have to, Alfa.
That Juba is yours.
No, Professor.
It's not mine.
It's someone else's.
That Juba is not yours.
But it's passed down to you.
So, take good care of it.
Yes.
At that time, Baran said...
That's my Gaebkang Juba.
That means...
It's from...
Come on.
Okay.
Let's not waste time.
Now...
Let's go to Aldo and ask him about this.
Why did I take the stardard back?
Let's go.
Alfa and the girl.
I think it's her mother.
Alfa's mother?
We can do it.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
Did you see Alfa?
No.
I looked for her in the warehouse.
Did you see her?
I looked for her too.
But I can't find her.
Where is she?
Maybe she's sad again.
Because we're busy with our parents.
I'm so angry.
Let's find Alfa.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
You can ask me.
We're going to the professor's room.
Why are we going to the professor's room?
It's none of your business.
It's none of my business.
I'm not going to the professor's room.
I'm going to the professor's room.
Purwa.
It's none of your business.
Do you understand?
Let's go, Alfa.
Mom.
Akira.
You're too much.
Hello, Purwa.
No way.
You're dead.
I saw it.
You know this.
If the Dark Lord finds out that I'm still alive...
...it will be very dangerous.
Okay.
Let's go.
"The Dark Lord"
Excuse me, sir.
Are you Jack's teacher?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Roga.
Jack's daughter.
Where are you going?
Excuse me, sir. I'm going to get my son.
Peace be upon you.
I'm so lucky.
Come on.
So, you've been hiding Gama and Aquila all this time?
Yes.
Where is Gama now?
Why is he gone?
Gama is unconscious.
I've tried to wake him up.
But he's still unconscious.
I'm also wondering...
...why Aquila is conscious again.
Because as far as I know...
...Gama and Aquila can be conscious...
...if their hands are smeared with the Dark Lord's blood.
That's what I know.
But I don't have any blood on my hands.
Can you guess what happened?
Aquila.
Do you feel anything strange about yourself?
This ring.
I think I know...
...what gives you the power to do everything.
The ring you're wearing...
...is made of the Sun Stone.
The only stone in the world...
...that has the same energy as the Sun.
That stone must be the one that gives you the power to do everything.
What if I wear that ring forever?
You'll still be alive.
I don't know yet.
But Aquila.
Where did you get that ring?
I don't remember. I don't know.
I just realized that I'm wearing the ring.
I don't care where you got that ring.
What matters is that you can come back to life.
Let me see.
Why did you take the ring from the ring?
I don't know.
Why is the black color of the ring...
...the same as the skin of a pig's hair?
Alfa.
What's wrong?
Nothing, Sir.
Nothing.
I'm so tired of being a daily job.
Me too.
Don't bother us.
We have to concentrate.
Don't make us make a mistake again.
One.
Two.
Three.
Teleportation.
Any report today?
Alfa hasn't found the soul stone yet, Sir.
That's all?
There's more.
When we took the report, there was Alfa and a woman.
I think it's her mother.
Yes, it's her mother.
Alfa's mother?
Yes, Sir.
Is it true that there's a soul stone in this ring?
No, it's impossible.
That's impossible.
Wait.
I think it's safe.
Akhila, you can open it.
Let's see.
Akhila.
What are you going to do tonight?
I'm going home.
I feel sorry for Gamma.
Don't.
My house is far away.
You'd better stay here tonight.
Because Alfa will miss you.
Right, Alfa?
Yes, I miss my mother too.
Alfa.
If your mother lives here, where do you want to stay?
In my apartment.
I have an apartment.
We'd better go home.
In my apartment.
You'd better stay in my house.
I said, in my apartment.
My house.
You don't understand.
I said, in my apartment.
I said, in my house.
My apartment.
In my house.
Shh.
It's okay.
[Akhila is going to stay in Gamma's house tonight.]
Sir.
Yes.
Can I stay in your apartment tonight?
Sure.
Of course.
But there's a condition.
What's that?
I'll do anything you want.
Anything?
Anything.
Okay.
I want you to stay in your house tonight.
Alfa.
Yes.
I agree.
That's a great idea.
No.
That's not a great idea.
Because...
Alfa.
Alfa has to sleep in the dormitory.
That's the rule.
And...
And that's the rule.
No.
The rule can be broken.
I'll take care of it.
No.
That's the rule.
It's written.
No.
I'll ask for permission.
I'll ask for permission from Professor Aldebaran.
To let Alfa stay in the dormitory.
No.
Professor Aldebaran will never allow it.
He will.
Stop.
Shh.
Purwa.
I still miss Alfa.
What's the condition?
I'm fine.
Okay.
You can all stay in my dormitory.
Let's go.
Let's go, Alfa.
I've found...
...the third soul stone.
Where is it, Prof?
Where is it?
To be continued...
Both of Alfa's parents are gone.
Why?
They died.
Don't lie.
If you lie, I won't let you go.
Do you want that?
Yes, Sir.
We're not lying.
It's true.
Enough.
Now, investigate and watch Alfa.
Hurry.
Yes, Sir.
Teleportation.
Please.
Please come in.
This is my house.
It's a nice house.
It's clean and neat.
Yes, Sir.
It's nice.
Thank you.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll take care of it later.
Oh, right.
Akhila.
Your room is over there with Alfa.
Okay.
We'll take a rest.
Yes, Sir.
Be careful.
Don't be so sad.
Remember.
She's my wife.
Get in.
Come.
Where is Alfa?
She doesn't come back.
Where is she?
She's gone.
Wait.
Don't tell me.
Alfa...
...was kidnapped by the Dark Lord.
Oh, no.
Don't say that, Plita.
Let's do this.
We'll wait until tomorrow.
If Alfa doesn't come tomorrow, we'll report to the Professor.
Do you agree?
I agree.
Then, a kind-hearted warrior came to save the princess.
He fought the evil Dark Lord with his sword.
Shoot.
And he finally saved the princess he loved.
Alfa.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
I still can't believe...
...that you're in front of me.
But I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
I'll try to stop time.
I'll always be with you.
Be patient, honey.
Your father and I will try to do that.
Mom.
When can I meet my friends?
Not yet, Alfa.
But even though you don't know your friends yet...
...I'm sure they're good friends for you.
Yes, Mom. They're very good friends.
Mom.
(Alfa's room)
The Fatang Blaster.
This is better.
It's time to sleep.
It's safe.
I can't sleep.
I was going to sleep on my head, but now I'm sleeping on my feet.
I'll remember this.
I'll wake up and everything will be fine.
I won't give up.
(Alfa's room)
Panji.
This must be you.
Open it.
I'm sorry, Sir.
You'll be a ghost when you sleep.
You're a ghost.
I'll make you pay.
Good morning, Sir.
Alfa.
What are you doing?
We were exercising.
A little exercise.
To start the Fatang Blaster.
Please enjoy this.
I'll pour you a drink.
Sir.
Here.
It's okay.
(Alfa's room)
I want an egg.
Why are you so angry?
You're so annoying.
You can't make a noise when you eat.
Eat properly.
(Alfa's room)
Kids, calm down.
Alfa is in a safe place.
Where is she?
Who knows? She's sad.
You're good friends.
You always think of your friends.
But Alfa is not sad.
She's happy.
Why is she happy?
Calm down.
Alfa is fine.
But there's something more important.
What is it, Sir?
I've found...
the third soul stone.
Where is it?
It's at Duyung.
Duyung?
Yes.
Duyung.
What is that?
Yes.
It's a sign of good news.
Alfa is happy.
What is it?
Alfa.
Alfa, where are you?
We've been looking for you.
Yes.
We're worried about you.
We're worried that you'll be mad at us.
Mad?
Why should I be mad?
You didn't do anything wrong to me.
You're always mad at us.
Because we've been looking for you.
I really miss my dad.
Don't worry about him.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I'm worried about my mom.
I didn't get to introduce her to you.
It's okay.
Relax.
I'm happy too.
You're happy?
What are you happy about?
You're happy that we're here?
Yes.
You're happy, right?
What's wrong?
I'll tell you later.
If there's a good time.
Okay.
Alfa, I have good news.
We're going to the professor's room this morning.
He has a task for us.
What task?
We have to find the third soul stone.
Find the soul stone?
What does it mean?
The one in the hand is not the soul stone?
What?
The Duyo's book was stolen?
Yes.
And we don't know who did it.
That's weird.
Why is their book in the magic school?
Who did it?
I have to educate Alfa again.
To find information about the soul stone.
To be continued...
(Preview of the next episode)
(Thank you for watching)
(Thank you for supporting us)