This story is purely fictional. If there are similarities in names, characters/figures, and places in this show, it is merely a coincidence without any element of intentionality.
MDentertainment presents
🎵 "Show your spirit, get your friends ready" 🎵
🎵 "Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars" 🎵
🎵 "Be brave, don't give up" 🎵
🎵 "Chase your dreams and hopes" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, never stop" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, fight with all your heart" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, make yourself proud" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, let's dream" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, we can do it" 🎵
🎵 "We can do it!" 🎵
Enough!
It turns out they've destroyed the first soul stone
To get that soul stone...
What if you...
Marry Bardi?
No, no, no, I don't want to marry him
Pangeran, make a replacement
Let me talk to Pangeran
Can you?
Yes
Okay, start now
You do the job of a soldier
But you don't answer me
Yes, Pangeran
If I don't marry Bardi
How can we get that soul stone?
I don't know what to marry, just say it
But I have a better idea
Okay, who's next?
Me
Go ahead
Yes, sir
I'm sure he'll bite me
Okay, sir
Okay
You use the mantra of deportation and move to the left
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
Are you ready?
Go ahead
Deportation!
Where's Cici?
Oh no, Cici's gone again
Okay, quiet
Back to the check
Hello, hello, hello, hello
Quiet
Move
Where did you go, Jack?
In the forest, boss
I moved to the forest
I'm sorry
Go back to your seat
No one can use this mantra properly
This class is really disappointing
Sir, I want to try
Okay
What's the matter?
I'm sorry, I'm disturbing your class
But there's something important I want to talk about
Come with me
Okay
Students
This is the last class
What's the important thing they want to talk about?
Boss, I think Leon is following the teacher and the teacher
Yes, let's follow him
Come on
I want to give you a difficult task
But I'm sure you can do it
What is it, sir?
Your task is to give this love mantra to Agni
It means you have to come to the eighth gate
My guess is right
Apparently, this has something to do with the eighth gate
What are you doing?
Yes
You're lying
You're talking about the teacher, right?
I'll kill you
The teacher is the one who's lying
What are you doing?
Professor
Run
Run, Agni
I don't know
Just admit it
You're talking about the teacher
Yes
I'm not lying
You're lying
I'll kill you
How dare you?
What are you doing? Stop
Stop
How dare you?
I'm the teacher
Stop
I'm the one who's lying
What?
He's lying
I'll kill you
Yes
Enough
Go back to your class
I don't want to go to class
I want to join the teacher's team
To save Professor Agni
[The teacher is the one who's lying]
Leon, that's not possible
It's too dangerous
No, I'm ready
I'm not afraid
Professor Agni is in this situation because of me
So, I have to take responsibility
Leon, you can't do that
I'll show him the way
He doesn't know the meaning of darkness
I can watch him go there
Okay, Leon
I'll let you go
Yes, thank you
[The teacher is the one who's lying]
We'll join the team, too
Yes, I'll join
Why do you three want to join?
You're making it difficult
We can't join
Leon can join
Yes, we can
Okay, I'll let you join
But, you have to be careful
Yes
Enough, stop it
Just stop it
Professor
Yes
What are you doing? Join them
They're the one who's hiding in the dark
I'm afraid
If we join them, we can be the heroes
We've saved Professor Agni
If we save him, we can get the money from him
Yes
Let's go
[The teacher is the one who's lying]
Let's get the key
What's the key for?
To cut his hair
Cool
It's so big
Let's play
Be careful
Let's go
Wait
One, two, three
His hair is so hard
(Don't be afraid of me)
(I'm not afraid of you)
(Where do you see me from?)
(I know you're out there somewhere)
(But, this time)
(My eyes are on you)
(And now!)
(I'm here!)
(This is a real ghost!)
(Cannot be seen!)
(I'll kill you!)
(No!)
(Cook!)
We're being haunted!
Stop! Stop! Go away!
Stop!
Bargi, you're too much!
Too much!
We promised to get married!
But, in reality
Why did you eat them?
I was wrong about you
If you keep doing that, we'll cancel the wedding!
I'm sorry
I regret it
Don't cancel it
I'm willing to do anything for you
Oh, so you're willing to do anything for me?
Anything
Alright
In that case
I want to get a haircut
Bargi!
I'm here to tell you
Don't you dare to do anything to anyone
Do you understand?
I understand
And if you do anything to anyone
You'll be haunted
And your fate will be the same as Barga's
Yes, God
Bargi?
Bargi is confused
Alright, I'll go
Wait!
Bargi, think first
Okay, wait
Before you go, get them out of the toilet
Hurry!
You guys are so brazen
Thank you, sir
You've saved us again
You're great, Panji
You're really great
As a man
You can win a woman's heart
Shut up!
We've eaten
And drank
Oh, right
Don't forget to bring books
And stories
Okay, as a man
I'll help Alpha Vega Regan Pelita
Okay
Tele...
What's the password?
I forgot
Okay, teleport, stop!
What's wrong?
Oh, right, teleport, stop!
I think I'm late
Where am I?
Help!
Help me!
Don't tell me I'm in the toilet again
Help!
I'm in the toilet
Tele...
Teleport, for mommy!
Who's this?
I think I'm in the toilet
(And they are in the same class lol)
(Another smart girl, that's for you)
(Putting all her effort into studying English, lol)
(Jjonyang-a-rush)
(I'm a genius, you know?)
(CHANSUNG-a-rush)
(Clean and tidy)
(Am I cool, bro?)
(Chang-u-rush)
(Don't you dare to look under my seat! LOL)
Eeeeek (He's going to hit me as well)
(UGH)
(This is bad...)
(I'm going to hit you)
Teleport!
BANGKII!
(I'm going to hit you)
Where is he?
I'm in the tree
(I'm going to hit you)
Don't bother me!
Ouch!
I'm hurt...
(I'm going to hit you)
Run!
Prof!
Why are we here?
We're using lollipop, Prof!
Why don't we use a new spell, Prof?
Yes, Prof!
What spell is it, Prof?
Tele...
Teleportation!
How about you?
The spell was just taught, right?
If you misuse the spell,
you'll be punished!
Do you understand?
Yes, Prof!
Why is it so late, Prof?
We should've waited until nightfall!
Yes, Prof!
There's a time in the day,
when the dark night...
becomes weak.
Oh, so if it's dark,
the dark night is stronger, Prof?
That's right.
That's why we attacked him in the day.
We had a chance to stop him.
Now, everyone, wait here.
Use the spell to protect you from anything.
I'll go inside to check on you.
Yes, Prof.
Lopurisa!
Armi!
Now, you'll do the basic task.
You'll catch Leon and Orion.
Yes, Sir!
Then, you'll go to the fire prison.
But, by the way,
what's the point of them being caught?
What's the point?
Because they ran away.
That's why you have to catch them and put them in the fire prison.
If they ran away,
the power of the Prince will be reduced.
The Prince will be damaged.
You don't think so, right?
I don't think so.
Then, what's the point of being caught?
Do you want to oppose my order?
No, Sir.
Your Highness, let's do this first.
Do what?
Your hair is not in good condition.
Let's do this, Your Highness.
If you do this,
you'll look cool and handsome.
Here, Your Highness. Look.
This one?
Cool?
Handsome, right?
Good.
I have another idea, Your Highness.
Your eyes shouldn't be black.
It's bad, Your Highness.
You don't look handsome.
You look weird.
Really?
Like that?
But, black eyes make me look scary.
But, a prince looks ugly.
Agni.
I'll save you right away.
Just wait.
I'll get you.
I'm sorry.
You're hungry.
Don't kill me.
Are you hungry?
Here.
I'll feed you.
Wait.
Here, eat this.
I don't want it.
You don't want it?
I'm hungry.
I want chocolate.
Here.
I don't want it.
I don't want chocolate.
I want chocolate.
I'm hungry.
Your Highness, Cinderella.
Here.
This is Cinderella.
Husband.
This is about Cinderella and her husband.
Husband?
Husband.
I'm going to die.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
I'm sorry.
I can defeat the monster without Nava's help.
I'm so happy.
Is Sambargi back yet?
He's waiting.
Maybe he's busy.
I don't know.
Kids.
I'm going to make a guess.
Which one do you think?
Do you think Neng Bargi loves his hair more?
Or do you think he loves you more?
Me.
Shut up, Megantara.
I think...
...Bargi's hair is more beautiful.
I'm serious. I want to marry him.
That's great.
I'm still thinking about it.
Then, I'll break my promise.
Right.
I'm not responsible.
I've disappointed a woman.
Right.
Bargi is a woman.
Bargi's heart is as soft as snow.
Right.
Or, he can be called a php.
Bargi's heart is as soft as snow.
Shut up.
Do you know?
I'm doing everything for you.
Look.
His wife is slow.
You're more important than my hair.
I'm willing to give my hair to you.
So, you want to give your hair to me?
I'm sorry.
Why is the sound of lightning so loud?
Maybe...
...something bad happened to Bargi.
But, it's impossible.
Because, Alfa and the others...
...are still alive.
They must be dead.
It means, the 11 souls are still safe.
Yes!
Mommy!
We did it!
Yes!
I'll count.
1, 2, 3.
3, 2, 1.
We did it!
We did it.
If we did it, we must go back to the magic school.
Yes.
That's right, Megantara.
Let's go back.
Let's go.
Bargi wants to get married.
Megantara.
Please help me.
Please let me go.
It's impossible.
We can't leave him.
That's right.
Where's his hair?
We got his hair.
Vega.
Do you want to say something to Bargi?
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry.
Bargi, sit down.
This is a hair clip for you.
It's for your hair.
You can use it when your hair is longer.
Megantara, wait.
I want to say something.
Please persuade Bargi to let me go.
Then, we can go back together.
That's a good idea, right?
Okay, I agree.
But, I think you're her husband.
You should talk to your wife.
That's right.
Let's go back.
We did it.
We can go back together.
Don't leave me.
You're evil.
You're stupid.
Romantic.
What should I do?
I feel sorry for him.
He's still in the class.
It's okay.
He promised.
We don't have to do it.
Right?
How about this?
Let's go back to the school.
We'll meet with the professor.
After we destroy the stone in his hair.
Then, we'll go back to pick up Panji.
We did it.
Bargi is beautiful.
"I'm sick."
Ouch, my stomach.
It hurts.
Don't be sick.
I have to be cured by Don Putri.
Give me the medicine.
Medicine?
Yes, medicine.
It's Don Putri Malu.
Don Putri Malu?
You're not the one who's shy.
But, Don Putri Malu.
You're not Putri.
Hurry up.
I have Don Putri Malu.
Ouch.
It hurts.
Hurry up.
Bargi.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
This is the father.
He's the one who taught the kids in the school.
Who is this?
I want to know.
I have to follow him.
"I'm sick."
Husband?
Where's my husband?
Husband!
Good afternoon, Professor Aldebar.
Good afternoon.
How is it?
You've succeeded in getting Bargi's hair.
I did it.
He woke up in the morning and ate an orange.
This is Bargi's hair.
It's as stiff as a tree.
I didn't expect you to get it so quickly.
Thank you.
As usual.
Alfa.
You're the only one who can do this.
I'm sorry.
"I'm sick."
If they all become my slaves...
...our power will increase.
We can do it.
Juri.
"I'm sick."
Yes!
We did it.
Sir.
Wake up.
38 fainted.
This is a good chance.
Sir.
How can you faint so easily?
You've cut your toenails.
The bacteria should be dead.
Why did you cut your toenails?
Sir.
Kids, get down to the mat.
Now, we go inside.
Sir.
Is there a dark room?
There is.
But, it's a dead end.
This is a good chance to save him.
Let's go.
Let's go, sir.
Oh, no.
You guys.
What do you want to do here?
Akmi.
We're here to save you.
Save me?
Yes, sir.
Why?
I'm fine here.
I don't need to be saved.
Don't run.
Let me go.
Hurry up and give her the medicine.
Come on.
Okay, sir.
Let's continue.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Let me go.
I don't want to drink your medicine.
Calm down.
Hurry up.
Drink it.
How dare you to come here without my permission.
You'll pay for it.
Professor.
We've got the first soul stone.
We've got the second soul stone.
But, next...
we have to find the third soul stone.
The question is...
can we know where the third soul stone is?
Unfortunately, until now...
I haven't got the information where the third soul stone is.
I'm dizzy.
Calm down.
I'll try to get the information.
Professor, if you haven't got the information, can we...
get one day's permission?
Yes, because we still have something to do with Panji.
Something to do with Panji?
What is it?
Don't be a pro.
I'm not a pro.
I'm just saying.
I'll go now.
Thank you.
Yes!
Finally, we've got the second soul stone.
We have to work together.
Now, I'm not dizzy anymore.
What does zinc shrink to strength?
But, we still have to get the tenth soul stone.
But, we have to be motivated.
We have to be motivated.
That's right.
Let's go to Panji's house.
Okay.
Hello, everyone.
Mr. Panji.
Mr. Panji, you scared me.
You're a good boy, right?
I'm a good boy.
Mr. Panji, are you ready?
Are you ready?
We were going to invite you.
What are you talking about?
Don't go there.
I'm not getting married.
That's right, Mr. Panji.
He's your husband.
Yes.
But, I was thinking...
It's his business, not mine.
Mr. Panji.
How do you do it?
I'm not Panji if you can't do it.
Mr. Panji.
How is it?
It's good.
What are you doing?
Be careful.
Husband.
This is the spirit of Panji.
He's following the ghost.
I'm following the ghost.
I have to stop the ghost.
So, I can find the other ghosts.
I'm going to find the other ghosts.
Your knowledge is useless.
You're all useless.
Enough, Leon.
You're the best.
You're coming with me.
Why are you in a magic school? You're useless.
No.
I don't want to be with a bad person like you.
Enough.
Your wish is my command.
Release.
What's wrong?
I'm going to kill you.
What's wrong with you? Why did you want them?
Don't.
Because when I was in school,
I was taught that we can't kill people.
That's a sin.
You can't, Mr. Erat.
That's true.
My teacher said that too.
You know that's a sin, right?
So, what should we do now?
Calm down, Sir.
We should make them...
become your followers.
So, there will be a lot of followers.
Not just one or two people.
You're right, Om Aki.
If they all become my followers,
our power will increase.
You take care of everything.
I'll take care of the rest.
Del,
let's go.
Professor Rani,
I know you won't hurt us.
Come on.
Drink this potion.
Come on, Professor.
Come on, Professor. Let's go.
Yes, Professor.
Drink it, Professor.
So, Professor Ali can come home with us.
I'm not going to be here.
Professor Rani,
come on.
Drink this potion.
Professor Ali!
Rakif,
you said you wanted to save us.
Let go of me.
Help us, Professor.
We're in the wrong, Professor.
I'm not the one who's going to drink this potion.
You all are.
Professor Ali,
I told you, Aki.
Don't let anyone touch you.
My husband!
What's going on?
Welcome to Cinta Super's meeting.
This meeting will make you all...
obey whatever the government says.
I'm not going to drink that potion.
Yes, Professor.
The director of the dark is evil.
But you're not like him.
You don't know that you're his followers.
Yes, Professor.
We're not a group.
Shut up, all of you.
It's useless for you to scream.
If the dark is listening,
you can all be punished.
It's even worse.
You're all going to the dark.
Enough.
Shut up.
Don't make noise.
Drink this now.
Drink.
I'm going to drink the Ramonito.
I'm sorry, my dear.
I attacked you first.
Yes.
If you win,
I'll give you Ramona.
But if I lose,
you have to give me Ramona.
Who's afraid?
Why is your hair so short?
Where's your hair?
My hair is gone.
You must have given your hair to someone else.
To my husband.
What husband?
My husband.
I told you.
Don't give your hair to anyone.
I'm sorry.
Your mistake is fatal.
I'm not sorry.
I'm sorry.
You've lost your hair.
And you've made my soul broken.
Feel this.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You've been grumbling.
I don't know.
I don't feel good.
What's wrong?
I miss...
My uncle.
You miss him?
Yes.
I miss him.
Don't be noisy.
If you miss him,
you have to come to him.
That's enough.
Finish your food.
I feel sorry for Bargi.
He's in the same class with his husband.
Imagine if he's in the news.
He can't imagine.
But...
Bargi must be heartbroken.
His heart is broken.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
You're a bully.
Shut up.
I'm going to hit you.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Who's that?
I'm dead.
Yes.
If I get caught,
I can't be caught.
Teleport.
I'm sorry.
There's no one.
Those kids.
They're making me angry.
It's better to be here.
It's better to live a fresh life.
I'm sorry.
Ouch.
What are you doing?
Where are you from?
Is this a school?
Yes, it is.
Yes.
Thank God.
I'm from the 8th Pangerang.
Where are you from?
The 8th Pangerang?
Yes, the 8th Pangerang.
I'm a bully.
A bully?
You met a bully?
Yes.
He was hit by a car.
He asked for forgiveness.
He was hurt.
Where did it happen?
In the forest.
Get the lollipop.
Fly.
Don't do that.
Because...
he loves me.
We can do this.
Bro, I must win.
I must win.
Bro, beat him.
He's almost dead.
Let's go.
You're a bully.
You're hurting my son.
Get the lollipop.
Beat him.
I must win.
Who wants to be a bully?
Beat him.
I must win.
Admit it, Agni.
You lost.
Now you must drink my wine.
It's a deal.
I want a drink.
Thank you, Yana.
Mr. Fahmi.
I want a drink.
You're a bully.
Now you must drink my wine.
It's a deal.
You must drink my wine.
I want a drink.
Bargi.
The eighth call.
You've gone too far.
You deserve it.
No.
Don't.
He's my professor.
Don't give it to him.
Shut up.
No.
I don't want it.
Drink it.
Who made this?
It's disgusting.
This is my drink.
I'm the one who made it.
You're changing your behavior.
Why?
I'm not a good person?
You're not doing your job.
Because I'll make you...
...not a good person.
Let me go.
Ankara.
Now...
...you should be a good sister.
A sister who understands the school tradition.
No, I don't want it.
No.
Let me go.
Drink it.
So, I can be the only one who can help you.
Husband.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Because of me...
...you're left by the prince.
Husband.
Give me the compress.
Give me the medicine.
Husband.
I have to clean his wound...
...and cure him.
Suhami.
Bargi.
Why are you left by the dark shadow?
A traitor.
A traitor?
What kind of traitor?
Don't you dare to touch anyone's hair.
Do you understand?
I understand.
And if you touch anyone's hair...
...I'll destroy you.
And your fate will be the same as Bargi's.
Yes, sir.
But...
...if that's the case...
...why did you give me your hair?
Because...
...Bargi loves me.
Bargi is very tired.
Bargi wants to sleep.
No. Don't, Bargi.
Don't sleep.
Your wound is severe.
If you sleep, you'll get a bruise and you'll...
No. Just don't sleep. Okay?
Bargi is tired.
Bargi, I said don't sleep.
Okay.
Let's talk.
We'll talk about many things.
I'll accompany you. Just don't sleep. Okay?
Go to sleep.
Bargi?
Bargi, wake up.
I'll make you all...
...fall in love with me.
Bargi! Wake up.
That's my uncle's voice.
Yes. Why did he call you?
Let's go.
Bargi!
What's wrong, uncle?
Bargi! Wake up!
This is all my fault.
I caused Bargi to be like this.
I asked for his hair.
That's why Bargi was tortured by the 8th prince.
Oh, right. I read in a book...
...that if a monster is in a bad condition...
...there's only one way to revive it.
How, Fik?
The way is...
...to kiss its penis.
Kiss?
That's right.
Let's kiss.
Come on, kiss it.
Kiss it.
No, I can't.
I don't want to kiss it.
But, Uncle, you're upset, right?
I'm not.
You're upset, right?
Because Bargi is like this.
You're upset, right? Then, just kiss it.
Don't let Bargi die in vain.
Please, Uncle.
Please.
Okay.
I'll kiss it.
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Bargi.
Bargi, you're awake.
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
What's wrong with Bargi?
Maybe it's true what I read in a book.
What's in the book?
What's that? A love story?
What's in the love story?
Guys, the monster that kissed the prince...
...will become a beautiful princess.
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Just like me, Berwi.
You're a monster, Bargi.
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Why isn't it a princess?
Why is it bigger than the world?
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Oh, right.
You think this is a storybook.
But it's a reality for kids.
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Poor me.
I thought I'd get a beautiful wife.
But it turns out...
I'm a loser.
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Poor me.
Professor Purwa?
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Ankara?
Professor Purwa?
Why am I here?
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
I succeeded.
And I'm back to being the only one who pays the bill.
I don't have a competitor anymore.
(Bargi's penis is being removed)
Professor Purwa?
Why can we be with this creature?
You've won the love lottery.
You've become a follower of the 8th prince.
No, no, no way.
I don't want to be a follower of the 8th prince.
Agni, you can say that because you're aware
that you've done a lot of bad things.
Ankara, it's better if you let go of my hand.
No, that's impossible, Agni.
Because now, I'm going to make all of you
bow to the 8th prince.
(Bow to the 8th prince)
Agni!
Agni, I'm home.
Bring me some food.
But that's the 8th prince's voice.
Why is he calling me?
I told you, Agni.
You've become a follower of the 8th prince.
Now, I'm going to report this.
He'll be very happy.
Watch out!
Sir, what's wrong?
Since when did you become Agni?
I called you Agni, why did you show up?
I'm your servant.
Oh, yes.
Ankara, you're in the discourse.
Why are you here?
Sir, please don't be angry.
I've apologized to you.
There's no more apology for you, Ankara.
I'm sick of being angry with you.
Sir, please understand me.
I can't not be your servant for a day.
So, please understand me.
I'll be your servant for the rest of my life.
I'll be your servant.
Sir, I have an extraordinary gift for you.
What gift?
When you left,
Purwa and some students from the magic school...
came to report you, sir.
What?
I don't know, sir.
I was lucky to see them.
What about Agni?
Agni is conscious, sir.
Because he was given a consultation by Purwa.
Agni is conscious?
But I managed to catch all of them, sir.
Including Agni.
And I've tied them up very tightly, sir.
So, they won't be able to get out.
And there will be many new candidates, sir.
(The next day)
I'm scared of lizards.
My husband.
What is it, Bargi?
Your hair is so smooth, Bargi.
I said no.
Bargi, don't ask.
You can't.
(The next day)
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with all your might
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Let's dream
We will
Bye bye..