This story is purely fictional. If there are similarities in names, characters/figures, and places in this show, it is merely a coincidence without any element of intentionality.
MDentertainment presents
🎵 "Show your spirit, get your friends ready" 🎵
🎵 "Run, jump, jump, conquer the stars" 🎵
🎵 "Be brave, don't give up" 🎵
🎵 "Chase your dreams and hopes" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, never stop" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, fight with all your heart" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, make yourself proud" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, let's dream" 🎵
🎵 "Go, go, go, we can do it" 🎵
🎵 "We can do it!" 🎵
I know everything, it turns out that you're evil
You're friends with the person who kidnapped me in the cave, right?
Then you want to harm Fega and Alfa, right?
I don't want to follow you
So Fega succeeded in making the princess realize the meaning of love and sacrifice
And finally all this madness ends
That's right, professor
That's the star
I can't fail this time
Thank you, it turns out that you've helped me
Sorry, I misjudged you
And I hit you too
Yes, when you landed, they were fighting for your victory
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
When you landed, they were fighting for your victory
So I took you away from there
I don't want to hear your excuses anymore
Why can you just let it go?
I have to get that fallen star princess
The star that can be returned to the sky when the moon is full
Oh, so the fallen star can return to the sky when the moon is full
I think it's done
So until it's done, I have to protect Selena
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Where are you going? You're in a hurry
I'm running in the morning
To be healthy, I'm going first
Wait
What is it?
I want to tell you that today is my professor's class
But not in a normal class, but in a minaret
There's a white star there
It's scary, it can be found
What should I do?
I'm going first, bye
Alfa
It's so weird
She's been like that since yesterday
Maybe someone is jealous of her
Selena, wake up
Wake up
Selena
I'm sleepy, Alfa
I'm awake at night
But when I'm awake, I have to sleep
I understand
But there's a lesson here
Come on, hurry up
You have to move from here
Professor, why is the lesson in the minaret?
Why not in class?
Why?
Is there a problem?
Alfa
What are you doing here?
Nothing, professor
I was running in the morning
I didn't mean to come here
Kids
Line up
Go to the classroom
Everyone
Listen up
As usual
I will teach you magic to defend yourself
The mantra we will learn today is
The magic of moving forward
Professor Agni will help me
Everyone, please pay attention
To the left
Find the jewel
Silence
Professor Purwa
I think you should tie your hair more often
Silence
Now I have changed into Professor Purwa
Professor Purwa
I think we should switch bodies
Move forward
As you can see
It's time to try
We will start with the turn
Vega
Tommy
Move forward
Remember the mantra
And the name
Move forward
Yes, I did it!
It's so cool
Vega's magic
Good
Tommy and Vega
Let's continue
I will try
Alfa
Tole
Move forward
Okay
Silence
What's that sound?
It's not anyone's sound, Professor
It was
My voice, Professor
I saw
The
Tole fell
That's why I was like that
Alfa
Move forward
Silence
Good
The last lesson here
Tomorrow we will start again
Alfa
Tole
Tomorrow is your turn
And you have to do it
If you don't, you will be dismissed
Yes, Professor
Luckily Selena didn't know
If not
Oh my
I'm sure
The fallen star girl
Must be in this school
Yes
I agree with you
We will find out
Through them
Hey!
What do you want?
Don't
Don't attack me
Please
Calm down
We won't hurt you
Yes
We want to give you a present
A present?
What present?
We want to give you this
Hey
It's not that easy
If you want this girl
You have to follow our order
But don't make it hard
Yes, don't make it hard
It's easy
Do you know about the fallen star?
No
That's your job
Find out about the fallen star
If it's true
The fallen star is in this school
Let us know
And you
Will get this diamond
As your reward
That was a cool shot
We got that
Yes
But how do we find out about the fallen star?
I don't know
Let's find out
It's not easy
The fallen star is in this school
I have to get it first
From the elf warriors
And give it to the dark lord
My sword!
Oh no
I can't use my power
I might get hurt
What's that?
This is my sleep powder
I'm going to sleep
The fallen star is in this school
[music]
[thunder]
help! help!
[music]
help!
thank you for helping me
[music]
but who are you?
I'm Selena
but don't tell anyone
that I'm Putri Bintang Jatuh
because only you and Alfa know
because if others know, it could be dangerous
[music]
I promise, I won't tell anyone
because you helped me
[music]
with this tool, we can catch Putri Bintang Jatuh
Jatuh
[music]
don't! Putri Bintang Jatuh is a good person, unlike you guys
do you know her?
no, I don't know her
but how do you know her?
[music]
I don't know her
but I know her
there must be someone hiding this from her
maybe she knows something
[music]
what's wrong?
did I meet Selena?
[music]
but don't tell anyone
how could you do that?
why are you so angry?
no, I'm not
Plita told me about the stick that stuck on the tree
yes, it stuck on the tree
I won't bother you anymore
I'll play first
[music]
what's wrong with them?
I don't know, no one is hiding it
[music]
sister
hi, Plita
I brought food for you
thank you, Plita
you're welcome
[music]
yes!
your work is very good
it means we got the star?
yes
not now
wait until we get the star
okay, go back to the school
you'll be searched
wait, I'll go with you
Eka, you must find the evidence
there must be something wrong
and the teachers will explain to us
don't worry, Tri
create the tool that can help me get in the school
[music]
wow, professor Megantara
you're great
[music]
Dantara
have you seen Alfa?
I've been looking for her
and Eka too
you're a coward
why am I a coward?
I'm with Tommy
[music]
that's him
don't lie to me
how dare you lie to me
that's him
[music]
he's a liar
that's him
[music]
don't play with me
how dare you play with me
accept the consequences
[music]
why can't he see?
the girl was there
we must concentrate
we can do it
Alfa, I'm afraid too
if he's played with the teachers
it's scary
we'll be punished
the punishment is weird
clean the toilet
clean the page
come on
when will we practice if you keep talking?
[music]
what's wrong with you?
[breathing]
okay
[music]
Vivinda Jiwa
Salena
[music]
that's my body
it's awful
why am I in Salena's body?
what's wrong?
[music]
here you are my door
let me go
[music]
let me go, professor Ankara
where have you been?
[music]
you're a bad person
who doesn't know you?
[music]
let me go
Vivinda
[music]
good evening, sir
I've got Putri Bintang
[laughing]
[music]
why is she shining?
how is it, sir?
a star should be shining
it's radiating light from her body
[music]
Ankara
I want you to make a shining star
because if a star doesn't shine, it's useless for me
[music]
make her shine, Ankara
after she shines, bring her to the black cave
I'll take her power here
[music]
how do I make her shine?
wait
[music]
it's bad, we need to attack Ankara
how can I be in Alfa's body?
it's weird
I'm not Alfa
what should I do?
[music]
Alfa
where have you been?
we've been looking for you
I'm not Alfa
Alfa, are you sick?
what's wrong?
[music]
come here
Vivinda
[music]
let me go
it's Alfa
[music]
Alfa, you must be sick
that's why you're angry
where are you taking me?
I want to go back
[music]
Alfa, you must be sick
that's why you're angry
we want to take you to the doctor
I'm not sick
let me go
[music]
I'm not Alfa
do you know?
Alfa, be patient
we're almost there
let's go
[music]
yes
I know now
the star will shine bright when it's happy
and it will fade when it's sad
the star likes to dance and sing
if I can make it dance and sing
it will be happy
and its body will shine
[laughing]
yes
this time I will succeed
[music]
where am I?
it's terrible
[music]
I'm still in Putri Selena's body
Putri Selena must be in my body
[music]
she must be afraid
I have to go back to school
[music]
oh no
the key again
[music]
there's a window
no
[music]
oh no
why don't I have a tongs?
[music]
where is it?
what is that?
[music]
why is it me?
sorry
everything is okay
no problem
it's very good
so I'm just fine
thank you
thank you doctor
okay, welcome beautiful
Alfa, don't get sick
tomorrow is the full moon
the magenta said to me
if it's the full moon later
we will play
that's right
oh no
tomorrow night is the full moon
I have to get my body back
if I don't get my body back
I won't be able to go back to space
I have to wait for the full moon next month
okay Alfa
I will give you
a calm down mantra
so you won't be angry anymore
so you can sleep well tomorrow
we can play
it's so fun
I don't want to
no no no
Alfa, don't be naughty
this mantra is not dangerous
not dangerous
it can only make you sleepy
and sleeping handsome
until tomorrow
okay Alfa
it's so bad
I can't sleep
I have to find my body
I don't want to be late
to go back to space
just lie down
that's right baby
okay Alfa
ready?
are you ready?
no no no
Alfa
Alfa is so naughty
why?
why is she so weird?
I think she's confused
let's go
thank you Dastin
oh my god
why is she so weird?
guys
please help me
I have to go back to school
get me out of here
why can't they hear me?
I think they're hypnotized
I have an idea
this is the key
I have to go back to school
I have to find the real Selena's body
wait
Gawat
there's a space professor
is the star already shining?
good
but
if that's the professor
why can she go out by herself?
I hypnotized them
so they can dance and sing
good
she's dancing and singing
she must be happy
but
why isn't she shining?
you
you're not the star
where's the star?
you
how dare you to play with me
our guess is right
I think she's Selena's friend
I like her
she's Selena's friend
we should give her the star
let's go after her
what?
help
I'm tired
why am I running?
Rita, help me
I'm not Alfa
help me
you're not Alfa?
if you're not Alfa, who are you?
I'm her star
you believe me, right?
I don't believe you
no
let me go
I'm the star
star?
yes
you're good kids
now
let me go
I have to find out where my body is
there
the star
let's go back
this way
yes
you're the star?
impossible
the soldier said
it's rare to find a star
that's right
if you don't believe me
ask Rita
I met her yesterday
Rita, you're the star?
the star that lives in the school tower
she helped me yesterday
no
you're the star
I don't believe you
you're Alfa
I'm Selena
you're Rita
I don't know
I'm in Alfa's body
maybe
you're Alfa's body
I don't know
when I jumped to the tower
I fainted
when I realized
I was trapped in Alfa's body
Alfa's body
the star fell
where is it?
I know how to find Vega
if he's the star
I'll ask him to shine
that's right
okay
I'll do it
shine
it's true
he shines
it means
he's Selena
see
I told you
I'm Selena
the star fell
if he's not Alfa
what does it mean?
Selena's body
we're right
Alfa's body is Selena's body
what should we do?
let's just follow him
let me see
let's go
Alfa is being chased by the robber
what should we do?
let's help Alfa
okay
let's go
I must be able to get out of the city
but
what should we do?
what if we can't help him?
what are you doing?
hurry up, we're late
hey, where are you going?
where are you going?
let's go
calm down
it's us
Vega?
Rey?
Lita?
why are you guys here?
how do you know me?
Rey, of course we know you
he's Alfa's soul
but I still don't believe you
why is my dress different?
where did you put my dress?
I'm sorry
I changed my dress there
but your dress is left behind
I'm sorry
let's talk later
now, you guys face each other
and then you guys change your soul
give me the cane
here's your cane
thank you
soul change
go!
what are you doing?
I'm back!
You did it!
Thank you, Vega.
Mei, Frita,
welcome back my friends.
Now, you're back to your body, right?
Star Princess.
Yes, I'm back to my real body.
Thank you.
You're so kind to me.
You've helped me.
So now, I just need to find a new place
so I can fly to the sky.
Tomorrow is New Year's Eve.
So, you can go back to your original place.
I can't meet Selena anymore.
Don't worry.
Later, I'll call you from the sky.
We can play together again.
Promise?
Promise.
Huh?
Who's that?
I'm being followed.
I don't know.
Who's that?
Help!
Help me!
You can't go anywhere, Star Princess.
What's wrong with you?
I'll catch you.
Hey, your power is not comparable to mine.
Come with me.
[Scream]
Let me go!
Arjan!
Good morning, Alfar.
Megatara.
And you too.
Help!
Let me go!
Sir,
Star Princess is very weak and hot.
I can't tie her.
Even if I tie her, she'll be burned.
Don't fight, Angkara.
Because the peak of Star Princess's power is at night.
You can be burned by the light.
So?
We'll wait until tomorrow.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll get Star Princess's power.
And with that power, I'll defeat Aldebaran.
Then,
I'll take the chosen child from Aldebaran's protection.
[Laughter]
Sir, where are we?
Princess Selena!
Where are you?
She must be taken by Professor Angkara.
Oh my God.
Her heart must be taken.
Yes.
Oh, Reimu.
If the army is explaining the history of magic,
you should listen.
He said,
the fallen star is taken because of what?
Because of hair, eyes, and heart,
it can make a great power.
Yes, it's true.
It's dangerous if it falls into the hands of the evil spy.
But we can't do it ourselves.
We need the help of Professor Aldebaran.
Okay.
Let's go.
So it's true.
The fallen star is in our school.
Yes, sir.
I asked her to stay at the school tower.
But because of Professor Angkara,
she was kidnapped.
Why are you hiding this from me, Alfa?
Your actions can be dangerous for yourself
and your other friends.
I'm sorry, Professor.
Because the fallen star told me
that I can't tell anyone.
So I have to keep my promise.
If so,
we have to find out
where they took the fallen star.
Use this telescope, Professor.
It's morning already.
I'm so tired.
I'm sleepy.
Now is the time.
Soon,
all the power of the fallen star
will belong to the Dark Lord.
Even if it's Aldebaran,
he won't be able to stop it.
[laughing]
We have to go there
before Angkara takes the power of the fallen star.
I'll go with you.
There's a fruit
and a curse.
This is dangerous.
You can't go with us.
But, soldier,
I have to take responsibility for this.
Besides,
I promised the fallen star
that I would help her
until she returns to the sky.
Alright, Alfa.
You can go with us.
Thank you, Professor.
What do we do now, Professor?
Yes, what do we do?
Don't you forget.
There's a very important task
for you.
What is it, soldier?
[music]
Are you ready, Angkara?
Yes, sir.
You go out, Angkara.
There's a guest waiting for you.
[sigh]
They again.
I won't give you a chance to break up, sir.
[grunt]
Face them, Angkara.
[music]
Yes, sir.
I will fight them for you.
[music]
Good morning, Alfar.
Megatara.
And also, you, Alfa.
Bring back the star princess.
Oh.
It's not that easy, Alfa.
And I'm begging you.
Don't ever bother me again.
[music]
They're together.
Let me face them.
Alfar, go.
[music]
Finally.
The star princess's hair is falling off.
[laugh]
[music]
The star princess's hair is falling off.
It will make me head to your weapon.
[laugh]
[music]
Sir.
How can I not get hit by this?
[music]
[laugh]
Finally.
The star princess's hair is falling off.
[laugh]
[music]
Now it's my turn.
To take the white tears from you.
[music]
[laugh]
Tear of tears.
[music]
[laugh]
With tears of tears.
God's power will soon recover.
[laugh]
Now it's time for me to take...
...the heart of the star princess.
[music]
Duplicate!
I have to tear the star princess's eyes and hair now.
After that, I will become a force.
[music]
You have to stop her.
Don't let her drink the tears that have been mixed with my hair.
Because it can cure all her diseases.
And she will be stronger.
[music]