To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Yeah, I did it!
Ankara, look at that
There's Alpha
It means that with us
You're really a Megatron
You better go
Let Alpha go
I won't let Alpha go
Alpha!
Attack her, Alpha
Now!
Team Ninja!
Let's go, Nek
Ready, Nek
One, two, three!
Ankara was defeated
Now it's just me
Let's go
Alpha
You won't get away with this
The door is locked
This must be a snake from the dark lab
Calm down
Open the door
Try it, Alpha
Okay
Open the door!
I can't get in
Let's read the mantra together
It's not as easy as you think
I won't let you leave this place
This is a virus!
Now
I'm getting stronger
You two
Won't be able to take me
And you, Megantron
Because you're looking for trouble with me
I'll kill you first
Get ready, Megantron
Let's go, V!
No, Alpha!
Get back!
Don't!
Let me face you
Get back!
Orphan!
Nado!
Get back!
What's wrong, Dad?
Are you okay?
I'm okay
What's wrong?
So, we have to fight the dark lab, right?
Yes, we want to help Alpha
Because the dark lab is really strong
Yo, the dark lab
Is not a match for us
We can be a match for them
Don't be afraid
But, I feel sorry for Alpha
Yes, you're right
So, you want to join us?
Yes
Okay, I'll join you
Let's go
Okay, sis
Wait
I'll join you too
Let's go
Okay
Wait
You're alone in the dark lab
Be careful
I want to join you too
I want to help Alpha
I want to be a hero too
So, you want to join us?
Let's go
Go!
Sis!
I'm sorry
Alpha, it's better if you help Megantara
So, I can face the dark lab
Yes, Prof
But, be careful, Prof
She's very strong
Seperang!
[The Dark Lab]
Prof, you're still wounded
Don't attack her!
Calm down
I haven't lost yet
Megantara!
Sis!
Wake up, Prof!
Megantara, wake up!
Wake up!
How did I get here?
Amazing!
Professor Ada Barante has woken up
Thank God!
I'm so happy!
Professor Ada Barante?
Forget?
Professor Ada Barante fainted
He was attacked by the Dark Lab
I'm very, very badly wounded
Alpha!
Where's Alpha?
Alpha and Megantara are still in the Dark Lab, Prof
Where are the teachers?
All teachers, go away, Prof!
They want to help Alpha and Megantara
You're a villain!
You've ruined Professor Ada's life!
This is the fate of those who oppose me
And you will have the same fate as them
[The Dark Lab]
I'm going to kill you!
No!
Why is Alpha so strong?
He can turn my attack back on me
What do you want, Alpha?
Answer me, Alpha!
I don't know
You don't know?
This is the ring, Barga
You can throw it away
Don't, Alpha
Who knows it might be useful to you
You better keep it
Let's go to Professor Barante's house
[The Dark Lab]
Alpha, give it back!
No
Whoever wears this ring will be defeated
And I will wear it
Just like Barga
No, Alpha!
Don't!
I want to protect Alpha!
[The Dark Lab]
Now, it's your turn!
This is for the Galaxy!
Take this!
And this is for the army!
Pegasus!
I want to fight!
You first!
[The Dark Lab]
The Dark Lab
is defeated by Alpha
[The Dark Lab]
Thank you, Pegasus
You saved me
Heal up
Army!
Wake up!
Professor Agni!
Wake up, Professor!
Army!
[The Dark Lab]
Let's go
Let's open the door together
Open the door!
Army!
What?
What happened?
What's going on?
The army of Professor Agni was attacked by the Dark Lab
This is bad
The Dark Lab is in the way
Professor Agni too
His heart is beating fast, Professor
No!
Are you okay?
I'm okay
[The Dark Lab]
Let's go
Professor Agni is back
[The Dark Lab]
Professor Agni!
Wake up
Thank God
Professor Agni
You've been healed
I can heal because of your help
Thank you
Alva
Where is the Dark Lab?
Tell me where it is
I've defeated it
What?
I don't know where it's called
You're great, Alva!
That's because of the army
Because I have a strong will
I won't let the Dark Lab hurt my teachers
Thank you, Alva
[The Dark Lab]
We have to go in
We have to help Alva
Let's go
Alva
Alva, you're safe!
One, two, three
Three, two, two, three!
That means you can't be a hero
You can be a hero
What hero?
The Dark Lab
Everyone, gather
Announcement, announcement
All students are required to go to class
Now
What's going on?
Is there another attack?
I'm bored, you know?
Men's war, men's war
No, we won't have a war this time
We will welcome a new professor
Who will teach at our school
Yes, a new professor
His name is Professor Tita
He is a great man
Very powerful
That's why Professor Aldebaran sent us to teach
Let's go
Who is it?
It's morning and they're already here
They're disturbing Professor Tita and Danajel
How could this happen?
Please
I'm sorry
Stop playing around
Let's go back
That's my staff
The Dark Lab
the most subtle and biggest dance in the history of dance.
[Music]
turns out my mantra is not perfect
if in front of the mirror my face hasn't changed
I'm afraid to look in the mirror
[Music]
come on, just open it, please
can
[Music]
we can
Hi Bro
how are you, Professor Lebaran
[Music]
sorry professor, welcome
you mentioned Professor Salah earlier
he is called Professor Aldebar
[Laughter]
sorry, I thought it was a little wrong
I'm sorry
yes, I remember
it looks like your name is Mega
Megaloman
right, right
wrong again
sorry, wrong, I'm sorry
I'm Begantan
yes yes
can I bring a pan?
please
there is a mosquito in your food
you are fat
but unfortunately you are also fat
[Laughter]
very accurate
very accurate, Professor Begantan
it's true
I can imagine how big the mosquito is
[Laughter]
Professor Titan, welcome to your school
welcome too, Professor Aldebaran
also introduce yourself, Professor
what's your name?
I'm Agni
Agni?
[Laughter]
Professor Titan
you should come to my class
okay
so you can introduce yourself to the children
thank you
later, let Megantara bring the gift
thank you, Professor Aldebaran
let's go
yes
[Music]
okay
Megantara, do you need help?
no, I just have to be like this
I'm still strong, Sir
I'm old, Sir
[Music]
good morning, children
good morning, Sir
today I will introduce you
a new teacher for you
his name is Professor Titan
please, Sir
good morning, children
good morning, Sir
I'm going to be a teacher
[Music]
thank you, Professor
children
children, listen
I have another important announcement
our school will hold a magic tournament
which will compete for a very exclusive magic trophy
wow
that's fun
it must be fun
yes, it must be fun
I want to join
yes, I want to join too
I often participate in it
I will win
because I have trained
that's great
we have trained too
children, this tournament will only be attended by two children from Kunang and two children from Ketama
wow
Sir, there are many of them
let's make it three, Sir
not just two, Sir
for the name of the participants
Mr. Rayhan, the father of Tommy
who will bring the list of children who will participate in this competition
[Music]
oh, this card is really six
really big
really heavy
really tired
really curious
really want to open it
[Music]
rather than being curious
just open it
what is this card?
[Music]
come on, just open it
please
please help me
[Music]
this card is a token from Professor Adek Barat
what is my right to open it?
I'm a good person
I can't be like this, I'll be punished
[Music]
push it
this miracle merchant
will give the names of the children who will participate in this competition
and those children
are two names of children from Gerhana
and two names of children from Purnama
[Music]
I have to choose
start choosing
[Music]
and the first name that comes out is
Alva
now you will only be an audience
because you will not be chosen
[Music]
so, I'm forced by Professor Adek Barat
to activate the miracle merchant
yes, Tommy
enter Tommy's name, Pi
don't put Alva and Vega's names
just the charming ones, Pi
here, Pi, the people
[Music]
Tommy
yeah
[Music]
the second name
Jack
yeah
congratulations Jack
[Music]
the third
Tole
yeah
[Music]
congratulations Tole
thank you, Pi
yes
why is he so good?
because he's fat
must be wet if in the water
the last
[Music]
Wee
yeah
congratulations, Tole
those are the four names of the participants
who will join the competition
[Music]
calm down, calm down, calm down, calm down
apparently, this miracle merchant
wants one more name
to be five children
and the name that has been mentioned
cannot be changed
[Music]
and don't you do it again
yeah Jack, I don't know
[Music]
the last name
Alva
[Music]
what is it?
what is this?
one, two, three
Zing, Duz, Jendel
[Music]
my plan is to run away with the boss
we lied
we promised Tommy
we won't put Alva's name
but why did you put Zing?
Tommy
I don't understand either
why suddenly Alva's name came out
what is it?
maybe
there is a mysterious person
who silently wants to enter Alva's name
okay, just let it be
but we won't let Alva
and Vega win
[Music]
Pi, please tell me
what is the first task
[Music]
Rey, Alva
good luck
but
you have to be tough
to be the winner
okay
[Music]
wait a minute
why are you so nervous?
huh?
why are you so quiet?
what's wrong?
I'm just confused
why I'm not chosen?
maybe
I'm stupid to think that way
beautiful, beautiful
you are so sensitive
already nervous
think you are stupid
Vega
this kind of competition
is just normal
we often do it
so don't think too much
just relax
right?
yes, Vega
I'm not stupid
all of you
all 100
none of you 0
yes
in class too
you always answer
when did you answer?
surely Vega first
[Laughter]
okay, sir
I support you
I'm sure
you can win
right
now
I will sing our cheer song
okay, ready?
ready
one
two
three
what the six wings
go to the
[Music]
my plan works
[Laughter]
[Music]
you are a bad guy
your evil will be revealed
there is something that will know this
shut up
[Music]
drink, drink
[Laughter]
you will be fooled
and don't you disturb all the girls
[Music]
you are finished
get out
[Music]
what is it?
good morning all
good morning, professor
now, professor wants to ask
who hasn't been to the brown rain part
raise your hand
me
so many
okay
brown rain
[Music]
come on, take it all
don't let anyone miss it
[Music]
if you're done, go back to your seats
dear, go back to your seats
all the children
there are still gifts for you
Lotto Riko
[Music]
one more
let's go back to your seats
[Music]
back
he wants to steal my child
my children
now we will learn
the government mantra
this government mantra is useful for someone
to order to do something
my children
this mantra is not easy
[Music]
so that this mantra can succeed
people who say this mantra
must have a very strong attitude
do you understand, children?
understand?
yes, sir
the government stands on the stage
[Music]
the government dances
enough
[Music]
children
now you try one by one
come on
[Music]
I'm already tired
hey
[Music]
don't be late
continue, professor
[Music]
the government is always winning
try it
be careful
[Music]
wow, this is
next
the government
please, sir
[Music]
the government sleeps
[Applause]
[Music]
the government
alpha
[Music]
wow, it's already done
thank you, sir
[Music]
if you can't, just don't
maybe you'll fall
don't be far away
[Music]
the government jumps
[Applause]
good, sir
good
you're great, sir
thank you
[Music]
okay
what do you want to be called?
Tom
Tom, can you write?
[Music]
this is a woman
[Laughter]
[Music]
what?
I can't
[Music]
the government
is defeated
[Music]
the children's advertisement
the government has done
please, go out
rest
yes
[Music]
Alphon
I'm happy with you
you have a great talent
[Music]
I'm a teacher
the most important thing is to be brave
yes
the professor also knows
this is one of your advantages
you're brave
[Laughter]
and one message from the professor
use the mantra
with good
in the competition tomorrow
the professor is sure
the mantra will be very useful
and the professor prays
you will win tomorrow
thank you, sir
you're welcome
[Music]
children
when the sound of the flute is heard
the participants must dive to the bottom of the lake
when they arrive at the bottom of the lake
they must take a net
which has been guarded by a turtle
therefore, you, the participants
must defeat the turtle
and bring the net to the edge of the lake
as soon as possible
[Music]
and now
in your hands
there is a box
in that box
there is a miniature of a turtle
which you will challenge
please open it
[Music]
I got a turtle
Ray, you're lucky
because the turtle with a turtle's hair
is the weakest
calm down, Ray
come on, cheer up
yes
I got a turtle with a turtle's hair
this is easy
I can definitely win
I got a turtle with a turtle's hair
I got a turtle with a turtle's eyes
I'm smart like Fika
and now
the first participant
[Music]
Nole
ready
[Music]
children
it seems like the turtle failed to get the net
because of that
the turtle automatically fell
[Cheers]
I'm so scared, Fika
I was attacked twice
actually I got the turtle
but I was attacked again
I'm scared, Fika
I hope it doesn't attack
don't be afraid, Ray
this is just a normal competition
if you want to win, it's okay
the important thing is you have the turtle
it's very useful for you
don't be afraid, Ray
keep fighting
keep going
thank you, Nole
thank you
and the next participant
the second one is
[Music]
Ray
please, Ray
[Music]
be careful
I'm sure I'll lose, Nole
I'll just go to the shore
just go to the shore
I'll go back to the sea
[Music]
one, two
why isn't there a professor here?
Professor Titan
[Music]
just take a break
yes, I succeeded
[Music]
I got the turtle
you're great, Ray
you're very long, Ray
yes, because you're in the middle
right?
impossible
I, Ray
good, Ray
you succeeded
and your time
30 minutes
it means that you who haven't competed
must beat Ray's time
[Music]
the next participant
Jack
[Music]
one, two
go, Jack
[Music]
[Applause]
he's so good
calm down, kids
it seems that Jack also failed to get the krang
it means that Jack also failed
what's wrong?
he's so strong
so I'm the winner
[Applause]
and the next participant
Tommy
you succeeded
be careful, Tommy
you're great, Tommy
[Music]
one, two
yes, luckily, Papi told me that I'm a seaweed
making a fish
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm the winner
[Music]
good, Tommy
you succeeded
and your time
15 minutes
beat Ray's time
[Music]
boss, boss
yes, boss
boss
15 minutes, Alva
it's the highest record
you must be able to do it
Papi, you won't be able to do it
just give up
no, I won't give up
I've never tried
and now
our last contestant
Alva, please
[Music]
one, two
favorita
give it to me
[Music]
[Applause]
very good, Alva
your time is
14 minutes 30 seconds
[Applause]
so, the winner of this first contest is
Alva
[Applause]
all of this is because of the women's mantra
the prayer
I thank God
[Music]
the contestant
this is me, Alva
[Music]
why is there no sound?
Prof. Titan
this is me, Alva
[Music]
Prof. Titan
why is there no professor here?
[Music]
I'm the one who's noisy
hey, Alva
[Laughter]
what are you doing here?
you're talking like that
come on, laugh
come on
no, professor
I just want to say thank you to the professor
because of the advice of the professor
I won the first contest
you won, Alva
[Laughter]
congratulations, Alva
congratulations
I'm happy
[Laughter]
professor
why is this shaking?
[Laughter]
Alva, you don't have to be afraid
what's in the closet
is just a baby centaur
[Laughter]
baby centaur?
yes
because baby centaur
can produce a very powerful poison
and Alva, you don't have to be surprised
and don't be surprised
if you find weird creatures
in this room, Alva
okay
then
I'll go to the toilet first
oh yes
[Music]
be careful, Alva
I lost again
I lost to Alva again
I have to think
how can I beat Alva
if necessary
she can't participate in the next contest
[Music]
I know how
help
I'm asking for help
the sound is around here
but where?
help
[Music]
maybe she's in the warehouse
hey
open the door
[Music]
hey
open
yes
I'll open it later
but if the fight is over
open the door
oh my God
the fight has started
[Music]
Alva
you have to succeed
but you have to trust us
yes, Alva
you can't lose
if you lose, I'll replace you
Ray and Alva don't know
what's the secret of the Angsa
if I already knew
I'll tell Papi
this time
I'll win
hahaha
isn't that Professor Titan?
why is he in front of the warehouse?
[Music]
let's go
Professor Alhara
why are you here?
[Music]