Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Why did you act against my order?
But God...
Shut up!
I don't want all my plans to be ruined
We'll wait until the full moon
Because now is the right time for us to fight
Mom, what's wrong?
Dad!
Hey, think!
Think!
What have you done?
Who are you?
Who are you really?
You're the one who stole my parents' house
Don't ask me!
I'm not lying!
I'm the one who stole it!
No, I'm not!
And they're my parents!
We don't have much time
We only have 6 hours
And I don't want to see Serigala turn into a pancake
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
I'm ready
Action!
Serigala, I'm coming!
Where are you?
I'm here, I'm here!
I'm coming!
Serigala!
Boss, let's go!
I'm here!
What the power!
Cut the rope!
Sir, don't pull me!
I'm going to break the rock!
You can't do it alone, right?
I'm coming!
Sir!
Help me!
There's a thief!
What's wrong?
I was attacked, sir!
What was attacked?
I was attacked by Serigala's monster, sir!
Serigala?
Serigala came out of my parents' house
If so, let's take him to the village doctor!
Let's go!
Professor
If that's the situation,
In my opinion,
The only way is
Starting tomorrow,
I will train the children
So they are more prepared to fight
But can they do it, Megantara?
They are brave children
At home, I won't leave them alone
If necessary,
I'm ready to sacrifice my life
Until the last drop of blood for them
But there's one more problem, Megantara
What's the problem, professor?
About Alfa
Until now
I haven't heard from Vega
I'm afraid
They have a problem with me
[Sigh]
Professor
Can we split the task?
Me, Professor Titan
And Professor Agni
We train the children at school
Meanwhile,
Professor Purwa
I think
He's the right person
To find Vega and his friends to my place
[Footsteps]
See?
We're left with just a little bit of blood
We're done!
Give us more, Vega!
If he wants to,
He can have our blood!
Where are we going?
You're the only one who can help us
Go!
Go, Srigala!
I know the way!
What's the lock?
It's a secret
If you're Srigala,
You'll be human again
If you're hit by a sunbeam
It's already 8 o'clock
Sunbeam?
Yes
Oh no
It's only 12 o'clock
So,
We have 6 hours left
Oh no!
It's already 12 o'clock
We're done!
[Groaning]
Calm down!
Let's go!
Oferita, go to sleep!
[Groaning]
[Screaming]
What's wrong with you?
[Groaning]
I can't
I'll try
Oferita, sit!
[Groaning]
What?
I'll try again
Oferita, shut up!
[Groaning]
What should I do?
I can't do it
I can't be Srigala
[Groaning]
It's time
My body
It's all painful
Hang in there
It seems your wound is not too bad
You should just rest
And don't think too much
All of this
Because of Srigala
We can't just be quiet
We have to discuss it
If not
There will be other victims
But how?
What about Srigala?
Listen to me
I am a good butcher
And I know
How to defeat Srigala
Srigala is afraid of fire
And if we attack him
And I burn him with eternal fire
Which comes from my butcher's axe
Then he will die
That's right
We should gather men
And burn him
Okay
[Many people talking]
Any more?
I think it's over
Let's go to the toilet
I want to go too
Me too
Uh we can't go there
I'm so tired
I want to go to the toilet
Calm down
It's better to be calm than being in a daze
It's getting closer
Oh yeah, I just remembered that the magic mirror is very sharp
After that, he knows where we are
Really?
Help!
Oh my god
Are you ready, Rita?
I don't know
Happy birthday
Rita, what if he's a ghost?
What about my parents?
I don't know
I'll look for another one
Wait, let's hide first
How do we hide?
Someone's down there
Let's go
[Ghosts]
I'm scared
Calm down, honey
Actually, a ghost can be a good pet
As long as you can touch its nose
[Ghosts]
My dad said
If you want to pet a ghost, you have to touch its nose
What?
Don't be ridiculous
Yes
Hold it, Rita
Are you crazy?
Just hold it
Don't be ridiculous
What are you doing?
[Ghosts]
It's a real ghost
Yes, we have a ghost
It's scary
I want to try
[Ghosts]
I'll look for another one
I'll go
[Ghosts]
I want to touch it
Now, I will try some music!
One, two, now stay still!
Yeah! We're the champions!
One, two, three!
We're the champions!
Yeah!
Let's burn that monster!
Hey, Panji, get out!
Panji, get out!
Get out!
Panji, what's going on?
Panji, get out!
Get out!
Panji, you can't be a monster!
You can't get out!
Panji, get out!
Professor Adebar,
What do you want?
I want you to come to my house.
Why would I go there, Professor?
Until now,
Vega and his friends haven't returned.
And this is what worries me.
You know how I am.
I'm afraid Vega and his friends will have a problem there.
But why should I, Professor?
Why don't you just hold the reins?
Or Professor Yasmin, or Professor Raki?
You know that I've never liked Panji.
He's a weirdo.
I know.
You're the only one who can go there, Professor.
Because the other professors,
Megantara, Yasmin, Agni, and Titan,
They have other tasks for the kids.
And one more thing,
You're the only one who can hurt Panji.
What do you think, Professor?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Whatever you say, Professor.
I will do it.
I'll count to three.
If you don't come out, I'll slam the door.
Huh?
Where is this?
Everyone's waiting for me to come out.
I'm scared.
One.
Two.
Three.
Go back there.
Run!
Let's chase them.
Don't run!
Let's go.
Be careful.
Don't run!
Where do you think you're going?
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Just burn them.
Let's go.
Burn them.
Don't burn them!
That's a good story.
This story is not bad.
There's no good story.
Let's burn them.
Is he really a good person?
He's a good person. / We don't know.
Let's run away.
I agree.
We should wait for this story.
Let's go.
What if something happens to us?
We won't be able to live.
Let's go.
It's quite far.
Let's just fight them.
How?
Just run.
Burn them.
Let's run.
Don't let them get away.
People.
Don't be afraid to attack those kids.
They're evil.
No.
That's a lie.
It's true.
He's evil.
You all are his followers.
You're a slanderer.
That's right.
People.
Don't believe him.
Kids.
Who believes you?
People.
Let's attack them.
Let's solve this problem.
Catch and burn those kids.
Don't.
Be a man.
5 minutes later.
We got caught.
Five minutes.
Five years.
Don't be stupid.
This can be a true story.
We should pity them.
Enough.
Let's talk later.
Let's go.
Run.
Where are we going?
Let's hide in the well.
Let's go.
It's so hard to find them.
Luckily, this is a good place.
If not, I won't be able to sleep.
Don't be noisy.
They'll come here.
Before they come here.
Let's just hide.
How many branches are there?
Five minutes later.
What's wrong?
I'm not afraid.
I won't let them destroy me.
Where are the kids?
Everyone.
I told you.
They're the kids.
They're evil.
They made us stupid.
We shouldn't waste our time.
Let's chase them.
Let's go.
I'm sure they're still here.
Let's look for them somewhere else.
Maybe they're not here.
Let's look for them.
Luckily, we're not caught.
If they're far away, let's go here.
Here.
Shh.
They can be gone.
Is that a sound?
Yes.
I think the sound is coming from here.
Where?
I think it's coming from there.
Let's go.
One, two, three.
You're going to pay for this.
Wait.
Let me check.
What's that?
"Police"
Let's go, Becky.
You can't go anywhere.
Don't leave me, Becky.
Let's go.
You can't escape this time.
"Police"
People.
Listen to me.
I'm Angkara.
A good slayer.
And now...
I'm going to burn this evil tribe...
with eternal fire.
And as you know,
this eternal fire...
can't be extinguished by the magic of people.
Let me go.
Let go of that witch.
Don't burn it again.
And now,
it's time for me to burn her.
No.
Let go of that witch.
"Police"
Let's go.
Let go of that witch.
Feel this.
My friends,
now you can go.
Let me see the magic of this witch.
Thank you, good slayer.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
"Police"
Let go of that witch.
And now, the second task.
Which is to bring you, Alfa.
I will give you to the eighth witch.
So that you will be consumed by her.
Let us go.
"Police"
Attack the green man.
Okay.
Three.
Attack him.
"Police"
The witch is holding on.
Where is she?
I'll go there.
Pavanam.
Let me try.
Don't cut the water.
"Police"
Let me try.
Hey, you.
You're being funny.
Stop fighting.
Fire!
We will win.
Just like what the professor said.
Baby, baby.
We will burn it.
Help!
The fire is so strong.
This is eternal fire.
It will not be extinguished.
What should we do?
Baby, hold on.
Now, go back to your place.
Make sure you're safe.
And bring the body here.
"We can do it"
Yes.
He can use the flashlight.
He can go from there.
No way.
He can't talk.
You're right.
He has to move.
So, we have to change him to be Mr. Panji.
But, how?
Yes.
He can't talk.
If he's exposed to the sun, we have to make him talk.
Make him talk?
No way.
How can we make him talk?
Well...
We have to try.
Let's try to find a book.
How can we do it?
It's too long.
I can't read.
I know.
I love you, Blacky.
Oh, right.
I know how.
Wait a minute.
Putri Bintang!
Help me!
I'm lost! Putri Bintang!
Putri Bintang!
Alfa?
Alfa, Plita, everyone.
How are you?
Alfa!
There's fire.
Are you having fun?
It's so fun.
It's not a fire.
It's a serigala.
Serigala is me, a human.
Oh, my God.
He's about to be burned.
I want to ask you for a favor.
Can you make the sun appear?
If there's a sun, it will turn into a human.
I want to go up. Can you do it?
But don't take too long.
I'm sorry, Blacky.
I'm so sorry, guys.
I can't help you.
Because I don't know the sun.
It appears in the morning.
If I'm here at night...
Oh, no.
We can't.
Can you make it?
How?
Oh, I know.
I can call my friends, the moon and the stars,
to hide.
So, the sun can come earlier.
Okay, let's do it.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Friends, the moon and the stars,
let's hide.
So, the sun can come earlier.
Okay.
It's morning.
Mr. Baji, you have to go there.
You have to use the mantap to move.
Move.
How's the result, Angkar?
I'm afraid of being caught by the wrong friends.
And they make me feel guilty.
I'm so nervous.
Angkar!
Why are you quiet?
Answer me!
Sir.
This time,
the Mahadasyat is successful.
I've managed to provoke all the villagers...
to burn all of those.
And now, all of those...
have become grilled meat, sir.
(The fire is burning)
Did you see it yourself when it died?
No, sir.
But...
it can't be successful.
Because I've burned it with eternal fire.
And eternal fire can't be extinguished, sir.
Idiot!
Now, go back to your place.
Make sure you stay there.
And bring the body here.
Yes, sir.
Okay, sir.
Wait, sir.
(The fire is burning)
Sir.
Mom.
Dad.
Sir.
Why are they here?
How is it?
The story...
is very sad.
(The story is sad)
In the past,
I was the son of the 8th Prince.
The 8th Prince...
taught me...
to be a cruel and cruel ruler...
who hurt anyone...
without looking back.
(The 8th Prince)
Spa.
Kill him.
(The 8th Prince)
Good.
But in the meantime,
I have two friends.
Those two friends are your parents.
Gama and Aquila.
Actually,
they often advised me to leave the 8th Prince.
But I didn't want to.
Because I wanted to be strong.
One day,
I was given a task by the 8th Prince.
But I failed.
When he knew my failure,
he was furious.
He wanted to kill me.
But suddenly,
someone threw a smoke bomb...
and killed me.
That person is Gama.
(The 8th Prince)
In the end, I decided...
to leave the 8th Prince.
But the 8th Prince didn't listen.
He was very cruel.
He was very angry with Gama.
And he insisted...
that he must destroy Gama and Aquila.
(The 8th Prince)
So, the way I talk in my book...
is just a dream?
We can do it.
Why?
Only my parents were killed.
Why didn't I?
You mean...
he didn't kill you and let you live?
No one knows about that.
But one thing is clear.
When the 8th Prince attacked you...
a power appeared in you...
and made the 8th Prince go berserk.
When he tried to attack you again...
he realized...
that he had lost all his power.
(The 8th Prince)
My magic power is gone.
This is impossible.
It's impossible.
My magic power is gone.
Then, why did the 8th Prince go berserk...
when he attacked me?
According to Aldebaran...
that was a love spell.
Your parents created that spell.
You know Aldebaran?
Yes.
He was the teacher of the 5 guardians of the magic.
When I was still in school...
he was a magician.
Now he's a schoolmaster.
Oh.
So, he was a magician?
He was half my age.
So, that means...
you're really old.
(The 8th Prince)
You're so naughty.
Do you want to hear the rest?
Of course.
Don't worry.
The 8th Prince who has lost all his power...
is trying to find a way...
to get back all his power.
He's looking for all kinds of sources.
And finally he realizes...
that there's a way...
to get back all his power.
That is with blood...
tears...
and Alfa's sweat.
Then, why are my parents here?
Gamma, I'm lost.
I'm lost.
Gamma.
Gamma, I'm lost.
I'm the chain of life.
Put me in the chamber.
(The 8th Prince)
I thought...
this chain of life could heal them.
But because their wounds are too bad...
they can't be healed, Alfa.
They can only sleep...
and can't wake up again.
This chain of life...
only supports their lives.
As far as I know, they can only get married.
So, my parents...
only came through a dream?
You said they appeared in your dream?
Yes.
No wonder.
They told me to pray...
and cheer me up.
Alfa.
If Gamma and I appear in your dream...
please ask them...
what I should do...
to wake them up.
Okay.
I'll be there.
I'll be going now.
I have unfinished business.
Sir.
Where are you going?
I want to meet Ankara.
I'm curious about him.
Why is he attacking me?
We used to be friends.
Don't meet him.
He's the 8th Prince's son.
Ankara is the 8th Prince's son?
Yes.
They're getting stronger.
Because they got...
my tears, sweat, and blood.
All of them must have been burned to ashes.
But...
I have to go back to Ankara.
(Gamma's dream)
I'm going to war.
The 8th Prince won't be able to differentiate.
Look.
This is his body.
He's already become a hero.
I'm dead.
Maybe it's not my destiny.
I'm going there.
I won't let him get away with it.
I finally defeated him.
What's wrong with you?
Who ordered you to kill him?
I'm sorry, sir.
Guys, someone's coming.
Don't tell me...
it's Professor Ankara.
As soon as the door is opened,
we'll attack Professor Ankara with the TV.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go in.
Don't lock the door.
TV!
Professor Burua!
Professor Burua?
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Professor.
Shut up, Professor!
Shut up, all of you!
Let's go back to the room.
No one can go back.
Shut up!
Professor Burua,
why are you here?
Shut up!
What's going on?
Panji.
This must be your doing.
You must have ordered the kids to attack me.
Right?
Don't you dare accuse me.
Professor Burua,
I'm sorry.
We didn't mean to.
We thought...
the professor was Professor Ankara.
Yes, sir.
We thought he was Professor Ankara.
So, we avoided it.
Yes, sir.
We avoided it.
(Professor Burua, what are you doing here?)
I was ordered by Professor Aldebaran...
to come here...
and pick all of you up...
to go back to school.
What?
So, Professor Burua came here to pick us up?
Yes.
(Professor Burua, what are you doing here?)
(I'm still here to protect you.)
(Or am I going to Professor Burua?)
We will eliminate Aldebaran.
And I will promote you as the head of the magic school.
I order you...
to pack your things...
and come with me to the magic school.
I'm sorry, Professor.
I don't want to.
I don't want to go home.
Alfa, I remind you.
You are still a student.
I am your teacher.
And I am responsible for your safety.
So, you have to come with me.
Tole, Vega, Pelita, Ray.
Let's go.
We don't want to.
I don't want to go home either.
I want to stay here.
We don't want to.
I don't want to either.
Yes, Professor.
We are being forced to eat.
We only have three meals.
We are not full, Professor.
Professor, we have an important mission here.
To all good people.
Panji.
I know.
This must be your doing.
You told the kids to stay here.
You brainwashed them, right?
No, no, no, Sir.
I am the one who is wrong.
I told you.
Don't just accuse me.
Now, it's clear.
They all prefer to be with me...
than with you.
We still have unfinished business.
You'll see.
Alfa, let's go home.
No. / Come on.
No, Sir.
I don't want to go home.
Shut up. You have to come with me.
No, Sir. I don't want to go home.
Enough, you two.
Let Alfa go.
Let them go. Go home by yourselves.
I'm warning you.
Don't get involved in my business.
Alfa, let's go home.
The other kids, let's go home.
Professor, don't go there.
Yes, Sir. Don't go there.
I don't want to go home with you.
I want to stay here with Mr. Banci.
I'm sorry, Sir.
I still have unfinished business here.
Alright.
If you want it this way,
Alfa,
I'll let you stay here.
But on one condition.
What is it, Sir?
You have to compete against me.
If you lose,
you and the others have to take me back to the magic school.
But if you win,
I'll let you stay here with Mr. Banci.
What do you say?
I'm in.
If you don't want to compete against me,
I'll consider you surrender.
And that means you failed.
And because of that,
you and the others have to go to the magic school.
Come on, kids. Let's go home.
I want to compete.
Alfa wants to compete?
Oh, God.
You're just looking for trouble.
Mr. Banci is dead, Sir.
So, what's our next plan?
I'll move on to the second round.
But before that,
I'll give you a present, Angkara.
Because you've done a great job on your mission.
What do you want, Angkara?
I'll give you a present.
I want you to be a good boy.
What do you want, Angkara?
I'll grant your wish.
I want to be the head of the magic school, Sir.
What a coincidence, Angkara.
That's what I've been thinking about.
Then,
we'll send Aldebaran to the fire prison.
And I'll make you the head of the magic school, Angkara.
Thank you, Sir.
Finally,
my chance to destroy Aldebaran as the head of the magic school has come.
As the head of the magic school of Mendiamkage Sayang,
I want to make the final vote
to decide who deserves to be the head of the magic school.
(VOTE)
Please.
The current position
for Professor Aldebaran and Professor Angkara
is the same.
There is only one vote left.
Please, Professor Agni.
I will win, because Agni will choose me.
(VOTE)
Professor Agni chooses Professor Aldebaran.
Long live, Professor Aldebaran!
Why did you choose Aldebaran?
Because you are my future wife's candidate.
Angkara,
we do have a close relationship.
And the school's head's choice
has nothing to do with our relationship.
I'm sure,
that Aldebaran can be a good school's head.
So, you mean
I'm not good?
No.
That's not what I mean.
I'm disappointed in you.
Take this!
Sir!
We can do it!
Now, attention!
Step back.
The third round.
The match starts now.
Round one.
One.
Two.
Three.
Finish him!
Sir!
It's just a small match.
It seems,
no one supports me.
Can I have a round of applause for my first round?
We are a strong team.
We don't want to be a burden.
Yes.
We are a strong team.
I don't want to be a traitor.
What's that?
Yes.
Let's just give it a try.
We are at risk.
Yes.
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, sir.
You might be wondering about the writing in front of you.
Here's the thing.
Our school will have a selection.
Who among you has the ability and is ready to fight?
The chosen one will be part of the Al-Nibbar squad.
The mission of the Al-Nibbar squad is...
First, you must be ready to attack the magic school.
Second, you must be ready to destroy the Dark Lord.
The Dark Lord?
Yes.
That's right.
So, from now on,
we can't just randomly choose a kid to be a part of the squad.
We must select him correctly.
That's right, kids.
What Professor Agni said is true.
That's right.
This is my chance to be a champion.
While Alpha is gone.
I'm in!
Me too!
Mommy, are you sure you want to join?
You said you wanted to join the Al-Nibbar squad.
Are you sure you want to join?
You ran away when we fought the raptor.
Just you wait.
I'll fight the Dark Lord with all I've got.
We've arrived at the magic school, sir.
Okay, kids.
Before we start,
let's sing the song,
"Mars, the Magic School".
Oh, my children.
Don't forget the style I taught you.
Yes, sir.
Kids,
since this is the song, "Mars",
you must be excited to sing it.
Yes, sir.
Good.
Let's start on three.
One, two, three.
Show your spirit,
get your friends ready.
Run, jump, and get on the stars.
Be brave,
don't give up.
Chase your dreams.
You,
if you become the head of the school here,
you change the song.
They all must be my followers.
Yes, sir.
I'll make this school the second headquarter.
Just watch me.
You'll know that I'm better at making a school than a war.
[Mars, the Magic School]
My children,
try to imitate me.
Ahai.
Give me a smile.
How is this,
the students of the same grade?
How can you beat the 8th grade?
You've already lost against the 7th grade.
Whose voice is that?
That's the voice.
That's not the voice.
[The Magic School]
Your task now is to find the right person.
Okay, sir.
Show your spirit,
get your friends ready.
Run, jump, and get on the stars.
Be brave,
don't give up.
Chase your dreams.
Go, go, go,
reach all your dreams.
never stop.
Go, go, go,
fight with your heart.
make yourself proud.
Go, go, go,
let's dream.
we will.