To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb the stairs
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, reach all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, run with courage
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
Go, go, go, never stop
That kid...
He took my blood, Alva!
Hit him!
I didn't expect that I could get the Dark Lord's blood
Finally, the holy blood is back to me
Go, it's time for you to go
Come on, professor, what are you waiting for?
Finally, I can be free from the fire prison
Shut up!
How dare you to mess with us?
I will kill you all
Beautiful queen, the jewelry you gave us is much better
And much more luxurious than the necklace you're wearing now
So, it's better if you give us the necklace
Your jewelry is beautiful
But I don't want to trade it for my soul stone
This prison is priceless
As far as you know, it's been 1,500 years
Oh my, this is dangerous
All the rumors, even my pride, are worthless
What's going on?
Why is everything black?
Yes, professor
When Angkar was the headmaster here
He told him to change the color to black
Angkar?
Yes
He even changed the curriculum at school
He told the teachers to teach black science to the children
Angkar is too much
Angkar!
Thank God, professor
Now the classroom and classroom are back to normal
Angkar will not like all this
Unfortunately, Angkar will never see this place again
Because I will not let him set foot in this school again
What should we do, professor?
With a mantra, of course
What else?
[The Mantra]
What's that dust, professor?
This is not just any dust, Agni
I think I've heard of that dust
That's the dust of protection, professor
That's right, Agni
Dear dust of protection
Protect the school and the children
From a man named Angkar
[The Mantra]
I hope that dust will not control this place again, professor
I guarantee that it will never happen
That's good, professor
Any news from Megantara?
Not yet
I'm still waiting for the news
Sir, sir
I swear, sir
I have nothing to do with these kids, sir
I don't want to hear any more of your betrayal, Angkar
Now, accept your punishment, Angkar
[The Mantra]
If they don't have a thing for you
They will never want you, Angkar
Sir, I don't know, sir
[The Mantra]
I told you, don't protect me!
But if you don't protect me, you will die
I don't care!
I told you, don't protect me!
But, sir
If you don't protect me, Angkar
Hey, enough!
Stay away from me!
Maybe
You will never be able to avoid it again
Professor!
Get out of the way!
But, Meg, I was killed by a dark force
It's okay, I'm still alive
It's okay, we're still alive
We can go to school
But, how?
Oh, this letter
It's from Professor Lebaran
Vega, keep this
What is this, sir?
That's a miracle letter
When you're in trouble or lost
You can light that letter
And it will bring you back to school
Now
You will all be destroyed
[The Dark Force]
Professor!
Angkara!
Don't be afraid
They're about to escape
Be careful!
Yay, we're back to school!
Okay, let's go
Because of you
I'm the name of the Dark Force
Don't be stupid
I will punish you all
What is this?
Huh?
Professor!
What did I see?
How can a professor be mentally ill?
I don't know
Because this school must be chanted
So that the professor can enter
Wait
Who chanted this school?
Me
[The Dark Force]
Professor Lebaran
Aldo Baran
Aldo Baran escaped
I will not let Aldo Baran escape
I will not let him escape
When can I see you again?
I miss you so much
Leon
I'm sorry
I can't keep my promise to you
I won't be a burden
I've decided to be one of the teachers
To teach you
The teacher is Agni
Huh? Agni?
This is the story, Leon
Orion!
I'm here to save you
Avantur!
Hey!
What are you doing here?
Catch him!
I've got it, Sir Ling!
[The Dark Force]
How are you?
Who are you?
Why are you here?
I'm here to save you
Here's the drink
[The Dark Force]
Agni betrayed me
He used me to get revenge on you
But he poisoned your teacher
And he poisoned his best friend
His name is Adi Balad
What?
My feet were poisoned?
And?
How are my feet?
Your feet are dead
[The Dark Force]
You have to listen to me, Leon
You have to get revenge, Leon
You have to get revenge on Professor Agni and Professor Adi Balad
Because they all killed your grandfather
[The Dark Force]
Your Highness
Indeed
The Kalung that you have been possessing
Has been poisoned by the evil force
If you keep on possessing it
Then your heart will be possessed by the evil force
I don't want to hear anything else
Your Highness
Actually, I don't want to tell you this either
I don't feel good about you
But if you keep on using it
Then you will become a weak leader
Try it
The queen is getting weaker, right?
Right?
What do you mean?
You said I'm weak?
Yes
Right?
Try it
Weak?
Weak or weak?
You're rude
Your Highness
How about this?
To prove whether the queen is weak or not
We will have a competition
A game of "Nasi Pindang"
A trade on the street
If I win
Then the Kalung will be mine
But if the queen wins
The Kalung will be the queen's
Then the gold and jewelry that I brought to the queen
Will be taken by the queen
And the competition will be decided by the queen
If I refuse
Then I will lose before I even start
Alright
I agree
Good
I hope we win the war
We will win the war
Amen
Then we will have a flying competition
But you will lose
You can't win against my daughter
You can't win
We will have a flying competition
As long as the queen knows
That all the students in the magic school
Are good at flying
Who's afraid?
I've returned the Kalung
And I
Will take back my share
And kick you out of the school
Come on, professor
Don't let him get away
Cut his side, professor
Professor
Finally
My top student is back
Take him away
Take my top student away
I will win
Go
Power
I will cut your head off
Cool
He's like a robot
Professor
Tolik
You're not the one who hugged me
I forgot, professor
Finally, professor is back
We're so happy
You can meet us again
We miss you so much
I'm happy to meet you too
And thank you
For taking care of this school
Especially you, Lata
Thank you
Sir
Where are you, sir?
I want to apologize, sir
I want to explain everything, sir
Sir
Sir, here
Open it
Sir
What are you doing?
This is a punishment for you, Angkara
For betraying me
Sir
Please listen to me, sir
I didn't mean to betray you, sir
You got it all wrong, sir
We're being tricked, sir
I don't believe you anymore, Angkara
You're so good
You're a coward
If you want to punish me
It's okay, sir
I'm willing to do it
Because
I don't know where else to go, sir
If it's not back to you, sir
Sir, Sirsir School has punished me, sir
And
The West has been burning my house
In the whole school, sir
So
I can't go to school anymore, sir
You're a traitor
Yes, sir
Sir, please listen to me, sir
I didn't mean to betray you, sir
Okay, Angkara
I'll give you one more chance
And if you succeed
I'll forgive you
And I'll help you to take that school back
Sir, please
Thank you so much, sir
You're so kind, sir
But if you fail
The punishment will be worse than this
Okay, sir
I promise, sir
This time I won't fail, sir
No one will hear you now!
[music]
Good, Leon! Good!
Finally you understand the lesson I gave you, Leon.
You better be ready now.
Now is your time.
Eda!
Queen Venus is really nice to all of us.
She has given us food,
drinks,
and shelter.
Soon, she will give me her heart.
So sweet!
Guys,
are you sure we can defeat Queen Venus?
That's why
I will train you.
Now, finish all of this food
so you have the strength to train.
Yes, sir! / Yes, sir! / Okay, then.
Guys,
let's go!
Let's go!
I'll go now.
Aren't you going to join us?
No.
Let's go! Let's eat!
Save some for me.
Ready, sir!
[music]
Buy a helmet.
An antique color.
Beautiful ladies.
Hi, sir.
Sir?
This piece of art is divided into two.
How can a handsome man like this
be called sir?
Beautiful ladies,
don't be shy.
You can call me
Megantara's sister,
or Megantara's brother.
But if it's the right one,
call me
A-A Megantara.
Yes, sir.
Can I ask you something?
Here's the thing.
Are you happy
using that wing?
Of course.
This wing can make us fly high and fast.
Wow!
How fast can you fly?
Very fast.
Can I see
how fast you can fly?
For example,
you can fly from here,
to the palace,
and back here.
Can you do that?
Yes, sir.
Here it is.
Stopwatch.
Here's the thing.
When I press the button,
you'll fly.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Why are you still here?
You said you wanted to fly.
Why haven't you flown yet?
When I press the button,
you'll fly.
You've flown.
You're back again.
You flew to the palace,
and then back again.
Only five seconds.
Can you do that?
Kids,
to remind you that
Professor Aldebaran is back,
we'll have a party today.
And all the classes will be canceled.
Yay!
You're smiling.
Kids,
to make this party more complete,
I'll give you a feast
that you'll never refuse.
The brownie!
It's so good!
I want more!
Yum yum.
Let's eat it all.
It's so good.
Sorry, I'm late.
Panji?
Professor Aldebaran,
my favorite teacher.
How are you?
I'm fine, Panji.
It's been a while since we met.
But,
how did you get here?
The kids brought me here.
Come on, please.
Thank you.
(The kids brought me here)
There you go.
Where's my brother?
I think he asked us to go to the toilet.
Right.
Where's my brother?
Let's find him.
Where are you going?
(The kids brought me here)
Where are you from?
I've been looking for you.
You're here.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm doing.
If you're not going to eat,
why are you here?
Let's eat.
No.
I'm not hungry.
You're crying, aren't you?
No, I'm not crying.
You're lying.
It turns out your eyes and mouth are red.
What are you thinking?
You're thinking about your brother, aren't you?
Yes, Vega.
I should be able to hug them now.
I should be able to joke with them.
I should be able to talk to them.
But everything failed.
Because I haven't got the 8th Pangeran blood.
It's okay, Ava.
Be patient.
Maybe you'll get it with your family.
But I'm sure you'll get it.
I'm not strong enough.
Yes.
I'm strong.
This school will be destroyed...
...by Leo.
Mik, Octav, let's go.
Try harder.
Faster.
Erik.
Fija.
Come on.
Show your abilities.
You have to be faster.
Fija, did you hear what the soldiers said?
I heard it.
We have to be faster.
Let's speed up.
(The soldiers are getting tired)
Soldiers.
Let's take a rest.
We're tired.
Yes, soldiers.
I'm so weak.
Take a rest.
You have to keep training.
Because you're still far behind the soldiers.
How much time do we have?
Your time.
Only 15 minutes.
While the soldiers are only 5 seconds behind you.
The difference is still far.
It's not true, soldiers.
We can't win against Venus.
Yes, soldiers.
Please, don't give up.
Remember.
You're the best students.
Don't give up.
You have to keep training until you succeed.
Okay.
If you want to rest, go ahead.
But we'll train again.
I'm going to go now.
Where are you going?
Semedi.
Leon.
This is the school you have to destroy.
You'll be a student here.
And you'll change your identity.
Your name is not Leon.
But Rionelo.
And you have to remember.
You can't use your power.
Especially in front of your enemies.
If they find out, they can do anything to you.
Just like they did to your grandfather.
Do you understand, Leon?
Do you understand, Rionelo?
Yes.
And you, Ankara.
As long as he's in school, you're my friend.
Sir.
I'm not disobeying you.
But I can't go back to school.
Because the school holiday is coming.
Calm down, Ankara.
I have a solution.
Change.
Why am I a hamster?
Now you're in.
Wow, you're right.
By changing into a hamster, I managed to pass this test.
The protection is only for humans named Ankara.
Not a hamster named Ankara.
You're smart.
Okay, I'll change my identity to be a student.
I'm not a hamster.
Why am I out again?
I told you, Ankara.
You're the only one who can get in if you change into a hamster.
Okay, sir.
Good afternoon, kids.
Good afternoon, sir.
Give me a smile.
Welcome to Sekolah Sihir.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Prof. Tintan.
I'm sure you'll be happy to live here.
Because the teachers here are kind, not arrogant...
...and have a high social status.
Just like me.
I swear.
Of course.
What a coincidence, Rio.
You can go to school here.
Ankara.
You're a hamster again.
Yes, sir.
Sekolah Sihir
Soon...
...this school will be destroyed...
...by Leo.
I don't give up.
I have to defeat the hamsters as soon as possible.
I'll try this.
So I can use the magic of rocket fire.
Avivi, rocket funk!
[ROCKET FUNK]
What's the time?
Only 10 minutes.
It's still far from the time of the Hamster.
This is bad.
I'll try...
...the tornado gas pedal.
Torvado gas pedal.
Here it is.
It's still very fast.
Torvado gas pedal.
[TORVADO GAS PEDAL]
It was 10 minutes.
Now it's only 8 minutes.
It's still not enough.
The tornado gas pedal can't be relied on.
The music of the horn can stimulate the adrenaline.
If the adrenaline is high, the speed will be high.
Music of the horn!
50 minutes.
The horn makes it longer.
Stop!
[TORVADO GAS PEDAL]
Now, try to...
...release the energy that you've received from the tornado.
Now, give it to me.
Give it with a smile.
You're a modern hippopotamus.
You're so energetic.
Stop!
You're a modern hippopotamus.
Thank you.
4...
5...
Give it with a smile.
My children...
...now you're all complete...
...so...
...we're going to start the process.
Wait!
[SCREAMING]
It's so fun!
Give it with a smile.
You're a new student, right?
Yes, sir. This is my letter.
But, how is it possible?
It's not correct. I have a tongsis.
That's my letter, right?
Oh, or maybe...
...my factor...
...has been forgotten?
Give it with a smile.
You're so shy, children.
The professor has been affected by the factor U.
Let's try. What's the factor U?
Ready.
No, it's not the right one.
Okay.
Now, follow the professor to the class.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Give this letter...
...to them.
Tell them you're moving from the high school across the country.
I'm sure they won't suspect anything.
As long as you follow the advice...
...they will believe you.
Okay, then.
Follow the professor to the class.
Okay?
Let's go.
Here.
Here he is.
Give it with a smile, professor.
My children.
We're going to meet...
...an important person in this high school.
His name is professor Ati.
So, this is the person who betrayed me.
And if you've met professor Ati and professor Alipar...
...you have to know...
...you have to be able to control your emotions.
Because you're a Syriac...
...as a darkness...
...who is a bad person.
A traitor...
...who is a traitor.
You have to get all their trust.
And after they trust you...
...you...
...you can destroy everything.
Good.
Welcome to Syriac school.
(Syriac school)
So, this is the person who betrayed me.
Men.
I heard that a new student is coming today.
A new student?
The student is a boy?
And he's taller than one?
I hope he's handsome.
Yes.
I heard that...
...you're a boy.
And you're small.
You said handsome.
That's it.
I heard that...
...you and Mr. Tole are really fat.
Yes.
I think he's fat.
He's handsome.
Thank you.
Professor Aldebaran.
The new students are here.
All of you...
...as usual.
According to our tradition.
That every half semester...
...we'll give a chance...
...to talented students from Syriac school.
To learn in the school.
Let's welcome the new students.
Congratulations, Miss.
She's pretty.
She said she wants to eat.
Maybe she's doing yoga.
Students.
I'm Professor Aldebaran.
The headmaster of your school.
So, this is the person who's going to be the new student.
I'll kidnap you both.
Let's go.
Now, it's time for the school's coffee...
...to decide which class you're going to.
First, I'll call Vela.
She's pretty.
She has the same hair as Reika.
You're noisy.
You're loud.
But, you're kind.
Okay.
You're going to Purnama.
Purnama.
Second, I'll call Veli.
He's the same.
He's loud.
He's a loser.
But, he loves his sister.
So, he's going to Purnama.
He's going to Purnama.
And now, it's Rionelo's turn.
To be continued...
What's wrong, Topi? Is there something wrong?
Something's weird.
As far as I know, there's no child named...
...Rionelo.
There's none.
I've tried everything.
But, the speed of a lollipop...
...is not as fast as a winged bird.
How?
Why do we all have two wings?
Two wings are for our balance.
Two wings make our wings stronger.
So, we can fly fast.
Nik, Fica, Oktav, Erik.
What are you doing?
We're relaxing.
Why are you relaxing?
You should be practicing.
How can we win against Queen Venus...
...if you're just relaxing?
You should be practicing.
How?
Nik.
Where's your lollipop?
What are you doing?
We're practicing.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to practice.
Come on.
Go.
Why are you not doing anything?
Are we all going?
Yes, we're all going.
Yes, we're practicing.
No.
I'm going to throw up.
Are you sure?
But, I forgot.
You know, I'm 3,200 years old.
I'm old.
300.
You're smart.
Yes, you're smart.
You're stubborn.
But, you're a bit naughty.
I think you're suitable to go to the orphanage.
Gerhana.
Why Gerhana?
I want to go to the orphanage.
Oh.
You want to go to the orphanage.
Yes.
Alright.
Then, you can go to the orphanage.
Wow.
Maybe, this is related to the eighth prince.
And Angkara.
We can do it.
Now, I've found the way.
How the speed of our lollipop...
can balance and even direct the speed of the wings...
of the queen of Venus.
Look at this.
Let me borrow it.
Use both.
Hey.
Why are you laughing?
What's wrong?
Well, the soldier just used both of them.
Yes, sir.
I'll prove it.
Nick.
Stop forward.
Yes, sir.
One.
One, two, three.
Forward.
Wow.
So fast.
[The Queen of Venus]
Nick.
How much time do you need to count?
Two minutes, sir.
Yes.
Two minutes.
Remember, how much time you need to fly?
15 and 10 minutes.
Now, with two lollipops, we can do it.
Two minutes.
Wait.
I have an idea.
What if we use three lollipops at once?
That's a good idea.
Let's try it.
Come on, Fija.
One, two, three.
Forward.
Yes.
Nick.
How much time do you need to count?
One minute, sir.
Yes.
Two minutes.
Wait.
What if we use four lollipops at once?
Four lollipops.
We have to try it.
Wait.
Give me the lollipop, Fija.
Nick.
How much time do you need to count?
One, two, three.
Forward.
It's so close.
It's like a rocket.
How much time do you need to count?
Five seconds.
We have to do it.
Wait.
What else?
I can do it faster than that.
You can do it faster than five seconds?
Just imagine.
Four lollipops.
It's really fast.
Especially five.
I think it's possible.
Let's try it.
Give me the lollipop.
Here you go.
One, two, three.
Wait.
It's so fast.
That's why.
This is a lesson for you, young man.
Don't be a coward.
Welcome to the first birthday party.
Thank you.
I thought the girls were pretty.
But, it's just like her.
You're talking nonsense.
What if they get offended?
I don't know.
It's true.
Shh.
By the way, who was your name?
I'm Vela.
You and I are Feli.
We're twins.
We're not twins.
What's that?
It's a statue.
What is it?
The statue is similar.
The clothes are similar.
And another thing is...
our beauty is similar.
But, we're twins.
Yes.
By the way, who was your name?
I'm Alva.
Alva.
Alva and Ryu are twins.
Which one do you want?
Which one?
I'll choose Alva.
Okay, I'll choose Ryu.
But, if we get bored, we can switch.
We're not that bored.
Why are you here?
What's that?
This is my pet hamster.
Oh, your pet hamster.
Oh, right.
What's your pet hamster's name?
It's...
Angki.
Oh, Angki.
It's so cute.
It's like a twin.
Be patient, Angkara.
You're just a hamster for a while.
But, you'll get that school back from Albaran.
What are they talking about?
Why are they so excited?
I'll call them.
It's the hamster.
It's okay.
Maybe it's hungry and wants to eat something.
Professor Tita.
Yes, Professor Albaran.
The number of students should be five.
Why are there six now?
Wow, you're smiling, Professor Albaran.
I'm confused, too.
Because the number of students should be five.
Why are there six?
Meanwhile, Rio Nilo...
also brought the official letter.
So, he's also our student.
Are you sure, Professor?
Well...
Maybe...
Maybe, Professor...
Hey, don't smile.
Maybe, Professor Albaran is just like me.
He's suffering from Picon.
So, he forgot to put Rio's name in the letter.
That's how Professor Albaran...
is so...
But, I still feel something's fishy.
Maybe...
he has something to do with the Dark Prince...
and Ankara.
If that's true...
I have to get rid of Rio.
I'm tired of being Professor Albaran.
There's no way out.
I'd better find Professor Ankara...
or the Dark Prince.
This is bad.
Albaran is suspicious.
I have to tell this to the Dark Prince.
Are you okay?
I'm looking for Professor Ankara's voice.
We can do this.
It's quiet.
I'm back to normal.
I hope...
I won't be paralyzed again.
[Ankara]
I'm so tired.
I'm tired.
Faiqa, did you hear that?
What voice?
It's Albaran's voice.
Did you hear that?
I think it's Professor Ankara's voice.
Professor Ankara?
No way.
Professor Albaran has given him protection.
That's true.
But...
But what?
It sounded like Professor Ankara's voice.
Maybe it's just a dream.
I don't know.
Where are you going?
I'm going out for a while.
You guys continue eating.
Okay.
I think he's suspicious.
I think so.
Let's follow him.
Let's go.
You're such a jerk.
I'll call the police.
Let's go.
What did you call me, Ankara?
Sir.
I have an important message for you.
It's about Albaran.
Albaran?
What's wrong, Ankara?
I think...
Albaran is suspicious of Leon.
Because he thinks Leon has something to do with us.
I knew it.
Albaran wouldn't believe that easily.
Then?
What should we do next?
Calm down, Ankara.
I have an idea.
You should do your job as Leon's protector.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
You're such a jerk.
My men.
Come here.
[Leon's men]
I think you know what your job is.
Go to that place.
And make it bigger.
Then, do your job.
Now!
[Leon's men]
A hole.
How could the protector I made be in that hole?
I think someone is trying to open the door.
I have to go home to make sure.
Are you okay?
I think I heard professor Ankara's voice.
No, Ankara couldn't be here.
Because this school is protected by the dust of professor Albaran's house.
I know.
But, why do I hear...
What's that?
Why are you shaking?
Oh, this.
I can't tell Alva about this.
It could be a problem.
It's nothing. It's not important.
Okay, I have to go.
What? Where are you going?
I have something to do at home.
And there's professor Albaran here.
So, I don't have to worry.
Okay, but be careful.
Tell my parents that I miss them.
Even though they're still sleeping.
Just tell them.
Of course.
I'll tell them when I get home.
Oh, right.
I have something for you.
Something?
A map.
Alva.
This is a map for you.
Take it.
This map is your father's.
I hope it's useful.
What's the use of this?
You'll know later.
I have to go.
Hey, wait!
There's a thief!
(Thief)
Why are you here?
Don't you have friends?
Poor you.
Why are you asking that?
Just answer it.
If you don't have friends, join our gang.
I'm trying to accept a new kid like you.
I'm trying to get in touch with you.
But, just so you know, my grandfather is the headmaster of this school.
So, if you want to join us,
you'll be cool, you'll be rich, you'll be famous.
Just join us.
You'll lose if you don't join us.
Right.
I'm not interested in your friends.
A thief!
Help!
What's that?
We got caught!
He's so cool.
But, he's not good at fighting.
He's my friend.
I taught him from my mom.
There's someone!
It hurts!
Why are you so mean?
Be careful!
We got caught!
Riyo, let's go inside.
Riyo, say goodbye to our orphanage.
It's called Purnama Orphanage.
Yes, it's fun here.
And the kids are good.
Yes, if you need anything, just tell us.
Let's go.
To be continued...
What's that?
Our friends are fainted!
Let's help them!
Rina!
Why are you so high?
To be continued...
Go, go, go!
Achieve all your dreams!
Never stop!
Go, go, go!
Fight with all your heart!
Make yourself proud!
Go, go, go!
Let's dream!
We will!