To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
What's this, Prof?
It seems like someone has changed the tool of victory into a tool of displacement
What has that tool moved?
Somewhere else
That we don't know where
I found our professor behind the wall
In the room
Behind the wall?
The prince of darkness and darkness
He even has a heart of gold
Drink that, prince
And get your power
What is this?
The prince!
I don't want to be defeated like my father and mother
Father, mother
Please help me
The prince of darkness and darkness
The prince!
Father, mother
Help me
We will help you, father
The prince of darkness and darkness
All of you want to fight me?
Help me!
Alpha, you better leave this place
Why do you have to help me now?
Father, mother
Hurry, Alpha
We can't hold on any longer
Alpha, only you can save us
You have to jump now
Only you can save the prince of darkness
Let's go, Alpha
Hurry!
Help me, father
Mother
Alpha, help me
[music intensifies]
[yells]
Ugh.
What?
Again, that kid succeeded in you.
Angkara.
How far is the end of this cliff?
I don't know, sir.
But with this high cliff, he shouldn't be safe.
[snores]
Like a soldier.
Where are you going, Vega?
Where are you going, sir?
Wait, I want to ask this telescope.
Oh, Vega.
Don't you see?
The teachers are busy.
It's not good to disturb them.
But you know what's dangerous.
You should be careful.
You're right.
Okay, you want to come with us?
Vita, do you want to come with us?
Okay, let's go.
But what about the teacher?
Just leave him alone.
Let's go.
[music intensifies]
[footsteps]
Why are you still awake?
We can't sleep because we're thinking about Alfa.
Oh, right.
Soldier.
Can you fix this telescope?
The clothes are torn.
The damage is severe.
It can't be fixed.
Professor Purwa.
Is it possible for you to fix this?
That's none of your business.
There's one person who can.
His name is Panji.
He's a magician repairman.
But his place is very far from here.
In the bush.
It's okay, Professor.
Even though it's far,
the important thing is that the telescope can be fixed.
Yes, because we want to find Alfa.
The bush is a dangerous place.
There are ball monsters there.
Ball monsters can turn into anything.
He can absorb your fear.
We're not afraid, Professor.
We'll still fight him.
Because we want to save Alfa.
Right, guys?
Yes.
We're not afraid.
You are true friends.
Friends who are always there when your friends are in trouble.
You are always there when you are happy and sad.
I'm amazed and proud of you.
Professor.
Let me accompany these children.
To go to the bush that is very dangerous.
Don't, Megantara.
I need your help to build this school.
To help the teachers.
Yes.
We don't need an army.
We'll go alone.
The important thing is that we must always be united.
Right, guys?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Professor.
I will train them first.
The mantra to destroy the ball monsters.
Okay.
Rai, Vega, Pelita.
Please pay attention.
As soon as I open this bag.
A monster will come out.
Or something that will scare you.
How to make you not afraid?
It's easy.
Don't have any fear in you.
Understand?
In this lesson.
You must imagine something funny...
...when you see something scary.
You know?
Okay.
Then, recite this mantra.
When you recite this mantra.
Something that scares you will become funny.
Very funny.
And if you laugh, the monster will...
...defeat you.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Good.
First, I will give you a chance.
Rai.
What will you see when you see this?
This ball.
My people.
Why do I have to be afraid?
Rai, don't be afraid. Just attack.
What should I do?
Why are you afraid?
I told you.
Imagine something funny.
What's so hard about that?
Concentrate.
Mr. Medi.
Good, Rai.
Look.
The people of Dangdutan.
There's no Dangdutan monster.
Yes.
I did it.
You did it, Rai.
Good.
Yes.
Very good.
Okay.
The second one.
It's your turn, Fiko.
Yes, sir.
Let's see.
What will come out of this bag?
Professor Purwa.
It's easy. I'm not afraid.
That's good.
Vega.
You're my student.
Good.
You won't pass my class.
I'll make sure of that.
No, Professor Purwa.
I don't want to leave the class.
When Professor Purwa came, you said it's easy.
Now, you're saying it's easy.
Come on.
Concentrate.
You're the smartest student.
You'll answer all the questions.
Yes, Vega.
Yes, sir.
Are you afraid?
You're not afraid of monsters.
You're afraid of the value of money.
Imagine that.
It's funny.
Come on.
Imagine it's funny.
Vega.
Wait.
I'm scared.
I'm a medic.
Vega.
Professor Purwa is a goddess.
Professor Purwa is famous.
He's cruel.
He's teaching.
Now, he's weak.
Like a boneless meat.
You're the best.
Okay.
Next.
You're a good boy.
Come on.
Move forward.
I want to succeed.
Let's open the bag.
What will you be afraid of?
Concentrate.
[Vega, you're a monster.]
[You're a monster.]
You're a monster.
You won't have a friend.
You'd better go there.
You're in my family.
I don't want to.
I don't want to leave my friends.
Pelita.
Don't cry, Pelita.
Concentrate.
Concentrate, Pelita.
Focus. Remember.
Imagine.
It's funny.
Try to remember.
Try to use your dark powers.
Let's go.
Uncle Mendy.
[The Dark Knight]
This is how the dark knights become like this.
What a sick, sick, loose, Jedi.
Just like I said.
For you. Remember.
There's a rat eating rice.
Focus and concentrate.
You'll succeed.
Thank you, soldier.
But remember.
You have to be careful.
And come back safe.
Don't worry.
We'll be safe, soldier.
Rey can make a poem.
Good.
I can do it, soldier.
Pelita.
You can make a poem like Uncle Megantara.
Listen.
That's sweet.
Don't cry. We'll be back safe.
[The Dark Knight]
Good.
The beautiful bird that can see the water.
The most beautiful is Pelita.
[The Dark Knight]
Vega, keep this.
What's this, sir?
That's a magic lamp.
When you're in trouble or lost,
you can turn on the lamp.
And it can bring you back to your school.
Okay, sir.
This is a magic map.
This map will lead you to your destination.
Keep it well.
You three have to be careful and be careful.
Remember.
You have to focus and concentrate.
Vega, this is the map.
Rey, this is the map.
Okay, sir.
We'll go now.
Kids, you have to be careful.
Kids, hurry back.
Sir!
[The Dark Knight]
Vega, can you take Pelita and the lamp?
Okay, sir.
Vega, I'll give it to you.
Where are you going?
I'll give it to you.
[The Dark Knight]
Why are they gone?
I'm jealous.
Look at me.
I'm going to be your team.
Why do I have to be your team?
Hey!
Give it to me.
Okay.
I ran out of it.
I'll fly to the sky.
I'm going to fly to the sky.
[The Dark Knight]
I'm flying.
Hey, I'm flying.
Wait for me, Vega.
Hey, Pelita.
Wait for me.
[The Dark Knight]
Guys, we're going to fly over the forest.
Get ready to fly zigzag.
There are many tall trees.
Okay, sir.
[The Dark Knight]
Why are they flying zigzag?
It's like they're apologizing.
Tole, you have to do it.
There's a car.
Look.
Ouch.
My head is aching.
It hurts.
Help me.
I'm tired.
I have to fight.
Wait for me.
[The Dark Knight]
With these 12 souls...
I will split my soul into 12.
And I will kill...
the ones who dare to challenge me.
[The Dark Knight]
I can change.
Let's go.
Guys.
We're at the swamp forest.
Are you scared, Ray?
No.
I'm not scared.
If I'm scared, why would I follow you?
Let's go.
Wait.
I think we have to split.
I and Vega will go to the right.
You go to the left.
What do you think?
Let's go.
I'm scared.
The forest is so deep.
Ouch.
Vega.
Vlita.
You guys are...
I'm scared.
There are so many of you.
[The Dark Knight]
Where am I?
It's so scary.
This house is so scary.
Maybe...
This house is the darkest.
I have to escape from here.
Ouch. It hurts.
[The Dark Knight]
Thank God you're awake.
Why?
If you don't want to drink, it's okay.
But don't blame me if you're getting weak.
[The Dark Knight]
My blood is not flowing anymore.
That's good.
Then who is it?
Sir, who are you?
And where am I?
This is my house.
I found you in the forest.
And I think you're from a high place.
Yes.
Someone is evil to me.
Wait for me.
I'm coming.
Alfa.
You better get out of here.
No. You have to jump now.
Sir.
Come on, sir.
Hurry, Alfa.
We can't hold it any longer.
That's why I jumped from the cliff.
Where are you from?
I'm from Sihir School.
Do you know the way to Sihir School?
I want to go home.
I'm sorry. I don't know.
I can't help you.
Because I can't leave here.
How about this?
For now, you stay here until you get better.
After you get better, I'll give you a map.
And you can continue your journey home.
Yes, sir.
Just think of this house as your own.
Take what you want.
But I only ask for one thing.
There's a grave next to this house.
With a black door.
You can't go in there without any reason.
Yes, sir.
I promise.
Good.
I'll do as you say.
Who is this guy?
He looks nice.
But why is he living in a house like this?
And there are so many people.
Where are you going?
We can do this.
Hey, guys.
Lita.
How dare you?
You're so stubborn.
I've been waiting for you.
What's that?
Look.
It's my team.
(I'm going to beat you up)
(You're going to get in trouble)
What are you thinking?
Why are you so stubborn?
You're so stubborn.
Come here, Samper.
Come here.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I said, I'm sorry.
You're so stubborn.
You're just a foodie.
It's not that far.
I think I heard someone.
Me too.
But, it can't be Tol.
Maybe it's a trap.
But I'm sure that it's Tol.
I think it's really Tol.
It's true.
Let's go there.
Come on.
Wait.
Wait for me.
I promise.
I'll be back.
I think I heard Tol.
I'll go to bed.
So, I can recover my energy.
Let us go.
Who's that?
Help.
Let us go.
Don't hurt us. Please let us go.
Where are they coming from?
Help.
Let us go.
Don't hurt us. Please let us go.
Where are you going?
Sir.
I heard someone asking for help.
From that door.
Maybe it's just your hallucination.
You should go back to your room.
Get some rest.
Is it just my imagination?
I think I heard someone.
Okay.
I'll go back to my room.
"I'm sorry."
Did you hear that?
Yes, I heard it too.
I think it's coming from that direction.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
You should learn from your mistakes.
You think that's all you can do?
No.
I'm sorry.
Who is that?
Why is Tole so scared?
It must be a ball monster.
Tole, don't cry.
I'm sorry.
Tole, you should focus.
You should focus on that person.
And use your over-medicine.
Come on.
I'm so tired.
I don't want to attack my own mother.
That's not your mother.
That's a ball monster.
Yes, you're right.
You should focus.
And use your over-medicine.
Come on.
Concentrate.
You can do it.
And imagine that your mother is funny.
Come on.
Concentrate.
I'm sorry.
Over-medicine.
My mother is so beautiful.
And funny.
My mother is funny.
Why did you disappear?
Where did you go?
You guys...
You disappeared.
Yes.
What are you doing here?
I...
I'm here to pick you up.
I want to join you.
You're scared of me, right?
You were sleeping last night.
Yes.
You were snoring.
Why?
You woke me up.
So, what are we going to do now?
We're going to Mr. Panji's house.
He can fix our telescope.
The broken one.
Yes, you're right.
Let's go.
I'm bored in my room.
What should I do?
Oh, right.
He helped me.
I should pay him.
But...
What should I do?
Well...
I'm here.
Throw it.
[The next episode]
Javatan, attack the labo.
Yes, I did it.
Javati, Bavaru.
I'm a newbie, right?
[The next episode]
I'm so tired.
Javatan, throw the trash.
Yes.
It's clean.
It looks neat.
It means, the labo is clean.
Help!
Let us go.
Please, let us go.
That voice again.
I think I know that voice.
But, why I don't know?
It looks like they're building another school.
Stop them.
Help!
Let us go.
Please, let us go.
That voice again.
I think I know that voice.
But, why I don't know?
[The next episode]
If I open this door,
he'll be mad.
[The next episode]
Please, don't.
Don't kill me.
Go.
Go away.
That voice again.
I think he's asking for help.
I have to help him.
I'll pay him.
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, sir.
Today, me and the teachers...
will build a school...
that was destroyed by the explosion.
And this school's improvement...
will take time and energy...
from the teachers.
For the next 12 hours,
we will concentrate...
on the school's improvement.
And as long as the process goes on,
it can't be stopped.
We ask you...
to be vigilant.
Always be careful in school.
Watch everything.
Don't let anyone...
get into the school's page.
Do you understand?
We understand, sir.
And while we prepare the energy,
Professor Titan will teach you...
the Totok Mantra...
to fight the bad guys.
You have to focus and concentrate.
We have to fight together...
for our school.
Yes, sir.
What poem do we want to learn, sir?
Hey!
Smile!
We will learn magic...
without using...
a magic wand.
Magic wand?
How can we use a magic wand?
Right? / Yes, sir.
How, sir?
You just found out, right?
Now, keep your magic wands.
All creatures have weak spots.
They are in the neck,
waist,
and toes.
Do you understand?
Hey! Give me a smile.
Come here, Jack.
Try attacking me.
Are you sure, sir?
I'm not hurt. / Just attack me.
Yes, Jack.
Yes, sir.
Sir!
Sir, help me!
Please, open my eyes.
To open the eyes,
you have to press...
one of the cheekbones.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Now, you have to try...
and find your partner.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Now, try to find your partner.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
Sir!
Help me!
You found him!
Sir!
Sir! / Try to press it.
Why can't I do it?
Try to step back.
Let the professor teach you.
Like this, Tommy.
The other one, please.
You, please.
Are you ready?
Let's build our school.
Yes, sir.
It looks like they're building another school, sir.
Stop them, Anggar.
Doctor!
Try to open your eyes.
Hurry!
Let's finish the other one.
What?
Where are you going?
This forest is dangerous.
You better not play here.
We're going to this forest...
to find a resident here.
His name is Mr. Panji. Do you know him?
Yes, I do.
I don't want to be a part of this.
I want to live. Excuse me.
What does he mean?
Why is he going?
I don't know. He's running away.
Let's go, sir.
I'm scared.
Where am I going?
I have to help him.
What's that?
I'm going to lock you up.
Lock her up.
To be continued...
We can do it!
Help!
Professor!
Can I help you for a moment?
Yes, Gantara.
The process of repairing the school has been completed.
If we stop it now, everything will be in vain.
To be continued...
I told you not to come near this cave.
Not to mention opening the door and entering.
But what happened?
You've violated my advice.
And you've violated your own promise.
No.
I heard a voice asking for help.
Actually...
What is it?
That's none of your business.
If there's someone who's hiding there,
that's my business.
That's my business so that people can be safe.
Actually, who are you to hide people like that?
You're probably...
a traitor!
If I'm a traitor, why would I save you?
If you're a traitor, why would I save you?
Whatever! I should go home now.
I should go home now.
The house is haunted.
The monsters are everywhere.
What's that?
Excuse me.
What's wrong with her?
Is this really Mr. Panji's house?
Yes.
I need your help.
Can you fix this telescope?
I can.
But I don't want to fix it.
Now, all of you leave.
Hurry up!
Ghost!
Stop!
Help me!
We have to help him!
But how?
I don't know.
You're stupid.
If I knew this would happen, I wouldn't have helped him.
But luckily, he didn't get in this room.
I have to change the key.
A painting patent.
From now on, if you want to open this door, you have to say the word.
Alfa.
That's the...
This is your food for the day.
I'm hungry.
I've chanted the door...
...with your names.
Please don't kill us.
Help!
We can do it!
Stop!
Guys, we have to help Jack.
We can't leave him.
But how? The monster is too high.
You can fly.
Use the poppy.
Okay.
Get ready.
Fly!
Boss!
Help!
Help us!
Get ready to attack.
Attack!
Help!
Tommy, help Jack!
Jack!
Jack, go!
Jack, come on!
No!
Yes!
Thank you, Boss!
It's too high.
Wait!
Hurry up!
Attack!
We have to get out of here.
Be careful, Nick!
Watch out, Nick!
Help!
Tommy!
Professor!
Can I help Nick for a moment?
Don't be reckless.
We're already focused.
The school is already happening.
But Nick looks injured, Professor.
Don't be reckless.
Nick is a strong kid.
He can handle this.
We have to trust the kids.
We have to be sure.
They can do it.
What's your next plan, Sir?
I want to fight back.
There are people who have destroyed me.
And the first one...
...is you.
What should I do, Sir?
We will do...
...the attack of the missile.
Get ready.
[laughing]
Sir!
What's wrong with him?
He's under attack.
Attack?
What attack?
Judging from his attack,
I think he's under attack by a monster.
Let's go.
Monster?
Don't tell me...
Help!
Is he under attack by a monster?
Yes, he is.
Don't go to the house in the middle of the forest.
The owner is a monster.
Be careful.
Help!
The house in the middle of the forest?
No.
That's his house.
[music]
Guys,
while Reptor is chasing Tommy, Jack, and Mike,
let's attack them from the side.
There are so many people.
That's why we don't have to fight.
What's wrong with you, Sir?
This is for fishing.
Don't eat it.
[music]