To be continued...
Show your spirit, get ready to find friends
Run, run, jump, climb, climb the tower
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams and hopes
Go, go, go, achieve all your dreams
Go, go, go, never stop
Go, go, go, fight with your heart
Go, go, go, make yourself proud
Go, go, go, let's dream
Go, go, go, we can do it
I will make him my son
I will make him proud
Is it true, my teacher?
Alva and Tommy, you have to ride your bike into the forest
And in the forest, you have to catch a ghost
After you catch the ghost, you have to bring it to the finish line
That's Alva, she made me lose my faith in life
I will make her lose
Alva, I'm going right, you go left, let's see who gets the ghost first
Where is the ghost? I can't find it
Where is it?
It's not here
Ouch, who threw the black cloth?
It hurts
Oh, it's you
How are you?
I'm fine
Do you want to surrender yourself, then I will catch you and bring you to the finish line
Do you want to? I need your help
Try to catch me if you can
Oh, you have been taught the ghost mantra
What are you doing, Alva?
Ghost!
That's all? You're so stupid
I'm going up
Where are you going?
I missed
You're so stupid, you can't catch me
Run!
Alva is gone
Ghost!
Ghost, sit behind me
Now I will win
My dad has a life fluid
So if you want to be caught by me, I will give you the life fluid
That's right, this time I want to be caught by you, but the life fluid first
Okay
Tom, is it true that I was given a life fluid?
Yes, you're so stupid, just sit down
I'm sure Alva hasn't caught the ghost yet
I'm sure I will win
My body hurts
I'm in pain
Is it here?
Ghost!
Oh, I tried to save Professor Titan
Where is Professor Titan?
I'm sure he's in the fake Professor Titan's lab
I told Professor Agni
I'm late for Alva and Tom's competition
Professor Agni!
Yes, Vega?
It's so scary
Vega, you didn't watch the competition?
There's something more important than the competition
What is it, Vega?
Professor Titan
What about Professor Titan?
Professor Titan, who has been in our school, is fake
He's the eighth ghost
The eighth ghost?
Yes, Professor
The real Professor Titan is hidden in the closet
I saw it myself, Prof
I even helped Professor Titan
But when I didn't help him, the ghost attacked me again
Are you sure about this, Vega?
Yes, Prof
That's why Professor followed me until we saw it together
Let's go, Prof
Where is the ghost?
How could it just disappear?
I can't see the other ghosts
Raya, where are you?
Raya, don't disappear!
I feel sorry for you, you haven't got the ghost yet
I already got the ghost
I'm going to win now
Bye
Bye, Prof
Don't come in!
That's why you shouldn't tease people
I'll look for the ghost again
So I can win
I'm going to win
You're the one who should be the one to ride the bike, not me
It hurts
You're always angry, that's why it hurts
Let's just rest here
Where is it? I haven't seen it
Where is it?
Let's look for it
Poor Raya
She's so brave
Even though our job is to catch her
She's a ghost
I'm going to catch it
There it is!
Where is it?
You're done, Alva
The ghost is hiding
You won't get the ghost
Here it is
There's a life line!
Raybounty, there's a life line!
Hey!
Alva, where's the life line?
Give it to me
Here it is
Ghost!
I'm going to pull it
You can't go anywhere now
Alva, you lied to me
Let me go
Move!
Let's go inside
Don't, Vega. That's not nice
We should make sure it's true
Professor Titan
Excuse me, Professor Titan
Yes, please come in
Professor!
I'm sorry, Professor
Ahoy!
Smile, everyone
There's a beautiful and talented professor
Professor Agni's presence is not embarrassing
But this is a blessing for me, Professor
Welcome
The flower!
I present this beautiful flower to Professor Agni
Super beautiful
Don't pretend, Grandpa
Where's the real Professor Titan?
Vega, you have to be polite
I'm sorry, Grandpa
This is impossible!
Professor Titan
I'm sorry, Professor
I didn't mean to suspect you
There have been a lot of strange things happening in our school
If I may know, and if you don't mind
May I know what's in that cupboard?
Ahoy!
That cupboard is filled with Centaurus's baby for my experiment, Professor
Liar!
Professor Agni, ask him to open it
Professor, may we see the baby Centaurus?
If you don't mind
Of course not!
I will be ready to make Professor Agni
Let me go, Alva!
He's not Alva
Let me go!
Mommy, I'm going first
How can he hold that?
Hurry up!
Yes, yes, yes, be patient!
Be strong! Get that baby!
Let me go!
Let me go, Alva!
Open the door!
Professor, Centaurus's baby is so cute
Yes
No way! This is impossible!
I saw the real Professor Titan!
This is impossible! I saw it myself!
I even helped him!
Vega, enough!
Let's put the baby there
Centaurus's baby, right?
Right!
I'm sorry, Professor Titan
Maybe Vega is not feeling well
That's why he can make up stories like that
I'm not sick, Professor!
Aha!
You're not sick, Vega!
But you're stressed and nervous
Yes, you're the one who always studies, right?
It's fine! I'm not stressed and nervous!
No, I'm not!
You're lying!
Vega, enough!
Okay, then, Professor
We'll leave now
Yes
Excuse me
Yes, Professor
Professor!
Vega, you're embarrassing me!
I'm not lying, Professor!
I saw it myself!
He's a bad guy! A liar!
And he's a fake!
Enough, Vega!
You're overreacting!
If we do this, it'll be called a slander
Do you understand?
No, Professor
I'm sure that Professor Titan is hiding something from him
Enough, Vega!
You should focus on the competition
You should support Alpha
Because he needs your support
How can I convince Professor Agni?
I'm sure that Professor Titan is hiding somewhere else
I'm sorry, Professor
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I can't give up
I have to prove to Professor Agni
That Professor Titan is a fake
But how?
I know!
I know! I have a book!
Oh no!
There are so many books!
I must have read it for a long time
But it's okay, I can find it
I have to find out where he keeps his book
Let's go
Hi!
Give me a smile
It's him again!
Oh no!
I thought he's not here
He will definitely investigate me
He's the only one who doesn't trust me
Oh no!
The most perfect conspiracy
Maybe this is the book!
There's a most perfect conspiracy
This is a very difficult black magic
Only controlled by a very powerful evil sorcerer
I'm sure this is the book's guide
Yes!
There's only one way to prove it
Which is by using...
The book!
The book flew away!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Come here!
The book!
I'm going to give it to Professor Agni!
Don't go!
The book!
Po-po-party!
Where's the book?
The book!
I'm going to give it to Professor Agni!
The book! Don't go!
Oh no!
The book!
Why is it so heavy?
What is this?
What's wrong, Po-po?
It's not hitting me
Po-po, wait!
I'm going to find out about the spell!
Ouch, it hurts!
Why is it still in the toilet?
I'll give you a smile!
Feel this, Kwek!
I still have a lot of other jobs!
Bye!
The book!
What are you waiting for?
I'm not smart anymore!
I can't do this anymore!
I'm going to kill you!
Get ready, Kwek!
The time will come!
Tom, hurry up!
Tom, help me!
I can't reach it!
Hurry up, Tom!
The time will come!
Help me!
Hurry up!
Ouch!
It's weird!
Why is this place different from the other one?
What's going on?
Ouch!
We can do this!
It's a trap!
Where's Rafa?
This is dangerous!
SOS!
Where is he? Who is he?
Where is he from?
I just got out of the fridge.
Hurry up, Sata!
He's still not here.
I'm getting SOS!
He's dangerous!
He's going to be a bad guy!
What should we do?
Agni, take care of the kids.
Yes, sir.
I'm coming with you!
Hold on!
Everyone is watching the competition.
I'm the king of this place.
Where did he hide the stone?
Here it is.
A very special stone.
I've got the soul stone.
I can destroy this school!
Tommy, what's wrong?
You're the one who made the SOS sign.
Yes, sir.
I made the SOS sign.
Because...
Because the ticket is gone.
And the alpha is gone, too.
I'm going to destroy this school!
We were holding the trophy.
Then, there was a strong wind.
We appeared in another place.
Then, there was a raptor.
It attacked me.
Then, I brought the wind.
And I came back here.
But, the alpha didn't come back here.
That's it, sir.
How could it be?
How did you move the place?
I don't understand, either.
What's this, sir?
It seems like someone changed the trophy...
...into a moving tool.
The tool moved the alpha to another place.
I don't know where it is.
How come Tommy can come back? But, the alpha can't.
It seems like this person just wants the alpha.
That's why he turned Tommy back.
It must be made by Professor Titan.
I think he did this to hurt the alpha.
It's not what you said.
A professor should teach the new students.
So, why did he hurt the alpha?
He just met the alpha.
I'm sure.
There's a fake Professor Titan.
And the real one is hidden in his room.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
He's wearing a shadow.
Actually, he's the Dark Knight.
How could you know that he's the Dark Knight?
Because I saw his shadow in the school mirror.
The Dark Knight
I think you're right, Vega.
He changed the universe...
...with the greatest transformation.
Yes, Professor.
His magic is so powerful.
I poured water on him, but he didn't change.
Maybe, this is the same magic as the one in the army.
The only weakness is the mirror.
I don't know.
You're so naive.
We were taught how to transform by the army.
The only weakness is the mirror.
So, if we look at the mirror, we can see the real one.
I have to check everything.
Yes, Professor. We have to go to school.
We have to ask Professor Titan where he hid the alpha.
Vega.
I'm still smiling.
I've installed all the grenades.
Soon, there will be a huge fire festival here.
The Dark Knight
What's going on?
What's this?
Professor.
Professor, I think someone is attacking our school.
Our school?
We have to evacuate the children.
Yes, Professor.
Vega, run.
Enjoy this mess, Aldebaran.
You're crazy.
Normal.
The Dark Knight
With this blood, my power will be perfect.
And soon, I will rule the world.
The Dark Knight
This is my wife.
Our school is on fire.
We have to go to school.
Where can we go to school?
What if our school is closed?
Jack, don't say that.
What if we can't go to school?
Yes, that's right.
But, that's just a rumor.
Professor Titan.
What's that sound?
Professor Titan, stay away from this wall.
I will destroy it.
Destroy it.
Thank you, Professor Titan.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
We have to get out of here.
Let's go.
Aldebaran.
Professor Titan.
Please, look at me.
I found Professor Titan behind the wall.
In this room.
Behind the wall?
Yes.
The Dark Knight is haunting me.
He even possessed my soul.
So, Vega's story is true.
What do you mean?
Vega told me...
...that Professor Titan is fake.
And the real one is hidden in the closet.
But...
I didn't believe him.
You mean, that girl...
Vega is not lying.
He helped me once.
But the Dark Knight is stronger.
I was captured again.
And Vega was made to faint.
Here we go.
[Vega is now possessed by the Dark Knight]
It's so scary.
I'll kill you.
Take that.
[Vega is now possessed by the Dark Knight]
Why is he gone?
I think he's just after my blood.
No, no.
Hey, wait!
What?
The school is on fire.
Why is there always a problem in this school?
Stop it.
You can't change the situation.
Let's just look for Alva.
What?
What do we look for?
The telescope.
Hello.
The telescope is inside the school.
You want me to go there?
I can burn the telescope.
Hello, you can use your magic.
What about you?
Hurry up.
I got the telescope.
It's a tsunami!
Freeze!
Flow!
Come here.
I'm going to look for Alva.
I haven't opened it yet.
Did you find her?
Not yet.
I'm still concentrating.
No, I'm concentrating.
I think the telescope is broken because of the fire.
And what do we look for at the door?
What do we use?
Raptor.
It's so fast.
How do I follow it?
I have to use another way.
I'm going to use this.
I forgot to turn it on.
Where's the lollipop?
This is good.
I'm going to look for the lollipop.
It's so easy.
There it is!
I found the lollipop.
It's easy to control.
Why did the raptor stop?
I'm going to stop too.
Stop!
The raptor is still alive.
Raptor.
You've done what I told you to do.
You've got Alva's tender.
I've succeeded.
Very good.
A perfect plan.
It's true.
Your plan to turn me into a raptor...
...is amazing.
Angkara!
Yes, sir.
Angkara.
I want you to turn into a raptor.
What for?
The ring I have...
...is now owned by Alva.
And she can't be attacked.
In fact, my attack will turn me back.
That's why I want you to turn into a raptor.
Because that ring...
...won't work...
...if you use my body.
I'm going to turn you into a raptor.
Turn into him.
Yes, sir.
How is my attack, sir?
Good, Angkara.
Perfect.
Raptor.
Go back to your place.
Now...
...take Alva's blood.
But the best part is...
...you turned into Professor Titan.
Everything was easily fooled.
Even Alva.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry.
So, the raptor...
The raptor is Professor Angkara?
A perfect deception.
Even Aldebaran was fooled.
But there's one person who wasn't.
Vega.
But we don't have to worry.
Because no one believes in him.
Even...
...he was blamed by his own teacher.
Professor Titan.
So, Professor Titan is the raptor?
Professor T...
Professor Titan is a raptor?
Then, I was attacked.
What? I woke up from my dream.
Ang...
So, I think...
...Professor Titan has something to do with the dark side.
Vega is right.
But I and Re Tole...
...don't believe in Vega.
I'm mad at Vega.
I'm sorry, Vega.
I don't believe in you anymore.
Actually, I'm more confident...
...that all of this can be avoided.
With this blood.
My power will be perfect.
And soon...
I will rule the world.
What should I do now?
To be continued...
Tara!
Tara, I need your help.
What's wrong?
Help me!
I'm not dead yet!
Professor Titan is here!
Help me!
Fire! Fire! Help me!
How long will this conspiracy last, sir?
Soon, sir.
Soon, the conspiracy will be ready.
And I will get the perfect power.
The unlimited power!
We have to help Mrs. Bertiwi!
But how, Vega?
The fire is too big.
If we go in, we can burn.
Open the gate!
Fire! Fire! Help me!
How?
Sir!
Let us help Mrs. Bertiwi!
But you're tired of being together.
You can't help her.
Let us help her.
Yes, sir. Let us help her.
We're special kids. We want to help.
Okay.
But be careful.
You're just a kid.
I'll help you.
No, don't.
There are three of us.
We might be late. Let's go.
Wait for me.
Bye.
Be careful, sir.
Don't come near me.
What's that?
Help!
Be careful, sir!
They're being attacked.
I'm scared!
Help me!
Calm down.
I'll help Ray and Toleh.
Wait.
Let me and Prof. Titan help Mrs. Bertiwi.
Smile, Prof. Agni.
Leave it to me.
I can handle it myself.
Help me!
Jump, Mrs. Bertiwi!
No!
It's dangerous!
Jump!
I'll catch you from here.
No!
What if my face is burnt?
I'm scared.
If you don't jump, you'll be burnt.
No!
I'm going to be burnt.
It's time.
This conspiracy...
is mixed with a trap.
I can't wait, sir.
I'm here.
Alva!
Give me back the bottle.
How dare you take the bottle from me?
Give it back!
Why not?
It's clear.
This is my tears, sweat, and blood.
So, this is my business.
The point is,
you're chasing me.
I'm not going to let you go.
I won't let you win.
The water is running out!
Why are you disturbing me?
I can't just stand here.
I have to help the dark side.
I'm here.
Help!
Drink it, Hera.
And get the power.
What's that?
Alva.
You're going to lose this time.
Because the dark side...
will soon come to an end.
You're going to lose!
To be continued...
We can do this!
Now...
My power has increased.
The dark side is very strong.
No one can defeat me.
Including you, Alva.
Good luck.
Hey!
Let go of his hand.
So I can help you from below.
Come on, let go of him.
Okay, let's just let him go.
Be careful, the soldiers are catching us.
Okay, let's count to three.
One.
Two.
Three.
He's here.
What's wrong with him?
Thank you, Wikendara.
Thank you, Tindara.
No, help me!
Come on, Doctor. Please, jump!
If you don't, you'll get burned!
What? Jump? Are you crazy?
No, no, no!
Please, pull! Hurry!
Hurry! Jump!
We did it!
It doesn't hurt.
It's amazing!
It's okay, Doctor.
But I'm a bit dizzy.
I'm sorry, Professor!
What happened? Are you okay?
Professor, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Professor?
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry!
The damage is severe.
The soul stone is gone.
Maybe the dark energy took it.
What?
Professor Lodebaran, what about the damage to the school?
Is it severe?
The damage is not a problem.
We can always build this school with the power of magic.
But now, there's a bigger problem.
The Dark Lord has stolen the soul stone from my room.
What?
With the soul stone,
the Dark Lord will be hard to defeat.
He can split his soul into 12 parts...
and put each part in a different place.
Because of that, he will be very hard to defeat.
Unless we can destroy all 12 parts of the stone.
Evil power!
What's that?
[POWER UP]
Now, I will split you into 12 parts.
It's useless, Alva.
This ring has no effect on me now.
Because my power now...
is much greater.
What's that?
It's a whip!
[POWER UP]
How's that?
Do you want to see?
Fire!
[POWER UP]
Get ready, Alva.
I... I have to survive.
I don't want to be defeated like my parents.
Dad... Mom...
Please help me.
[MUSIC]
With these 12 souls,
I will divide my soul into 12.
And I'm sure,
the survivors will have a hard time facing me.
[MUSIC]
Huh?
It's a ghost.
So, it's a ghost.
Help!
Let us go!
That voice again.
[MUSIC]
Show your spirit,
get ready to find your friends.
Run, jump, jump,
and conquer the stars.
Be brave,
don't give up.
Chase your dreams and hopes.
Go, go, go,
reach all your dreams.
never stop.
Go, go, go,
fight with your heart.
make yourself proud.
Go, go, go,
let's do it, we can do it.