To be continued...
Heart's strength
Go, go, go
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can do it
Alva, why did you take that stone?
Professor Agni asked me to
Because this school is in danger
Only that stone can save this school
Three days from now
He will get unlimited power
And will destroy this world
You are expelled from school
What is this?
Where am I?
Maybe they want me to follow them
Don't move
To be continued...
I'm running away!
Why are you guys here?
Come on, hurry up!
I'm sorry, Alva. I don't trust you anymore.
To be continued...
Alright, if you're still mad at me, it's fate.
Because I was wrong.
To be continued...
No, I'm not mad.
Are you serious?
Yes.
You're my friend, right?
To be continued...
Alva.
We believe that you're innocent.
That's why we prevent you from leaving.
Then, I want to get out of here.
I can still go to school, right?
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Unfortunately, only the three of us believe in you.
So, you're still expelled from school.
That's why we have to do this.
We have to clear your name so you can go to school again.
But, how?
The way is...
we have to catch the person who took the stone.
That's right!
Yeah, that's right!
The person who slandered you.
The Dark Lord, right?
Not the Dark Lord.
But the person ordered by the Dark Lord.
This person's magic is very powerful, Alva.
That's why...
I will train the three of you...
so you can fight him.
Especially you, Alva.
The Dark Lord's Revenge
That's so cool!
Vega.
Take that stone.
Then, throw it at me.
But...
Hurry!
Throw it as hard as you can.
Now, try my magic.
Okay, Dark Lord.
Revenge!
Rey.
Throw Alva with the apple.
Really, Dark Lord?
Come on, Rey.
Let's test Alva's magic.
Alva.
The magic you made is still too thin.
It's not thick enough.
You have to concentrate more...
in reading my magic.
Come on.
Try it again.
Okay.
I'll try again.
Throw it as hard as you can.
Sorry, bro.
I think...
this is enough for today.
We'll continue later.
No, no.
No, Dark Lord.
I still want to try again.
I have to keep practicing until I can.
Don't, Alva.
You're too tired.
If you force yourself,
it can be dangerous for you.
Come on, Rey.
Come on.
Where are you taking me?
Alva.
You have to stay here.
We have to leave here...
because we'll be searched.
Okay?
Alva.
If anything happens,
just say my name three times.
But if you don't show up,
just run away.
At least,
there's still someone who trusts me.
Um...
I'm sorry.
Thank you...
for helping me.
We're happy to help you too.
Right, girls?
Yippee!
The dragon fruit,
the slush fruit,
I also want to say...
thank you...
for helping me.
There's another one!
Attack!
To Be Continued...
It's so quiet...
without Vega and Rey.
I have to practice...
so that I can...
To Be Continued...
Ouch.
It hurts.
I can't give up.
Go, go, go!
Be proud of yourself!
Let's dream!
Go, go, go!
We'll make it!
To Be Continued...
You guys...
What?
You have to act faster...
before it's too late.
Don't let the dragon fruit...
fall to the ground.
Yes.
I'm looking for that person.
Remember,
don't look for anyone...
other than the dragon fruit.
Maybe you don't know what's inside,
but what's inside...
is not the dragon fruit.
You have to choose carefully.
Stop!
Why do I always dream about them?
But they're right.
I have to stop the darkness...
from getting that stone.
I have to keep practicing.
Police!
Stop!
Drink that!
Drink it!
Drink!
Drink that!
Drink it!
What a hero!
Hooray!
Yeah!
We did it!
Well done, Afan!
Perfect!
That means...
now...
you can do your research.
Yes!
Now, let's make Agni sad.
Agreed.
Let's not make him sad.
You do it, Afan.
Huh?
You will interrogate Professor Agni...
by pretending to be Professor Adebaran.
Huh?
Hooray!
Here's the interrogation.
With this interrogation, you can become Professor Adebaran.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I've followed everything in the book.
Prove it.
I want to see the result.
Okay.
I'll prove it.
All of it.
Where is it?
What?
Now, stand on this cloth.
Huh?
Wow.
That's so cool.
Now, I'm Professor Adebaran.
But, how do we do the interrogation?
There's only one way.
You can't get wet.
If you get wet, you will become your original self.
Right, Dara?
Yes.
That's right.
Remember the rules.
Come in.
Professor Adebaran?
Good afternoon, ma'am.
I mean, Professor.
What is it, Professor?
Is there anything important that made you come to my office?
I came here to ask you...
if you have any questions.
What is it that made you come to my office?
I'm studying self-defense right now.
I need your help to attack me.
Attack you?
Yes.
You tried to attack me with a strong mantra.
I fainted.
That mantra is called...
Meriamfang Mantra.
And it's a black magic.
I've never learned that magic,
and I can't do it either.
Ouch.
My hand suddenly hurts, Prof.
Let me try, Professor.
Ouch, it hurts, Prof. Let me try.
You don't have a ring?
Where's the ring, Prof?
You don't wear a ring.
I've never worn a ring.
I'm sorry, Prof.
Let me help you.
Oh, God.
I forgot.
I can't get wet.
I have to get out of here.
Prof.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
It's a thin blanket.
Professor, you said you needed my help.
It's okay.
Professor!
Professor Purwa.
Alva.
You've been expelled from this school.
Why are you still here?
Sabin's ring.
So, Professor Purwa did it.
The professor who took the ring.
How dare you kill me like that?
Now, come with me.
We're going to face Professor Aldebaran.
You have to leave this school.
Let's go.
How dare you fight me?
Alva.
Where are you?
Professor.
Alva.
Where do you think you're going?
Get out.
Alva.
You can't run anymore, Alva.
Stay there.
What's that?
Where is he?
He was here.
I think Professor Purwa can't see me.
Is it because of this ring?
Alva.
It's true. He can't see me.
We can do it.
Alva, where are you?
It's been a long time.
I want to sleep.
It hurts.
Alva.
What are you doing, Rey?
Why are you fighting?
What did I do to you?
Don't pretend.
Who's pretending?
Stop it.
You've been fighting.
It's noisy.
Calm down.
It's more comfortable.
It's more safe.
Gosh.
Both of you are mad.
How dare you hit my ears?
Here, Tendara.
Stop it.
No, Tendara.
Stop fighting.
Alva.
When did you come?
Because I'm wearing this.
Try it.
If we wear it, we won't be seen.
This is a magic wand.
Where did you get this?
Suddenly, this wand fell from the sky.
When I was chased, Prof. Purwa was locked in a labyrinth.
Thanks to this wand, I'm safe.
I know who stole the stone.
Who?
Prof. Purwa.
He's a man wearing a cow's moon ring.
He's the one who chased me until I fainted.
And he took the stone.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I saw him wearing the ring.
I'm sure.
He must be the culprit.
Don't say anything if there's no evidence.
That's why we have to guard Prof. Purwa's office.
Who knows, the stone is hidden there.
Prof. Purwa's office
We have to hurry.
Don't make noise.
We'll be caught.
Can you be quiet?
Yes.
Don't make noise.
Let's look for him.
Prof. Purwa's office
Let's walk slowly to the door.
Then, we'll run away.
I'm scared.
Stop!
Prof. Purwa's office
Where's the stone?
Prof. Langkara?
Thank you for saving us.
Kids, come to my house.
I want to talk to you.
Yes.
I know Prof. Purwa is the culprit.
He took the stone.
That's why we have to guard his office.
Why?
Because there's a hole in the stone.
We have to hide it.
Kids, what you've done is dangerous.
I'll try again.
Remember.
Next time, you have to be careful.
If you want to do research,
you have to plan it carefully.
And don't make a mistake.
Okay?
Yes, Prof.
You can go now.
Let's go.
Prof. Purwa's office
What's going on?
Don't pretend.
You did it, didn't you?
Answer me.
What do you mean, Purwa?
Fine.
I'll make you understand what I mean.
What's this?
It's nothing, Professor.
I just want to make sure that Prof. Langkara...
The enemy is right in front of us.
We should unite.
Not split up.
You're right, Professor.
The enemy is right in front of us.
I'll prove that I'm right.
Just wait and see.
Tomorrow is a holy month.
And we haven't found the stone yet.
We have to keep an eye on Professor Purwa.
Tomorrow, he'll go to school to give the stone...
...to the Dark Lord.
So, we have to follow him.
Not us.
But me.
But it's impossible, Alva.
You can't do it alone.
It's dangerous.
Hold on.
If you and Rey go with me...
...the teachers will be suspicious.
I'm the only one who can sneak out...
...without being suspicious.
Because everyone knows...
...that I've been expelled from school.
Alva, wait.
We're friends.
No matter what happens, we have to be together.
Hold on, Rey.
Please, listen to me.
You've helped me a lot.
And now, I have to solve this myself.
This is all my fault.
I took the stone.
And now, I have to get it back.
Alva.
Enough, Rey.
Professor Agni.
Lead all the children to gather at the playground.
Tonight, we have to pray for the safety of the school.
Hurry up.
Don't let the Stone of Eternity...
...be given to the Dark Lord.
To be continued...
Why are there two professors?
This way.
Let's go.
GAUNTER
One of them must be using a transformation spell.
You can't reach the water.
If you don't reach the water,
you'll become a monster.
Water.
I have to find water.
Where's the water?
There it is.
It's here.
Get it.
GAUNTER
Alva.
Don't push Alva.
She's in danger.
What are you talking about?
You're the bad guy.
I'm here to pray for Alva.
Alva.
What do you think?
Who do you trust the most?
You have three minutes...
to clean this page.
I'm working with Professor Ankara.
Good, Alva.
Help me attack him.
Let's attack him together.
GAUNTER
You're a coward.
You don't deserve to be in this school.
GAUNTER
Alva, help me!
Alva, stay there!
GAUNTER
I'm sorry, Professor.
But I won't let anyone disturb my mission.
To take the Stone of Eternity.
Why are you surprised, Alva?
Yes.
I'm the culprit.
Professor!
GAUNTER
I took the Stone of Eternity...
to give it to the 8th Prince.
So...
I hypnotized Professor Agni...
by using Professor Turung's body...
so I could make Alva take the Stone of Eternity.
Alva...
Then I protected you and your friends...
so you could trust me...
and suspect Professor Purwa.
And I conspired with Professor Agni...
to take the Stone of Eternity easily.
GAUNTER
And lastly...
I used your life again, Purwa...
to defeat you.
GAUNTER
I swear...
the 8th Prince will rise again.
His power will recover...
and you will all be destroyed.
The destruction of this school...
will begin with you.
But...
the first one I will destroy is you.
GAUNTER
Alva...
are you sure you want to fight me?
The power you have...
is nothing compared to the power I have.
Don't be mean.
I won't let you hurt anyone.
GAUNTER
I give up!
In that case...
I will destroy you both.
GAUNTER
Professor Aldebaran?
I'm here to help you.
GAUNTER
Forgive me, Professor Purwa.
I have wrongly accused you.
Your actions are very reckless, Alva.
You could have been killed.
GAUNTER
Attention, everyone.
Please listen to this important news.
As you know,
the Stone of Eternity has been stolen.
But now,
I'm happy to inform you that...
the thief has been caught.
GAUNTER
Now,
I will call a child...
who has helped us find the thief.
Alva!
GAUNTER
And from now on,
the school has decided...
that Alva...
will not be allowed to leave the school.
And even...
the school will give Alva a medal...
for everything she has done.
Alva!
Congratulations, Alva.
Thank you, Professor.
Alva! Alva! Alva!
Follow your dreams
Go! Go! Go!
Achieve your dreams
Never stop
Go! Go! Go!
Fight with all your heart
Make yourself proud
Go! Go! Go!
Let's dream
We can do it
Go! Go! Go!
Achieve your dreams
Never stop
Go! Go! Go!