To be continued...
The power of the heart
Go, go, go
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can do it
Why was he accepted at a magic school?
Three days until the full moon
And what if in the full moon
The dark lord gets his stone
He will get unlimited power
And will destroy this world
I will prove that I'm right
Just wait and see
I will not let anyone disturb my mission
To take the stone to eternity
And from now on
The school has decided
If Alva is not expelled from the school
Congratulations
Let's eat together
Let's eat
Don't sleep
It's hot
Okay
Why are you shaking?
I got a pimple
If it's a pimple, it's a pimple
I'm scared
My food will be eaten by Kharizan
No, it's a pimple
Really?
Yes, there will be a pimple there
Hurry up
The toilet is down there
The toilet is still far away
There's a lake
I will go to the lake
I want to meet the guards
Alvaro!
Let me go!
You will regret it
Because you have caught me
And don't you think
The Dark Lord won't wake up
Because you have caught me
Terror won't end here
And in the end
You will lose
This school
Will collapse
Let me go!
Watch him
Yes, sir
Let me go!
Don't let the students hear his scream
Yes, sir
Let me go!
Alvaro!
Students
Now I will teach you
How to destroy the enemy's weapons
Pay close attention
Weapon blast
Now it's time for you to practice
Try Ray and...
Tole?
Where's Tole?
I haven't seen Tole since yesterday
I don't know where Tole is
What should we do?
Professor Adni
I'm sorry, I have to interrupt
Students
I've told you a thousand times
Gorilla is a coward
Dream of a giraffe
If you want to be a child, don't be a coward
Throw the leftovers in the trash
Who did this?
Huh?
Pee
Who did this?
Hey, Alva
Don't tell me that's Metal Chicken
That's right
Now he's a chicken
Because he's afraid of being eaten
Megantara
Where did you get that chicken from?
Near the lake
He swallowed it
And then he ate it with Boya
Here, Karim
This is a gift for your birthday
Why is it only for flowers?
Thank you, Nick
You're welcome, Karim
Nick, Nick
Why did you do that to Boya?
I don't know
I'm sorry
Iì´ï¿½ a
It's okay
I'm sorry
I won't do it again
I didn't mean to
I won't hurt her
I won't move on
I won't do it again
I didn't mean to
I'm so sorry
I'm sorry
Come back
You pig
Seriously
It's not right
Are you strong enough?
Is it in your head?
You're too frail
Evro
I'm your good kid
Don't you have feet?
Okay
Oh
Don't be an ouch boy
It hurt
I'm sorry
Understood
Finally
Take the ball
and throw it
Yes, sir
Come on, Danang
Follow me
I have to go back to Danang
Who knows
If I can save Tole
I can be a champion like Alva
Hey, don't run
Come back to me
Don't give up, Sarin
Run, Sarin
Don't come close, Sarin
Don't come close
Come back to me
And this is our savior this time, Rey
Who saved Tole and Karin from the attack of...
Rey, hold this
Where's Rey?
Where is she?
That's Rey
Why is she there?
She's not far
Wait, wait
Something's not right
Rey doesn't look like this
Let's follow her
Maybe she has something on her mind
Let's go
I can't be afraid
Because I'm going to be the champion
But...
I don't know what the enemy looks like
What if the dog is fierce?
What if I get bitten?
What are you guys doing here?
We're going to the lake
We're going to beat up the guy who kidnapped your friend
Tolek
He's your good friend
Good friend?
I'm sorry
We're not good friends
We just want to be heroes
We don't care about your friend's fate
You're just like me
I want to be a hero too
What if we go there together?
Let's go
Where is he?
I don't know
Maybe he's in the lake
We have to find him
Let's go
Where are you guys going?
All students are ordered to stay in their respective dormitories
Come back or I'll give you a punishment
Yes
What are you guys doing in the lake?
We're going to beat up the guy who kidnapped your friend
Tolek
He's your good friend
We're not good friends
We just want to be heroes
We don't care about your friend's fate
You're just like me
We have to find him
Let's go
Where are you guys going?
We're going to beat up the guy who kidnapped your friend
Karim?
He's my friend
Wake up
Where am I?
I don't know either
I'm sure we're being escaped by Duyung
Mom, Dad
I'm scared
Tolek
Where are you going?
I'm sorry, I got scared
It's so scary
We don't have anyone left
We're all alone
Wake up
If Duyung doesn't show up
Let's go fishing
Then we'll catch him
What do we do if Duyung doesn't show up?
Yes
Someone has to swim to catch him
Please, Tolek
I can't swim
You know I can't swim
Don't tempt me
I don't feel good
Yes, Tom
I can't
Don't try it
This is it
If you want to lose, you have to swim to the middle
I can't swim
Hurry up, Dandrink
I'll go with you
If something happens to me
My mom will be mad
Do you want to be expelled from this school?
Yes, Tom
Let's go to the middle
It means one of you has to swim
Yes
Two more
It means you and Ray have to swim
Who will lose?
Me
You have to swim to the middle
Yes, I don't want to
You have to
Jacky can't swim
He's already wet
Don't try it
Hurry up, Dandrink
You have to go to the middle
You have to swim to the middle
You want to be expelled, don't you?
Hurry up
Hurry up, Ray
Don't go too far
Go to the middle, Ray
Hurry up, Ray
Help me, guys
Attack
Help
Help me
Do you think
It's easy to defeat Duyung?
Do you think you're great?
Because of your actions
Some students have to be treated in the treatment clinic
If there's a serious problem
This school can be closed
What do you want?
No, sir
Now
You all go back to the dormitory
And no one is allowed to leave the school
Without any reason
And without exception
Understand?
Understand, ma'am
All of you, I will punish you
To clean the school toilet
Without magic
What are you doing?
Have you changed your mind?
Now I want to talk to Professor Alubaran
I'll go with you, professor
Let's go
I'm sure
Duyung is just a prisoner
It seems like there's a bigger power
Controlling them
I agree
Duyung is a good person
Good
They kidnapped the students
And hurt the students
That's right, professor
Nine of them are injured
And three of them are missing
And if the parents find out
This school can be closed
In my opinion
We have to take action against Duyung
I disagree
Duyung is a good person
If we don't take action against Duyung
There will be more victims
We have to take action
Now
I agree
Get the doll
Change
Duyung
Professor
Let's attack
Let's go
Attack
Help
Dad, it hurts
Dad
Stop the attack
They can hurt the students
Duyung
We should be able to defeat Duyung
But we can't do anything
They kidnapped Karin, Tole and Ray
I give up
We have to help them
They are so stubborn
They don't want to listen
I miss Duyung
There must be a reason
Soldier
Why are you so surprised?
What's wrong?
Do you know Ray was kidnapped by Putri Duyung?
Yes, I know
We want to talk to Ray
Do you know what's wrong with Putri Duyung?
I don't know
But Putri Angsa might know
Let's go
What?
Where are you going?
We want to find Putri Angsa
Ouch
Alpha, I'm going to call Angsa
Hide, Angsa doesn't like men
Putri Angsa
What's wrong, Angsa?
What's wrong, Vega?
Can we help you?
Here's the thing, Angsa
Duyung is attacking us
And my friends are being attacked by Duyung
I want to help Angsa
As far as I know, Duyung is a good person
Really?
But why are they attacking my friends?
I don't know
But as far as I know, Duyung doesn't like to attack people
He prefers to have sex
And if they have sex, it can last for hours
Is it true, girls?
It's true
We got the answer, Vega
Duyung doesn't like to have sex
So, we have to make them have sex
There's a man
Help
Alpha, don't go out
He doesn't like men
They're so fierce
Let's stop playing
We're almost there
Let's go
Jofreka!
Get the mirror!
Get the needle!
Jofreka!
If you want to be free, answer my question first!
You're our friend, why do you have to help them?
It's so late, Beka.
We'll meet them again tomorrow.
Let's go.
Hey!
We'll meet them again tomorrow.
If you want to be free, answer my question first.
Let's go.
What's that sound?
Let's check it out, Mike.
Let's go.
That's Duyung!
Yes.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Yes.
That's perfect, Mike.
If we take him to the cave,
we can be hunters.
Yes, bro.
We can be more famous than Tommy.
That's right.
Let's go.
It's so heavy, Duyung.
Just stay still.
It's heavy.
Where is he?
Why are you two being chased by the devil?
It's not like that, boss.
We just attacked Duyung.
Both of you went to the lake?
No, boss.
Duyung is at the back of the school.
Are you serious?
Yes, boss.
That's why it's so dangerous.
We have to get out of this school.
I'll call my dad first.
Okay.
Where are they?
There must be something.
He's bleeding.
We have to help him.
Why is he running away?
I don't know.
Maybe he's afraid of us.
Okay, Vega.
Hurry up and give him the mirror.
So, he'll calm down.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Mirror.
We're late.
Medicine.
Here, Vega.
That's rude.
They're friends with Duyung.
Maybe they're the ones who planned the terror at school.
I have to report this.
He's smiling.
That means he's not angry anymore.
Yes.
Maybe he knows that we're going to cure his face.
I think he wants to kiss you.
Putri Duyung.
We're friends now, right?
Answer me.
Where are my friends?
I got it.
What is this for?
To eat.
What is this, Vega?
I've read it in a book.
The mirror from Duyung...
...can make the person who eats it...
...breathe underwater.
Wow.
That's cool.
Vega.
It feels weird.
Yes.
But we can breathe underwater now, right?
To be continued...
You're in jail.
They're in the pool.
Don't.
You have to attack my friends.
So?
Where are our friends?
You don't want to tell me?
Where are you taking us?
To be continued...
Vega.
Wake up, Vega.
Wake up.
Vega.
Duyung.
Why did you buy soap?
Because of you.
Let's take Vega to the clinic.
Hurry.
Hold Tara.
Come on.
To be continued...
Dr. Pertiwi.
Where's Dr. Pertiwi?
Why are you here?
I need Dr. Pertiwi.
Dr. Pertiwi ran away.
Why did he run away?
Professor Adebaran told him to go to the village across...
...to cure people's illness.
So, I'm the one who's responsible.
Okay.
Okay, that's enough.
Now, please, Vega.
He's under the spell of Professor Purwa.
Oh, no.
It's Purwa.
I can't do that.
I mean Professor Purwa.
Mom.
Do we need to call Purwa?
Like when we cure Ray?
I don't think so.
I think...
...it's worse.
It's worse.
So, what do we do?
He has to use the spell.
Now, the spell is gone.
What do we do?
Vega.
Wait for me.
I'll find water for you.
Duyung.
I and my husband...
...don't want to hear any excuses.
And now, I'm going to bring my beloved son, Tommy...
...to the village.
Because I think...
...it's not safe here anymore.
Right, Tommy?
Right, honey?
Sir.
Mike and I want to go with you.
Come on, sir.
Let's go.
Sure.
I've prepared the boat.
Duyung, you can't ask him to come.
I won't stop you...
...if you want to bring your son home.
And I, as the head of the school...
...apologize...
...for all the inconveniences...
...that your son and mother had.
And I will try to solve this problem as soon as possible.
Think, guys!
Tommy!
Think!
Vega!
I'm sorry, sir.
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Alva.
How's Vega?
Well, sir.
I want to tell you...
...that the only way to save Vega...
...is to use Duyung's Air Mata.
Duyung's Air Mata?
Okay, Alva.
Let's go find Duyung's Air Mata...
...so that Vega can be saved.
Come on.
Alva, let me call Duyung.
No, sir.
Duyung will be scared.
Let me do it.
Putri Duyung!
Where are you?
I need your help!
Putri Duyung!
Putri Duyung.
Vega is still unconscious...
...because of the ancient sorcery.
They say the sorcery is your Air Mata.
Can I ask for your Air Mata for Vega?
Java, hold on tight!
Alva, put it here.
Thank you, Putri Duyung.
You're so kind.
Putri Duyung!
Who did that?
I did it.
What do you want?
It's none of your business.
You should go now...
...and bring your friend's Air Mata.
Now!
Java, you should bring the Air Mata.
Poor Vega.
I'll make sure...
...Putri Duyung will be fine.
Go now.
I'm sorry, Putri Duyung.
I have to go now.
But I'll help you.
Roll the dice.
Putri Duyung.
I've been cured, Vega!
I've been cured!
I was bewitched by Professor Purwa.
What happened to Duyung?
He ran away.
Thank God.
But he came back.
Why?
Because the only way to make you aware...
...is Air Mata Duyung.
He came back...
...just to help me.
Yes.
Because he came back...
...he was caught by Professor Purwa.
We have to help him.
I don't want him to get caught.
Let's go.
I managed to catch Duyung.
And now we can interrogate him...
...to find out where the students are.
Come, I'll show you.
It's so good.
Let's go home, honey.
Luckily, you came here quickly.
Otherwise, we could've kidnapped Duyung.
Right, Tommy?
Alva and Vega will be kidnapped by Duyung soon.
What's going on?
Tommy, help me!
Tommy!
What's going on?
Mike? Jack?
Tommy?
Why is he here?
I don't know.
Let me go!
Open the door!
He's going to be kidnapped!
You're so cruel, Jack!
Let me go!
Two more kids.
Then your task will be done.
And I will return your voice.
Remember.
One of those kids...
must be named Alva.
Alva.
That voice is so familiar.
Yeah, I feel like I know him.
But who is he?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's so weird.
Why does that person know Alva?
Who is he?
Alva.
You're wrong if you think I always lose.
I never lose, Alva.
I will never lose.
Where did he go?
Aldebaran.
Terror will continue.
Until I get the chosen one.
Everyone will attack the dungeon.
We can do it.
Now, tell me where the students are hiding.
Answer me.
Answer me!
Don't joke!
I will kill you!
Calm down.
Come in.
Get out, professor.
Out!
Let's go.
Tommy.
My son.
He's been kidnapped.
Tommy.
Tommy, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What happened?
Something happened.
A huge wave.
Suddenly, a paradigm appeared.
It pulled Tommy and his friends to the sea.
Tommy.
That's why we're here.
To ask for your help.
We have to find the paradigm and destroy the castle.
I agree.
Let's attack the paradigm.
They're too much.
I disagree.
Actually, Duyung is a good person.
Megantara is right.
The proof is, he wants to give his treasure to Vega.
If Duyung is a good person,
why did they kidnap the students?
I agree.
I will help them.
There must be something forcing them to do that.
Megantara.
If you're afraid, you can stay here.
But you're too slow.
Everyone, get ready.
Let's go.
Your friends have kidnapped the students.
We won't stay still.
We will attack your castle to free the students.
Do you see where Duyung is going?
To the sea.
Everyone wants to attack Duyung's castle.
Alva, let's go to the sea.
Okay.
Alva.
Megantara.
Why are the students in danger?
Wait.
You're wrong.
Duyung is a good person.
They're evil.
Professor Purwo.
Did you hear what Alva said?
Yes.
I think we should stop this attack.
Instead of doing stupid things and endangering people.
No.
I have to find my students.
And I have to get revenge on Duyung.
Because he's my enemy.
Alva must have been brainwashed by Duyung.
What should we do?
We're late, Vega.
Let's just follow them.
Alva.
Vega.
What are you doing?
You can swim.
You can attack.
Palm trees.
Turquoise trees.
You can't attack.
You can only attack.
But we don't have a choice.
We don't want to hurt Duyung.
We'll use this method.
This is the method.
Javatang.
Bevebaju.
Beverenang.
That's cool.
By using this, we can breathe and talk inside.
Okay.
Ready.
One, two, three.
That's where Duyung's palace is.
Let's call them.
Hi, Duyung.
Come out.
We've kidnapped one of your friends.
If you don't come out and surrender...
...we'll kill you.
...we'll kill your friend.
Why aren't they showing up?
Calm down.
We'll wait a little longer.
They'll show up sooner or later.
Be ready.
You're being used as bait.
You're a bait.
Alva, it's dangerous.
We don't have a choice.
No, Mama.
I'm scared. We're all scared.
And hungry.
Karim!
I'll open it.
Shut up.
Remember this.
If you dare to do anything...
...I'll make sure you become a fish.
To be continued...