To be continued...
The power of heart
Go Go Go
Make your proud
Let's dream
Go Go Go
We can do it
What are you dreaming?
Barga is a strong monster
He is the hand of the dark
He can beat him
Who is he?
Alpha
Tonight
Before the sun goes down
You have to go back to the secret room
And take the stone of eternity for me
Ouch
What are you doing there?
When will you kill me?
Ouch
Why did you realize that?
You fainted
I did faint
But because you hit me
I got hurt
Let me cast a spell
Dangdut Dafang
Why is it so hot?
It's because you casted the wrong spell
Dafang Tanduk
This is the right one
Come on
Dafang
Dangdut
How do I catch it?
Dafang
Dangdut
Oh my God!
I can't stand it anymore!
What kind of poison is this?
This is poison from the Three-Headed Dragon.
What? Three-Headed Dragon?
Oh my God!
The Three-Headed Dragon's poison hasn't been cured yet.
You better go to Megantara now.
What do you mean?
I mean Captain Megantara.
Because he's the guardian of Megantara, the dragon.
Hurry!
Okay, I'll go to Megantara now.
Go, go, go!
Megantara
Oh my God!
I need to concentrate.
Now, by listening to this, I can know what's behind it.
Dafang!
Megantara
The Myth
Here!
Tentara!
Ouch!
Tentara, wake up!
Burung Kutilang Burung Parkit
Because of you, the roasted chicken lost a sore butt
Please, Tentara, help me!
I'm Tentara
I got hit by a three-headed dragon
And then, Dr. Pertiwi doesn't have a cure
That's why I'm asking for help
What's the story?
Why did he enter the forbidden room?
Because we want to take...
We?
You mean, not just Shireya?
Yes
Explain
Who are we?
We are...
Me, Rey...
And Alfa
Alfa?
Alfa is looking for trouble
Ouch!
Tentara, Alfa is not wrong
He went in there...
Just to take the stone from you
Come...
Alfa...
Tentara, where are you going?
Tentara, Tentara!
What's wrong, Tentara?
Tentara, where are those angels?
They are not angels
But they are...
Angel girls
Angel girls?
Yes
Angel girls
See?
They turned into beautiful girls
Vega, now it's your turn
You have to approach them
You have to figure out a way to get them to the clinic
To cure Rey
Why me, Tentara?
I already know you
Just call me Tentara
Here's the problem
They are...
Unlikable creatures
And masculine creatures
Like me
Especially if I'm handsome
They will be allergic
Enough
Don't think too much
Do you want to cure Rey?
Come here
Hey, who are you?
Are you the one who called us here?
Yes, I am
Because I really need your help
My friend is a three-headed dragon
Only you can cure my friend
Why do we have to help you?
We don't even know you
Come on
Please
I promise
I will do whatever you want
Please
That's right
You can do whatever you want
Yes
Okay
If you want to do whatever we want
You have to make us happy and laugh
But how?
Think about it
We haven't laughed for a long time
Right, girls?
That's right
It won't take long
I'll count to three
If not, we'll leave
How?
One
Two
Enough
Wait
Follow me
I'll make you laugh
That's right
I can do it
Trust me
Come on
Let's go
Sorry, Tentara
Men!
I'm not a man
How are you?
You said you're tired of men
What are you waiting for?
Beat him up
Don't
Attack
What are you doing?
Don't
Yes
He's gone
I've made you laugh
Now, help my friend
What are you doing?
Yes
Quick
We are
Yes
Yes, yes
We are
Yes
Thank you
It's nothing
So now, please tell me
Why are you in that room?
Here's the thing
Alva said
This school is in danger
And she needs that stone to save the school
If not, many lives will be in danger
This is so annoying
Alva doesn't need that stone
What is she doing?
I don't know
Alva is in danger
What are you doing?
What are you doing in there?
Alva
How is it, Alva?
Yes, Ma'am. I got the stone
Excuse me
What are you doing in there?
Help!
Alva fainted!
Sir!
For the next two hours, your voice will change into the voice of an animal
To be continued...
Goodbye, Ma'am
What do you mean, Alva?
I managed to get the stone
And I gave it to the professor
I never told you to do that
Alva, why did you take that stone?
Professor Agni asked me to
Because this school is in danger
Only that stone can save this school
Alva, I never asked you to take that stone
But last afternoon, Professor Agni asked me to take the Stone of Eternity
No, Alva. I never asked you to take that stone
Professor, the Stone of Eternity has...
The Three Headed Dragon, they all fainted
The Three Headed Dragon
Alva, how did you know all of this?
Professor Agni, Professor Agni told me
And Professor Agni also told me about the food of the Three Headed Dragon
Alva, I never and never asked you to do all of that
Yes, Professor
Alva, it's time for you to go back to your dorm
But, Professor, I really gave the stone to Professor Agni
And after that, I don't know what happened
I think someone followed me until I fainted
I never received anything from you, Alva
That's impossible, Professor. I can't be lying
Listen, Alva. The stone can't save this school
On the contrary, if the stone falls on your head,
this school will be in danger
For example, the Dark Prince
The Dark Prince?
Who is he?
You shouldn't be hearing this name
And you don't need to know who he is
He's the son of a witch, a thief, a thief
He's the son of a witch, a thief, and a thief
Enough. Now, go back to your dorm
I'm sorry, Professor
This time, you're really naughty, Alva
You went into the room, took the stone, and the stone was gone
And you lied again when you were asked by Professor Agni
But, Tentara, I'm not lying
I don't believe it
How can you believe it?
Professor Agni has been a teacher at this school for decades, Alva
So, it's impossible for him to be lying
But, I'm telling the truth, Tentara. I'm not lying
I'm not lying
Tentara, who is the Dark Prince?
The Dark Prince?
It's not time for you to know, Alva
Clearly, the Dark Prince is very dangerous, Alva
Not a single person expects him to come back
Rey, you've recovered
Rey, I know everything
You took the Stone of Kabadian
And you lied
You said Professor Agni asked you to do it
But, you didn't
Now, you're denying it
Is it true or not?
No, Rey. It's a lie
I gave the Stone of Kabadian to Professor Agni
And suddenly, someone took it from me
And I don't know what happened
Someone took it from me
Really? But, I don't believe it
Vega, you don't believe me either
Alright, if you don't believe me, it's okay
I'll prove it to you later
If what I said is true
He's the one who's angry
I should be the one who's angry
I defended him until he got poisoned
But, he's just a victim of the PHP
I don't think he's wrong, Rey
What do you mean? Professor Agni lied?
He's a liar
Hey, guys
You've heard that Alva is a thief
She stole the Stone of Kabadian
How can a thief be allowed to enter this school?
It turns out that Klepto doesn't know shame
He's already a thief, but he still dares to show up here
Hey, guys
It's not fun if there's a thief in our school
I have an idea
We have to make a petition, guys
What do you think? Do you agree?
Agree
Petition? No way
By the time, they are taken to the school
It's very unlikely that they can find Bung Sapiens
But, maybe we can find your plan
Let's be smart, guys
You disappointed the parents
Dear God, it's our chance
We shouldn't be careless
Wow, there are a lot of signs
If this continues, Malik will be expelled from this school
Do you know, guys?
Dasar Malik, Dasar Malik, Dasar Malik
Kava, let's go
Rai, what are you doing?
Come here
You are the reason why Alva got expelled
Alva betrayed us
Rai, Alva is a good person
He saved me from the bad guys
A good person like Alva can't do that
I'm sure that he is trapped now
Come on, a rat can't be trapped
Alva, listen to me
I don't want to be poisoned
If you want to help Alva, go there
I want to sleep
Rai!
Alva said that she was trapped in front of the forbidden room
I think I need to investigate that room
Maybe there are some evidence left there
Alva!
Alva, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Ouch, it hurts
Hey, don't go there!
Why is this room sealed now?
It wasn't like this before
Yes, because Alva entered this room yesterday
And this is a very forbidden room
That's why this room is sealed with a spell
So that no one can enter
And you, don't go there
I don't want to see you
And you, don't ever try to enter this room
Do you understand?
I'll go now
If you don't use the spell,
I'm sure you can open it with a spell
I have to find a spell to open this seal
Alva!
Now no one believes me
Tentara, Rey, and Vega
They think I'm lying
But I don't have any evidence
And I don't know where the bodyguards are
Hi, bro
Why are you smiling?
Do you believe me?
Yes
Here, a candy from me
Take it
One for you, one for me
Thank you
You're welcome
Let's open it
Is it good?
It's not good
It's good
Why is your voice like this?
It's so funny
What I gave you is a voice changer
So for the next two hours,
your voice will change into an animal's voice
That's a lesson, who's that?
You're expelled from school
We're expelled
Don't ever say a spell in front of a mirror
Because the spell will come back to you
For that, there's a spell you can use
You have to say this spell
Before you say the spell you want to say
Repeat after me
Javangan Panto
One more time
Alva
Why don't you repeat the spell?
Do you think you're smart enough?
Why are you so quiet, Alva?
Come on, repeat the spell
Javangan Panto
You rejected me, Alva
Shut up!
You've gone too far, Alva
For that, I will punish you
Javangan Panto
I'm sorry
Attention, everyone
All teachers gather in the classroom
Javangan Panto
What is it that needs to be discussed?
Until I have to leave my class
What steps should we take against Alva?
I don't think it needs to be discussed
Alva must be expelled
Javangan Panto
Expelling a student from school
Can't be done easily
But, Professor
What Alva has done
Is out of bounds
If we don't expel her
We will be protested by the parents
It's too soon
The full moon is in three days
And if in the full moon
The Dark Lord gets the Stone of Eternity
He will get an unlimited power
That will destroy this world
And all of that will happen because of Alva
Professor
During the break
Some of the students
Gave me this petition
The petition states
That all the students in this school
Agree to expel Alva from this school
It seems
We have no other choice, Professor
Alva must be expelled from this school
Megantara
Call Alva
Tell her to come here
Luckily my voice is back
If not
Professor Aldebaran will be mad
Megantara
Why did you call me?
Good morning, Professor
The words you will hear
Won't be pleasant to the ears
But you have to listen
Why, Professor?
You are expelled from this school
Now
Get your things ready
Tomorrow morning the school guard will bring you to the dance
I'm done talking
You can go now
Goodbye, Professor
Goodbye
Professor
Rolf
Did Alva
Really take the stone?
No
The child didn't do anything wrong
If it wasn't Alva
Does it mean Professor Aldebaran
No
Agni is not lying
Something happened
And we have to find out
What really happened
Rey
Professor Aldebaran just called me
You don't want to know
I got a punishment from Professor Aldebaran
It's all my fault
I lied
Rey
Rey, come here
Help me
To find the mantra to open the seal
Okay
Do you want to read?
No, I'm fine
I came here for a refreshing
Not to read a book
You don't want to know, you have to help me
Dufuduk
I want to read a book
The last mantra
Reyka
Stop it
I'm so sleepy
Let go of the mantra
You can sleep later
But after I read the mantra
I'm so tired
Yay, I got the mantra
Yay, I can sleep
Amen
I just remembered
The ring
The ring of the moon
But it's useless
You were taken out
What's wrong?
The ring of the moon
Yes, I did it
Why did you go there?
Because I'm scared
There was a kid who was bewitched
And fainted here
Don't attack Alva
Oh my god, my head
Don't ask anything to my mother
I don't want to tell you anything
Understand?
But you have to tell me, who attacked Alva?
At first, there was Professor Agni
Professor Agni?
Then, this place was so smoky
So, I didn't see who attacked the kid
But he attacked with magic
He must have a great power
I want to go to the other farm
It's scary here
At least, now I know
Alva is not wrong
Where are you going?
Wait, wait
Where's Alva?
Have you seen Alva?
Alva?
Alva was taken out of the school
What?
Yes
Now, she's at home
What?
She can sleep here?
Yes, why?
Ri, Ri, wake up
Ri, Ri, Ri
Alva, Ri, Ri
Alva was taken out of the school
Ri, come on
Alva was taken out
Come on, let's ask the teacher
Come on, hurry up
Yes
The news you heard is true
Now, Alva is being taken to the lake by the school principal
It's my fault
I was mean to Alva
She wanted to tell me about the punishment
I didn't want to listen
You're too much
You're so insensitive
Everyone says that
Even though she's pretty, she's not sensitive
Why?
But, Tentara
Alva is not wrong
We have to make her go back to this school
But, we don't have any proof
You're talking nonsense
There can't be any proof
But, we have to investigate this together
Besides, Alva is Tentara's friend
How can Tentara see her own friend who's not wrong
But, she's being punished
Alva, get on this boat
This boat will take you back
Let's go back
All three of you
I will make sure that you won't see Vega again
But, if you don't
I don't care
They hate me
What's that?
You've been expelled from this school
Why are you still here?
Sabine's ring
Do you know who stole the stone?
Who?
Professor Tuluak
I will prove that I'm right
Just wait and see
Run!
Don't let Abadian's stone
Be given to the next generation
There are two Professor Tuluak
Hey, hey, hey
Show your spirit, get ready
Buddy, buddy, buddy
Run, jump, climb
Star, star, star
Be brave, don't give up
Chase your dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with your heart
Be proud of yourself
Go, go, go
Let's dream
We are sure