To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
Let us go!
Please, let us go!
I'll destroy you!
I've told you not to come near the lock,
not to open the lock,
not to enter the dungeon.
But what happened?
You've violated my advice,
and you've violated your own promise!
Please.
Please don't kill us.
Please, Feywon.
From now on,
if you want to open this door,
you have to tell me.
Alva.
I want to avenge...
the people who destroyed me.
And the first one...
Banji.
To be continued...
What's that?
Stop it!
Let's just go.
We won't win.
Let's just give up.
No, we can't give up.
The future of the school is in our hands.
We have to unite with the monster.
I'm so scared.
The monster is so big and sharp.
I have to be careful.
Let's just leave it.
You want to?
Then, just give it up.
Alright.
Let's go somewhere else.
Let's go.
The monster is so fierce.
How can I defeat it?
Let's just leave it.
Don't think about them.
Let's focus on defeating the monster.
Okay?
Let's go!
The monster is so fierce.
How can I defeat it?
Let's just leave it.
We have to focus on defeating the monster.
We have to defeat the monster.
Let's go!
The monster is so fierce.
How can I defeat it?
Let's just stay here.
Instead of going to Onyol.
I agree.
Okay.
I know that voice.
Me too.
What are you doing?
Sana, push!
I have done some attacks.
And I'm sure...
...that people will be more curious about you.
Good, Sana.
Keep an eye on Panji.
And wait.
Until the time comes...
...you attack him.
Let's go there.
Yes.
Where is the scary face?
The scary house?
I want to fix the telescope.
Whatever it takes...
...we have to go back there...
...and take his heart.
Why do you want to be chased again?
Just look at his face. I'm tired of it.
That's why we have to make him happy.
So, we don't get chased.
So, what should we do?
I know what to do.
What is it?
We have to protect him.
We have to cook something good for him.
So, he'll be nice to us.
I want to do that too.
Me too.
Let's go.
Come on.
Catch him.
I want to feed him.
Come on. I want to feed him.
For Panji.
Hurry up.
So, we can kill him.
I'm scared.
We'll get revenge.
It's been a long time.
Yes.
Let's catch the chicken.
It's been a long time.
Yes.
Chicken.
We got it.
Guys.
While Raptor is chasing Tommy, Jake, and Mike.
Let's attack them from the side.
Remember.
We only have one slogan.
Die once, wait a thousand.
If someone falls, replace him.
Don't give up.
Keep your spirit up.
Okay?
Let's go.
The next day.
Sasa.
Who is this?
We're fighting.
That's why you shouldn't be arrogant.
What's wrong with you, Fiko?
Why are you so arrogant?
I know that this is for Panji.
So, I'm going to feed you.
I'm hungry.
I want chicken.
But, I'm hungry.
I don't know.
What should I do?
Firi.
The next day.
Gosh.
We're in trouble.
It's a disaster.
The next day.
Try to go up a little bit.
Higher.
I can't.
The skin of the raptor...
is not like a human.
The skin of the raptor is very hard.
So, it can't be weakened just by tongs.
Then, what should we do?
Order my men to use the magic spell.
They have mastered it.
Nik, fight them with the magic spell.
Yes, sir.
The magic spell.
Yes.
We did it.
You're great, sir.
Megantara.
Yes.
What's the matter, Professor?
What are you?
If I can't catch your tongs,
our school will be destroyed.
Gosh.
Ouch.
I'm sorry, Professor.
It's my pleasure.
Take it back.
Of course.
Your tongs are nothing.
Oh, yes.
You're right.
Come on, everyone.
Let's concentrate.
Our school is almost done.
Yes, sir.
Let's go, everyone.
Our school is done.
Yes.
It's all because of us.
Because we distracted the monster.
So, they chased us.
Yes, that's why, everyone.
Thank us.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Is there a phone number?
Here.
We made food for you.
Sir.
Since when did I marry your aunt?
I'm going home.
I don't like chicken.
I'm going to dance.
Sir.
Are you serious?
I don't want to.
Just make it for me.
Wait.
Make it for me.
Just for me.
No.
Don't.
I'm dizzy.
I'm scared.
I don't want to dance.
Just make it for me.
Those naughty kids.
They're so naughty.
Rita.
If he's a vegetarian, it means it's easier for him to find food.
I agree.
Okay.
Here.
Turn left.
Turn right.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to miss you.
What else?
Ta-da.
We made food for Mr. Vegetarian.
Yes.
Do you think I'm going to feed you?
That's enough.
Get out of here.
I'm not hungry.
Do you understand?
Get out.
He said he's a vegetarian.
I don't want to.
I don't know.
Let's go home.
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
I just want to go home.
If you say you want to go home, I'll turn you into chicken.
What should we do?
Wait.
He said he's a vegetarian.
Let's do something else.
What should we do?
Who is it?
Come here.
Okay.
Now, they won't bother me anymore.
So, I can sleep peacefully.
Excuse me.
To be continued...
We can do it!
How is it?
Do you still feel it?
I can't stop smiling.
Kids.
Yes, sir.
Don't bother me!
Watch out if they bother me again.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry because I got mad at them.
I ran out of food.
Forget it.
Let's go shopping.
I haven't gone out for a while.
To be continued...
Ray, don't give up.
This is for our friend, Alva.
I won't give up for Alva.
Don't be like that.
Datur, it's Alva.
What's wrong with him?
Let's help him.
We don't have to help him.
He doesn't even have our scope.
We can't do that, Ray.
This is for humanity.
If someone is in trouble, we have to help them.
Let's go.
To be continued...
I can't stay here.
Everyone will be afraid of me.
To be continued...
Look at that.
It's Medi.
To be continued...
What's wrong?
Thank you.
You're a good boy.
Okay.
I'll invite you to dinner at my house.
I'll fix your telescope.
Yes!
Those kids again.
Why are they here?
Sya!
Let's go.
Uncle.
Wait, Ray.
Why are you afraid of the moon?
Because it's big.
You're scary.
But I'm afraid of the moon.
Can you be quiet?
To be continued...
I just remembered.
I forgot something.
I'll help you later.
Ray.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
But don't expect us to help you again.
We don't like scary kids.
Okay.
To be continued...
I'll fix your telescope.
Really?
Yes!
What are you doing?
Because it's big.
But I want you to do one thing.
Don't go anywhere.
Stay here.
And none of you can go to that cave.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Tuli, wake up!
We're so scared.
He didn't tell us.
That cave is so scary.
It's so big.
I'm scared.
Omel, you're useless.
It's better to fix your telescope now.
It's better than nothing.
That's right.
Don't do that, Omel.
Just be patient.
I hope you can fix it soon.
That's all I know.
Yes.
Help!
I want to go home.
Let's go home.
I'm scared.
How?
Can you fix it?
Nothing can't be fixed.
It's done.
Thank you, Om.
Thank you.
You're so nice.
I'm leaving.
Thank you, Om.
Thank you.
Yes!
Bye, Om.
Open it!
Thank you, Om.
Let's go!
My friends, wake up!
Pati, Pati!
Yes, Pati.
Thank you.
Yay!
Yes, the telescope is right!
I can find Alva!
Yes!
Hey!
You!
Stop following us!
I'm sorry.
I was too excited.
The telescope is right.
Where's Tole?
Oh, right.
He's still unconscious.
Let's go inside.
No.
You go alone.
Or you go with Plita?
I don't want to.
Fine.
I'll go alone.
Help!
Ouch!
Tole!
It hurts!
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
You're the one who left me.
I almost got stabbed.
Don't be angry.
Calm down.
At least you're safe.
Let's go help Alva.
Let's go.
That's Alva!
Alva is near here.
She's in the village clinic.
Yes!
I want to see her!
Me too!
Me first!
Don't fight.
The telescope.
Let's look for Alva.
Let's go.
Ouch!
It hurts.
I'm sure it's Panji's doing.
Panji has a monster.
Yes.
It's Panji.
You don't have any feelings.
Okay.
Let's do this at Panji's house.
I want to see Alva!
You don't have any feelings.
You guys?
Why are you here?
We're looking for you.
Let's go home.
Come here.
We can go back to school.
Come on, Alva.
What's wrong, Alva?
I don't know.
I still have something to do.
What is it?
It's none of your business.
Do you know why?
Yes.
I want to decorate Panji's house.
Panji's house?
Panji's house.
Why do you want to go there again?
It's a scary house.
It's scary.
Are you from there?
Yes.
We repaired this telescope.
It was broken.
Why did you repair it?
It's haunted.
I want to know who it belongs to.
Here, wear this.
Okay.
I hope it's not a ghost.
It's not here yet.
Let's try here.
It's broken.
It's broken again.
Let's repair this at Panji's house.
I want to go there.
Don't.
I don't want to go there.
I want to go there by myself.
I'm scared.
I want to go there.
I know.
But, I don't trust Sandra.
They keep asking for help.
Look at them.
They're attacked by Panji's monsters.
I feel sorry for them.
I want to go to Panji's house.
Do you want to come?
If you don't want to come, it's okay.
I'll go there by myself.
It's okay.
I'll go with you.
Me too.
Okay.
You want to come too, right?
We're friends.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Zing!
Why are they there?
I have a plan.
What is it?
Sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
I can make Panji appear in front of the people.
If he appears in front of the people...
...he'll be fired, sir.
You're an idiot, Angkara.
Why didn't you do what I told you?
But, sir...
Shut up!
I don't want to ruin all of my plans.
We'll wait until the full moon.
Because that's the right time for us to do it.
Tonight is the night of the full moon.
I have to hide.
I can't go out.
Because I don't want to hurt anyone.
I'm sorry, sir.
Excuse me.
Who is this?
What are you doing here?
Sir.
The telescope is broken.
Can you fix it?
Come here.
This is what makes me angry.
Wait.
It's safe.
It's okay.
Why is it so dark?
It's easy to get in.
There.
Why can't I do it?
Go upstairs.
Why is there a password?
You're wrong.
Remember.
If you're wrong three times, you'll be blocked.
You're blocked.
I can't tell anyone.
Sir.
Tentot.
You're wrong again.
I'm wrong again.
What's the password?
Last chance.
15 seconds left.
I just saw you here.
What's your name?
If you're wrong, you'll be blocked.
What's my name?
Why is it open?
You said the password.
Please come in.
So, what's the password?
That's it.
This can't be fixed.
It's badly damaged.
Here.
You can go home now.
I still have things to do.
It hurts.
We're so tired.
Can we stay here for a while?
My leg hurts.
Let's stay here.
Let's promise not to make any noise.
Okay.
That's...
Dad.
Mom.
Wake up.
Dad.
Dad, wake up.
Mom.
Wake up.
Dad.
Dad, wake up.
Mom.
Wake up.
How can he breathe?
So, they're still alive.
Dad, wake up.
Mom.
Mom, wake up.
Wake up.
Mom.
Dad.
Dad, wake up.
Wake up.
Dad.
So...
...they're just here for fun.
My dad is so stubborn.
Now, my dad is being punished.
I have to let him go.
Uncle Ancol.
Mom, what's wrong?
Dad.
Mom.
To be continued...
Someone broke into the cave.
I don't know what to do.
Let's hide.
No.
We have to help him.
Let's go.
Mom.
Dad.
Stop.
What did you do?
You can't free them this way.
But, you killed them.
They can't get out of here.
I just want to free my parents.
Go.
Get out of here.
You don't have to know.
I'll kill you if you leave.
No.
Who are you?
You're the one who kidnapped my parents.
Your parents?
You said, your parents?
Don't be ridiculous.
No, I'm not.
I'm Alfa.
And they're my parents.
You're Alfa.
Yes, I'm Alfa.
They're my parents.
Why did you kidnap them?
Alfa.
You have to listen to me.
Wait.
I'll explain.
The truth.
Don't be ridiculous.
This is bad.
This is bad. I'm going to change.
Alfa.
You have to leave.
You too.
Now.
Now, you have to leave.
No.
I want to go.
Don't be ridiculous.
Both of you have to leave.
You're possessed.
Bebiksa.
Alfa.
Where is he?
Maybe he's gone.
Maybe.
It's time to attack.
Alfa.
You have to let them go.
Don't touch them.
If we let them go, they'll faint.
They can't breathe.
Let's look for him.
He's the only one who knows how to do it.
Let's go.
He's over there.
Mr. Panji.
What should we do?
He's not here.
Mr. Panji.
Where is he?
Don't.
He ran away.
Let's go back to school.
We'll tell the teachers about this.
Yes.
Then, we'll come back here.
No.
I don't want to.
If we go back there,
maybe my parents are gone.
Where's the telescope?
Here.
But,
the telescope is broken.
It can't be used anymore.
It's totally broken.
We can't fix it.
Maybe there's a clue.
Let's try.
Where is it?
There's a sound.
Why is there a sound?
I don't know.
Maybe,
he didn't show it to us.
But, he tried to point it out.
Maybe it's because of the sound.
That's impossible.
That's not possible.
The telescope is broken.
There's nothing wrong with trying.
You know it.
Where's the telescope?
I don't know.
I'm scared.
It's scary.
No.
I'm not scared.
I'm brave.
I'll find my dad.
Please, help me.
Please, take care of my parents.
I'll be back.
No.
The monster is back.
It's broken.
He's not brave.
I'm scared.
Let's go in.
Where is it?
There it is.
Let's try again.
It's behind us.
Kill them all.
Don't let them escape.
Yes, sir.
Change the target.
Attack them all.
Yes, sir.
Kill them all.
Don't let them escape.
Yes, sir.
Hurry.
Where is my dad?
I have to find him immediately
I have to find my dad
Because
I have to save both of them for me
There's a raptor too
Professor Antara
I've defeated you once, Panci
What?
The kid is still alive?
Agar!
Hurry and finish that kid and that animal
Hurry!
I want to see that kid
Agar!
Hurry!
Why isn't Asma here yet?
Don't!
What is it now?
Don't tell anyone
Okay
It's better if Asma doesn't come back
Let's just follow him
To the cave
I'm tired
I'm exhausted
Let's just wait
Don't!
What's inside?
Let me go!
Don't torture me!
Don't!
Don't be noisy!
You're so noisy!
Let me go!
I want to see the kid
Don't do that
I want to see the animal
Let me go!
Fireball!
Now, this is the time!
Now, I can save you, Panji.
Where are you, Alva?
Are you scared?
Oh, poor you.
That's right.
Because your power is not as strong as mine.
Where are you, Alva?
Who's scared?
You're new, right?
You're back, right?
But I have to finish you first, Panji.
She's gone.
You're confused, right?
There's no Purwosongkara.
This must be Alva's trick.
Alva, get out!
What are you doing?
Angkara!
How dare you attack me, Angkara?
I'm sorry, sir. It's nothing, sir.
What's wrong with the old man?
You've ruined them.
Answer me!
Don't be angry, sir.
You'll be in trouble later.
Shut up!
You must be angry.
Right?
Right, Angkara?
Answer me!
I told you to shut up.
Alva, get out!
He's shocked.
To be continued...
But how, professor?
Meanwhile, we know...
that the 8th prince...
has recovered.
In fact...
he's getting stronger.
The only way...
is to find the soul stone.
Find the soul stone.
Alright.
Professor.
Allow me to find it.
Don't, Megantara.
This mission is too dangerous.
And I don't want to involve the children.
We don't need to involve the children.
It's better...
if I...
and the other professors...
will go on this mission.
That's the problem, Megantara.
Whether we want to or not...
we have to involve the children.
Because the soul stone...
is filled by the 8th prince's soul.
It can only be seen by the children.
To be continued...
I'm going to throw up.
Let's go.
Wait!
What's that?
I don't know.
I'm sure it's Alva.
Alva, where are you?
Alva!
Alva, come out!
You scared me.
Alva, I'm going to look for...
the soul stone.
I'm going home with Gugug.
That's not Gugug.
That's Serigala.
Alva, what are you doing with Serigala?
Where are you from?
I'm from Suram.
I saw a raptor attacking Serigala.
Raptor?
Yes, a raptor.
It's a creature from Angkara.
It attacked Serigala and fainted.
If Serigala lost...
why did you bring it here?
Are you going to cure it?
Come on.
This is not about Serigala.
Then?
Papa Anji!
Papa Anji?
Yes, he's hiding in Serigala.
Serigala is so cute.
Rita, don't be scared.
I'll give you a name, Serigala.
It's called...
Pleki.
Rita, why Pleki?
Pleki is a raptor's name.
Be careful.
Rita, don't!
Wake up.
Let's play.
Sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
I promise...
I'll do my best, sir.
Sir.
Very well.
I'll give you one more chance.
But don't fail.
We don't have much time.
We only have six hours...
before the sun sets.
And I don't want...
Serigala to turn into a rat.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
I'm ready.
Why did you call me?
I want you...
to come to my house.
Everyone!
Don't hesitate to attack the child.
They attack everything.
They are evil.
No.
That's a lie.
They are evil.
Dad.
Mom.
To be continued...