To be continued...
The power of the heart
Go, go, go
Proud of yourself
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can definitely do it
We don't have much time
We have to destroy the crystal ball
Because if the crystal ball is full
That means the energy of the children has been taken
Then the children can die
Muthiara
This is all because of the curse of the 8th prince
Muthiara has leaked where the children are now
Starting tomorrow, you will have a mid-semester vacation
And you will do a field trip to Sihir village not far from the school
I just got the news
If the children from Sihir school will start their tourism to Sihir village
And I feel
We can attack Alva there
This time I don't want to fail again
It turns out that the curse is true
The plan has come
We will all be affected by the curse of the monster
He's right
What did the people mean?
What is the legendary monster?
Go back, go back
Be quiet all
As students of Sihir school
You all can't be afraid
What if we become a stone?
Calm down children
We will definitely find out what has happened
Megantara
It's better if you take the children out of here now
And don't let a single child fly
Okay
Tavan
Bafinda
Children
Let's go to Sihir village
We have to be together
And don't let anyone go
Do you understand?
Yes, sir
Let's go
We have to tell Professor Libaran about this incident
Yes, sir
Good afternoon, Professor Aldebaran
Something terrible has happened here
When Nick wanted to report to the galaxy village
Suddenly he turned into a stone
Nick turned into a stone
Who did that?
We don't know, sir
It all happened so suddenly
But now all the children have been taken to Megantara
Okay, you all keep an eye on the students
And keep an eye on them
I will go there with Mr. Tiwi
To treat Nick
Okay, sir
Stop
Stop, stop, stop
Why did you suddenly stop?
What's the problem?
Does it hurt?
Megantara
We can't go inside this village
What?
Is there anything that can stop us?
Oh no
Luckily I didn't go in there
If I didn't, I would have been burnt
What really happened to this village?
Mr. Lura
For a child who experienced something like this
What should we do?
In this village
There is a lake that water can cure all kinds of diseases
Who knows
It can ward off this curse
Okay, thank you, Mr. Lura
I will go to the lake right away
Please keep an eye on the children
Okay
Be careful, Megantara
Be careful
There is a lightning
Don't worry
Megantara
Will come back
Stop, Megantara
Megantara
Don't cross this gate
Professor Aldebaran
Concentrate, Megantara
Look slowly
Professor
Who instigated this horrible magic in this gate?
I don't know either, Megantara
Obviously
You can't leave this village
And we can't enter the village
But Professor Aldebaran
I have to look for a lake outside this village
Because the lake water
Can restore Nick as he lost
There is another way, Megantara
In this village forest
There is still a mushroom that can cure the curse
Why are you looking for that mushroom now?
If in three hours
The child can't be bought a mushroom
Then he will be a stone forever
Professor
In the forest there are millions of mushrooms
Which mushroom can cure the curse here?
The mushroom is different from the others
The head is below
The position is upside down
It's fast
Okay, I will look for that mushroom
By using the Davatang Mantra
Wait, wait, wait
You can't do that
Don't use magic
The strength of the mushroom will be reduced
It's better to use
Your hands
Remember, don't use magic
And one more thing, Megantara
You have to stay calm
Don't show your weakness in front of the children
If they get scared
They will run to this gate
And endanger them
Yes, Professor
Soldiers
Where are the soldiers?
Yes, that's medicine for farming
I happened to meet Professor Aldebaran
And Professor Aldebaran apologizes
He can't gather with you
Because he has something to do
What should I do?
I want to go home
Yes, Bro
We also want to go home
Children
Professor Aldebaran has a message for you
So that you can help me
To look for the forest mushroom
Mushroom?
Yes, the forest mushroom
Because according to Professor
This forest mushroom can cure Nick
But this mushroom is not just any mushroom
This mushroom grows the fastest
The umbrella is below
The mushroom stalk is above
And
Pay attention, this is important
This mushroom cannot be taken by manual
Professor Aldebaran also has a message for all of you
When in the forest
Please
You have to focus
Don't play
Don't look left and right randomly
And hold something that is not important
Do you understand?
Yes, Sir
Okay
Now you can get ready
I
Want to talk to
Professor Purwa and Professor Akar
Megantara
Is there a problem?
This village gate
Is given a very strong mantra
That's what makes people here
Can't get out
And can't get in
Because of that
Professor Aldebaran
Can't get out
And can't get in
Professor Aldebaran
Can't come here
Professor Aldebaran has a message
So that we can protect the children
Don't let
There are children who dare to break the gate
Because this will be very dangerous for them
Wait
Children
Before we go into the magic forest
To look for forest mushrooms
I will
Divide you into groups
One group
Five people
Okay
Let's go
Get the fluid
Now
You have been divided into groups
If one of you
Have got the mushroom
You just have to make the sound of the fluid
Do you understand?
Yes, Sir
And if there is a danger approaching you
You just have to make the sound of the fluid
Professor
Why are you alone?
Because he is Megantara, Alva
He is a very strong and tough person
But you
You can't be alone
You still need a companion
Let's go
Four Weeks Ago
This thing is so big
Ramil!
What are you doing?
Focus on finding the mushroom that grows upside down.
Do you understand?
I understand, Prof.
Don't touch anything in this forest.
Okay, Prof.
Hurry, go back to your friends.
Four Weeks Ago
Srigala
I'm Megantar.
A passerby.
May I?
There's something wrong.
I was hit by a tree on the iron bridge.
Smart boy.
Megantar
Excuse me.
Good.
Four Weeks Ago
Srigala
Wow, it's so cool.
Oh, right.
Prof. Soaldebaran told me not to touch or see anything.
I'd better look for the mushroom.
Wow!
I almost got hit by a tree.
But it's okay.
I'm sure I can catch it.
Four Weeks Ago
Srigala
It's the mushroom!
I got it.
I can use my magic.
What should I do?
I'll use my magic.
It's impossible.
I can't catch it.
There it is.
Four Weeks Ago
I got it.
How is it, Vega?
Did you get the mushroom?
Yes, Prof.
But it's over there.
I can't get it.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Four Weeks Ago
Srigala
Thank you, Prof.
You're so kind.
You'd better keep your voice down.
So, the others will know that we got the mushroom.
Yes, Prof.
Four Weeks Ago
The mushroom has been found.
So, we can catch it.
Let's go there.
Let's go.
I'm so happy.
Help!
Four Weeks Ago
Let's go there.
Help!
The mushroom has been found.
Four Weeks Ago
No, Alva.
Alva!
Alva, where are you?
It's useless to look for Alva.
Maybe, Alva has turned into a rock.
Yes, it's been a day.
Let's go.
Where are you?
Alva!
People like that can't be found.
Let's look for Alva again.
Alva!
Alva, where are you?
Four Weeks Ago
Help!
My arm!
Let me go!
Don't make noise!
God!
Let me go!
I want to go back to the group!
They will find me!
Help!
Don't call me!
Who are you?
God Almighty!
You have to go with me...
...to the eighth heaven.
The eighth heaven?
Help!
Do you want a gun?
I don't know...
...if you want to attack me.
Shut up!
You're lying.
It's okay.
It's better...
...if I use my power.
Let's go.
Come on!
Oh my God!
I want a gun!
Come on!
There are so many of them.
Let's fry them.
We can do it!
Last time...
...a ghost like you...
Now...
...do you know...
...how great I am?
Now...
...you...
...take your magic wand...
...and...
...I'll count to ten.
If you don't take your magic wand...
...tomorrow morning...
...you'll be my breakfast.
The eighth day.
Let's do it again.
One.
Two.
Three.
Why are you just standing there?
I'm just kidding.
I'm serious.
Can't you see?
I'll take your magic wand.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
I'll count to ten.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
What are you doing here?
Why are you attacking that way?
The Eighth Day.
It's hard.
There are so many.
I'll fry them.
Pretty girl.
There are so many.
Tiara.
I know you don't like men.
But now, you have to help me.
Malik is evil.
He wants to take me to the Eighth Day.
Girls.
Angfa is kind.
She helped me before.
So, we have to help her.
Come on, girls. Let's help her.
You're annoying.
You don't know who we are.
How dare you to play with me?
Now, feel this.
How come?
Girls.
Help!
Angfa.
You should go.
It's all your fault.
Poor her.
She can't swim.
She'll drown.
What if she drowns?
She'll die.
Poko.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Just let her be.
She doesn't like men.
That's why she hates men.
Come on, girls.
Help!
Poko.
Bobo.
Thank God.
You saved Bobo.
Sial.
What's wrong, Sial?
You saved Bobo.
Now, you want to give him to me?
No.
Now, I have to go back to the group.
Wait.
Do you think I like this?
I have to do this.
I have to.
Fine.
If you have to do this, then don't.
I won't ask for it.
Don't say that.
Who saved Bobo's life...
...will be my employer.
If not...
...Bobo will die.
But, Bobo is my promise.
So, do you want to be my employer now?
So?
Yes.
I'll be your servant.
But, I have to go to the village.
I have to meet many people there.
Just say it.
Bobo saved you.
You're right.
Let's go there.
Don't.
Yes.
Just say it.
If you don't go there...
...you'll be eaten there.
If you don't go there, what will you wear?
So?
Who is this, Alva?
What are you doing?
To be continued...
After this mosquito is killed...
...they will recover in 48 hours.
I hope...
...both of them will be fine.
Prof, how is Netola and Kanik?
Don't worry, Vega.
They will recover in 48 hours.
Mosquitoes are venomous.
So, they will recover.
Dad, help!
Dad, help me!
Shut up!
I'll beat you up.
You never listen to me.
Bobo.
Don't be like that.
Poor him.
I'm looking for him.
Dad, help me!
Dad.
Dad, those kids came in from our roof.
Alva.
Alva, thank God.
It's okay, honey.
Don't be afraid.
Alva is your friend, too.
Alva, where have you been?
I'm worried about you.
I thought you were a rock.
You've been lying to me.
I'm not lying. I'm just worried.
Stop it.
Alva.
Alva is safe now.
That's it.
It's not easy for Bobo.
I fought with them.
Then?
Who is this, Alva?
What are you doing?
Do you want to get whacked?
Bobo, don't be rude.
Introduce yourself.
My name is Bobo.
Where are you going? I'm lost.
What should I do now?
Bobo and Alva...
Because Alva is kind enough to help Bobo.
Bobo Kurcaci who lives in Subatangkara...
...doesn't have a place to stay.
Can Bobo stay with you?
No.
You can't do that. You have to be polite.
Bobo, you can stay here.
It's time to eat.
Let's eat.
You must be hungry.
Let's go.
Bobo Kurcaci
Please enjoy.
Don't be so rude.
I had to do it.
You don't have to do it.
Alva, why did you bring him here?
He's scary. You can't trust him.
He looks scary.
Look at him.
Bobo Kurcaci
How could we be trapped here?
Don't be so harsh, Professor Purwa.
We have to cover this up.
Don't make the kids panic.
Yes.
I feel sorry for the kids.
We brought them here...
...to have a field trip.
To have fun.
But the truth is...
...we're all trapped here.
I have an idea.
There's a bomb...
...under the school.
It's a new disease.
Don't worry, Professors.
Tomorrow...
...we'll ask them to do something fun.
A FEW HOURS LATER
Rita.
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
I'm scared, Feika.
Scared of what?
What happened today...
...can't be the same...
...as in the legend.
Legend?
What legend?
A FEW HOURS LATER
Dad?
Why are you crying?
I told you to come here, Alva.
But why are you so stubborn?
This place is too dangerous for you.
Who are you?
Why do you keep showing up in my dream?
I'm Gamar.
I'm Quila.
We're both...
...so close to God.
Now you have to remember, Alva.
Don't ever look at those eyes again.
Remember.
What do you mean?
Whose eyes?
Gamar!
Quila!
Why did you wake up?
Were you dreaming?
And?
I couldn't sleep.
Why?
I don't know, Dad.
But I have a feeling.
I think the teachers are hiding something from us.
Hiding something?
Two kids have been killed.
But we can't go home yet.
And...
...Professor Lebaran.
He said he was coming.
But he's not here yet.
If this legend is true...
...it means the monster is gone.
And later we have to find out...
...who took the power.
What are you doing here?
It's a good question.
I have a clue about this.
Come here.
Here.
This is the book.
100 years ago...
...the people of Sihir village lived in peace.
Until one day...
...a disaster came to the village.
Help!
The disaster was a curse.
The village was in chaos.
And many people turned into stone.
Help!
It's so scary.
The only hope of the village was...
...a great sorcerer named Bima Sakti.
BIMA SAKTI
The villagers were still scared.
They couldn't trust anyone.
Even a good sorcerer like you.
What's wrong, Bambi?
Help!
Save this village, Bima Sakti.
Look.
This village is like dead.
No one dares to leave the house.
Because they're afraid of being cursed into stone.
Why did you curse the snake?
My family...
...was destroyed...
...by the monster.
Finally, Bima Sakti faced the monster.
Bu Furuh!
Bima Sakti defeated the monster...
...and locked it in the cave.
No one knew where the cave was.
But...
...the spell didn't last forever.
So the monster...
...could be released.
BIMA SAKTI
Only the fifth generation can open it.
If this legend is true...
...it means the monster is released.
We have to find out...
...who is Bima Sakti's descendant...
...who can lock the monster inside.
Who is he?
BIMA SAKTI
All the disciples and teachers in the village are in danger.
What should I do...
...so I can enter the village...
...and help them?
Children.
Even though we're on vacation...
...we still have to learn the spell.
Children.
Now I'm going to teach you...
...a spell.
This spell can neutralize...
...the attack of the enemy...
...that makes you powerless.
It makes you stiff.
And you can't do anything.
But if you use this spell...
...you will be free...
...and normal again.
Yes. Great.
I have to be able to do it...
...so I won't be stiff like Tole.
Teach me.
Okay.
Now get ready.
We will make you stiff...
...and powerless.
Kavaku Bada.
Concentrate.
Now I'm going to teach you...
...a spell...
...that will make you free...
...from your powerlessness.
The spell is...
...free first.
Come on, children.
Concentrate.
Who can be free first...
...can take the chocolate on the table.
And if you can't free yourselves...
...you will be punished.
To be continued...
Be free!
Don't!
Don't bother us!
Don't bother me!
But he didn't mean to.
He was so scared.
He mispronounced the spell...
...and he got you.
Forgive him.
Be free!
Children.
Help me.
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
I'm surprised.
How can a snake talk to you?
I'm surprised too.
But I used to talk to a snake.
When?
When I lived with my uncle and aunt.
Is it weird that I can talk to a snake?
Wait.
You can talk to a snake when you're sick.
What else can you say about a snake?
You're lying.
The snake's teeth can kill.
But you can kill it...
...through its teeth.
You're talking nonsense.
Maybe I'm a descendant of the snake.
If it's like this...
...how can we get out of here?
And we can't go home either.
Because the village gate...
...is haunted by a very powerful spell.
We're all trapped here.
Now we know...
...that the monster likes chocolate.
So we have to warn our friends...
...so they don't eat chocolate.
I agree.
So the others can't get the monster.
Let's go.
Opo.
Do you want to help me...
...in my new job?
To be continued...