To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Be proud of yourself!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
I will be your shield.
I will empower him.
Go!
Tell me the truth.
Alva and Tommy,
you have to ride your bike into the forest.
And in the forest,
you have to catch a ghost.
After you catch the ghost,
you have to bring it to the finish line.
That's Alva.
She made me lose my faith in life.
I will make her lose.
Alva, I'll go right, you go left.
Let's see who will catch the ghost first.
Where are the ghosts?
I can't find it.
Where is it?
It's not here.
Who threw the black cloth?
It hurts.
It's you.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Do you want to surrender yourself?
After that, I'll catch you.
And I'll bring you to the finish line.
Do you want to help me?
Try to catch me if you can.
Oh, right.
You've been taught the ritual.
What are you doing, Alva?
That's all?
You're so stupid.
I'm going up.
I can't catch you.
You're so stupid.
You can't catch me.
Run.
Come on.
Alva is gone.
Ghost, sit behind me.
Now, I'm going to win.
My father has a lifeline.
So, if you want to be caught by me, I'll give you my lifeline.
That's right.
This time, I want to be caught by you.
But, I'll give you my lifeline first.
Okay.
Tom, is it true that I was given a lifeline?
Yes, you're so stupid.
Just sit down.
I'm sure that Alva hasn't caught the ghost yet.
I'm sure that I'll win.
My body is aching.
Pipi!
Oh, yes.
I tried to save Professor Titan.
Then, where is Professor Titan?
I'm so sure.
He must be trapped by Professor Titan.
I'll tell Professor Agni.
I'm late for Alva's competition.
Professor Agni!
Yes, Vega?
It's horrible, Prof.
Vega?
Don't you watch the competition?
There's something more important than the competition.
What is it, Vega?
Professor Titan.
What's wrong with Professor Titan?
Professor Titan, who has been in our school, is a fake.
He's the eighth ghost.
The eighth ghost?
Yes, Prof.
Professor Titan was trapped in the closet.
I saw it, Prof.
I even helped Professor Titan.
But, when I didn't help him,
the eighth ghost attacked me again.
Are you sure about this, Vega?
Yes, Prof.
That's why Professor Titan followed me.
Let's watch it together.
Let's go, Prof.
Where are you, Raya?
Why did you just disappear?
I can't see the other ghosts.
Raya, where are you?
Raya, don't disappear!
Raya!
It's a pity that you didn't get the ghost.
I got the ghost.
Now, I'm going to win.
Bye.
Don't come in.
That's why you shouldn't tease people.
I should find another ghost.
So, I can win.
Bye.
Ouch.
Watch your bike.
Don't scratch it.
It hurts.
Ouch.
Your body is stiff.
It hurts.
Let's take a rest here.
Raya.
The ghosts haven't come out yet.
Where are they?
Let's look for them.
Poor Raya.
Raya is so brave.
It's our duty to catch her.
She's a ghost hunter.
Where is she?
She's over there.
You're done, Alva.
The ghosts are hiding.
You won't get the ghost.
I got an idea.
Hey, there's a river of life.
It's so cool.
There's a river of life.
Alva, where's the river of life?
Give it to me.
It's right here.
Where is it?
You can't go anywhere now.
Alva, you cheated on me.
Let me go.
Move.
Let's go inside.
No, Vega.
It's not safe.
Let's make sure it's true.
Professor Titan.
Excuse me, Professor Titan.
Please, come in.
Let's go.
Professor.
I'm sorry, Professor.
Smile.
There's a beautiful and handsome Professor Agni.
The arrival of Professor Agni doesn't bother me.
But, this is a blessing for me.
Welcome.
I present this beautiful flower...
...to Professor Agni.
It's so beautiful.
Don't pretend.
Where's the real Professor Titan?
Vega, you have to be polite.
Okay.
That's impossible.
Professor Titan.
I'm sorry, Professor.
I didn't mean to suspect you.
There have been a lot of strange things...
...that happened in our school.
If I may know...
...and if you don't mind...
...may I know...
...the contents of that closet?
The contents of that closet...
...are for my experiment, Professor.
You're lying.
Professor Agni.
Ask him to open it.
Professor.
Can we see the contents of that closet?
If you don't mind.
Of course not.
For Professor Agni...
...I will prepare it.
Let me go, Alva.
Let me go.
You're Alva, aren't you?
Mommy, you go first.
Let me go, Alva.
Why is she there?
Hurry up.
Yes, be patient.
Be strong.
Get that liquid.
Let me go.
Let me go, Alva.
Alva, let me go.
Professor.
That baby is so cute.
Yes.
This is impossible.
I saw the real Professor Titan.
I saw it myself.
I even helped him.
Vega.
That's enough, Vega.
Let's just leave it there.
The baby knows it now.
Right?
I'm sorry, Professor Titan.
Maybe Vega...
...is not feeling well.
That's why he can make up stories like that.
I'm not sick, Professor.
You're not sick, Vega.
But we're stressed and nervous.
That's because you're always studying.
Right?
That's right.
I'm stressed and nervous.
No, I'm not.
You're lying.
Vega.
That's enough, Vega.
That's enough, Professor.
We'll leave now, Professor.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Yes, Professor.
Professor.
Vega.
You're embarrassing me.
I'm not lying, Professor.
I saw it myself.
He's evil.
He's a liar.
He's a fake.
That's enough, Vega.
You're overreacting.
If we're like this, it can be called a slander.
Do you understand?
No, Professor.
I'm sure...
...the real Professor Titan...
...can be hidden by him.
That's enough, Vega.
You should focus on the competition now.
You should support Alfa...
...because Alfa needs your support.
How can I convince Professor Agni?
I'm sure...
...the real Professor Titan...
...can be hidden somewhere else.
I'm sure...
...the real Professor Titan...
...can be hidden somewhere else.
I'm sure...
...the real Professor Titan...
...can be hidden somewhere else.
Now, it's time for me to take action.
I can't give up.
I have to prove to Professor Agni...
...that Professor Titan is fake.
But, how?
I know.
Gosh.
There are so many books.
I must have read them for a long time.
But, it's okay.
I can find it.
I have to find out...
...where he is.
Give me a smile.
There he is.
Gosh.
He's not here.
He must be investigating me.
He's the only one...
...who doesn't trust me.
Disguising...
...is the most perfect way.
Maybe, this is the book.
Disguising is the most perfect way.
This is a very difficult black magic.
It's controlled by a great sorcerer.
I'm sure...
...this is the book's guide.
Yes.
There's only one way to prove it.
That is by using...
...the book.
The book is flying.
The book.
What are you doing?
Come here.
The book.
I want to read it.
Don't go.
The book.
Where's the book?
Don't go.
Gosh.
The book.
The book is gone.
It's gone again.
The book.
Wait.
I'm going to find out...
...where it is.
Ouch. It hurts.
The book.
Why is this in the toilet?
Hi.
Give me a smile.
Feel the difference.
I still have a lot of work to do.
Bye.
The book.
What are you waiting for?
It's gone again.
There's only one way.
The book.
Get ready.
The time will come.
Hurry up, Tom.
We're almost there.
The book.
This is weird.
Why is the place different?
What's that?
Let's go.
To be continued...
What's that?
This is dangerous.
SOS.
Where is it coming from?
Calm down.
I think it's going to explode.
We don't know yet.
That's SOS.
It's dangerous.
What if something happens?
What should we do?
Agni, take care of the kids.
Yes, sir.
I'm coming with you.
Everyone is watching the race right now.
I can take over this place.
Where is it coming from?
Here it is.
The soul stone that I've been looking for.
I've got the soul stone.
I can destroy this school.
I'm going to destroy this school.
Tommy.
What's wrong?
Did you make the SOS sign?
Yes, sir.
I made the SOS sign.
Because...
The ticket is gone.
And the alpha is gone too.
We were holding the ticket.
Then, there was a strong wind.
We appeared in another place.
Then, there was a raptor.
It attacked me.
Then, I brought the wind.
And I came back here.
But, the alpha didn't come back here.
That's it, sir.
How could it be?
How did you move places?
I don't understand.
What is this, sir?
It looks like someone...
turned the winning ticket into a moving tool.
That tool moved the alpha to another place.
I don't know where it is.
Why did Tommy come back? But, the alpha didn't.
It looks like this person only wants the alpha.
That's why he brought Tommy back.
This must be the work of Professor Titan.
I think...
he did this to hurt the alpha.
That's nonsense.
A professor should learn something new.
So, why did he hurt the alpha?
He just got to know the alpha.
I'm right.
There's a fake Professor Titan.
And the real one is hidden in his room.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm very sure.
He's using a magical tool.
Actually, he's the Dark Lord.
How did you know that he's the Dark Lord?
Because I saw his shadow in the school mirror.
The Dark Lord
Don't tell me you're right, Vega.
He changed the world...
with the greatest transformation spell.
Yes, Professor.
The spell is very powerful.
Because I poured water on him.
But he didn't change.
Wow.
Maybe this spell was made by the soldiers yesterday.
The weakness is only the mirror.
I don't know.
You're so naive.
We were taught to change the world by the soldiers.
The weakness is only the mirror.
So, if we look at the mirror, we can see the real one.
I have to check everything.
Yes, Professor.
We have to go to school.
We have to ask Professor Titan...
where he hid the alpha.
Vega.
Fire.
Love with a smile.
I've installed all the devices.
Soon...
there will be a huge fire festival here.
The Triangle
What's that?
What is this?
What is it?
Professor
Professor Rahmi
Professor, it looks like someone is attacking our school
Our school?
Hurry up, we need to evacuate as soon as possible
Yes, Professor
Let's go, Figa
The Triangle
Enjoy this mess, Adembaran
Normal
Ha ha ha ha
With this blood, my power will be truly perfect
And soon, I will rule the world
The Triangle
Our school will be destroyed
If our school is destroyed, where are we going to study?
Don't worry, our school will be closed
Oh no
Jack, don't say that
What are we going to do?
Let's go
But I don't want to go there
Professor Gita
What's that sound?
Professor Gita, stay away from this wall
I will destroy it
What do you mean destroy?
Professor Gita
Do you want to die?
Thank you for your help
Thank you very much
You're welcome
We have to get out of here
Yes
Professor Gita
Are you okay?
I found Professor Gita behind the wall in his room
Behind the wall?
Yes
The Dark Lord possessed me
He even bewitched me
So, Vega's story is true
What do you mean?
Vega told me that the Professor Titan in the school is fake
And the real one is hidden in the closet
But I didn't believe him
Do you mean that girl?
Vega is not lying
He once helped me
But the Dark Lord is stronger
I was caught again
And Vega was made to faint again
Let's go!
Let's go, Pindu!
She's so strong
She can't hide
Professor!
Where did he go?
I think he's just looking for my blood
Maybe
Hey, wait!
What?
The school is on fire
Why is there always a problem in this school?
Don't worry
You can't change the situation
Let's just look for Alpha
The situation?
Huh?
Look for what?
The telescope
Hello!
The telescope is in the old classroom
Did you ask me to go there?
You can burn the telescope?
Hello! You can also use magic
What about you?
Hurry up!
Get the telescope!
It's a tsunami!
Freeze!
Here!
I want to look for Alpha
She's not here yet
Did you find her?
Not yet
I'm still concentrating
No, I'm concentrating
I think the telescope is broken because of the fire
I don't care
Let's go to Pripin
Let's look for Alpha using OPPO
Oh no, Raptor
He's so fast today
How can I follow him?
I have to use another way
Oh, right
I forgot to turn around
Where's Lollipop?
This is a good idea
I have to find Lollipop
It's easier this way
There he is!
I got you, Lollipop!
It's easier this way
Why did the Raptor stop?
Whatever, I'm going to stop too
He's still alive!
Raptor!
You've done what I told you to do
You've got Alpha's tender
Of course, I did it
Good job!
A perfect plan
You're right
Your plan to make me turn into a Raptor
It's amazing
Angkara!
Yes, sir
Angkara
Now, I want you to turn into a Raptor
What for, sir?
The ring that I have
is now owned by Alpha
and he can't be attacked
In fact, my attack goes back to me
That's why I want you to turn into a Raptor
Because that ring
won't work
if I turn you into him
Yes, sir
How do I look, sir?
Good, Angkara
Perfect
Raptor
Go back to your place
Now
take the ring
and turn into a Raptor
What for, sir?
But the best part is
you turned into Professor Titan
Everything was easy
Even Alpha
So, Raptor is...
Raptor is Professor Angkara?
What a perfect disguise
Even Aldebaran was fooled
But there's one person who wasn't
Vega
But we don't need to worry
Because there's no one who trusts him
In fact
he was attacked by his own teacher
Professor Titan
So, Professor Titan
is the inspiration of the Dark Lord?
Professor Titan
So, I was attacked?
What?
I woke up from my dream
So, I think
Professor Titan
has something to do with the Dark Lord
Vega is right
But I and Retole
don't trust Vega
I'm mad at Vega
I'm sorry, Vega
I don't trust you anymore
Actually, I'm a warrior
All of this can be avoided
With this blood
my power will be perfect
And soon
I will rule the world
What should I do now?
To be continued...
Look at the TV!
Fire! Fire!
How long will it take, sir?
Soon, sir
Soon, Ramuan will be ready
And I will get perfect power
Unlimited power!
We have to help Robert Dewi!
But how, Vega?
The fire is getting bigger!
If we go forward, we can burn it!
Retole!
Fire! Fire!
What should we do?
Bro! Bro!
Let us help Robert Dewi!
Yes, sir!
We are tired of being together
Let us help him!
Yes, sir!
We are special kids
We want to help too!
Alright
Be careful
Are you sure this is the right way?
Do you want me to help?
You don't have to
There are three of us
We can make it
Let's go!
Wait for me!
Bye!
Be careful!
Don't get close!
Help!
Be careful, Retole!
Retole!
I'm scared!
Help me!
Calm down!
I will help Ray and Tole
Megantara
Let me and Prof. Titan help you
Hi!
Give me a smile, Prof. Agni
Just leave it to me
I can handle it myself
Agni! Agni!
Robert!
Let's go to Prof. Dewi!
No!
It's dangerous!
Agni!
Let's jump!
I will catch you from here!
No!
My face will be ruined!
Agni!
If you don't jump, it will explode!
No!
It will explode!
It's time
Ramuan...
...has been mixed with sempurna
I can't wait any longer, sir
Here's your water, sir
Alva!
Give me back the bottle, Alva!
How dare you take the bottle from me, Alva!
Give it back!
Why not?
It's clear
This is my tears, my sweat, and my blood
So, this is mine!
The point is
The evil
Will never win!
The evil will never win!
Why are you interfering?
I can't just stand by
I have to help Pangeran in the dark
The evil will never win!
It's broken!
Drink it, Pangeran
And get your power back
Alva, run!
The evil will never win!
Alva
This time, you will lose
Because Pangeran the Dark
Will soon change its destiny
I'll bite you!
The evil will never win!
We won!
We can do this!
Now
My power has really increased
Pangeran the Dark has become very strong
No one can defeat me
Including you, Alva
Congratulations, sir
You can do this, sir
Release him
Let him help from below
Let's do it
There's no way Pangeran will catch us
All right, let's count to three
One
Two
Three
Go!
Are you all right?
Thank you, sir
No, help me!
Come on, Doctor, please
Jump!
If you don't, you'll get burned
What? Jump?
Are you crazy?
No, no, no!
Please!
Hurry!
Jump!
We did it!
It doesn't hurt
It's so amazing!
It's okay, Doctor
But I can't be a magician
I'm sorry, Professor
Professor, what happened? Are you okay?
Professor, are you okay?
What?
Professor
I'm sorry, Doctor
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to
The damage is severe
The soul stone is gone
Pangeran will take it
Professor Lodebaran
What about the damage?
What's so bad about it?
It's not about the damage
It's not a problem
We can always build this school with the power of magic
But now
There's a bigger problem
Pangeran Kegelapan
He stole the soul stone from my room
What?
With the soul stone
Pangeran Kegelapan will be difficult to defeat
He can split his soul into 12 parts
And put those parts in different places
Next
He will be very difficult to defeat
Unless we can destroy the 12 parts of the stone
This is bad
I'm going to kill you
Call the ambulance
Now
I'm going to kill you
I'm sorry
This ring doesn't affect me anymore
Because my power is now
Much greater
What are you doing?
I'm going to kill you
How is it?
Do you want to see?
What is this?
I'm going to kill you
Hurry up
I have to survive
I don't want to be defeated like my father and mother
Father
Mother
Please help me
Father
Mother
Please help me
With these twelve stones
I will divide my soul into twelve
And I'm sure
The invaders will have a hard time facing me
Huh?
What is this?
Help!
Let us go!
That voice again
Don't give up
Chase your passion and dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with your heart
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Let's go
We can do it