To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
To be continued...
We're not done yet, Megantar.
We still have to close the cave's door with a mantra.
So that Antaboga won't appear again forever.
I only had my father when I was little.
Now he's gone.
I'm all alone.
Megantar.
You're not alone, Ko.
You still have us.
Just join us to school.
Now you're free.
You're not a servant to anyone.
Free?
Yay! I'm free!
I have to get that life fluid.
I have to defeat them all.
So I can live again.
And remember.
Life fluid is very rare.
Only one person can get that rare life fluid.
No one can defeat Raya.
She's so pretty.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm bored.
She's so lame.
Whatever.
I'm going to make her lose.
I have to win.
What's wrong, Pegah?
I don't know.
Guys.
Pegah.
You've been in the toilet for so long.
I'm sorry.
I met a ghost.
A ghost?
That's scary.
It's not scary anymore.
But it's annoying.
It's annoying.
And it sings.
It's trying to scare the contestants.
So that they'll fail.
I see.
There were some kids who gave up.
And flew the white flag.
And they were defeated.
So we have to be careful.
And remember.
We can't give up.
Let's go.
Ray.
Don't.
Did you hear that?
We can't eat this.
I know.
If we eat it, we'll fail.
No way.
I know.
But I really want to eat it.
It looks delicious.
I'm hungry.
Let's go.
Ray.
Do you want to fail?
No.
Let's go.
Okay.
I have to scare them.
So that they'll eat it.
If it's like this, I'll become a normal kid.
I'll eat it.
I'll become a normal kid.
It's delicious.
Hi.
Do you want it?
Just eat it.
I'm hungry.
But they said you can't eat it.
Who said that?
Just eat it.
Just a little.
I won't be caught by the judges.
Just eat it.
I'm hungry.
I'll eat it.
It's delicious.
Hi.
I'm Raya.
I'm Ray.
The ice cream you're looking at is delicious.
Yes, it's delicious.
Just eat it.
If I eat it, I'll fail.
Who said that?
I've tried it.
Really?
Just eat it.
You'll regret it.
You again.
What are you doing?
Open the door.
Wait.
What are you doing here?
You made me lose.
So what?
It's not your fault.
Listen.
If I win, I'll get a life sentence.
So, you're a prostitute too?
We're trying to win.
We'll win against you.
Okay.
You'll win against me.
So, just give up.
Just give up.
I won't give up.
Yes.
But, it's up to you.
If you lose, don't cry.
What are you doing?
We're doing our homework.
Let's play.
No, we don't want to play.
We're doing our homework.
Let's play.
I don't want to lose.
Let's go.
You don't want to play with me?
I'll call Vega.
Can I borrow this?
No.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Don't waste our time.
Okay.
Vega doesn't care about me.
He cares about Alva.
I don't want to lose.
Dad, I miss you.
I'm lonely.
I'm lonely, dad.
A key?
What should I do?
I'm getting more scared.
I'm scared.
I want to hit it.
Don't.
Just a little.
I can't.
Don't.
Just a little.
Alva, wake up.
Alva.
Vega.
What did I do?
You bit my hand.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
It hurts a little.
Don't eat this.
We're here to win the competition.
For Alva.
I'm sorry, Reda and Vega.
Because of me...
...they're having a hard time.
Let's go.
We're here to win the competition.
Don't.
Don't touch me.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Come here.
I'll help you.
Don't.
Come here.
Let's go.
In this park...
...there are a lot of candies.
Your task...
...is to collect...
...100 candies in 30 minutes...
...in a bucket.
The one who succeed will go to the next round.
The one who fail...
...will be eliminated and sent home.
Get ready.
Start.
Remember.
The candies you collect...
...shouldn't be eaten.
If you eat it...
...you'll be sent home.
The candies that fall from the bucket...
...won't be counted.
I got it.
Raya.
Why are you so slow?
I'll go first.
You should be brave.
Raya.
Watch out, Raya.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Five, too.
Four.
Five.
Look at this.
I got two papers.
You're so arrogant.
Let's go.
Raya.
Oops.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Watch out.
Raya.
You missed.
Watch out.
You're so slow.
That's enough.
It's better...
...to collect the candies that you dropped.
Raya.
That's enough.
Let's go.
Why is it gone?
Raya.
I just remembered.
The candy that fell from the bucket...
...won't be counted.
That means it won't be counted.
It's because of Raya.
Raya.
Rai.
Calm down.
There's still time.
There's still time...
...for the replacement.
What?
There's no time.
There's only five minutes left.
Where are you going?
I'm going with Vega.
I'm going to throw up.
This is just a practice.
If we lose because of him,
I won't forgive him.
Where's your camera?
Where's my camera?
There it is.
Let me try it.
There are two of them.
Try again.
Yes!
We did it!
Let's give it to the jury.
Let's go.
You won.
Yes!
Friends forever.
Best friends forever.
Yeah!
I think they're the toughest opponent.
I have to beat them...
...and win their trust.
Because that's the only way...
...I can come back to life.
You lost.
You won.
Help!
Hello!
Alva!
I'm coming!
Where's Alva?
She's with my little friend.
Don't call me little friend.
I'm Kurcaci Ganjang.
You don't know?
If you call me Kerdil again...
...I'll turn you into a monster.
Calm down.
Where's Alva?
I want to see her.
Alva is looking for medicine.
With them.
Alva is sick.
They're looking for medicine.
Why didn't they invite me?
I don't know.
What's that?
A new mantra?
I don't know.
That means I don't know.
That's a fairy tale.
I should talk to pretty people...
...instead of talking to ugly people.
Hey, you!
Move!
Kurcaci Ganteng wants to pass.
I'm here.
You're weak.
Hello, Pelita.
Do you still remember me?
I'm Kurcaci Ganteng, Alva's friend.
Yes, I still remember.
Don't you want to take my hand?
I'm sorry, I can't.
Why not?
You're not polite.
Leave me alone.
I want to be alone.
Because I'm Kurcaci...
...you don't want to shake hands with me?
You're arrogant.
I'm not arrogant.
I still have self-esteem as Kurcaci.
I feel like I'm being trampled by you.
You should shake hands with me.
No, you should leave.
Go away!
I'm not arrogant.
I'll force you.
Popo!
Someone found out about this.
If they find out, I'll be kicked out of school.
Pelita!
To be continued...
Popo, I want you to stay here.
I want you to stay here.
This is a dead end.
What if...
...there's another attack?
We have to report this to the professor.
Let's go.
This is weird.
I feel like the weather is changing.
A few hours ago, it was 30 degrees.
Now it's 17 degrees.
Yes, you're right.
What if there's another attack?
I don't feel any negative energy from this.
I don't think this is an attack.
What is this, Professor?
This is a special power...
...owned by a student in this school.
Who is he? Who is his son?
I don't know.
But we have to find him.
If this power is not controlled, it can be dangerous.
Now I'm wearing gloves.
If my friends touch me, they'll be in trouble.
Hey, Pelita!
Pelita, come here.
No, I don't want to.
Why don't you wear the gloves?
But I don't want to.
He's so rude.
He's just like his friends, Alva, Vegas, and Ray.
Alva, Vegas, and Ray. They're not cool at all.
Don't call Alva, Ray, and Vega.
They're good friends.
The best friends in the world?
I'm the best.
Alva!
Help!
What's going on here?
He's a monster!
What are you doing here?
I'm not a professor. I don't know what's going on.
He's lying!
I saw him with my own eyes.
He must be a monster!
Let him out!
I'm innocent.
Don't throw me out of school.
I don't have anyone else.
He's a monster!
Don't work with him!
He must be expelled from school!
Let him out!
Maybe Tommy was right.
I can't be here.
Because I can hurt innocent people.
Like Popo.
I'm sorry, Professor. I didn't mean to.
Rita!
Now you have to walk through that bridge.
You have to use your powers.
No magic, no flying, and no magic.
Don't forget, you have to be careful.
Because if you fall, you'll be in danger.
Popo can fly.
He must be number one.
But don't worry.
I can make other kids fall.
But the camera is for focusing.
What's this cover for?
Let's try it.
I have to win. I can't lose.
That's Raya's voice.
It can hear people's voices.
When I pass, I'll tell Vega, Ava, and Ray...
...to fall and bring smoke.
Just watch. I'll make them lose.
Guys, wait.
Do you know how to use it?
I know.
It can hear people's voices.
I heard Raya was about to attack us.
Are you serious?
We have to be careful. Raya is behind us.
To be continued...
I can't fall.
If I fall, I'll fail.
What should I do?
I can't fly.
If I fly, I'll fail.
Guys, let's just leave him.
It's useless to help him.
Poor Vega. What if he really falls?
He's a ghost.
He's gone. It's useless to help him.
If he falls, he won't die.
We can't just leave him. We have to help him.
Let's go.
No, Vega. We have to help him.
I won't be long.
Ava. Raya.
Give me your hand.
You're my mom, right?
Yes.
We're rivals.
That's fair.
Give me your hand.
To be continued...
Thank you, Ava.
If you don't help me, I'll fail.
Goodbye, Raya.
Ava, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Ava.
It's because of you, Raya.
What should we do?
In five minutes, you have to arrive at the next gate.
The children who are late will be sent back to the gate.
What should we do?
Oh, my God.
So, this is the effect of the child named Pelita?
Yes.
I've heard of a power that can turn everything into ice.
Freezing.
Even a small child can't handle it.
And it turns this school into freezing.
Ice.
And it can freeze itself.
This is very dangerous.
You three can go to the next gate.
Yes.
Thank you, Raya, for helping me.
Now, we've entered the first gate.
And there's one more gate that we have to pass.
I want to tell Pelita that we're on an adventure today.
We're on an adventure today.
Why is it on?
Maybe Pelita is calling me.
Maybe.
Pelita.
Pelita, are you calling me?
Pelita, answer me.
Pelita.
I want to go home.
Don't go.
Don't leave me.
I want to go home.
Pegah.
Come on, let's go.
Why are you wasting our time?
If they see me like this, they'll be afraid to be friends with me.
Let's not give up.
Raya's soul has fallen.
So, we have to hold on.
To be continued...
All of this is because of one thing.
My power has become weak.
Sir.
Help me, sir.
Where did you come from?
Why can't you come back to your senses?
All of this is because of Ullah Aldebaran.
He always stops me.
And all of my plans failed because of him, sir.
If that's the case, I have to kneel.
But sir, your power hasn't recovered yet.
You won't be able to fight Aldebaran.
But now I have a great weapon that can defeat Aldebaran.
He will get the chosen one.
It's weird.
Why can't he answer?
Maybe he's playing with his friend.
It's possible.
Okay, let's inform him later.
It's better if we continue our journey.
Okay.
Let's go.
Welcome back, children.
I wish you all the best.
Because you have passed the first gate.
The gate of dreams.
This second gate is called the gate of patience.
As the name implies.
In this gate, you will be tested for your patience.
In this gate, you can't be angry.
You can't be selfish.
And you can't force your opponent.
Do you understand?
Let's go.
That's right.
This is the canteen.
Now, you can eat first.
Yes.
Finally, we can eat.
I'm sure the food is better than the first gate.
That's right.
I'm sure there's grilled chicken.
Where's the food?
Enjoy your meal.
I'm sure the food is delicious.
Food.
Let's open it.
One.
Two.
Three.
Ta-da.
Look at the food.
The food is all over the place.
The food looks like this.
It's delicious.
I don't like vegetables.
I don't want to eat it.
Me too.
I don't want to eat vegetables.
Rai.
I don't want to eat it.
As I said before.
This place is for trial and error.
You have to finish the vegetables and don't get angry.
If you get angry or give up.
You'll go back to the first gate.
And if you finish the food.
You'll be considered a loser and go back to the first gate.
What should we do?
We can't give up.
Rai is a loser.
So we have to be patient.
Yes, we have to be patient.
Even though I don't like tomatoes.
But I have to be patient.
I have to eat this tomato.
As long as I have a snake in my body.
I want to eat meat.
Especially this tomato.
We have to be patient, Fah.
You have to handle your emotions.
Because we have to go through all this.
Yes, Vega.
To be continued...
Concentrate.
And read the mantra.
So you'll be stable.
Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
They must be cold.
And they fainted.
It's better if we carry them with a pole.
Let's go.
Daffata.
Why is the magic useless?
The magic can't work.
Because the air here is too cold.
Now...
How can we save them?
Let's carry them one by one.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
It's bad, sir.
Jack and Hit are weakening.
Mike, too.
This kid, too, sir.
We have to hurry.
If we're late, these kids will die.
Oh, my God.
Ray, you're out, too?
Yes.
I don't want to eat vegetables.
You don't want to eat vegetables?
Vegetables are good for your health, Ray.
Why do you have to eat vegetables?
It's not good.
Ray.
Where's Alfa?
Alfa has been locked up twice.
It's been a long time.
It's better to just have fun.
I'm sure I'll win.
This is called winning without fighting.
I'm excited.
What if we become friends?
But Alfa is afraid of me.
I have a strange power.
I can make everyone freeze.
Now the school is frozen.
But who's going to do it?
The one who will do it is a fairy.
A fairy?
Go, go, go.
Achieve all your dreams.
Never stop.
Go, go, go.
Fight with all your might.
Make yourself proud.
Go, go, go.
Let's dream.
Never stop.