To be continued...
Go, go, go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go, go, go!
We can do it!
What's this, Prof?
It seems like someone has changed the tool...
into a moving tool.
What has that tool moved?
Somewhere else.
I don't know where it is.
I found it, Prof.
Behind the wall.
In the room.
Behind the wall?
The prince of darkness has no mercy.
He even conspired against me.
Drink that, prince.
And get your power.
What's that?
The Prince of Darkness
I can't do it!
I don't want to be treated like my parents.
Dad...
Mom...
Please help me.
Dad...
Mom...
Please help me.
Dad...
Mom...
We'll help you, Alva.
You're all going to fight me.
Go, go, go!
Alva!
Spaghet, you need to get out of here.
I'm going to save you.
Go, go, go!
You need to get out of here.
No, you have to jump now.
Come on, Mom.
Hurry, Alva.
We can't hold on much longer.
Hurry!
Alva, you're the only one who can save Mom.
You have to jump now.
You're the only one who can fight the Prince of Darkness.
Come on, Alva.
Hurry!
Dad...
Mom...
Alva!
Once again, our son succeeded.
Anggara.
How far is the end of this cliff?
I don't know, sir.
But with a cliff this high, he shouldn't be safe.
The End
Gosh, I'm so sleepy.
I feel like I'm going to faint.
Where are you going, Fega?
Wait a minute.
I want to ask the Prince of Darkness.
Oh, Fega.
Can't you see?
The teachers are busy.
It's not good to disturb them.
But you know you're in danger.
You have to be strong.
You're right.
Do you want to come with us?
Rita, do you want to come with us?
Let's go.
Here, hold this.
But what about Tole?
Just leave him alone.
Let's go.
What's wrong, kids?
Why aren't you sleeping?
We can't sleep.
We're thinking about Alva.
Oh, right.
Soldiers.
Can you fix this telescope?
The clothes are wrinkled.
It's badly damaged.
We can't fix it.
Professor Purwa.
Is it possible for you to fix this?
That's none of your business.
There's one person who can do it.
His name is Panji.
He's a magician.
But his residence is very far from here.
In Semak Forest.
It's okay, Professor.
Even though it's far, the important thing is that the telescope can be fixed.
Yes, because we want to find Alva.
Semak Forest is a dangerous place.
There are ball monsters there.
Ball monsters can devour anything.
They can absorb your fear.
We're not afraid, Professor.
We'll keep fighting.
Because we want to save Alva.
Right, guys?
Yes.
We're not afraid.
You're true friends.
Friends who are always there when you're in trouble.
You're always there when you're in pain.
I'm amazed and proud of you.
Professor.
Allow me to accompany these children...
...to go to that dangerous forest.
Don't, Megantara.
I need your help to build this school.
To help the teachers.
Yes.
We're not afraid, Tentara.
We'll go alone.
The important thing is that we're always together.
Right, guys?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Professor.
I'll train them first.
The spell to destroy the ball monsters.
Okay.
Rey, Vega, Belita.
Pay attention.
As soon as I open this bag...
...a monster or something will come out...
...that will scare you.
How to avoid being scared?
It's easy.
Don't be afraid at all.
Understand?
In this lesson...
...when you see something scary...
...you have to imagine something funny.
You know? Something funny.
Okay.
Then, recite this spell.
Go, go, Medi.
When you recite this spell...
...something that scares you will turn into something funny.
Very funny.
And if you laugh...
...the scary monster...
...will...
...defeat you.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Good.
First, I'll give you a chance.
Rey.
What will Rey see...
...when she comes out of this bag?
Barga.
Why Barga? I'm scared.
Rey, don't be afraid. Just attack.
Barga.
Where are you, Tara?
How?
Why am I so scared?
I told you.
Imagine something funny.
Something funny.
Why is it so hard to imagine something funny?
Concentrate.
Medi.
Good, Rey.
Look.
Barga and Duta.
Where is Duta?
Yes.
Success.
You succeeded, Rey.
Good.
Yes.
Very good.
Okay.
Second.
Now, it's your turn.
Okay, sir.
Let's see.
What will come out of this bag?
Professor Purwa.
It's easy. I'm not scared.
That's good.
Vega.
You challenged me?
Okay.
You will not pass my class.
I will make sure of that.
No, Professor Purwa.
I don't want to.
I don't want to miss the class.
Vega.
When Professor Purwa came out, you said it's easy.
You're not scared.
Now, you're scared.
Come on.
Concentrate.
You're the smartest in the class.
You can answer difficult questions.
Yes.
Let's go, Vega.
Let's go.
What?
You're scared.
You're not scared of monsters.
You're scared of your grades.
Come on.
Imagine it.
It's funny.
Come on.
Please.
Imagine it.
Vega.
Wait.
Let's go, Vega.
Medhi.
Professor Purwa is a judge.
Professor Purwa is famous for being fierce...
...and cruel.
When he's teaching...
...now, he's soft like...
...a boneless meat.
Hey.
You can't pass.
Okay.
Next.
We're pretty boys.
Let's go forward.
Let's go.
We have to pass.
Let's open the bag.
What do you think will scare him?
Concentration.
Rika.
You're a monster.
You won't have friends.
Listen.
You're a kid.
Join me and be my son.
I don't want to.
I don't want to leave my friends.
Pelita.
Don't cry, Pelita.
Concentration.
Concentrate, Pelita.
Focus.
Remember.
Imagine.
It's funny.
Try to remember.
Don't think it's funny.
Concentration.
Uncle Mendy.
This is how you become a high school student.
What a sick, sick, loose, to die.
Like I said, it's for you.
Remember.
There's a rat eating rice.
Focus and concentration.
You'll succeed.
Thank you, soldier.
But remember.
You have to be careful.
And come back safely.
Don't force me.
Don't worry.
We'll be safe, soldier.
Ray can make a poem.
Good.
I can do it too, soldier.
Pelita.
You can make a poem like Uncle Megantara.
Listen.
It's sweet.
Don't cry.
We'll come back, soldier.
That's good.
The most beautiful bird in the sky...
...is Pelita.
Vega, keep this.
What is it, sir?
It's a magic lamp.
When you're in trouble or lost...
...you can turn it on.
And it will bring you back to school.
Yes, sir.
This is a magic map.
This map will lead you to your destination.
Keep it well.
You three have to be careful.
Remember.
You have to...
Focus.
And concentrate.
Vega, this is the map.
Ray.
This is the map.
Let's go, sir.
Kids.
Be careful.
Come back soon.
Let's go, sir.
Vega and Pelita are sleeping.
No.
Vega, wake them up.
Why are they gone?
I'm jealous.
Look at me.
Because I'm in your team.
Why did I become one?
Hey!
Let's follow him.
Okay.
I ran out of magic.
Why did I fly?
I don't know.
I'm flying.
Wait for me.
Vega.
Ray.
Pelita.
Wait.
Where did they go?
Guys.
We will pass through a forest area.
So, be ready to fly zigzag.
Because there are many tall trees.
Okay.
Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Why are they flying zigzag like that?
Like they're apologizing.
Tole, you have to be able to do it.
There's a car.
Ouch.
My head is aching.
It hurts.
Ouch.
I can do it.
I have to fight.
Wait, sir.
With these 12 stones,
I will give my soul to 12 people.
This is mine.
Those who dare to challenge me.
To be continued...
NEXT EPISODE
It's changing.
Let's go.
Guys.
Now, we have arrived at Semak Forest.
Are you scared, Rey?
No, I'm not.
I'm not scared.
If I'm scared, why would I follow you?
Let's go.
Wait, sir.
I think we have to split up.
I will go to the right with Vega.
You will go to the left alone.
What do you think?
Let's split up.
Why do we have to split up?
I'm scared.
I'm going to die in the forest.
Ouch.
Mom.
Rey!
Vega!
Kelita!
Don't do that!
There are so many of you.
To be continued...
Maybe, this is the 8th floor.
I have to get out of here.
Ouch, it hurts.
Thank God, you're awake.
To be continued...
What's wrong?
If you don't want to drink, it's okay.
But don't blame me if you're getting drunk.
To be continued...
My body can't take it anymore.
That's good.
Whose house is this?
Sir, who are you?
And where am I?
To be continued...
This is my house.
I saw you in the forest.
And it looks like you came from a high place.
Yes.
Someone is mean to me.
Don't move!
Covering light!
Alpha!
You better get out of here.
You have to get out of here now.
Sir, let's go.
Hurry up, Alpha.
We can't hold on any longer.
That's why I jumped off the cliff.
Where are you from?
I'm from Sihir School.
Do you know the way back to Sihir School?
I want to go home.
I'm sorry, I don't know.
I can't help you.
Because I can't leave this place.
How about this?
For now, you stay here until you get better.
After you get better, I'll give you a map.
And you can continue your journey home.
Yes, sir.
Just think of this house as your own.
Take whatever you want.
But there's one thing I want.
There's a hut next to this house.
With a black door.
You can't go in there without any reason.
Yes, sir.
I promise.
Good.
Hold this.
Who is this guy?
He looks nice.
But why is he living in this scary house?
And there are so many ghosts.
Where are you going?
To be continued....
I'm so scared.
What if someone is waiting for me?
What is that?
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I'll report you to the police.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so lazy to study?
You only think about eating.
You're such a coward.
That's enough.
You're a coward.
I'm sorry.
That's Tole's voice.
I heard it too.
But it's impossible that Tole is here.
Maybe he's in a trap.
But I'm sure that Tole's voice is clear.
I think this is Tole's voice.
That's right.
Let's go.
I heard Tole's voice.
I'm going to sleep.
So, I can recover faster.
Let us go.
Whose voice is that?
Help.
Let us go.
Don't hurt us.
Please, let us go.
Help.
Let us go.
Don't hurt us.
Please, let us go.
Where are you going?
Sir.
I heard someone asking for help.
From the door.
Maybe it's just your hallucination.
You should go back to your room.
Get some rest.
So, you can recover faster.
Is it just my hallucination?
I think I heard something.
Okay.
I'm going back to my room.
Did you hear that?
Yes, I heard it too.
I think it's coming from there.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
You have to learn.
Don't just think about eating.
No.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Who is that?
Why is Tole scared of him?
It must be the ball monster.
Tole, don't cry.
Rih, Pegah, Lita.
Tole, you have to concentrate.
You have to talk to that person.
And use Medi's mantra.
Hurry up.
I don't want to.
I don't want to attack my mom.
That's not your mom, Tole.
That's the ball monster.
That's right, Lita.
You have to focus.
And use Medi's mantra.
Come on.
Concentrate.
You can do it.
Imagine if your mom is funny.
Come on.
Hurry up. Concentrate.
Yes, ma'am.
Use Medi's mantra.
To be continued...
The ball is gone.
Where did it go?
What are you doing here?
Me?
I'm here to pick you up.
I want to come with you.
Are you scared of me?
You were sleeping last night.
Yes, I was.
You were still sleeping last night.
Where were you?
Why?
I just woke up.
What are we going to do now?
I don't know.
We're going to Mr. Panji's house.
He can fix our telescope.
The broken one.
That's right. Let's go.
Let's go.
I'm bored in my room.
What should I do?
Oh, right.
He helped me.
I should help him.
But...
What should I do with the broken one?
It's broken.
Trash!
To be continued...
I'm so tired.
Trash!
It's clean.
It looks neat.
That means, I'm happy.
Help!
Let us go!
Please, let us go!
That voice again.
I think I know that voice.
But why don't I know it?
It looks like they're rebuilding the school, sir.
We have to stop them.
To be continued...
I think I know that voice.
But why don't I know it?
To be continued...
If I open this door, he'll be mad.
Please, don't!
Don't kill me!
Go!
Go away!
That voice again.
I think he's asking for help.
I have to help him.
Should I pay him?
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, sir.
Today, the teachers and I...
will rebuild the school...
that was destroyed by the explosion yesterday.
And this school's renovation...
will take a lot of time and effort from the teachers.
For the next 12 hours,
we, the teachers, will concentrate on the school's renovation.
And as long as the process goes on,
it can't be stopped.
We ask you...
to always be vigilant.
Always guard the school.
In every corner, keep an eye on everything.
Don't let anyone...
enter the school.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
And while we prepare the energy,
Professor Titan will teach you...
the Totok Mantra to fight evil.
You have to focus and concentrate.
We have to fight together for our school.
Yes, sir.
What magic trick are we going to learn, sir?
Give me a smile.
We're going to learn a magic trick...
without using tongs.
Without using tongs?
How can we use tongs?
Yes, sir.
What do we do, sir?
You just found out.
Now, keep your tongs...
Every creature has a weak spot.
It's around the neck,
the waist,
and the feet.
Do you understand?
Give me a smile.
Check this out.
Do you understand?
Give me a smile.
Check this out.
Try attacking me.
Are you sure, sir?
Don't be rude.
Yes, Jack.
Yes, sir.
Sir, help me.
Sir.
Help me, sir.
To open the Totok Mantra,
you just have to press...
one of the points of the thumb.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Now, you have to try...
to find your partner.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Now, try to find your partner.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
There's a boss.
Help me.
He's gone.
Help me, boss.
Try to press it.
Why can't I do it?
Try to step back.
Let me teach you.
Like this, Tommy.
Don't play around.
Are you ready?
Let's build our school.
Pembangkali!
It looks like they're building another school, sir.
Stop them, Angkar.
Raptor.
Let's try to catch them.
Hurry.
Let's finish this.
Where are you going?
This forest is dangerous.
You shouldn't play here.
We're going to this forest...
because we're looking for a resident here.
His name is Mr. Panji. Do you know him?
Yes, I do.
I don't want to get involved.
I still want to live. Excuse me.
What does he mean?
Why is he going?
I don't know.
Let's keep looking.
Where are you going?
I need to help him.
What's that?
I'm locking it.
To be continued...
Help!
Professor!
Can I help you for a moment?
Yes, Gantara.
The school's repair process has begun.
If we stop it now, everything will be in vain.
I told you not to come near this cave...
let alone open the door and go inside.
But what happened?
You've broken my advice...
and you've broken your own promise.
No.
I heard a voice asking for help.
Actually...
who is it?
It's none of your business.
If there's someone out there,
it's my business.
It's my business to keep people safe.
Actually, who are you?
Why are you looking for someone like that?
I don't want to be...
a bad person.
If I'm a bad person,
why would I save you?
If you can't follow my orders,
please leave.
Leave and never come back!
But...
I said leave!
I think that person is really creepy.
But...
whatever.
It's better if I go home now.
A few days later...
This house is scary.
Yes.
There are so many monsters.
So many.
A few days later...
Come in.
Excuse me.
Sir.
Yes, what is it?
Is this really Mr. Panji's house?
Yes.
I want to ask for help.
Can you fix this telescope?
I can.
But I don't want to fix it.
All of you leave now.
Help!
Stop!
We have to help him!
But how?
A few days later...
No way.
If I knew this would happen, I wouldn't help him.
But luckily he didn't manage to get in this room.
I have to change the key.
The key to the painting.
From now on...
if you want to open this door,
you have to tell me.
Alfa.
This is the key.
This is your food for the day.
The door has a mantra.
In the name of your child.
To be continued...
Please don't kill us.
Please.
To be continued...
Help!
Guys, we have to help Jack.
We can't leave him behind.
But how? The monster is so tall.
Don't forget, you can fly.
Use the poppy oil.
Okay, Nick.
Get ready.
Fly!
Boss!
Help!
Help us, Boss!
Get ready to attack.
Attack!
Help us, Boss!
Tommy, help Jack.
Jack.
Jack, Boss.
Help!
Jack!
Come on!
Yes!
Thank you, Boss.
Bye.
Wait!
Hurry up!
To be continued...
I have to watch the recruits.
Watch out, Nick!
Attack!
Professor.
Can I help Nick for a moment?
Don't, Megantara.
We have to focus.
The school is on fire.
But Nick looks injured, Professor.
Megantara, Nick is a strong boy.
He can handle this.
We have to trust the kids.
We have to be sure...
that they can do this.
What's your next plan, sir?
I want revenge...
on the people who destroyed this school.
And the first one...
is me.
What should I do, sir?
We will do...
a big attack.
Get ready.
To be continued...
Sir.
What's wrong with him?
He's under attack.
Attack?
What attack?
Judging from the attack...
it looks like a monster attack.
Let's hurry.
Monster?
Don't tell me...
Help!
Is this a monster attack?
Yes, sir.
Don't go to the house in the middle of the forest.
The owner is raising monsters.
Be careful, sir.
Help!
The house in the middle of the forest?
Don't tell me...
that's your house?
Guys.
While Raptor is chasing Tommy, Jack and Mike,
let's attack them from the side.
I told you not to fight.
That's why you don't have to fight.
What's wrong with you?
You're so mean.
I told you this is for fishing.
So, don't fight.
To be continued...
Don't stop. Go, go, go.
Never stop. Go, go, go.
Fight with all your might.
Go, go, go.
Make yourself proud. Go, go, go.
Let's dream. Go, go, go.
We'll make it.