To be continued...
What are you doing to my sister?
I'm here to see you.
You have my permission.
No one can stop you.
Good afternoon, children.
Wow, you can make the hat.
Wow, it's so cool.
Don't you dare to enter this room.
Alfa entered the secret room and met the third-in-command.
What we fear will happen.
What's going on?
Children, calm down.
I'm here, ma'am.
There's a demon who managed to enter.
Is it the food of the children?
Yes, ma'am.
Don't make noise.
It's better if you don't come out now.
And don't come out before I order you.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Come on.
Do you see Vega?
Vega.
Where are you?
I was with Vega.
He said he wanted to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Ma'am, don't.
We can't go out with him.
He's safe.
But he's our friend.
What if something happens to him?
It's dangerous.
Ma'am, wait.
What's going on?
No!
What do you mean?
It's huge!
Why is it so small?
Ma'am!
What's going on?
Let's go.
Fire.
Murder.
Where are we going?
Let's go.
Help!
Hurry up.
Ma'am.
Vega, run!
Run!
You!
My family.
Let the kid go.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Fire.
Murder.
Let's go.
Where are you?
Mr. Fitir.
Fire.
Murder.
Lolipop.
The teeth can kill.
But you can kill it through the teeth.
Concentrate.
Use your Lolipop.
Fire.
Murder.
Let's go.
Alva.
Thank you, Alva.
It's not your fault anymore.
You're the only one who can do this.
Why me, Professor?
Alva.
Promise me.
Don't tell anyone.
If you've defeated the monster.
Now.
Go back to the safe house.
Let your friends handle this.
The monster.
What do we do?
Barga is a very strong monster.
He's the hand of the 8th prince.
The only one who can defeat him...
...is the 8th prince...
...and a chosen child.
Who is he?
Alva.
He's the chosen child.
The daughter of Gamar and Akira.
She will be our saviour.
That's why...
...we have to protect her.
Train her...
...with all our abilities.
So that when the time comes...
...Alva can fight the 8th prince.
Agni.
Please keep this a secret.
Don't let anyone know...
...that the chosen child is in this school.
If anyone finds out...
...the 8th prince...
...will find out sooner than we think.
Yes, sir.
We're both...
...ready to be sworn.
I swear.
Where's the monster?
Calm down, Ray.
There's no monster here.
That's right.
But I was in Gamar.
Weren't we fighting the monster?
That's right.
But you fainted.
And?
Where's the monster now?
Who's the other one?
There he is.
Hey, Pegah.
Don't go in there.
I'm curious.
I woke up in Gamar.
But you fainted.
And the teachers...
...and Professor Aldebaran...
...came.
Professor Aldebaran is the monster?
That's right.
So, you're the monster.
Professor Aldebaran was fighting...
...and you're the monster.
As long as Professor Aldebaran is here...
...we're safe.
That's right.
Why am I here?
Thank God.
Both of you are awake.
Professor Adi.
Where's the monster?
Calm down, Professor Purwa.
The monster is defeated.
So, the Dark Lord is here.
Because only he can defeat it.
Calm down, Professor Purwa.
The Dark Lord is not here.
But...
...the chosen one has defeated him.
Who is he?
I'm sorry.
But I promised not to tell anyone.
Clearly...
...the chosen one is among our students here.
Alva?
Alva.
You have to protect the Stone of Eternity in this school.
What is the Stone of Eternity?
The Stone of Eternity is a very strong stone.
That stone cannot fall into the wrong hands.
You have to protect that stone.
But how do I protect it?
Protect it with your heart, Alva.
Why do you know about this school?
And you know my name?
Who are you?
One day, you will know who we really are.
Hey!
Who are you?
What is it?
I had a weird dream.
What dream?
This.
Help me.
What is it?
I was visited by someone.
And that person is really nice.
I can feel it.
They love me.
And the strangest thing is...
they told me to protect the Stone of Eternity in this school.
The Stone of Eternity?
What is that?
I've never heard of it.
Maybe it's just a dream.
I'm going to sleep. I'm sleepy.
Wait!
The dream is real.
It's real.
The person in the dream must be serious.
Who is the person in your dream?
I don't know. I don't know.
How about this?
Let's ask Centara tomorrow.
Maybe she knows.
Where is Centara?
There she is.
Really?
Let's go.
Centara.
What is the Stone of Eternity?
The Stone of Eternity...
is the stone that guards the three-headed dragon.
So, the Stone of Eternity really exists?
Alva.
You...
How do you know the Stone of Eternity?
You're just in the first grade.
You don't know that yet.
Over there.
I'm busy cooking for the three-headed dragon.
So, the three-headed dragon...
likes rendang, gudeg, and asinan.
This.
This is my cooking.
I love eating gudeg, asinan, and rendang.
I'm hungry. Don't disturb me.
Over there.
Let's go.
Gosh.
My mouth.
I can't keep my mouth shut.
There's a stone behind the dragon.
And the dragon guards the stone.
What's so special about the stone?
I don't know.
To be continued...
Don't you dare to eat...
or do anything...
during my lesson.
You all know that.
The students have entered our school.
And for that, there's a new rule that will be applied.
After 8 p.m.
All students are forbidden to leave the classroom.
And if anyone steps...
the perpetrator will be punished.
And one classroom will be punished.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Now I'm going to teach you a new spell...
that you can use...
to take other things.
Pay attention.
Rafaatong Buku.
Now...
focus.
And you all try.
Start.
Rafaatong Buku.
That's so cool!
Rafaatong Buku!
Rafaatong Buku.
Alva.
You are to clean this page.
How long do you need?
Three hours, Prof.
Living in this world is not as easy as living in the real world.
You have three minutes to clean this page.
And you have to finish it.
Do you understand?
Three minutes.
Prof.
I think, Prof.
For Alva's size,
the punishment is too heavy.
This is still in my class.
So I have the right to decide anything for the students' education.
I forgot, Prof.
If so, please continue.
Thank you.
Alva.
Do as I say.
If you can't finish it,
your punishment will be heavier.
Three.
Two minutes and 59 seconds.
Two minutes and 58 seconds.
Tukang Sekotong.
Tukang Lemper.
There's a ripe fruit.
I'm hungry.
I'll try it.
I'm sure it's delicious.
Dafatong Buah.
Yes.
I'm hungry.
Dafatong Buah.
Oh, yes.
I've learned the Mantra Bindai Menda.
It's a good idea.
I can use the mantra for this punishment.
Let's try.
Dafatong Ketas Kecil.
Dafatong Karti.
Dafatong Jokri.
It's heavy.
I did it.
I've finished it.
Three.
Two.
One.
Three.
Two.
One.
Three.
Two.
One.
Three.
Two.
One.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Twenty.
Twenty-one.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three.
You have to answer my question.
Who's the chosen one?
I can't answer, Prof.
Because my mouth has been swore by the mantra to tell anyone.
I see.
Now you have to do what I ask you to do.
Because you know who the chosen one is.
You have to be able to order the chosen one...
...to enter the secret room...
...and take the stone to his body.
Yes, Prof.
One more thing.
You have to lead the chosen one to take the stone to his body.
Alva, we want to help you with the punishment.
Yes.
Do we still need to do it?
No.
The punishment is over.
Why is it so fast?
Yes.
How is it possible?
Alva, come to my room now.
Why?
Because you're smart.
You know everything.
But I don't know everything.
Let's find out.
Alva, I called you because you have to do something for me.
Tonight.
Before the sun rises, you have to go back to the secret room...
...and take the Stone of Eternity for me.
Isn't that forbidden?
This school is in danger, Alva.
And only the Stone of Eternity can save us all.
But why do I have to take the stone?
Because you have defeated Vargas.
The monster will come back to life when the sun rises.
But how, ma'am?
There's a Triceratops over there.
And it's very strong.
I will tell you about the Triceratops.
300 years ago.
There were three great warriors.
They loved their heroes so much.
They gave them their favorite food.
Until one day...
...the great Triceratops...
...came back to life.
The great Triceratops...
Until one day...
...they were faced by the Dark Lord's army.
The Dark Lord's army.
And they were defeated.
The Dark Lord's army was defeated.
Ashifa and Daini died.
The Triceratops felt very lonely...
...because they lost their master.
The cry of the Triceratops...
...lit up the darkness.
This caused the three Triceratops to unite...
...and form a powerful army.
So, the three Triceratops...
...can eat the same food as their master?
I saw the army cooking three different foods.
Is that true for the Triceratops?
It's true, Alfa.
I've told you everything.
Now, it's up to you to decide...
...whether you want to be a Triceratops or not.
Now, it's up to you.
You're the only one who can take the Stone of Eternity...
...and save our lives.
To be continued...
It's 6 o'clock.
Now, we have to make three different foods...
...that the Triceratops likes.
That is, rendang, udang, and asinan.
The Triceratops is afraid of us.
So, we have to burn the Stone of Eternity.
That means we have to go to the kitchen.
That's it. Let's go.
Professor!
Who's there?
Come out!
I said, come out or I'll have to use magic.
One.
Two.
Professor Purwa.
I want to talk to you.
Can you give me a chance?
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Hurry up. Let's cook.
Okay.
Be careful.
Help me.
The Triceratops
Come on, Sar.
Come on.
The Triceratops
It's like someone's cooking.
Who's in there?
The Triceratops
It's heavy.
Be careful.
The Triceratops
Rey, Vega.
The Triceratops doesn't like this food.
And it's getting worse.
You have to defend yourself.
So I can face it.
Okay.
Let's go.
The Triceratops
It's so scary.
Be careful. It can burn your mouth.
Rey, wake up.
It's not blue.
It's the Triceratops.
The Triceratops
Vega!
Rey, wake up.
It's not blue.
It's the Triceratops.
The Triceratops can kill you if you don't have the antidote.
What should we do?
We have to take it to the clinic.
No, no, no.
Just do your job.
You have to take the Triceratops before the sun sets.
I'll take care of it.
But...
It's okay.
The Triceratops
Let's go, Rey.
Alpha.
You have to succeed.
The Triceratops
The Triceratops is not ready yet.
You'd better go to the clinic now.
They are not the Triceratops.
But they are...
The Triceratops' daughter.
Alpha.
Why did you take the Triceratops?
Professor Agni asked me to.
Because this school is in danger.
Only the Triceratops can save this school.
Alpha must be released.
Three more days until the full moon.
And if in the full moon, the Dark Lord gets the Triceratops...
He will get unlimited power.
And he will destroy this world.
To be continued...
Go, go, go...
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go...
Fight with all your might
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go...
Let's dream
We'll make it