To be continued...
Go Go Go, make yourself proud
Go Go Go, let's dream
Go Go Go, we can do it
The monster likes chocolate
Weird, how can a monster like that like chocolate?
You have to destroy all the chocolate in the village
If necessary, destroy all the chocolate trees there
Go Go Go, let's go
The monster is great
The monster is not dead, it just escaped
So the monster can come back?
It can come back if it smells chocolate
The chocolate is in my hand
And you tell Alva
If Alva still wants this child to live
Then she has to give up
The sound of a flute played by the head of darkness
Makes Altagoga calm
Be a servant
You teach the sound of the flute
Okay, I'll teach
Seriously?
Even if you don't like it, even if you force it
Eat it, Momo
Professor
What's up?
What's wrong, Vega?
Alva went back to the village
What's wrong with Alva?
Because...
The police kidnapped Professor Rangkara
And Professor Rangkara said
Alva has to go there
There's no one to accompany her, she has to be alone
If not, the police will be in trouble
I'm in a hurry
I'll go after Alva
I won't let Rangkara hurt Alva
I'll go too, Professor
I have to go save Alva
If Alva's hair reaches Rangkara
I'll cut off Rangkara's body
I'll go too, Professor
You can go
Yes
But there's a condition
What's the condition?
Miffy is Vega's daughter
Why did Professor Rangkara become a witch?
What does that mean?
We're going to be witches
With a kid like you
It'll be easier for me to hold your hand
I'm Megantara Rangkara
Wow, Professor's clothes smell so good
Eat this, Vega
Wow, a witch
That witch won't be gone for a week
Thank you, Professor
It's a rat
It bit me
A rat!
It bit me!
Chicken satay
With fermented rice
Relax, man
It's still a long way
It's still a long way?
I can't breathe here
I'm going to die
A rat!
When's the last time you took a shower?
For me, cleanliness is number one
The last time I took a shower
Was three weeks ago
Huh? Three weeks ago?
I'm bleeding!
It stinks!
Excuse me
Professor, thank God you came
Professor, please help me
The rat was kidnapped
Please, Professor
Yes, I know
That's why we came here
Thank you, Professor
I'm sure you can find the rat
Come on, Professor
I'll show you my way
A rat!
Ouch!
That's not how you do it, Alva!
You taught me!
Sorry, I'm still learning
Okay, I'll try again
That's enough!
You're always wrong!
You should just continue
You're going to fail!
Don't be like that, Popo!
I'll try again
Popo, where are you going?
That's right!
I'm sure you're dancing with the rat
Hooray! I can do it!
Yeah!
Hooray!
I can do it!
Thank you!
Thank you for teaching me!
Huh?
Popo got hugged?
Usually, everyone treats Popo rough
Popo...
Popo, why are you crying?
Popo, give me a hug!
Now, you can do it!
Let's go to the cave!
Okay, let's go!
Let's go there!
Galaxy, are we still there?
We're still going straight ahead, Sir
Frita!
Oh no, I'm leading Frita!
Poor her, she's all alone there!
Frita, it's me!
Can you hear me?
Why are you doing this to me, Sir?
I'm so scared, Sir
It's so dark here, Sir!
I'm so scared, Sir!
What's going on?
I'm in the cave, I'm being kidnapped, Sir!
Sir!
Shut up!
Now, you can't talk anymore, little girl
I've never been through that path with my father
It's full of rocks and dark, Sir
Please help me, Sir
Sir!
How dare you use that mirror without my permission!
Frita!
Sir!
I think this is not the right path
Galaxy, who's the real killer?
Alkara, Sir
How do you know?
Wasn't Frita alone in this room?
And why did you bring us here?
Shouldn't you be leading us to the path of rocks?
Do you know the right path?
I don't know, Sir
Too bad, you're too late to know that
This is sand, Sir
You're wrong, Sir
This sand emits magic
It's useless here
I'm sorry, Professor
I can't lead you to the path of rocks
Only Alpha can go there
Galaxy!
Galaxy, where are you?
Where is it?
Popo, it's still far away
It's over there
Okay, let's go there
Be careful
Popo!
Wait for me
Popo, thank you for saving me
Popo!
Let's go, Sir
Professor, there's an avalanche!
I'm scared!
Ray, Vega, help me!
Help me, don't touch me!
Find a rope or something that can help them
There's an avalanche, Professor!
Ray, help me!
Hurry!
Keep going!
Keep pulling!
The rope!
Hold the rope!
Dad!
Thank God, we're safe
Vega, Ray, thank you
You two have saved us
You're welcome, Professor
It's not a loss if you bring me and Vega
Why, Galaxy? Why did you do that?
It's none of your business, Professor
Why, Galaxy? Why?
I'm sorry, Professor
I was threatened by this avalanche
If only they could help me
I don't want to lose you, Professor
Help me
Mr. Galaxy
Why did you do that?
But you know where the real treasure is, right?
I know, Professor
Come on, I'll show you the way
What's this?
How do I get in?
I know how to open the door
And then?
Shake, shake, shake
I'm scared, I'm scared
If I'm still there, I'll be killed by Professor Ankara
Because I'm scared
If you're scared, you don't have to come in
Let me come in
I can't, I can't
Even though I don't want to
Even though I'm suffering
I have to come in
Okay, you can come in
But you have to be careful
I'm sorry
Boss!
What are you doing?
Don't do this to me
I told you to come in
I'm scared
I'm scared!
Pita!
Where are you, Pita?
Boss!
Thank God you're okay
Let's get out of here
To be continued...
Let's go!
I'm scared
No one can help you now
Fight the devil
Let's go!
Hurry!
Help me!
To be continued...
Papa, wake up!
Wake up, Papa!
To be continued...
Papa, wake up!
Pita!
To be continued...
We're finally together, Sis
Yes
Thank you, Popo, for helping us
It's okay, right?
Yes, it's okay
Let's go
It's Karah!
You can't just leave like that
Because we're not done yet
You're a traitor
It's your turn
After her
I'm here, Sis!
To be continued...
And now...
Feel this
Don't!
To be continued...
Wake up, Sis!
Papa!
Wake up, Papa!
Professor Jahat!
Papa, wake up!
Wake up!
Wake up, Papa!
Alva, where's your father?
Where's your father?
Papa!
Wake up, Papa!
Alva!
Alva seems to have been hit by a bullet
Watch your step!
Professor, we're not done yet
We still have to close the cave's door with a spell
So Antaboga won't appear again forever
That's right, Professor
Let me try, Professor
What if we try together?
Who knows, we might be able to do it
Let's do it
To be continued...
Wake up, Papa!
Why is the door so strong?
You try, Alva
I'm sorry, Professor
But Alva doesn't seem to be able to do it
Alva, do you want to try?
Of course
Let's do it
Concentrate!
You can do it!
Corvo!
Alva, you're so cool!
You're amazing, Alva
My guess was right
Alva is...
Alva!
Alva, wake up!
Dad!
Wake up, Dad!
We can do it!
Vega... Ray...
Dadara...
Welcome, Alva
Vega, where's Polita?
She's fine
But, Mr. Galaxy...
What about Mr. Galaxy?
Mr. Galaxy saved you and Polita
He was attacked by Professor Angkara
He's being treated by Professor Lebaran
Dad...
Dad, wake up...
Be patient, Polita
You have to be sincere
Your dad is in there
I only had my dad when I was little
Now, he's gone
I'm all alone
Polita...
You're not alone
We're here for you
I want to go to school with you
Do you want to?
Yes
Come with me later
You want to, don't you?
Yes, I do
Thank you
6 months later
Now, we can all go back to magic school
Polita, we'll always be together
So, don't be sad
Dad...
Wait...
I want to come with you
Popo, you can't
We're going to school
If I don't come with you, I'll die
Alva...
The only way for me to not come with you...
...is for you to stop being my teacher
But, what do I do?
The only way is to give your hair to Popo
Then, she'll be free
Cut!
6 months later
This is for Popo?
Yes
Are you serious?
Now, you're free
You're not a servant
Free?
I'm free!
Thank you, Alva
You're the best teacher ever!
You're welcome, Popo
You helped me a lot
I'll go now
Okay
6 months later
Good evening, kids
Good evening, Sir
Now, I'd like to introduce a new student
Her name is Pelita
Pelita?
Hi, I'm Pelita
My name is Toli
Pelita, please sit with me
Come here, kids
I'm Pelita
What do you want to eat?
Kids, please continue eating
Okay, Sir
Alva!
Why are you so big?
It's like you haven't eaten for a week
I'm confused, too
Why do I keep getting bigger?
I feel hungry
I'm confused
6 months later
Alva!
What's wrong with you?
I don't know
I'm scared
I want to eat a rat
I know it's delicious
Do you want to try?
Alva!
What's wrong with you?
Popo!
Alva!
Alva, wake up!
Help!
Alva!
What do you feel now?
I feel dizzy
Alva has been poisoned by a snake!
The snake has to give her the antidote
If not within 3 days
Alva will turn into a snake
It's terrifying!
Where's the antidote?
The antidote?
It's in a place far, far, far away
It's in a mysterious island
A mysterious island far away from home
The antidote is very rare
It's called the liquid of life
The liquid of life is very powerful
It can cure all diseases
All diseases
And it's said that the liquid of life can revive a dead person
So, very amazing!
Very amazing!
Professor
I will go there to find it
You can't, Megantara
Only children can go there
Okay, I'll go there
Me too
Should we let the children go there?
You're right, Professor
I'm also worried
This is a difficult decision for me
I don't think I can let the children go there
Without our protection
But we can't let Alva turn into a snake
Professor
We often pass dangerous obstacles
Because we're always compact
So, we can pass this obstacle
Yes, Professor
I hope we can pass this obstacle
Okay, I agree
Thank you, Professor
What's wrong?
There's a lot of sand
You don't have to be like that
We're your friends, aren't we, Ren?
Yes, we're friends
So, no matter how hard it is
Or if we're happy, we're together
That's right, Ren
Best, Ren
Wow
I'm Pelipir
I'm Nangka
I'm bullied in the market
You don't know me
I'm Megantara
Tentara
Why?
I'm too cute when I was a kid
But I'm handsome, right?
Tentara, you should join us
Yes
Let's go in
I can do it, right?
Yes
Tentara
I'm not that smart
This island is smarter
Tentara
No!
Don't use magic here
It's dangerous
But, Tentara
If you use magic
The magic will come back to you
Tentara
Catch it
Keep it well
It will be useful for you
At the right time
Tentara
Alva
Vega
Ray
Both of you
The three of you
Remember
You have to be alert
Tentara Kira
We rarely meet, right?
I don't know
But Tentara said
This will be useful
Let's keep it
Welcome to the Mystery Island
You will pass the first gate
Which is
The Gate of Dreams
A place where you can eat all kinds of food
But remember
Once you eat that food
You will not be able to continue your journey to the next place
If you give up
Like a white flag
Automatically
You will be at the first gate
That's great
Ray
Don't worry
The important thing is we have to pass all the challenges
Who will be the first one to set up the blue flag at that place?
He will be the winner
And if there is a disqualified contestant
He will be disqualified
I have to get that liquid of life
I have to lose everything
So I can live again
And remember
That liquid of life is very rare
Only one person can get that liquid of life
Do you understand?
Yes
Before we start
You can get ready
The toilet is over there
And the costume room is over there
Let's go
There is no one who can beat Rayyan
He is so beautiful
He will make us scared
Why is someone missing?
I have to make them scared
So they can run away
Why is someone missing?
I have to make them scared
So they can run away
And remember
I have to make them scared
So they can run away
Help!
What is this?
I am scared
I want to go home
Me too
Are you ready?
Yes
Who are you?
Where are you from?
We are from the inside
We give up
Why do you give up?
Because there are a lot of ghosts
Fishing for anchovies
Who got help
This is a mystery island
There are a lot of ghosts
What about Vega and Rayyan?
Did they get the water of life?
I miss you, dad
Now I don't have anyone
Why did the force reappear?
It's been a long time since it reappeared
After mom died
Mom
Don't leave us
Who are you with?
Rita
Are you ready?
RITA'S SADNESS
Rita
The sadness that's too deep and long
Will make your strength appear
If you're angry
It will endanger you
And others
So you have to be careful
You have to be able to control your emotions
If you're sad
Don't cry
And you have to be calm
I can't be sad
I have to be strong
Until the force reappears
I can't turn it off
There's a ghost here
It will make me scared
There's someone missing
I'm scared
Give me the flag
Give it to the jury
That's it
If I throw the white flag
It means I failed
I can't be scared
Why did she throw the white flag?
I'll scare her again
I'm not scared
I'm not scared of you
Come out
I'm not scared
Why?
You're scared of me, right?
Look at your face
You're so scared of me
You don't know who I am, Raya
I'm not scared of you
I've been beaten
I got hit on my head
You don't know anything about me
Really?
Look at your face
You're so scared of me
Look
I'm not scared of you
She's so scary
Whatever
I'll make her lose
I'm the winner
Where are you going?
What?
Raya!
I have to get rid of her
And win her trust
Because that's the only way
I can live again
You're so cool, Alva
To be continued...
Don't ever stop
Fight with all your heart
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
We'll make it