To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
We will never stop until we get that fire!
So that we can all be one.
Yes, they are one.
We can't let this happen.
I have to stop them.
Don't touch me!
Ouch!
Brita, you're so brave.
You know what?
You're just a bad person who dares to attack his own friend.
I'm a bad person?
He's not a bad person.
He just can't control himself.
I'm glad I can help you.
But you have to remember.
You can't use your feelings.
You have to control yourself.
You have to think for yourself.
And you have to let go of your love for others.
Let me go!
Help!
Shut up!
It's useless to call them.
They won't get you.
Finally, they called me.
I'm so lucky.
Where am I?
Help!
Brita!
Where are you?
I'm here!
What should I do?
I can't help you like this.
I'm over there!
Brita!
Help!
What?
I've learned Pegasus' spell.
This is good.
Let me try.
Pegasus!
She's so small.
How can she help me?
Tell me!
Bulgarda.
I want Bulgarda.
Pegasus!
She's so small.
Bulgarda.
Let go of my rope.
Thank you, Bulgarda.
Vivi Lang.
Brita!
Rai!
Wait!
Where are you?
Brita!
Rai!
Where are you?
Wait!
Brita!
Where are you?
Rai!
Rika!
Alva, I'm here!
Rai!
Where are you?
Alva, I'm here!
Let me go!
Rai!
Let go of the rope!
Rai, are you okay?
You look for Pegasus.
I'll look for Brita.
Let me go!
Help!
Help me, Heran!
Brita.
You must gather your strength and attack them.
Now, you throw the people who seduced you.
Now!
Brita!
Brita, where are you?
Where is Brita?
I don't know.
When I got here, Brita was gone.
Where is she?
Brita!
Rai, use your hairpin.
Okay.
Guys, we are being chased by that guy.
Stop!
Brita, let's go back to school.
Okay, let's go back to school.
Let's go.
Don't follow him anymore.
He is evil.
Let's go back to school.
Don't follow him anymore.
Don't be fooled, Brita.
Do you remember?
They have made you sad.
They have disappointed you.
Brita, let's go.
Let's go back to school.
We are going to play house snakes again.
Let's go, Brita.
Let's go.
Venga!
Are you okay?
Venga.
Brita.
Don't push yourself too much.
It's better for you to take a rest.
Okay?
Brita is so brave.
She made Venga become like this.
I told you.
She is a monster.
That's why we shouldn't get close to her anymore.
I feel sorry for Venga.
I shouldn't have gone.
I'm sorry, Kameran.
You don't have to feel sorry.
Make this a learning experience for you.
You have to remember.
I will never leave you in any condition.
And...
This is your place.
I will always be by your side.
It's true.
Kelita has a very dangerous power.
And we have to be careful to catch her.
We have to prepare more to fight that child.
If we can tame her,
all this snow will melt.
Tri.
You have to make a new weapon.
A great weapon.
A weapon that can defeat the child named Kelita.
Alright.
We will take revenge on them.
Kelita.
Kelita, let's go home.
Let's go back to school.
Come on.
Let's play together again.
I feel sorry for Vega.
Come on, Kelita.
She must be very sad.
She must be thinking about Kelita.
Kelita, let's go home.
Come on, Kelita.
Kelita.
Kelita, let's go home.
Wait.
Wake up, Kelita.
Wake up.
What's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
I'm not sick.
I feel sorry for Vega.
Kelita, let's go home.
Let's go home and play together again.
Tentara, we have to help Vega.
We have to take Vega to Kelita's place.
Tentara, do you feel sorry for her?
Ava, don't worry.
That place is very far away.
We will find a way.
Don't worry.
That place is very far away.
Not only far away,
that place is very dangerous.
That's why, Tentara.
I ask you to help me, Tentara.
To make me safe.
Can you, Tentara?
Please, Tentara.
I feel sorry for Vega.
Please, I beg you.
Yes, Ava.
We have to go there.
What are we going to wear?
How about this?
What do you think?
It's a good idea, isn't it?
Buy a card.
It's filled with coconut.
It's a good idea.
It's Ava's idea.
Okay.
Let's go.
Wafamun Naga Kepala Tiga.
Naga Kepala Tiga.
I brought your favorite food.
Please, enjoy.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for disturbing you.
Change.
Let's go.
Finish it.
Hold it tight.
Hold it.
We will succeed.
This arrow is very powerful.
Whatever it hits...
...will turn into ice.
Good.
Let's go.
So, what should I do now?
We have to hold on.
Until I can control that kid.
Hi, kid.
He's the one who kidnapped me.
Why does he know you?
Besides...
...you don't have to worry.
Because I've made Aldebaran...
...and the other teachers...
...fight back with the Elf warriors.
So, they won't disturb our plan now.
Good, Angkara.
Now, your job is to get rid of Ray and Vega.
I will make the people destroy Alva.
You have to kidnap Alva.
Okay.
Soon.
Soon, Alva will be mine.
What are you doing?
Stay there.
You're a bad person.
I won't let you hurt Vega.
Pelita.
Don't run.
Where are you going?
It's late.
You should sleep.
I'll teach you a new knowledge tomorrow.
I don't want to.
I know everything.
You're a bad person.
You're friends with the people who kidnapped me.
You want to harm Vega and Alva, right?
I don't want to follow you.
Good.
Come here.
How dare you.
I'll kill you.
Pelita.
Let's go.
Thank you, Naga.
I think the place is close.
Naga.
Pelita.
Wake up, Vega.
Vega, wake up.
Wake up.
Wake up, Vega.
Keep going, Naga.
Finish them.
Wake up, Vega.
Wake up.
Vega, wake up.
Vega.
Wake up.
Wake up, Vega.
Yes, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Yeah.
Wake up, Vega.
Vega.
Wake up.
Wake up, Vega.
Go, go, go.
Vega.
You're alive.
Vega, you're safe.
Vega.
Make yourself proud.
Go, go, go.
Let's dream.
We can do it.
I'm glad you're not frozen.
I'm so happy.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm not frozen because of you.
Because I love you.
That's why I'm not frozen.
Felita.
From now on, fill your heart...
...with love.
Okay?
And don't hate anyone.
One more thing.
Don't be afraid to be left behind.
We'll always be with you.
Okay?
Okay.
Go, go, go.
We can do it.
Everyone, wait for me here.
I want to show you something.
Go, go, go.
Let's dream.
Don't laugh.
We can do it.
Where's Popo?
Popo.
Where are you?
Where are you, Popo?
Gawat.
That's our target.
Break up.
Look.
The ice is melting.
Everything is back to normal.
This means...
...the firecrackers...
...will come back to us.
Don't laugh.
The firecrackers are back.
Yes.
So, Vega succeeded...
...in making Blita realize the meaning of love and sacrifice.
And finally, all this mess ended.
That's right, Professor.
And you, Megantara.
Why did you let Alva and Vega...
...escape from school...
...and bring the headmaster...
...without reporting to me?
Eating fish...
...shared with coconuts.
I'm sorry.
Again.
I forgot.
I failed again.
I thought I could get Blita to be my weapon.
So, I don't have to face Aldebaran directly.
Anggara.
Yes, sir.
Do you know what you have to do?
Tomorrow night, the Fallen Star will appear.
I will get it and give it to you...
...so you can get the power from the Fallen Star.
No.
You have to get it, Anggara.
Don't fail.
Yes, sir.
The Fallen Star.
The Fallen Star is...
...a space star...
...that fell to the earth.
And when it fell to the earth...
...the star turned into a beautiful woman.
Then...
Tommy.
Yes, sir.
When was the last time the star fell?
I don't know.
Tommy.
When was the last time the star fell?
I don't know, sir.
Pay attention.
Vega knows when was the last time the star fell.
The star fell...
...about a thousand years ago.
Good.
That's right.
Thank you, sir.
Then...
The question is...
...why did the Fallen Star...
...get a lot of attention from the people?
Ray.
Why did the Fallen Star...
...get a lot of attention from the people?
Maybe because...
Why?
Because...
Because it's beautiful.
Vega.
Why did the people get a lot of attention from the people?
Because the Fallen Star gives power.
There's no limit...
...for those who catch it.
Especially for the heart.
That's right.
A round of applause for Vega.
Why did the Fallen Star get a lot of attention from the people?
Because the Fallen Star will be fought...
...by people who are thirsty for power.
That's why...
...Professor Aldebaran insisted...
...that all of us...
...are forbidden to catch the Fallen Star.
Thank you, Aldebaran.
There's a party.
Party.
I like parties.
Popo.
What?
Don't touch me.
I'll turn into ice.
I'm afraid of the cold.
Don't be afraid, Popo.
I can handle my power.
I'm sorry.
I made you freeze.
It's true.
You're crazy.
Crazy? What am I?
Popo.
Let's go home.
What?
Home?
That's great.
I'm free.
I'm not helping anyone.
It's all because of Alva.
I don't want to get hurt.
We're sorry.
We want to hurt you.
It's okay.
Okay.
Excuse us.
Let's go home.
Kids.
Let's gather.
There's a firework party.
What?
That's not a firework.
You better give up.
Before the 8th of Pangeran comes.
That's not a firework.
Don't do that.
It's not a firework.
Rai will be happy.
He will be happy.
I'll tell her myself.
Actually, I've never been happy with a girl.
That's not a firework.
This is very rare.
We have to get the falling star.
Let's go.
What's that?
I don't know.
That's the falling star.
I can't fail this time.
Hey!
Get out!
You better give up.
Before the 8th prince comes here,
we won't let him go.
Before we get his heart.
Don't dream.
Everyone wants his heart.
But it's not that easy.
Step on my body first.
It's so heavy.
Let me rest for a while.
It's heavy.
Are you going to take my heart?
Right?
No.
Not me.
You're a bad person.
We can do this.
Help me.
Okay.
I'll help you.
I'll make you sleep forever.
Devil!
You're so rude.
It turns out you can use my magic.
But I won't lose.
Devil!
Hey!
Thank you for helping me.
I'm sorry. I misjudged you.
And I hit you too.
Yes. When you landed, they were fighting for your battle.
So I took you away from there.
I'm so sorry.
I feel bad.
You want to forgive me, right?
Yes.
DEVIL!
Where's the devil?
The devil is gone.
It's all your fault.
You have to accept the consequences.
DEVIL!
Listen!
The devil is mine.
If you meet him, you can't touch him.
You can't even see him.
Do you understand?
Good.
Goodbye.
DEVIL!
I think this belongs to Sido's school.
I'm sure they took Putri Bintangjatu.
It's them.
Let's go there.
My name is Selena.
Alva.
I'm from Sigir's school.
I beg you.
Don't tell anyone that I'm Bintangjatu.
Because they will fight for me.
My hair will be cut.
Because my hair can make any kind of clothes.
And my tears will be squeezed.
Because my tears can create new power.
And can cure any kind of disease.
And my heart.
If my heart is taken and eaten.
It can create unlimited power.
It's their fault for fighting to get you.
I'm scared, Alva.
I want to go back to heaven.
Okay.
Don't be sad.
I promise I won't tell anyone about you.
And I will help you to go back to heaven.
Are you serious?
Yes.
You're so kind.
Thank you, Alva.
Promise?
Don't go anywhere.
Because this place is safe.
I want to go back to the festival.
Because they are looking for me.
If you don't tell us where Putri Bintangjatu is.
We will find her ourselves.
Salam Lestari!
Ali Baran!
What are you doing here?
Are you a warrior?
Or are you a bandit?
What's the truth?
Where did you hide Putri Bintangjatu?
Give her back to us.
Because she belongs to us.
Putri Bintangjatu.
I don't understand.
Stop pretending.
This is the proof.
We found this brooch at Putri Bintangjatu's place.
Calm down.
I'm sure this is just a misunderstanding.
The proof is with us.
And that's not wrong.
If you don't tell us where Putri Bintangjatu is.
We will find her ourselves.
Wait.
I won't let you in.
Without my permission.
You have to face me.
Putri Bintangjatu.
Okay, let's go.
The base of the kidnappers.
They really did it.
Just a little bit.
And they're gone.
Professor Ali Baran.
What about this?
This is a very serious problem.
I will find out about Putri Bintangjatu.
You stay here.
I will find the answer.
Agni.
Take the kids inside.
Come in.
Alva, where are you from?
Yes, Alva, where are you from?
We're looking for you.
I can't tell them that I'm Putri Bintangjatu.
I made a promise.
I have a stomachache.
That's why I've been in the toilet.
Alva has a stomachache.
I'll take the medicine in the clinic.
No need.
I'm fine now.
Let's go there.
The teachers will hear us.
Let's go.
It's been a long time.
What is he doing?
He's singing.
To be continued...
Alva.
Selima.
It's so crowded here.
What are you doing here?
Do you want to sing and dance?
Come here.
No.
I don't want to.
I don't want to sing and dance.
What are you doing here?
I want you to be quiet.
Why?
Because if you sing and dance...
Your voice will be heard in my dorm.
People will be suspicious.
What should I do?
Just sleep.
It's late.
Alva, I'm Bintang.
Bintang's job is to keep me awake at night.
So, I can't sleep at night.
But, you can't be noisy.
If you're caught, and...
You'll be arrested.
What will you do?
That's why...
You can't be noisy.
I'll go now.
Bye.
Idiot.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's all because of you.
I don't want to hear your excuses.
Why did you let him go?
I have to find Bintang.
Help!
Wow.
It's huge.
You're great, sir.
Cool.
How can it be in someone's house?
This is weird.
To be continued...