To be continued...
Heart's strength
Go, go, go
Make yourself proud
Let's dream
Go, go, go
We can do it
Stop, stop
I'm sure
The Duyung are only in war
Run
It seems there is a greater power
That controls them
Terror will continue to spread
Until I can get the chosen one
Do you see where Duyung is going?
Down to the lake
Everyone wants to attack the Duyung
Why don't they show up?
Be patient
We'll wait a little longer
They will definitely show up to kill him
Be patient
To be continued...
They are very cunning
Let's hide first
Once they show up, we attack
Agreed
What are you doing?
Now answer my question
Where did you hide the students?
Don't play around
Answer my question
Do you think you can play around?
Fine
I will teach you
Fire
Don't hurt them
They want to pray
Putri Duyung
Putri Duyung, are you okay?
Thank you for saving me
With your tears
I promise
I will set you free
Along with your friends
Vega
Retreat
Hurry
We're here to save our friends
Good
If we retreat
Duyung's people will be punished
We can't hurt Duyung
We have to work with them
You don't know how to teach me
Professor Purwa
It's not our fault
We don't have much time
If you lie
You will be punished
Fire
Retreat
They went to their house
What are we going to do?
We can't just fight
That's why
We have to listen to their opinions
They are still kids
But sometimes
They are smarter than adults
Alpha
Ask them
Where are our friends?
Duyung
Please tell me
Where are our friends that you kidnapped?
What are you doing?
Are you playing?
Calm down
Duyung can't talk
Lightning
It seems
What Alpha said is true
They are not lying
But they can't talk
Because of one thing
How can they lose their voices?
Why?
Why can't you talk?
Who is he?
Did you order him?
Do you want me to read your mind?
Duyung
Help
Help us
So because of that attack
You can't talk?
Duyung
I
The 8th Prince's order
I stole your voices
And if you want your voices back
Then
You have to kidnap 8 kids from a magic school
And one of those kids
Must be a boy named Alpha
Those kids
You have to bring them to the headquarters of the 8th Prince
Which is located in
That headquarters is a secret
So
You can't tell anyone
And if one of you leak it
Then
All of you will be cursed to be bullies
Hahaha
The 8th Prince's order says that you have to kidnap 8 kids
Which means
You have to kidnap 2 boys
And one of them must be a boy named Alpha
Duyung
Hurry Duyung
Hurry
Duyung
What are you doing?
Alpha
Hurry up
Duyung
Food
Thank you
Hurry up
Kristi
What?
Grass again
There's no other
What?
Why do we have to be like this?
We're not happy
I'm ready, ma'am
I'm also
I've learned the vocabulary
So
I'm sure
I can protect myself
Yeah
Alpha is not alone
I'll protect him
The dragon fruit
Oh my god
It's dangerous
Don't worry, soldier
We've fought the three-headed dragon
So we're sure
Okay
I think there's no other choice
I'll count to three
If there's no better idea
We'll use Alpha's idea
Professor Purwa
One
Two
Three
We'll use Alpha's idea
Alpha Taung Poveris
I've set up a shield
And a trap for you
Alpha
Vega
Wait
Alpha
Vega
You have to be careful
I promise
I'll save you
Putri Ruyung
Let's get out of here
You
Take us
To the Dark Mountain
What should we do?
I don't want Alpha to get hurt
But
I can't tell him where we're going
Hurry, Putri Ruyung
We don't have much time
We have to save my friend
Hurry, Putri Ruyung
We don't have much time
We have to save my friend
Alpha Taung Poveris
Good
Very good
Finally, I succeeded in saving Putri Ruyung
Give her to me
Mom
I'm scared too
We're all scared
And hungry
Mom, Karim
Listen, Karim
I heard your voice
I was wondering how to get out of here
I've been crying
I want to go home
What happened?
They must know about the trap
And they deliberately destroyed it
Without the trap
How can we save them?
This is all because of Professor Purwa
Because of you, Purwa
Alpha's life is in danger
Megantara
What do you mean?
This is not my fault
But that's the truth
You accused me
I was trying to save the children
Megantara
Listen, listen
What are you doing?
Don't touch me
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with all your might
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Remember
Don't be afraid
If you dare to do anything
I will turn you into fish
Don't
I'm hungry
I want to eat again
Alpha
Mega
Mega, wake up
It hurts
Where are we?
We're in a village
Where's our village?
Oh, right
Where's my village?
Don't
We'll get caught
Bro, if we lose this village
The teachers won't know where we are
We won't be safe
We don't know where we are
Go, go, go
We're cut off
Open it
Shut up
Remember
If you dare to do anything
I will turn you into fish
Don't be afraid
Weapons
Go
Go, go, go
Weapons
Now
You can't turn us into fish
Guys
Let's get out of here
Wait
It's not that easy
Professor Rangkara
Alpha
Thank you for still recognizing me
Professor
Why are you here?
You should be in prison
Yes
You underestimated me
A prison like that
Is nothing to me
And you, Alpha
Don't be happy
Because you took my Tongsi
Because without Tongsi
I can still use my magic
Go back, Rizal
Suck their energy
Rizal
What should I do?
I feel sorry for Alpha and Vega
They are my friends
But if I tell them about their secret
I...
Shut up!
Vega!
Alpha and Vega
Rekobot, attack!
What's wrong with this robot?
It's useless if you two fight
Okay, let's find where the kids are
But what should we do?
We have no other choice
He told us to follow him
He knows where the kids are
Let's go
Okay
Wait!
What if it's a trap?
Do you have a better idea?
Hurry!
What is this place?
It must be a trap!
He told us to follow him
He's one of our supporters
He told you to press the stone
If you lie to us
You will be punished
Rekobot, attack!
To be honest
There's something wrong
Who is it?
Even though I've destroyed the company
How do you know?
Let's go
Rekobot, attack!
Let's go in
How do we get out?
We have to break the stone
Let's go
We have to get out of there
Let me do it!
We have to get out of here!
I'm going to be a robot
I'm going to be a robot!
Ankara?
There are two roads
Which one should we take?
We should split up
Wait
I think that's the smoke
A message from the children
Let's just follow the smoke
So we don't have to split up
Let's go
So Professor Ankara
Escaped from prison?
Don't you dare
The darkness won't rise again
Because you've caught me
The horror won't end here
In the end
You will lose
Kidnapping the children
Must be done by Ankara
Don't be afraid
Let me deal with this
Let's go
Everything is ready
Let's continue our journey
Let's go
Don't be afraid!
Let's use the power of water
Okay
Let's go
Mupunjo, water!
Thank you.
How dare you!
Angkara?
So, you're the one behind all this.
Angkara, you managed to escape from the jail.
Hahaha...
Hey, you're underestimating my magic power.
Do you think I can't escape from such a cheap prison?
Hahaha...
Angkara, let me handle this.
You guys, save the kids.
Hurry up.
You guys, go!
Let's go.
Hurry up.
The coconut was eaten.
Where do you think you're going, Angkara?
Avancur Bintu.
Let's go.
Wait.
Isn't this the energy transfer crystal?
This weapon is very dangerous.
This crystal can collect the energy of the people who want it.
And it can absorb all the energy.
We don't have much time.
We have to destroy this crystal ball.
Because if the crystal ball is full,
it means the energy of the children has been taken.
The children could die.
I will destroy it.
Avancur!
Let's attack.
Good bye, Professor Megantara.
Go to Japan through the north.
It's easy to defeat Megantara.
Let's go.
Let's destroy it together.
Avancur!
Let's go.
Let's go together.
Tommy.
Are you okay?
Avancur!
It seems that the destruction of the crystal has destroyed this place.
We have to get out of here.
Let's go.
Avancur!
Vega.
Professor!
Megantara is still inside.
Yes.
He's fighting against Ankara.
Megantara.
Alva!
Megantara!
Where are you?
Alva.
Megantara!
I'm here!
Megantara.
Megantara!
Alva.
Professor!
I'm here, Professor!
Thank you, Professor.
Here, Megantara.
The road is closed.
What should we do, Professor?
Alva.
Professor.
Look.
There's a hole.
The hole needs people.
Alva.
Come on.
Go inside that hole.
Hurry.
Come on, Professor.
Go inside.
Follow Alva.
No, Megantara.
You go inside.
You can take care of him.
Professor.
Go inside, Professor.
Stay in the middle.
Where are you, Professor?
Professor.
No!
Don't sting me!
I'm sorry, Megantara.
Megantara.
Don't leave me, Megantara.
Get up, Megantara.
You promised...
...to give me a future.
Megantara.
Get up, Megantara.
We have to go, Alva.
We have to go.
Alva, wait!
Alva.
Alva!
Megantara!
Megantara, get up!
Megantara.
Megantara, get up, Megantara.
Megantara, wake up.
Megantara.
Megantara, get up.
Megantara, wake up Megantara.
Megantara, wake up.
Megantara.
What are you doing?
Be careful, don't push me like this.
I'll beat you up.
Hey, Prof.
Coconut fruit.
Alva.
Don't cry.
Why are you smiling?
I've promised you...
...that I'll save you all.
Captain Megantara...
...never breaks his promise.
Okay.
Where's your tux?
Captain Megantara.
Are you all okay?
Putih Duyung, you can talk now?
Yes.
I'm sure it's because the effect of the magic is gone.
The place is destroyed.
Thank you, Putih Duyung.
I'm so happy...
...that you've saved us all.
My name is Utiara.
I'm so happy to meet you.
Let's come here again sometime.
Right, Alva?
Yes, I'm happy to meet you too.
You're good kids.
I'm also thankful that you saved me.
Utiara.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Utiara.
Where are you?
It's all because of the Dark Lord's curse.
Utiara has leaked the kids' whereabouts.
And now...
...he's being possessed.
Utiara.
It's better than nothing.
It's better than nothing?
Let's just play.
What if we go to an island?
We won't be there.
I don't want to.
I don't want to go to an island.
I'll miss you, Utiara.
I don't want to.
He left me.
Fine.
If you don't want to play, let me.
Don't.
Don't do that again.
Don't hurt me again.
Don't be afraid.
We're not human anymore.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Are you alone?
What else can I do?
Because...
I'm alone.
Alka and Vega are still sad.
Because Utiara is possessed.
Don't say that.
Come here.
I want to talk to you.
What?
I'm going to leave, Alva, Vega.
I'm going to be a ghost.
Please, don't go.
Please, Utiara, don't go.
Utiara, I'm sad.
I'm sad.
Let's go.
Alva, Vega.
What a surprise.
I have a new surprise for you.
I'm sure...
you won't regret it.
No.
We're going to Asrama Purnama.
Me too.
It's true.
You don't want to meet Utiara.
Don't lie.
It's true, I'm not lying.
Be careful.
But, on one condition.
What is it?
Do you want to be a girl?
That's not funny.
It's true.
Just follow me.
Is that a boy or not?
I don't know.
I don't feel good.
Hurry up, Rey.
Where's Utiara?
Rey, if you're lying,
I'll tie you to a tree.
Just wait.
They'll be here soon.
What?
They.
Let's go.
A FEW HOURS LATER
That's Utiara.
Utiara.
Remember what I said?
I met Putri Duyung.
She told me...
if a girl from Angsa...
takes Utiara's girl,
Utiara can live again.
Then, Utiara...
becomes a member of Angsa.
Hurry up.
Come here.
I'll wait for you here.
They don't like men.
Let's go.
A FEW HOURS LATER
I'm happy to see you again.
Now!
It's so fun!
There's another man!
A FEW HOURS LATER
Thank you, Rey.
I'm so happy to meet Utiara.
Me too.
Even though it's just for a while.
But I'm happy because he's a good boy.
I know.
But my body aches.
A FEW HOURS LATER
Attention, children.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll have a mid-semester vacation.
And you'll do a field trip...
to Sihir village, not far from the school.
There, you'll stay at the residence...
and hang out with the people of Sihir.
Professor Agni, Purwa, and Megantara...
will accompany you...
to keep an eye on you...
so that you don't do anything stupid.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
There will be a sports competition in the village.
It will be fun.
There are a lot of activities.
I'm so excited.
It will be fun.
I can't wait to go there.
Let's go!
Any news?
I just got word...
that the children from Sihir school...
will start a field trip to Sihir village.
And I think...
we can attack Alpha there.
I don't want to fail this time.
So that I can regain my strength.
I have to get that child.
Don't worry, sir.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Alpha.
How did you get in here?
Don't get too close, Alpha.
Why?
It's dangerous, Alpha.
Please, don't go there.
But why?
Most of the children here go on field trips.
What if I don't go?
The event must be fun.
Alright.
I'll keep you safe.
Hey!
Where is he?
It's just a dream.
But...
does that mean...
I'm not allowed to go on a field trip?
Why?
Those two...
always show up in my dreams...
and give me a hard time.
Children.
We'll leave soon.
On the count of three...
we'll go to Sihir village.
we'll chant the mantra together.
One.
Two.
Three.
Fly!
Sihir Village
They're here.
Yes.
It's like a prophecy.
It means...
one of them...
will open the door...
and make chaos in this village.
Nik.
Now, go to Sihir village.
His name is Pak Galaksi.
Tell him we're here.
And then...
come back here.
Yes, ma'am.
Children.
Let's see.
Sihir Village
There's someone over there.
It's noisy.
Janik!
Faiqa!
What?
Where are you?
We can't be separated.
We have to stay together.
Let's go.
Faiqa!
Janik!
That's Janik's bag.
Yes.
Sihir Village
Janik.
Why is Janik turning into a rock?
Maybe she needs it.
Sihir Village
It turns out the prophecy is true.
The disaster is here.
We're all going to be affected by the monster's curse.
That's right.
That's the legendary monster.
What did those people mean?
What's a legendary monster?
What really happened to me?
Don't worry.
Megantan will be back.
Who are you?
I'm Megantan.
You're amazing.
How is it going with Kanik?
It's a good time to come here.
I have a clue about what happened.
Come here.
To be continued...