To be continued...
I want to have a strange power
I can make everyone freeze
Because we are friends
I will let you know my secret
I also have a strange power
I can't freeze
Alva is safe
Although his face is a little wounded
Bad news
The 8th prince has taken the news away
We give time until tomorrow morning
If our Kris doesn't return
And our servants are no longer made normal
We will attack the magic school
And your teacher
Your teacher will not return
How is this possible?
We can't give Kris that fire
If we give Kris that fire
Our children will be in danger
Children can die of cold
Plita must be lonely
Poor Plita
I can't leave Plita alone
I have to help Plita
To be continued...
Because he has a very high level of knowledge
So...
Professor Purwa can take care of himself
We have no other choice, Rolf
Whether we want it or not
We have to fight them
This is all for the sake of the children and the school
What?
Professor Purwa was kidnapped?
Then?
What about Plita?
Who is looking for her?
A month later
It's safe
We can open it
Ouch
It turns out that you guys
Made us know
You're lucky
You didn't ask us out
We can't sleep either
I miss Plita
I miss her too
Poor her
She must be lonely
Let's go find Plita
We have to take responsibility
We're the ones who brought her here
You're right
Let's go
It's so cold
My hands are freezing
It's cold
Wait
Alfa
Try to find her using the telescope
Where is Plita now?
There she is
We brought her here
Where are you taking her?
How are we going to find her?
It's so cold
We have to help her
We can't give up
Let's go
It's so cold
I can't do this anymore
What do we do?
It's so cold
I can't do this anymore
Don't leave me
What do we do?
It's so cold
They think I'm an ordinary person
Where do you think you're going?
Eka, Tri, Cato
I'll deal with him
Let's go
Kara, nice to meet you again
Children
We brought food for all of you
Yes
We brought fruits
Eat fruits so you'll be healthy
Let's share it
Okay
But wait
There's one more thing
I want to ask you
What is it?
Okay
But wait
Where's Ray?
What?
Vega?
He's not here
We don't know
Oh no
This is bad
Ika's son ate the fruit
I'm sure they ran away
They ran away
Please share it
Take it all
I'm telling you all
Don't trust Ankara
He's a liar
A traitor
Don't trust him
He and all the people at the magic school
All of them are liars
Liars
You've seen it for yourself
The proof is
He hid the ice in the school's school yard
And that's a very clear proof
And all of this is his doing
Along with all the people at the magic school
He's a liar
We didn't do that
We didn't steal the ice
He's a traitor
He did all of this
What else can you prove, Purwa?
Everything is clear
Ksatria Catur has seen for himself
How stupid he is
And you have no reason to scream like this
Just answer, Ankara
Just answer
Where are Purwa and Vega?
Where are they?
Why did I get left behind?
I'm so scared
I'm scared
Dad!
Vega!
Why did I get left behind?
This hole
Can tell me anything
That I want
I want to see Alva and Vega
Where are they?
Alva?
Vega?
Thank you for saving us
Thank you
You're so kind
You're welcome
You're our best friend
Thank you
You're welcome
You're our best friend
Vega, where's Rey?
Why isn't she here?
Where is she?
Why don't we help her?
Why are you guys like that?
I feel sorry for Rey
I feel sorry for her
I don't know
We have to help you, Alva
We have to help you because we have to, Alva
If it wasn't for Tiana's request
We wouldn't have helped a guy
Right, girls?
Right
Where is she?
We have to find Rey
What do we do?
Hi
Hi, Alva
Hi, Vega
Hi, Gangsa
I'm so lucky
I thought it was a girl
If it wasn't for her
I would've been beaten up
How did you know we're here?
Reyna
Rey
How did you know we're here?
What are you doing here?
I know where you are
Because of this
It's dangerous
Go back to school
Because the weather is extreme
We have to help Brita
She's Asian
Girls
Yippie
Lotion
In the cold weather
What is this for?
The lotion can help you
Stay warm in the cold weather
So you can stay strong in the snow
Wow
It's so cool
Thank you
You're welcome
Let's go
Where is your friend?
Wait, I'll look for her
Where is she?
There she is
She's in the building
What's her name?
I don't know
Her name is...
Kondok Hitam
I know where she is
How do we get there?
Yes
We'll take you there
That's so cool
Girls
Yippie
You can all go up now
It's so big
Yes
Girls
Brita
You have to be strong
You have to keep your emotions
You can't be afraid
You can't be nervous
And you can't care about others
If you care
You'll be disappointed
And you'll be hurt
I'm sure everything will be better
Wow
It's so cool
We can fly
Yes, we can fly
By the way
Where did you get this kite?
I was going to Kondok
And then
I remembered
My family doesn't like men
So
I got this kite
Where did you get it from?
Brita
It's a red kite
What's that?
Help
Yippie
It's not over yet
Oh yeah
I want to play with a kite
It's so funny
You're so smart
What's your name?
Brita
Have all the kids eaten?
Yes, Sir
I think Prof. Radebaran is stressed
Because he's thinking about
The great warriors
And I
Have to keep it a secret
From Ray, Vega, and Alva
Megantara
Call Agni and Yasmin
We have to get out of here
Because soon
The great warriors will come
We have to get out of here
Megantara
Yes, Sir
Andri Madan
Get out
Get out, all of you
Give Chris the kite
I'll count to ten
If you don't give Chris the kite
We will attack
They will attack us
We have to fight
If we don't
Our school will be destroyed
That's right, Professor
And the students will be the victims
Listen
We are peacekeepers
We don't want a war
But
We won't stay quiet
If there's someone who's threatening us
We will use our abilities
To protect the students
Let's go
Let's unite
We will protect this school and the students
For the future
Boss, our school is under attack
What?
Attack?
What are you doing?
Chris, your kite
Where's Chris?
We decided to fight
And protect Chris
We will protect this school
And protect the students
For the future
We will protect this school
And protect the students
For the future
We will protect this school
We won't stop
Until we have Chris
We must all unite
Unite?
Why, Aldi Baran?
Are you afraid of losing?
How do you know I'm here?
You're all useless
Who do you think we are to lose?
Professor Aldi Baran's ability
is far superior to yours
I don't like this
You see
Everything is frozen
We can't leave Chris
And we need Chris Aldi
To take care of the kids
If not, they can die
Okay
We've released your teacher
Thank you
Now
It's time to find the kid named Plita
Yasmin
Take care of the kids
Don't let them leave this place
Before it gets back to normal
Yes, Professor
Damn it!
They've united
We can't let this happen
I have to stop them
Thank you for saving us
You're so kind
For helping us
You're welcome, Rega
Rega
If you need anything
Don't hesitate to call us
We'll definitely help you
Girls
Okay, bye
Bye
Bye, Plita
So annoying
Why do I have to be a girl?
Plita!
Plita, I want to talk to you
Don't touch me
What's wrong?
Are you mad?
Forgive us
We left you yesterday
But
We're back now
Yes
It's better
If you go back to school with us
Will you?
Because everyone is asking about you
Yes
We miss you so much
Plita
Let's play again
I promise
I won't leave you
You have to forget them all
Who's that?
Why does he bring Plita here?
Plita
You have to make a decision
Do you want to stay here with me
Or do you want to go to Someret?
Plita
You haven't forgotten, right?
We promised
We'll always be together
Plita
You have to focus on your recovery
He's a traitor
Don't go with him
You have to kick him out of this school
You have to kick him out
Guys
Let's just go
Don't waste our time
You guys go
I want to stay here
You have to stay with us
Yes
I want to stay here
You guys go
I don't want to
I want to take you home
If you don't want to go, just go
Plita
Your hand
Come here, I want to see
Don't touch me
Plita
It's okay
Plita, why are you so stubborn?
Do you know?
He's just a bad guy
Who dares to attack his own friend
I'm a bad guy
We came here because he's a bad guy
He's not a bad guy
He's a bad guy
But he can't control himself
He's like a brother to me
So, I want to protect him
Plita
Let's go home, Plita
Let's go back to school
Plita
If you don't want to go with them
Just kick him out
Monster S
What should we do?
Take them away from here
Let's go
Plita, don't
Okay
Monster
You have to think for yourself
And you have to let go of your love for other people
Because this feeling can destroy you
Monster
Let me go
What you're doing now is right
You have to train yourself so that you can recover
You're safe now, Vega, Kharva, and Kary
I can't go any further
I've come this far just to be kicked out by Plita
Let's report this to the police
Yes, let's report this to the police
Vega
Stay there
I want to see Plita
Move
No
Why?
You're awesome
When are you going to learn how to swim?
Because
I often see the army
I can do it
It's better
If we go home now
After school
No
I don't want to go home
I don't want to go home if I don't bring Plita
Come on, Vega
You heard it yourself
Plita doesn't want to talk to you anymore
It's better if we go home
You're always being teased by Plita
Alva is right
Let's go home
No, I don't want to
I want to talk to Plita again
If you don't want to bring me
Fine
I'll go by myself
I'm so scared
Somebody help!
Alva, help!
What should we do?
Let's attack together
What?
Attack!
Yes!
We did it!
Great!
Forever
Yes, forever!
Yes!
Great!
Alva!
We did it!
You can't think of anything
You have to concentrate
My hand is healed
Thank you, Mr. Ngeran
I'm glad I can help you
But you have to remember
You can't use your feelings
You have to control yourself
You have to think of yourself
And you have to let go of your love for people
Because those feelings can destroy you
It can make you hurt
It can make you sad
Yes, Mr. Ngeran
We can do it
Let's gather here
It's over
Fire
Okay
I'll get some water
And make a drink
It smells good
Yes, of course
This drink not only warms your body
But also boosts your stamina
Can I try?
Sure, go ahead
Be careful, it's hot
Thank you
Agni?
Mr. Agni?
You intentionally hurt Agni
Yes, we did
You're such a jerk
Don't blame us
Shut up!
I don't know anything about this
The evidence is clear
You can't escape
It's all because of me
Good
Keep fighting
You can't fight each other
You have to surrender
What's wrong, Tri?
Nothing
Enough
Enough!
Stop it!
Hold your emotions
I can cure Agni
You must have misunderstood
We should be united
Agni
It hurts
I'm sick of this
I'm going home
Let's go home
Where are you going?
Let me go
I want to take Plita home
Vega
You don't have to do that
The monster has attacked you
It attacked all of us
If we go there again
We'll get sick
Let's go home
No, I still want to try
I'm sure Plita is a good girl
She has a soft heart
So, I want to talk to her
Just the two of us
Men shouldn't know
What does it have to do with men?
I'm sure
Men must be the ones who affect Plita
You saw that, right?
Plita is very close to men
Alright
I'll go with you
Really?
Alright, I'll go with you too
Yes, you're going with me
Yes
But, how do we get there?
I'm sure the monster is over there
How about this?
Ray and I will lure the monster
So, the monster will chase us
You'll take Plita home
Yes, I agree
Best
Friends
Forever
Best friends forever
Yes
Devastate
Vega, let's go
Vega
What?
Zeru
Zeru, run!
Where are we?
We're here
Do you want to play?
Plita
Come here
Let's play
Come on, Plita
Or do you want to walk?
Or do you want me to walk?
Come here
I'll spin the dice
Yes
I'll walk again
I'll spin the dice
Yes
Yes, on the 10th
Now it's your turn, Plita
Yes
Yay
Are you happy playing this?
I'm really happy
Especially when you play this at school, Plita
It must be more fun
There are a lot of kids playing
Yes
That's why
You should go home, Plita
We can play together again
Please
We've promised that we'll always be friends
I don't want you to be lonely
You should go home
Please
We can play together again
Let's go, Plita
Okay
So, you want to go with Vega?
Yes, it's all up to you
But you have to remember my words
You can't use your feelings
Because your feelings
Will only hurt you
And you can't care about others
Because caring about others
Will only make you sad
I'm sorry, Sir
But I can't leave Vega
It's okay
Use this
If you need my help
I'll come and help you
Wherever you are
Thank you, Sir
Audrey!
Let me go!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Sir
I just sprained my ankle
I'm sorry
It's okay
Now, Plita wants to go home with us
That's great!
But don't hold my hand
You'll get cold
Yes
We'll meet Professor Lelebaran there
I'm sure Professor Lelebaran
Can cure you
Let's go home
I'm so happy to be with you
Me too
Especially me
Sir
Come here
Can I ask you for a favor?
What is it?
Can you find Professor Lelebaran?
You tell him
That we're on our way home
About Plita
Okay
Thank you, Sir
You're welcome, Alfa
There's a message from Alfa
Alfa is on his way home with Plita
Megantama
Why is Alfa outside the school?
Actually, I wanted to tell you this morning
But...
The EOF is in a hurry
So...
I forgot
Tell Alfa
I'll be waiting for him
In this bamboo forest
Okay, Sir
Thank you
You're welcome, Sir
We should take a rest here
While we wait for Alfa and Plita
Megantama
Next time
You have to tell me everything
Okay
Make sure it's clean
I'll keep you posted
Alfa
Where are you?
I'm on my way home
Okay, Sir
Thank you, Sir
You're welcome
Megantama
Where are you?
I'm on my way home
Okay, Sir
Make sure it's clean
I'll keep you posted
Megantama
Where are you?
I'm on my way home
Okay, Sir
Make sure it's clean
I'll keep you posted
Okay, Sir
Megantama
Where are you?
I'm on my way home
Okay, Sir
Make sure it's clean
I'll keep you posted
Okay, Sir
Let me help him
No need
Leave it to me
You want revenge, don't you?
Hey
Go to Gandaria
Buy a sharp sword
Ksatria
Remember
Slander is worse than murder
You can see for yourself
This is slander, not slander
Okay
Let's go our separate ways
We'll use our own methods
Wait, Professor
Just leave it
We don't need to be stopped
For what?
We should be united
Not separate like this
I'm not in the mood
Yeah
They're looking for trouble
Where's Siri?
Maybe he's taking a nap
He'll be here soon
You guys go first
Let's go, Prita
Alva
Hey
Where's Alva?
Ray's gone
He attacked Alva
What should we do?
Prita, wait here
I'll look for Ray and Alva
Alva
Ray
Where are you guys?
Alva, Ray
Alva
Ray
Alva, Ray
Where are you guys?
Who are you?
Don't move
Don't make noise
Where's the cafe?
It's taking too long
Let me go
Help
Shut up
If you call them
They'll come for you
Maybe this is a trap
The cafe, Ray and Alva
Are working with these people
Why are they here?
I trust the cafe
Alva
Finally, Prita called
Help me, Eran
Prita
You have to gather your strength
And attack them
Now, attack the people who hurt you
Prita is so brave
She made Vega become like this
I told you
She's a monster
That's why we have to stay away from her
She's not a friend
She's running, jumping, jumping
She's a monster
She's brave
She never gives up
She's chasing her dreams
Go, go, go
Chase all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Fight with your heart
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Let's dream
We will