To be continued...
Go, go, go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go, go, go!
We can do it!
Oh my God!
This wound is very bad.
Very, very bad.
And it must be treated immediately with energy transfer.
Kramat Penamat Sword.
Huh? Kramat Penamat Sword?
Defat Ambarga!
Destroy them all.
Don't let them enter the castle.
Let me go!
I want to remember Alva.
Vega, Ray, Soleh.
Have you got the sword?
Not yet, bro.
Now, I'm the one who's wrong.
To become the sword.
Alva?
They will definitely meet.
If the Dark Lord...
will capture and destroy Alva,
then I...
will be the one who will be destroyed first.
Head of the school, head of the head!
Aldubaran!
But don't worry about me.
I will infuse Aldubaran.
I will help you.
Just...
what I will infuse is not the Dark Lord in Aldubaran,
but poison.
Huh?
Poison, poison!
Mr. Nelly!
I have to find help.
Alva?
Alva, where are you?
Isn't that the Dark Lord?
He often comes to my house.
Alva,
do you know who that kid is?
Who?
That kid is you.
The Dark Lord?
My parents?
That's right.
If they killed my father,
if I'm not taken care of,
then...
where are they now?
Of course they don't take care of you.
Because both of them...
are dead.
Dead?
Let's go.
Why are you so late?
Ketomi, Ketomi.
Please.
Professor Ankara is attacking Professor Aldebaran.
What?
Mr. Vega, Mr. Reza, and Mr. Tole are fighting him.
But I don't know if they are strong enough or not.
We have to do something.
Jack, wait for the kids.
We have to save Professor Aldebaran.
Okay.
Let's go, Boss.
Thank you, Ketomi.
Guys!
We have to save Professor Aldebaran.
He's being attacked by Professor Ankara.
Let's go.
Boss.
Have you got it?
Here.
I got it all.
Let's look for the others.
What's that?
It's a monster.
It's scary.
Ankara.
Kids.
Hold on.
Say it.
Feel it.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
We want to help you.
Guys, get ready.
Hey.
Do you think you can beat me?
You're underestimating me.
Even though you have 1,000,
you still can't beat me.
Professor Ankara.
Don't play with us.
Yes.
We're special.
How do you know...
...why they're dead?
Here.
Take this.
Don't let them get away.
Get them.
To be continued...
Grandpa!
A drop of water from a chosen child...
...can restore my power.
Mr. Bonda!
Let me go.
His teeth can kill,
but you can kill him...
...through his teeth.
His strength is his weakness.
What?
What did I teach you?
You killed my monster.
Now, listen to me.
Boko!
Children,
you're all great.
Going to Egypt...
...to buy turtles.
The children of the magic school...
...are really great.
To be continued...
I left a mark on your blood.
That's why God's power is perfect.
Because your blood...
...can restore my power.
No.
I don't give up.
My blood works like yours.
Boko.
I fight to the death...
...so that...
...you can't...
...take my blood anymore.
Who do you think you are?
Do you know who you're dealing with?
I'm the Dark Lord.
Your power...
...can't beat mine.
And I don't need your blood.
I will take your blood...
...by force.
Take his blood.
Watch out!
Brother!
To be continued...
Wake up!
It's all because of you, Alva.
Please go home, Alva.
Your mission is done.
I won't let the Dark Lord...
...wake up again!
To be continued...
You've made me so angry, Alva!
Alva.
Feel this.
Do you know what this means?
It's a torture spell.
After this,
you'll be in great pain.
And you'll hate your parents.
Father.
Mother.
Why did I have to meet you?
Alva.
Father.
Mother.
Now,
I know who you are.
Father.
Mother.
I've been fighting.
But I lost.
I think...
I'll meet you both.
No, Alva.
You can't give up.
Riana.
We'll meet again.
You must defeat the Dark Lord.
You're our only hope.
What do I do?
He's so strong.
He has the power of a Star Maiden.
Only with the determination and love in you...
can you overcome all of Alva's evil.
You must believe in yourself.
You can do it.
Alright.
I won't give up.
Be patient, Alva.
We'll meet again.
I want to learn.
If the Dark Lord gets my blood,
he'll get stronger.
He'll hurt more people.
I must survive.
For Sega.
For Ray.
For Peta.
And for Tentara.
Pegasus!
Bird, help me.
To be continued...
So, he joined us.
So, our effort is in vain.
Hey.
Don't say it's in vain.
There's a white chicken.
It's climbing the tree.
Don't be sad.
Because you've defeated Ankara.
That's right.
Ankara has escaped.
You've saved Professor Aldebaran.
Now,
it's better for you to find and save Alva.
Sega.
Ray.
Tole.
Save Alva.
Go.
You can also bring the Dark Lord.
Yes, Peta.
Oh my God.
This is so big.
I'm going to be a chicken.
I'm going to be the strongest.
I'm not afraid.
Oh my God.
I've just been beaten.
I'm a chicken.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
Let go of me.
What happened to me?
Why am I here all of a sudden?
I thought I was dreaming.
I'm confused.
Thank you, Mrs. Runda.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mrs. Runda.
I have to find the Sword of Purnama.
And go back to school.
Why are you here, Alva?
Are you looking for the Sword of Purnama?
Yes.
The Sword of Purnama is here.
That's my plan to trap you.
But...
Doctor Pertiwi said that if...
Doctor Pertiwi?
He has been affected by hypnotism.
He will talk according to what I want him to talk.
Baseless.
Evil.
Enough, Alva.
It's better...
if you join me...
than to die in vain.
You can be my bodyguard.
And we will rule this world.
No.
I don't want to.
I don't want to work with you.
You're a villain.
Murderer.
You're not good enough, Alva.
How dare you look at the dark side.
I'll focus.
Angkara...
failed to get the Sword of Purnama.
But not with your dark side.
Help!
It hurts!
I, Alva...
will take you.
You want to be my bodyguard?
No.
I won't give up.
It hurts!
Help!
I think I hear Alva's voice.
Sky...
please show Alva to me.
Alva?
Enough, Alva.
It's useless to fight.
You're just sick.
Bite her!
Let her go!
Putri Bini.
What are you doing here?
You want to give me your heart?
Do you?
Open your eyes, Alva.
I'm talking through your skull.
Because you're the only one who can hear it.
Come on, open your eyes.
Pangeran.
Do you know what a star's duty is?
A star's duty...
is to increase my power.
Wrong.
A star's duty is...
to shine!
My eyes!
Alva, let's get out of here.
Run!
Alva!
The darkness only wants my sweat, tears, and blood.
We can do it.
That's Alva.
Alva!
Alva, let's go!
Hi, everyone.
Let's go up.
Let's go up!
That's not enough!
Just a little more and I'll be able to use my power!
Shaleda!
Thank you!
Just take it as my reward...
because you've brought me back to the sky.
Yes, you're welcome!
Let's go.
Come on, calm down.
Goodbye, Alva.
Goodbye, Vega and Ray.
Who's that?
I know Vega.
Alva, Ray.
Who's Ray?
She's pretty.
Let's go back to the sky.
We can do it!
The dust has been separated by the lightning.
Thank goodness.
Now Alva is safe.
How are the kids?
Did you get the sword?
There's no sword.
It's just a trick.
It's a trap.
The Dark Lord just wants my sweat, tears, and blood.
Pertiwi can't be lying.
Dr. Pertiwi is not lying.
He was just noticed by Professor Angkara.
It's true, guys.
It's true.
I was looking for Mushroom.
I met Professor Angkara.
I'm hypnotized.
It's scary.
Now, Pertiwi.
How do we save Professor Adebaran?
This kind of energy transmission is the best.
And now, Professor Adebaran can rest in the clinic.
And in 1 x 24 hours,
Professor Adebaran will be back.
Isn't it amazing?
Thank God.
Wait.
For the sake of Professor Adebaran's safety,
I will use this door.
So only the teacher can enter.
That's a good idea, Professor Purwa.
Good.
Lock the door.
What kind of adventure is this?
In the middle of the road, I met a centaur.
It has a human head.
But it has a horse body.
So, can you defeat it?
Of course.
I, Rey Vega, can defeat it.
Obviously, I'm the strongest.
But, there's more.
The centaur is a white tiger.
The tiger is huge.
I'm about to be beaten up.
Why are you quiet?
Speak up.
The centaur is a white tiger.
Sir, you're amazing.
You can defeat the centaur by yourself.
How can you defeat the centaur by yourself?
Tell me.
Wake up, Alfa.
Alfa, do you know who that is?
Who?
It's you.
Why are you crying?
Alfa, what's wrong?
Come on.
Tell us.
What's wrong?
In the dark, he's evil.
He killed my parents.
First, my father was attacked.
Then, he was burned.
Then, my mother was attacked, too.
Because of him, I became an orphan.
Because of him, I don't even know who my parents are.
I don't know.
Why are there evil people in this world?
Alfa.
Not everything in this world...
...can be understood.
But one thing is clear.
No matter how strong the evil is...
...one day...
...it will be destroyed by the good.
Because in the end...
...the good will win.
To be continued...
Wake up, Farga!
Wake up!
Sir, do you want to use Farga again?
I think it's useless, sir.
Because Alfa knows how to defeat Farga.
I will make Farga again.
Farga!
Like this!
Listen to me. You will not lose.
You only have one chance.
If Cici is separated from you, now...
...you destroy this school.
You bring Aldebaran here.
Now!
If we defeat Aldebaran...
...then the child will be born with us.
No!
Today we will learn a new mantra.
A mantra that you can use to defend yourself.
The mantra is...
...Divinjo.
This mantra...
...uses the power that comes from within you.
Imagine...
...the person you love...
...is sick.
You want to protect him.
You want to do something.
The greater your power...
...the greater your ability to protect the person you love...
...the greater the power of this mantra.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Now, pay attention.
Divinjo!
Now, we will see...
...the mantra.
Now...
...your turn.
Divinjo!
Next.
Toleng.
Divinjo!
Silence.
Tommy.
Divinjo!
Toleng.
What is that?
That's crazy!
It's pointing at me!
Alva.
Your turn.
Create your feeling.
Imagine the person you love.
Then, memorize the mantra.
Divinjo!
Toleng.
Alva!
Very good, Alva.
What do you imagine...
...so that you can release that great power?
My parents, sir.
Alva.
Alva, where are you going?
Where are you going?
I want to fight Barga, sir.
No, you stay here.
But, sir.
No.
I won't let the kids get hurt.
You stay here.
Let the teachers do their job.
Do you understand?
Sir.
What else?
The weakness is in the belt.
If the professor takes off the belt...
...he will be robbed.
Alva.
Everyone.
Attack Barga.
I will try to break the belt.
Because Barga's weakness is in the belt.
Let's go.
Sir.
Alva.
He's gone.
He's back.
He's here again.
What should I do?
I'm scared.
Let's go.
Alva.
What should we do, sir?
I think I can make him stronger.
Let's go there.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Barga.
Alva.
I feel weird.
I feel dizzy.
I want to faint.
Don't do that.
He's so strong.
You attacked him?
Let me help you.
Defend yourself.
Yes.
You're so cool, Alva.
You're welcome.
Try me.
You're dead.
You can't defeat Barga, Alva.
Barga is stronger now.
Barga won't be defeated.
Good, Barga.
Keep going.
Don't give up.
Okay.
Now.
On the count of three.
We'll fight him.
One.
Two.
Three.
Attack.
It's okay.
Wake up.
We should go.
We'll lure him out of the school.
If we stay here, the children will be hurt.
The school will be destroyed.
Let's attack him.
One, two, three.
Attack.
To be continued.
Pika.
Wake up.
Help me.
That's bad.
That's Karaklinik.
He's going to attack the teacher.
Ouch.
What happened?
OMG.
The children must be practicing.
Be careful.
I'll stab you.
Wait.
Pegasus.
Help me.
Wake up.
Pegasus.
I'm safe.
Pika.
Where's Alva?
Alva.
Alva, where are you?
Alva is in the other room.
It's heavier.
Don't say it now.
Pika.
Let's look for her.
Alva.
Damn it.
How dare they kidnap a teenager in the middle of the night.
They're disgusting.
They're scary.
Stop it.
There's no point in fighting like this.
It won't change the future.
Then, what should we do now?
There's a letter.
From who?
From Angkara.
Read it.
I'm sorry.
I've kidnapped your beloved head of the school.
But don't worry.
There's a way to save Professor Aldebaran.
That is...
...to give up Alva.
Alva?
Tonight...
...before the sun sets...
...the teachers...
...have to come and give me Alva.
I won't give Alva to them.
Then, what should we do now, Megantara?
We're in a very difficult position.
We have to save Alva...
...or...
...Professor Aldebaran.
We can't give Alva to them.
So, it's better...
...if one of us...
...becomes Alva.
Who?
Me.
You, Megantara?
I will find a way...
...to save Professor Aldebaran.
But right now...
...the power of the Dark Palace has increased.
It won't be easy for you to defeat him.
But, Professor Ragni...
...I agree with Megantara.
They won't be suspicious...
...if Megantara is missing...
...from the teachers.
And it's useless for us to debate, but we won't do anything.
Everyone, wait here.
I will prepare a mantra to change the ending.
Now, stand on the chair.
Change.
Alva
I ate five of them.
I'm so full.
I'm Alva the Handsome.
Megantara.
Wait in front of the teacher.
Now, it's time to face them.
Let's go.
I can't go out.
I'm scared.
Alva.
Let's go.
Wait.
Alva.
Take off your coat.
Who are you looking for?
The Handsome.
Handsome.
I will kill you all.
I want to tell you...
...that Professor Aldebaran was kidnapped by the monster.
Kidnapped?
So, we have to stop the professor.
And we have to defeat the monster.
But, how?
The professor is stronger than the monster.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Why?
Alva was kidnapped by the monster.
He's hanging on the wall.
Oh, no.
Show your spirit.
Get ready, my friend.
Run, jump, jump.
We are...
...brave.
Don't give up.
Chase your dream.
Go, go, go.
Achieve all your dreams.
Never stop.
Go, go, go.
Fight with all your might.
Make yourself proud.
Go, go, go.
Let's dream.
We are sure.