To be continued...
Go, go, go.
Make yourself proud. Go, go, go.
Let's dream.
Go, go, go.
We can do it.
Why don't you act according to my order?
But, sir...
Shut up!
I don't want all my plans to fail.
We'll wait until next month.
The time is now.
Mom, what's wrong?
Dad!
Think!
What have you done?
Who are you?
You stole my parents.
Don't ask me.
I'm not lying.
I'm Alva.
And they're my parents.
We don't have much time.
We only have a short time.
Before the sun sets.
And I don't want...
...Srigala to become Panji.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
I'm ready.
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
Help!
Srigala!
Boss, come here.
I'm scared.
What's wrong?
I want to buy a stone.
I can't do it alone.
Sir!
Help!
What's wrong?
I'm attacked.
Attacked by what?
I'm attacked by Srigala.
Srigala?
Srigala came out of...
...Panji's house.
Let's take him to the village doctor.
Let's go.
Professor.
If that's the case.
In my opinion.
There's only one way.
Starting tomorrow.
I'll train the kids.
So, they're ready to fight.
But, can they do it?
They're tough kids.
In the village.
I won't leave them alone.
If necessary.
I'm ready to sacrifice my life.
Until they run out of blood.
But, there's one more problem.
What is it?
It's about Alfa.
Until now.
I haven't heard from Vega.
I'm afraid.
They have a problem with Panji.
Professor.
Can we...
...share the task?
Me.
Professor Titan.
And Professor Agni.
We'll train the kids.
Meanwhile.
Professor Purwa.
I think he's the right person.
To bring Vega and his friends to Panji's house.
Look.
Panji left us.
Give it to Vega.
What if he wants it?
He wants to hurt us.
Where are we going?
You're right, Naya.
Let's go.
I know the way.
What is it?
Can we?
If we become human again.
If we're hit by the sun.
It's already late.
It's only midnight.
So, it's 6 o'clock.
That's right.
It's 6 o'clock.
We're going to be chased.
Let's go.
I want to use the toilet first.
Ferita, go to sleep.
I can't.
I'll try.
Ferita, sit down.
Where are you going?
I'll try again.
Ferita, be quiet.
Where are we going?
I can't.
I'm going to be chased.
I can't be chased.
It's time.
My body...
It hurts.
Hang in there.
Looks like...
Your wound isn't that bad.
You should rest.
And don't think too much.
All of this...
Because of Serigala.
We can't stay silent.
We have to get rid of him.
If not...
There will be other victims.
But, how can we defeat Serigala?
Listen to me.
I'm a good hunter.
And I know...
How to defeat Serigala.
Serigala is afraid of fire.
And if we attack him...
And I burn him with eternal fire...
Which comes from my soul...
Then, he will die.
You're right.
We should gather men.
Let's burn him.
Let's go.
You're going to die, Panji.
Let's go down.
I want to try.
Let's burn him.
Let's go.
I want to try.
I want to burn him.
Not yet.
I want to join.
I want to burn him.
Hey, you.
Don't push me.
I'm scared.
Let's burn him.
I'm tired.
Calm down.
It's better to burn him than to stay alive.
Let's burn him.
I just remembered.
Serigala's arrow is so sharp.
Then, he will know where we are.
Really?
It's frozen.
Are you ready, Prita?
I don't know.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Prita.
It's frozen.
What should we do?
I don't know.
I'll try again.
Wait.
Let's hide first.
Come on.
There's no way to hide.
There's someone down there.
Water.
Serigala
Dad, I'm scared.
Calm down.
Serigala can be a good pet.
As long as you can touch his nose.
Okay?
My dad said,
if Serigala wants to be a pet,
you have to touch his nose.
Don't be ridiculous.
Yes.
Hold it.
Are you crazy?
Just hold it.
Don't be ridiculous.
What are you doing?
Is that really Jinat?
Yes, it's Jinat.
It's scary.
I'll try.
Lift one leg.
It's cold.
Serigala,
now,
you have to jump.
I'll try.
Now, stay still.
One, two, three.
Yes, Jinat.
Let's burn the monster.
Let's burn it.
Maji, come out.
What's going on?
Serigala can be a good pet.
You have to come out.
Maji.
Maji, come out.
Professor Adebar.
What do you want?
I want you...
to come to my house.
Why do I have to go there?
Until now,
Vega and his friends...
haven't come back.
And this is what worries me.
You know how I am.
I'm afraid...
Vega and his friends will get into trouble there.
But why me, Professor?
Why not Megantara?
Or Professor Yasmin? Or Professor Ragni?
You know that...
I've never liked him.
He's a weirdo.
I know.
But you're the only one who can go there.
Because the other professors,
Megantara, Yasmin, Ragni, and Titan,
they have other tasks.
And one more thing.
You're the only one who can harm Paci.
What do you think?
Are you ready?
Whatever you say, Professor.
I'll do it.
I'll count to three.
If you don't come out, I'll slam the door.
Huh?
Where are we?
We've been waiting for so long.
Yes.
Why didn't you come out?
I'm scared.
One!
Two!
Three!
Let's go!
Come on, Paci!
There they are! Let's chase them!
Don't run!
Where do you think you're going?
Let's go!
Let's burn them!
Don't burn them!
That's a good idea.
This is not a bad idea.
This is not a good idea.
Let's burn them!
He's right.
Let's just run away.
I agree.
Let's go.
He knows about life.
What if something happens to him?
I can't live anymore.
Let's just follow them.
How?
Just follow them.
Let's burn them!
Don't listen to them.
People.
Don't hesitate to attack those kids.
They're evil.
No.
That's a lie.
It's true.
He's evil.
You're all on his side.
He's a liar.
He's a traitor.
Yes, people.
Don't trust him.
Kids.
Who believes you?
Come on, people.
Let's attack them.
Let's solve this problem.
Let's burn them.
Let's go.
Be careful.
It's been 5 minutes.
It's been 5 years.
Don't be stupid.
This can be a truth book.
Let's give it to them.
Let's just talk to them.
Let's go.
Let's run.
Where are we going?
Let's hide here.
Let's go.
Luckily, this is a good place.
If not, I won't be able to sleep.
Don't be noisy.
They'll be here soon.
Let's hide here.
Where should we hide?
Let's hide under the leaves.
They're here.
I'm going to attack them.
I'm going to kill them.
Where are they?
Everyone.
I told you.
They're evil.
They made us stupid.
Let's not waste our time.
Let's go after them.
I'm sure they're still here.
Let's look for them somewhere else.
Let's go.
I don't know where they are.
If they're far away, let's hide here.
They're here.
They're over there.
I think I heard their voices.
Where are they?
I think they're over there.
Let's go after them.
You're going to pay for this.
Hold on.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
You can't go anywhere.
Let's go.
Hold on.
You can't go anywhere this time.
Let's go.
Everyone.
Listen to me.
I'm Angkara.
I'm a good slayer.
And now...
I'm going to burn this evil tribe...
with eternal fire.
As you know...
this eternal fire...
can't be extinguished by human magic.
Let me go!
Let go of that witch!
Don't touch me again!
Let me go!
And now...
it's time for me to burn her.
Don't!
Let me go!
Feel this.
Traitor.
Now you can go.
Let me see...
what you've done.
Thank you, good slayer.
Let's go home.
To be continued...
And now for the second task.
Which is to bring you to Alpha.
I will take you to the Dark Abyss...
so you can be destroyed by him.
Let us go!
What are you doing?
Take that!
Hurry up!
Attack him!
Go!
One, two, three!
Attack him!
Serigala!
Defend him!
Where should we go?
Where?
I'll go there.
Pavanam!
Sir!
Let me try.
Don't cut the water!
Serigala!
Let me try.
Let me go!
This is not funny.
Where are they?
They're fighting!
Wait for me!
We're going to die!
Just like what Professor Akari said!
Let me go!
We're going to die!
Just like what Professor Akari said.
This is eternal fire.
We're going to die.
What should we do?
Go!
Defend him!
Go back to that place.
Make sure he's safe.
And bring his body here.
Yes.
He can use teleportation.
He can go from there.
That's impossible.
He can't talk.
You're right.
He has to move.
So, we have to turn him into Mr. Panji.
But how?
Yes.
He's not a human anymore.
If he's exposed to the sun, we have to steal the sun.
Steal the sun?
That's impossible.
If he's exposed to the sun, what should we do?
Whatever it is, we have to try.
Let's try to find him.
What should we do?
He's too slow.
He's going to turn into me.
I know.
I know what to do.
Let's find him.
Putri Bintang!
Help me!
I'm lost!
Putri Bintang!
Alva?
Alva, Plita.
How are you?
Hi, sister!
There's fire!
You're making a fire?
That's so exciting!
It's not a fire!
It's a serigala!
Serigala is Mr. Panji!
He's a human!
Oh my God!
He's going to be burned!
I want to ask you for a favor.
Can you make the sun appear?
If there's a sun, he'll turn into a human.
But don't take too long!
It's still hot!
I'm so sorry, guys.
I can't help you.
I don't know the sun.
He's a human.
He appears in the morning.
I appear at night.
Oh no!
I can't do it!
Where is it?
Oh, I know!
I can call the stars and the moon...
to hide.
So, the morning will come faster.
Okay, hurry up!
Hurry up!
Okay.
Friends of the stars and the moon,
let's hide.
So, the morning will come faster.
Yes, it's morning!
Sir!
You have to go there.
You have to use your right hand.
Right hand!
Hurry up!
What's the result, Angkar?
I can't feel anything...
if I don't see Angkar and his friends there.
And they make me feel nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Angkar!
Why are you quiet?
Answer me!
Sir.
This time,
the magic has worked, sir.
I've managed to provoke...
all the villagers to burn all of that, sir.
And now, all of that...
has become...
grilled meat, sir.
You'll see for yourself when he's dead.
No, sir.
But...
he can't get away.
Because I've burned him with eternal fire.
And eternal fire can't be extinguished, sir.
Idiot!
Now, go back to your place.
Make sure you're safe.
And bring his body here.
Yes, sir.
Alright, sir.
Wait here.
Angkar
Sir.
Why are they here?
What's the story?
The story...
is very sad.
In the past,
I was the son of the 8th Prince.
The 8th Prince...
taught me...
to be a cruel and evil ruler...
who doesn't harm anyone...
without my permission.
Angkar
Hurry up.
Kill him.
Angkar
Good.
Meanwhile,
I have two friends.
They are your parents.
Gama and Aquila.
Actually,
they often advised me...
to leave the 8th Prince.
But I don't want to.
Because I want to be strong.
One day,
I was assigned by the 8th Prince.
But I failed.
When he found out about my failure,
the 8th Prince was very angry.
He wanted to kill me.
But suddenly,
someone threw a smoke bomb...
and killed me.
That person is you.
In the end, I decided...
to leave the 8th Prince.
But the 8th Prince didn't leave him alone.
He was very cruel.
He was very angry with Gama.
And he insisted...
that he must destroy Gama and Aquila.
Do it!
To be continued...
Why?
Only my parents were killed.
Why not me?
You mean,
he didn't kill you and let you live?
For that matter,
no one knows.
But one thing is clear.
When the 8th Prince attacked you,
a power came out of you...
and made the 8th Prince furious.
When he wanted to attack you again,
he realized...
that the 8th Prince...
realized...
that he had lost all his power.
To be continued...
It can't be!
I can't lose my power!
Then,
why did the 8th Prince faint...
when he attacked me?
According to Aldebaran,
that was my love mantra.
That mantra was created by your parents.
Do you know Prince Aldebaran?
Yes.
Back then,
he was the teacher of the 5 Earthlings in Sihir.
When I was still in school.
In Sihir School.
Now, he's a school principal.
Oh.
So, you're a Sihir student.
Aldebaran is half my age.
So, that means...
you look really old.
You scared me.
Do you still want to hear the story?
Of course.
Of course I do.
Don't worry.
The 8th Prince has lost all his power.
He's trying to find a way...
to regain all his power.
He's looking for all kinds of resources.
Finally, he realizes...
that there's a way...
to regain all his power.
That is with blood,
tears,
and your sweat, Alva.
Then, why are my parents here?
Gamma, I'm lost.
I'm lost.
Gamma.
Gamma, I'm lost.
Panji.
The chain of life.
Put it on me.
It's in your closet.
No.
The chain of life...
should be able to heal them.
But because their wounds are so bad,
they can't be healed, Alva.
They can only sleep...
and can't wake up again.
This chain of life...
only supports their lives.
As far as I know, they can only get married.
So, the way my parents talk...
is just a dream.
You said they appeared in your dream?
Yes.
No wonder.
They told me...
to pray and cheer up.
Alva.
If Gamma and I said they appeared in your dream,
please ask them.
Ask them what I should do...
to wake them up.
Okay.
I'll tell them.
I'll go now.
I still have unfinished business.
Sir, where are you going?
I want to kill Angkara.
I'm confused with him.
Why is he attacking me?
We've met before.
Don't meet him.
He's the son of the 8th Prince.
Angkara is the son of the 8th Prince?
Yes.
They're getting stronger...
because they've got...
my tears, sweat, and blood.
Angkara is the son of the 8th Prince.
I'm sure the ant has been burned to ashes.
But...
what should I bring home for the 8th Prince?
5 years later
This is for Kayu.
The 8th Prince will never be able to stop him.
5 years later
Look, Sir.
This is his body.
He has become worse.
I'm dead.
How do you know that's not Panji's body?
I'm going there.
I won't let you do anything to Panji.
5 years later
Finally, I won.
Shut up!
Who told you to do that?
I'm sorry, Sir.
5 years later
Guys, Adi is coming.
Don't be scared.
That's Professor Ankara.
As soon as the door is opened,
we'll attack Professor Ankara with the TV.
Okay?
Okay.
Just go in.
Don't lock the door.
TV!
Professor Burua?
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Professor Burua.
Shut up, Sir!
Shut up, all of you!
Let's go.
No one can go back.
Shut up, all of you!
Professor Burua.
Why are you here, Sir?
Shut up!
5 years later
What's going on?
Panji.
This must be you.
You ordered the kids to attack me.
Right?
Don't you dare accuse me.
5 years later
Professor Burua.
I'm sorry.
We didn't mean to.
We thought you were Professor Ankara.
Yes, Sir.
So, we avoided it.
We avoided it.
Professor Burua.
What are you doing here?
I was ordered by Professor Aldebaran...
to come here...
and pick all of you up...
to go back to school.
What?
So, Professor Burua came here to pick us up?
Yes.
Sir.
What should I do?
Should I stay here and take care of you...
or should I go with Professor Burua?
We'll send Aldebaran to the fire prison.
And...
I'll take you as the head of the magic school.
We can do it.
I order you...
to pack your things...
and come with me to the magic school.
I'm sorry, Professor.
I don't want to.
I don't want to go home.
Alva.
Let me remind you.
You're still a student of the magic school.
I'm your teacher.
And I'm responsible for your safety.
So, you have to come with me.
Toleng.
Vega.
Belita.
Ray.
Let's go.
We don't want to.
I don't want to go home.
I want to stay here.
We don't want to.
I don't want to.
Yes, sir.
It's like eating...
three meals a day.
It's not good, sir.
Sir.
We still have important things to do.
What are you doing?
Panji.
I know...
this must be you.
You told the kids to stay here.
You brainwashed them.
Right?
No, sir.
So, I was wrong?
I told you...
not to accuse them.
Right?
It's clear now.
They chose me...
over you.
We still have important things to do.
You'll see.
Alva.
Let's go home.
No.
Let's go.
No, sir.
I don't want to go home.
Shut up. You have to come with me.
Let's go.
No, sir.
I don't want to go home.
Enough.
Let Alva go.
Let them go home.
I'm warning you.
Don't get involved in my business.
Alva.
Let's go home.
Where are the other kids?
Sir, don't go there.
Yes, sir.
I don't want to go home with you.
I want to stay here with Panji.
I'm sorry, sir.
I still have things to do here.
Alright.
If that's what you want.
Alva.
I'll let you stay here.
But on one condition.
What is it, sir?
You have to fight me.
If you lose.
You and the others have to come with me to Sihir's school.
But if you refuse.
I'll let you stay here.
With the others.
I don't want to go home.
How is it?
If you...
Don't want to fight me.
I'll assume that you give up.
And it means that you fail.
And due to that.
You and the others have to come with me.
Come on kids, let's go home.
Dad.
I want to fight.
Oh my God.
You're like this.
You're always looking for trouble.
Panji is not dead.
Panji is dead, sir.
So, what's our next plan?
I'll move on to the second list.
But before that.
I want to give you a present, Angkara.
Because you have successfully completed the mission perfectly.
What do you want, Angkara?
I'll grant it.
I want to be the head of the magic school, sir.
What a coincidence, Angkara.
That's also on my mind.
Then.
We'll send Aldebaran to the fire prison.
And.
I'll promote you as the head of the magic school, Angkara.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Finally.
My chance to get rid of Aldebaran as the head of the magic school has come.
As the head of the magic school.
I want to make the last vote.
To decide who deserves to be the head of the magic school.
Please.
To be continued...
For the time being.
For Professor Aldebaran and Professor Angkara.
It's unanimous.
There's only one vote left.
Please, Professor Agni.
I will win.
Because Agni will choose me.
Professor Agni chooses.
Professor Aldebaran.
Long live Professor Aldebaran.
Why did you choose Aldebaran?
Because you're my future wife.
Angkara.
We do have a close relationship.
And the election of the head of the school.
Has nothing to do with our relationship.
I'm sure.
Aldebaran can be a good head of the school.
So, you mean...
I'm not good?
No.
That's not what I mean.
I'm disappointed in you.
Finish him!
Sir!
To be continued...
One.
Two.
Three.
Sir!
Finish him!
I think this is just a small competition.
Looks like...
No one supports me.
May I shake your hand...
For my first round victory.
We're a safe team.
We don't want to be a traitor.
Yes.
We're a team.
I don't want to be a traitor.
What's that?
Yes.
Let's just vote. We're at risk.
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, sir.
Maybe you're all wondering...
About the writing in front of you.
Here's the thing.
Our school will have a selection.
Who among you...
Has the ability and is ready to fight?
The chosen one...
Will be a part of...
Laskar Aldebaran.
The mission of Laskar Aldebaran...
Is, first...
You're ready to serve the school.
And second...
You're ready to destroy...
Pangeran Kegelapan.
Pangeran Kegelapan?
Yes.
That's right.
So, we can't just choose a kid...
To be a part of the team.
We have to select him correctly.
That's right, kids.
What Professor Agni said.
That's right.
This is my chance to be a champion.
I don't have Alpha anymore.
I'm joining the army.
Me too.
Mami, are you sure you want to join?
When we fought the raptors, you ran away.
We'll see.
I'm going to fight Pangeran Kegelapan.
We've arrived at Sekolah Sihir, sir.
Okay, kids.
Before we start the activity.
Let's sing the song...
Mars Sekolah Sihir.
Kids.
Don't forget the style I taught you.
Yes, sir.
Kids.
Since this is the song of Mars.
You have to sing it with spirit.
Yes, sir.
Good.
Let's start on three.
One.
Two.
Three.
Amkara.
If you're the head of the school here.
Change the song.
They all have to be my followers.
Yes, sir.
I'll make this school the second head of the school.
You'll see, Agni.
You'll know...
I'll make this school the second head of the school.
Try to imitate it.
Do it with a smile.
How is this?
How can you beat Pangeran Kegelapan?
You lost to the raptors.
Whose voice is that?
That's his voice.
That's none of your business.
Don't give up.
Chase your dreams.
Go, go, go.
Achieve all your dreams.
Never stop.
Go, go, go.
Fight with your heart.
Be proud of yourself.
Go, go, go.
Let's dream.
We'll make it.