To be continued...
Go, go, go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go, go, go!
We can do it!
Participants have to dive to the bottom of the lake.
When they arrive at the bottom of the lake,
they have to take a net that has been protected by their tail.
Papadita!
Give it to me!
So, for this first match,
the winner is...
Alva!
I have to think about it.
How can I beat Alva?
I need Alva.
She can't take part in the next match.
I know how to do it.
Help!
Her voice is around here.
Where is she?
Help!
Open it!
Kids,
the match will start in 15 minutes.
For the participants,
gather at the school page as soon as possible.
Where is Alva?
Why is she missing?
I've been looking for her for a long time.
Alva must be eliminated.
What if Alva is here?
What should I do?
Alva must be here.
I'm going to look for Alva.
Where is Alva?
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to look for Alva.
It's getting darker.
Who is she?
She's around here.
I must find her.
To be continued...
I'm going to look for Alva.
Where is she?
Calm down.
I'm going to look for Alva.
Don't worry about me.
Calm down.
Just sleep.
I'm going to look for Alva.
If you want to attack me again,
I can attack you back.
Look at this.
It's not moving.
This is bad.
To be continued...
It's dangerous.
Because there's a reptile inside.
A reptile?
How can a reptile be in a school?
Yes.
This is a reptile.
Actually,
I caught it from the forest.
It's still wild.
So, it's dangerous.
That's too bad.
I heard a scary sound.
Luckily, there's a reptile inside.
It's scary.
The problem is,
I'm preparing a cage for the reptile.
So, I'm going to put it in the cage.
Stay away from the cage.
Don't come near it. It's dangerous.
This is the food that reptiles like.
Are you sure?
That's why I told you not to come near it.
It's better to come near the competition.
Let's go.
Help!
Help me!
Alfa must be scared.
Because he's late.
Professor Aldebaran.
It's time.
Okay.
We're going to start now.
Kids.
The competition will start in five minutes.
For those who are not here yet,
the participants will be eliminated.
Bro.
I was playing in the dark.
In the dark?
Really?
I'm not lying.
I saw it in the mirror.
I looked for it, but I couldn't find it.
There's a crow and a lazy cow.
Don't lie.
You're dreaming.
It's true.
I'm not lying.
I'm not dreaming.
There's a horse eating a donut.
I'm just kidding.
Don't be mad.
Vega.
Maybe you're still traumatized...
by being in the dark.
So, keep thinking.
Really, Tendara?
Yes, you're stressed.
Instead of thinking about it,
it's better to ask Alfa.
So, your mind will be calm.
And you'll be happy.
Your heart will be at ease.
And you'll feel better.
Okay?
Let's go.
Help!
It's attacking.
Hey, Alfa.
Mr. Titan.
What are you doing?
It's like a cow eating a donut, Alfa.
Enough.
Go away.
I don't want to be helped.
It's dangerous.
This kind of problem is annoying, Alfa.
Enough.
Go away.
You're going to join the race, right?
Race?
I want to go first.
You need this...
to win the race.
Get in.
Zira.
No, thank you.
What is it for?
You'll understand.
Okay, Sir.
Thank you.
Thank you, Sir.
Take this.
To Be Continued...
It's not here.
Where is it?
Gosh.
This is weird.
Where is Alva?
I'm scared, Tom.
Yes, I'm scared.
Let's go before the war.
Kids.
Now, I'll start counting.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Hurray, Alva is here.
Thank you, Sir.
Finally, you're here too, Alva.
Where have you been?
Where have I been?
But, King.
I'll replace you.
I have something to do.
Kids.
The competition will start soon.
The rule is...
Every contestant...
must get three horses...
from Gadis Angsa.
Three horses from Gadis Angsa.
Where can we get them?
She doesn't like men.
Get the door.
Kids.
This is the magic door.
Every contestant...
who enters the magic door...
will go to the residence of Gadis Angsa.
Let's start...
with the first contestant.
Please.
Rey.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Twenty.
Ouch.
That's the Gadis Angsa.
How can we get the 30 horses?
I know.
Get the red door.
It's so hard to be a conservationist.
Why can't I get the red door?
I want...
the red door.
The red one.
GADIS ANGSA
Now, I want to be a woman.
Hi, Gadis Angsa.
Yes, I did it.
Who are you?
I'm Rey.
Don't say Rey.
I'm Reyina.
Why don't you remember me?
I'm the one from that time.
So, what are you doing here?
I'm lost.
I can't go back there.
I have to go to school.
I want to get the 30 horses.
Poor you.
What should we do?
We don't want to give it to them.
Right?
Yes.
Where should we give it to?
We can give it to them.
But, only to people...
who can understand us.
How?
That's the secret.
Right, girls?
That's right.
Gadis Angsa is happy.
I know.
We can...
give it to vegetables.
Why vegetables?
We don't like it.
We're not normal.
Right?
That's right.
Girls.
Yippee!
We got it.
What's wrong with you?
I got hit.
How?
Calm down, girls.
Because you didn't get the grasshopper,
you're disqualified.
You did it.
Alva, you have to succeed.
Just trust us.
Yes, sir.
You can't lose.
Yes, Alva.
If you lose, I'll replace you.
Alva and I know...
what's the secret of Gadis Angsa.
If I knew it,
Papi would have told me.
Today, I'll win.
And now,
the next contestant.
Tommy.
Tommy!
But, boss.
He got hit.
Tommy!
There's a man.
Attack!
Wait.
I have something for you.
Here.
Thank you, boss.
Wait.
If you want to compete with this red flower,
you have to give three of your Angsa feathers.
Yippee!
What do you think, teachers?
Is it real?
What do you think, Professor Agni?
Can you guarantee it's real?
It's real, Megantara.
It's real, professor.
It's real. What do we do?
You have to do it, Alva.
Alva, you have to win.
You can't lose to Tommy.
And now,
the next contestant.
Please, Alva.
It's real.
Be careful, Alva.
I can hear it.
Hi, everyone.
It's a man.
That's Alva.
Are you here to ask for our feathers, too?
Like your friend?
Yes.
Can I?
Of course.
Thank you, Megantara.
Yippee!
Don't!
Our feathers are precious.
Don't just give it to him.
But I know you want to help him.
Sure.
As long as he can pay with something worth it.
To win the contest.
I have something.
What is it?
It's real.
Yippee!
Alva, can you give us more?
We still need more.
We have 10.
I know.
I got it.
It's a camera.
It's a twin camera.
If you take a picture,
the number will be high.
Do you believe me?
Okay, I'll try.
I'll try.
There.
We have 10, right?
Yippee!
Here, Alva.
Why are there so many?
I only said three.
Alva, this is a bonus for you.
Because you made us happy.
Is it true?
It's true.
Okay.
Thank you.
Why isn't Alva here yet?
It's been so long.
I'm worried.
I know, it's been so long.
Be patient.
Alva will be here soon.
Alva is great.
Alva will succeed.
Trust me.
Alva won't win this time.
The winner is Honyok!
What do you think, Alva?
I didn't get it, Prof.
See, it's true. Alva didn't do anything.
She failed.
But, I have something.
Here's the proof.
To prove it,
we'll hand it over to Prof. Akli.
Akli will investigate which one is fake and which one is real.
Please.
Alva! Alva! Alva!
What do you think, Prof. Akli?
What?
It's real.
Real?
It's real, Prof.
And it's more than Tommy.
If that's the case,
for the second match,
the winner is...
Alva!
Alva! Alva! Alva!
Attention, kids.
The third match...
will be held in three days.
So, to the contestants,
Alva and Tommy,
please get ready.
Yes, sir.
Prof. Alhara, why are you here?
We can do it.
That's right.
Your opponent is me, Prof. Alhara.
Bang!
You're dead.
I will make this laptop mine.
I will use it.
Get ready.
Stamper.
Stamper is a sign...
that you're mine.
You're mine.
How did you know...
that the colors of the pencil...
are brown and pink?
I don't know.
I was given by Prof. Titan.
Wow.
That's cheating.
Cheating?
Cheating.
Prof. Titan gave you a sketchbook.
He didn't give me a sketchbook.
He only gave me brown and pink.
He said it would be useful.
That's the same.
Prof. Titan knows how to draw.
I'm getting lazy.
Vega.
Don't be like that.
Prof. Titan is a good person.
He's my teacher.
You too.
I was saved...
when I met Sir Raptor.
Sir Raptor?
The one in the warehouse?
Yes.
I was trapped there.
I became Prof. Titan.
I want to be like you.
Alva.
Come here.
I became suspicious of Prof. Titan.
Why does he keep helping Alva?
What does he mean?
Alva was helped by Prof. Titan...
to get brown and pink.
That's cheating.
I know.
I have to fight Alva with the professor.
Then, he will get mad at the professor.
Then, he will get mad at me.
Then, he will be disqualified.
I will win.
What should I do?
You gave it to me.
Why did you put it in my bag?
I don't know.
What did I do?
Prof.
Wait.
Tommy.
Prof.
There's something I want to tell you about Alva.
What's so important about Alva that you want to tell me?
It's very important, Prof.
I assure you.
Prof. Purwa and Prof. Aldebaran...
will get mad.
Tell me.
What's the matter?
Yesterday, during a competition to get Alva's hair...
Alva...
What's wrong with Alva, Tommy?
Tommy.
Say it.
Alva...
What's wrong with Alva?
Why is my voice like this?
I will explain it in sign language.
I remind you, Tommy.
Don't play around.
Al...
Enough!
You're wasting my time.
If you do this again, you will be punished.
Do you understand?
You're wasting my time.
Why is my voice weird?
Hello?
It turns out that Tommy is here.
Hi, handsome.
I have a present for you.
I got it.
Chocolate.
I got chocolate from you.
Why did you reject me?
I know why you rejected me.
Because of your teeth.
Professor Gadil.
Professor Curang.
You helped Alva.
I will tell Alva and you to Professor Aldebaran.
Wait, Tommy.
While we're waiting, I will show you something.
Yes!
Come on, Tommy.
Show me how to play from scratch.
Tommy.
First, I have to show you.
Now, I have to show you again?
Think about it, Tommy.
Ah, Papi.
Show me.
If you don't show me, I will scream.
Ah!
Don't make noise.
That's why I told you.
But...
That's enough.
Don't make noise again.
Okay.
Okay, Papi.
Let me tell you.
I brought you two flowers.
And a heart-shaped chocolate.
If you give it to that girl, they will be happy.
Oh, I see.
Yes!
Look, Tommy.
You don't have enough proof.
I gave you flowers and chocolate.
But I showed that picture to Professor Aldebaran.
You will be disqualified, Tommy.
Professor, I'm sorry.
Don't tell Professor Aldebaran, please.
Don't, Professor.
Okay, Tommy.
I won't tell you.
But you have to stay still.
And we don't have to explain anything.
Just concentrate on the third test.
Okay, handsome?
Darn it.
Isn't that Professor Titan?
Why is he standing in front of the warehouse?
There he is.
Professor Aldebaran?
Why is he here?
Ouch, it hurts.
Give him a lesson.
Ouch.
Oh, my God.
My eyes are so scary.
But I'm going to be a witness to Professor Titan.
Maybe he has something to do with the dark wizard.
If he uses a real magic, he will change soon.
We can do it.
What should we do, Pi?
I can't. I always lose.
If I keep losing, I will be his opponent.
Shh.
Tommy, don't be harsh.
If other people find out, it will be dangerous.
What about me?
If I don't participate in the competition, it will be hard for Tommy to win.
Yes, I'm also confused.
Your friend named Alva must be very smart.
You often give him a tip, but he never wins.
No, Pi. Alva is not smart.
Alva is a wizard.
That's why he can't keep losing.
Anyway, Tommy has to win this time.
If he doesn't win, Tommy will be beaten for a week.
Shh.
Don't do that.
Your friend will be stressed.
That's why Tommy has to win.
So, what's the task for later?
I don't know.
Oh.
So, you want Tommy to lose.
It's okay.
Tommy will be beaten for eating and drinking.
Don't do that.
But, promise me.
If I tell you the task, you have to win.
Okay.
Okay, I'll tell you.
Huh? Catching a ghost?
Professor Tim.
We're in the dark.
I'll be attacked.
I'll wake up from my dream.
Why are you laughing?
I think my dream is a clue for me.
Come on, Pegah.
If it's a dream, it's a dream.
Don't get involved with real life.
Yes, Pegah.
It's a slander.
The professor often gives us lollipops and chocolates.
So many of them.
Hey, listen.
You guys.
Don't trust people.
You have to remember.
Professor Rangkara.
Professor Rangkara?
He pretended to be nice to us.
Very nice.
But, what did he do?
He gave us lollipops.
It means he's a genius.
So, I think...
...Professor Titan has something to do with the dark.
Pegah.
You're exaggerating.
No one is nice since then.
It's a slander.
Professor Titan is nice.
Right, Re?
If you don't believe me, I'll prove it.
That's it.
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, sir.
Why are you guys not excited?
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, sir.
Alright.
Today's lesson is...
...the history of magic.
Where we're going to learn...
...about the magic of changing existence...
...without confusion.
This magic includes...
...high level black magic.
And...
...it's not time to be mastered by you.
What's so great about this magic?
This magic...
...can change someone's existence...
...into someone else's existence.
What's so great about this magic...
...apart from changing someone else's existence...
...but it can also change...
...the nature of the person.
That's why this magic...
...is a perfect magic for the person.
And it can last up to a year.
Sir.
Isn't there any weakness in this magic?
There is.
Of course there's a weakness in this magic.
Then, what is it?
The weakness of this magic is...
Maybe some of you know...
...what the weakness of this magic is.
Someone has to answer.
Where's Vega?
He usually knows the answer.
Vega, what do you think the answer is?
Look.
Where's Vega?
He's not here.
I'm confused too.
I'm confused.
It's weird that he's not here.
Why did he give up?
Because I have to prove that...
...this kind of illusion is definitely bad.
I have to prove that...
No, no, no, Mika.
Mika, what's wrong?
What's wrong with your face, Professor?
Your face is pale.
Sorry, Professor. I didn't mean to.
If he uses the illusion...
...he will definitely change.
What's wrong?
Vega.
What are we looking for?
Why are you staring at Professor?
Professor is scared, Vega.
Sorry, Professor.
It's okay.
It's okay, Professor.
You're smiling.
Professor has a gift for you.
Okay?
You got...
...a lollipop.
Vega.
This is a sweet lollipop...
...for you.
Thank you, Professor.
Let's go, Professor.
He hasn't changed.
Did I make a mistake?
But, Professor is still not here.
To be continued...
Enough.
Since Vega is not here...
...and none of you can answer...
...the weakness of this mantra...
...let me tell you.
The weakness of this mantra...
...is...
...shining.
Oh, shining.
Why is it called shining, soldier?
There's a way to change the world...
...without using magic.
Vega.
What?
You're such a good friend, but you didn't come in.
You're such a bad friend.
The lesson was so fun.
We were taught a changing mantra.
You must be upset that you didn't come in.
Enough. You're so noisy.
I'm studying. Don't disturb me.
Let's study somewhere else.
So noisy.
That person is so weird.
Maybe he's crazy.
He's so sensitive.
He's right.
If it's a girl...
...she's the most difficult to understand.
No wonder.
It's a girl.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Can you come to my room after lunch?
The professor will give you a private lesson...
...for free.
Free.
Do you want to come?
I really want to.
So cute.
The professor has a gift for you.
It's ready.
Chocolate.
This is chocolate from the professor for you.
And for you.
Thank you, professor.
You're so kind.
Okay.
You're welcome.
What's going on?
The professor is kidnapped.
Rettor.
This is your favorite food.
Come out.
Rettor.
This is your favorite food.
Come on, Rettor.
Don't hide.
Hi, Rettor.
Come out.
Rettor.
Eat as much as you want, Rettor.
But remember, Rettor.
I have a task for you tomorrow.
Come on, eat.
I should have gone to his room.
But the professor is gone.
Yes, someone's here.
I'll check the other side.
What's that?
What's inside?
Why is it locked?
I'll open it.
Mom.
Someone's at the door.
Alva's here.
She thinks I'm Professor Titan.
I'll just go out.
It's better if I don't go out.
She'll be mad if she finds out I'm stalking her favorite teacher.
Alva saw Mari too.
I'm sure Alva will be suspicious of Mari.
Be patient, Sentaurus.
You'll be released.
The professor is gone.
Be patient, Sentaurus.
There's a child in this room.
I want to tell her.
I know you must be bored in there.
Right?
Be patient.
You'll be released.
Alva.
Professor.
What are you doing here?
Sentaurus is so noisy.
Maybe he wants to be released.
Maybe he's bored.
Be patient.
Don't worry, Alva.
The professor will play with Sentaurus.
Now, the professor will cast a spell on you.
This spell is used to catch ghosts.
Ghosts?
Have you ever seen a ghost?
Are you scared, Alva?
No. I've seen one.
That's great, Alva.
You can catch ghosts.
I can't, professor.
Ghosts are transparent.
I can only touch them if they're dense.
That's right, Alva.
That's why the professor will teach you this dense spell.
Okay?
Alva, look at the ghost.
Now, the professor will catch it.
Spell!
Alva, look.
I've caught the ghost.
Now, you can try, Alva.
Alva, look.
I'm sorry, professor.
I didn't mean to.
I have to be free.
Since there's a kid in this room.
It's okay, Alva.
Now, you can try again.
I'm sorry, professor.
He's kind.
He taught Alva a new spell.
That means I was wrong.
A, B, C.
What's that noise?
I did it!
Good, Alva.
You did it.
Thank you, professor.
You're welcome.
Help!
I'm the real professor.
Let me go.
A, B, C.
What's that noise?
I think it's from Titan's room.
I think Titan's professor...
...is training with Sentaurus.
Oh, right.
I have to go.
Kids.
It's time for the final match...
...between two contestants.
Alva and Tommy.
Alva!
Calm down, kids.
Alva and Tommy.
You have to ride your bike...
...into the forest.
In the forest, you have to catch...
...a ghost.
Ghost?
That's scary.
After you catch the ghost,
you have to bring it to the finish line.
When you get there,
you have to run...
...to get the prize.
The first one to get the prize...
...will be the winner.
Alva and Tommy, are you ready?
Yes, sir.
One.
Two.
Three!
Tommy!
Don't let him catch us.
It's taking too long.
I'm on standby.
It's a waste of time.
That's it.
He won't be able to catch me.
I'm so weak.
That's Alva.
Yes, that's Alva.
She made me lose my faith in life.
I will make her lose.
Guys,
you better hide.
Don't show up...
...in front of Alva's magic school.
Don't we have to show up?
What should we do?
One is fine.
But Alva is not.
Is that important?
But...
No buts.
We have to catch her.
Don't say buts.
Just follow me.
Don't show up in front of Alva's magic school.
That's it.
Over there.
You're done, Alva.
You won't get the ghost.
And you will lose.
Alva, I'll go right, you go left.
Let's see who gets the ghost first.
Vega?
Don't you watch the race?
There's something more important than the race.
What's that, Vega?
Professor Titan.
What about him?
Professor Titan...
...who's been in our school...
...is a fake.
Bye, Alva.
Don't show up.
You're done, Alva.
The ghost is hiding.
You won't get the ghost.
I'm going.
To be continued...