To be continued...
Go, go, go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go, go, go!
We can do it!
Watch out!
Go, go, go!
Yeah! I did it!
Angkara, did you see that?
There's Alpha over there.
Does that mean he's with us?
So, you're Megatron.
You'd better go.
Let go of Alpha!
I won't let go of Alpha.
Alpha!
Attack him, Alpha.
Now!
Let's attack him!
Let's go, Megatron.
One, two, three!
Yeah!
Angkara was defeated.
Now, it's just me.
Yeah!
Alpha.
I won't let you go.
The door is locked.
It must be a snake from the dark lab.
Calm down, Alpha.
Open the door.
Try it, Alpha.
Okay.
Open the door!
I can't breathe.
Let's chant together.
It's not that easy to get out of here.
I won't let you leave just like that.
This is...
Vira!
Mother!
Now, I'm getting stronger.
Both of you...
won't be able to take me.
And you...
Megantron.
Because you're looking for trouble with me.
Why did you want to kill me first?
Poor Megantron.
Let's fight!
Don't, Alpha!
Back off!
Don't!
Let me face you.
Back off!
Son of a bitch!
You, too!
I can't.
It's okay, Alpha.
Don't be afraid.
Don't, Alpha!
So, we have to fight the dark lab, right?
Yes.
We have to help Alpha.
The dark lab is really strong.
Yo!
The dark lab...
is not a bungee jump like us.
We can do it.
We can be a parachute.
I'm scared.
But, I feel sorry for Alpha.
Yes, you're right.
So, do you want to join us?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll join you.
Let's go.
Okay.
Wait, wait.
I want to join, too.
Let's go.
Wait, wait.
You're alone in the dark lab.
Be careful.
I want to join, too.
I want to help Alpha.
I want to be a hero, too.
So, you want to join us.
Let's go.
Xixi!
I can't breathe.
Alpha, it's better to help Megantara now.
Let me face our next challenge.
Yes, Prof.
Be careful, Prof.
She's very strong.
Sephera!
Professor is still injured.
Don't attack her!
Don't worry.
I have never lost.
Professor!
Wake up, Professor!
Megantara, wake up!
Why am I here?
Amazing!
Professor Aldebaran is awake!
Thank God!
I'm so happy!
Professor Aldebaran,
forget
Professor Tengsan
was attacked by the Dark Knight.
I'm very, very badly injured.
Alpha!
Where's Alpha?
Alpha and Megantara
are still at the Dark Knight's place, Prof.
Where are the teachers?
The teachers?
Go away, Prof!
They want to help Alpha and Megantara.
You're a villain!
This is the fate of those who oppose you.
And you will have the same fate as them.
You're a villain!
Why is Alpha so strong now?
My attack can turn him back.
What do you want, Alpha?
Answer me, Alpha!
I don't know.
This is Cici, isn't it, Barga?
Do you want to throw it away?
Don't, Alpha!
Who knows it might be useful to you.
So, you better keep it.
Let's throw it away together.
Alpha, return the ring, Alpha!
No.
Whoever wears this ring,
he will be defeated.
And I will wear it,
just like Barga.
Don't, Alpha!
Return the ring, Alpha!
Now, it's your turn.
The people with the key,
will you return it?
Destroy them!
Destroy them all!
Down with the viles!
And east!
And this is for the army!
Pegasus!
Kill him!
Attack him!
The Dark Lord is defeated by Alva!
Thank you, bird!
You've saved me,
Ivi-Lang!
I'm sorry, Ivi-Lang.
The Dark Lord is defeated by Alva!
Army!
Wake up!
Wake up, Professor!
Army!
Let's go.
We'll open the door together.
Open the door.
Army!
What?
What happened?
What's going on?
The army of the Dark Lord was attacked by the Dark Lord.
Terrible.
The Dark Lord is dead.
Professor Agni, too.
His heart stopped.
Professor, get out.
Professor!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's go.
Professor Agni, too.
Professor Agni.
Thank God.
You've recovered.
I can recover because of your help.
Thank you.
Alva.
Where is the Dark Lord?
Tell me, where is he?
I've defeated him.
I don't know where he is.
You're great, Alva.
That's because of the army.
Because I have a strong identity.
And I won't let the Dark Lord hurt my teachers.
Thank you, Alva.
Let's go.
We have to go in.
We have to help Alva.
Let's go.
Alva.
Alva, are you okay?
Yes!
One, two, three.
Three, two, two, three.
That means...
I can't be a warrior anymore.
You can be a warrior.
What kind of warrior?
The Dark Lord.
Everyone, gather.
Announcement, announcement.
All students are required to go to class.
Now.
What is it?
Is there another attack?
Yes.
I'm bored.
Do you know?
Men's war.
No.
This time, we won't have a war.
We will welcome a new professor.
Who will teach in our school.
Yes, a new professor.
His name is Professor Tita.
He is a great person.
Very powerful.
That's why Professor Aldebaran sent us to the classroom.
Let's go.
Who is it?
It's early in the morning.
Disturbing Professor Tita.
Why is it like this?
I don't know.
Please.
You're just playing around.
Let's go back.
That's right.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
That's right.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
It turns out...
My mantra is not perfect.
When I'm in front of the mirror, my face doesn't change.
I can't be like this.
Come on.
Open your eyes.
Please.
Hi, bro.
How are you, Professor Lebaran?
I'm sorry, Professor. Welcome.
You called me Professor Salah.
He's called Professor Aldebaran.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I thought I made a mistake.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Oh, yes.
I remember.
I think your name is...
Mega...
Megaloman?
That's right.
Wrong.
I'm sorry.
Mega...
I'm Megantar.
Yes.
Can I bring a pan?
Sure.
There's an ant...
in your food.
You're fat.
But, I'm also fat.
That's right.
That's right, Professor.
I can imagine how big the ant is.
Professor Titan.
Welcome to your school.
Welcome, Professor Aldebaran.
Let me introduce you.
Professor...
What's your name?
I'm Agni.
Agni?
Professor Titan.
You should come to my house.
Okay.
So, you can introduce yourself to the kids.
Thank you.
Let Megantar bring the gift.
Thank you, Professor Aldebaran.
Let's go.
Okay.
Megantar.
Do you need help?
No.
But, I have to do this.
I'm still strong.
I'm old.
Congratulations, Megantar.
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, Sir.
Today, I'm going to introduce you...
to a new teacher.
His name is Professor Titan.
Please, Professor.
Good morning, kids.
Good morning, Sir.
Blue Pujan!
Chocolate!
Chocolate.
Thank you, Professor.
Kids.
Listen.
I have another important announcement.
Our school...
will hold a magic tournament...
that will compete...
for a very exclusive magic trophy.
It's going to be fun, right?
Yes.
It's going to be fun.
I want to join.
Yes.
I want to join too.
I often do magic tricks.
I'm sure I'm going to win.
Because I've practiced a lot.
That's right.
We've practiced too.
Kids.
This tournament will only be held...
at the school's school.
Kids.
This tournament will only be held...
by two students from Purnawa...
and two students from Jogja.
There are so many of them, Sir.
There are three of them, Sir.
There are three of us, Sir.
It can't be just two of us, Sir.
For the name of the participants,
Mr. Raihan,
the father of Tommy,
will bring the list of students...
who will participate in this tournament.
1st Place
2nd Place
3rd Place
4th Place
5th Place
6th Place
7th Place
8th Place
What?
6th Place
Oh no
This box
There are really 6 of them
So big
So heavy
So tired
So annoying to push
So curious
I want to open it
Let's just open it
What is this?
Come on
Just open it
Help
Help me
What is this?
This box
Is a gift from Professor Adek Barat
What right do I have to open it?
I'm a good person
I can't do this
I'll be punished
Come on
What is this?
This miracle merchant
Will release the names of the children
Who will join this competition
And those children
Are two names of Gerhana
And two names of Purna
Who are they?
I have to choose
Start choosing
And the first name is
Alpha
Now you will only be a spectator
Because you won't be chosen
So
I have to be punished by Professor Adek Barat
To activate this miracle merchant?
Yes, Tommy
Just put Tommy's name
But don't put Alpha and Vega's names
Just put the names of the children
Here are the names
Tommy
Yes
The second name
Jack
Yes
Congratulations Jack
Okay
The third name
Tole
Yes
Congratulations Tole
Thank you Vega
Why is he so strong?
Calm down, he's fat
He'll get wet if he's in the water
The last name
Ray
Yes
Congratulations Ray
Those are the four names
Who will compete in this competition
Why is he wet again?
Calm down, calm down
This miracle merchant
Wants one more name
To be five children
And the name that has been mentioned
Can't be changed
Don't you do it again
Yes Jack, I don't know
The last name
Alpha
Why is it Alpha?
But it smells
To be continued
Why is it Alpha?
But why did you put it in?
Tommy, I don't understand
Why is it Alpha?
What's going on?
Maybe
There's a mysterious person
Who wants to put Alpha in
Just let it be
But we won't let Alpha
And Vega win
Pih
Tell us the first task
First task
Ray, Alpha
Congratulations
But
You have to fight hard
To be the winner
Okay?
Wait
Why are you so nervous?
Why are you so quiet?
What's wrong?
I'm just confused
Why wasn't I chosen?
Maybe
I'm stupid
You're so pretty
You're so sensitive
You're nervous
You think you're stupid
Vega
This kind of competition
Is a common thing
We do it often
So don't think too much
Just relax
Okay?
Yes, Vega
I'm not stupid
All of you are 100
None of you are 0
You're always the one who answers
When did you answer?
I'm always the one who answers
Okay, sir
I'll support you
Now
Let's sing our cheer song
Okay, ready?
One, two, three
What the six wings
Let's go
My plan went well
I'm so happy
You're such a bad guy
You'll pay for this
Shut up
Drink it
You'll pay for this
And don't you dare disturb my plan
Good morning, everyone
Good morning, professor
Now, I want to ask
Who hasn't been to the brown rain?
Raise your hand
Me
So many of you
Okay, brown rain
Come on, take all of them
Take all of them
Don't let any of them go
If you've taken all of them
Go back to your seats
All of you
There's still a present for you
It's for you
Go back to your seats
What do you want?
Okay
Thank you
My children
Now, we're going to learn
The government's mantra
Is useful for someone
To tell them to do something
My children
This mantra is not easy
In order for this mantra to work
The person who recites this mantra
Has to have a strong will
Do you understand, my children?
Yes, sir
Ladies and gentlemen
Stand on your chair
The government's mantra
Is useful for someone
Enough
What are you doing here?
Kids
Now you try to
One by one
Come on
Be careful
Don't forget
Hey
Don't
Look at me
Keep going, professor
The winner is
Sringala
Be careful
Next
Wega
Please
The government's mantra
Is useful for someone
Congratulations!
Congrats
The winner is
Alva
Did we pass the test?
Please
If you can't do it, you can't do it
Maybe you'll fall
Don't go too far
We can do it
Jump!
Congratulations!
Good job!
You're the best!
Thank you
Alright
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I don't know
You can do it!
The winner is
We're going to sing
The bell has rung
Please come out
The winner is
Alva
I'm glad to have you
You have a great talent
I'm not a professor
The one closest to number one is Vega
The professor also knows
This is one of your advantages
You have a great heart
And one of the professor's advice
Use the mantra
Properly
Especially in the competition tomorrow
I'm sure
The mantra will be very useful
And I pray
That you'll win tomorrow
Thank you
Kids
As soon as you hear the whistle
You have to dive to the bottom of the lake
When you get there
You have to take a net
That has been kept by a turtle
You have to beat the turtle
And bring the net
To the edge of the lake
As soon as possible
And now
In your hands
There's a box
Inside the box
There's a miniature turtle
That you're going to catch
Please open it
Wow
I got
A turtle
Ray, you're lucky
Because the turtle
That has a turtle's hair
Is the weakest
Calm down, Ray, cheer up
Yes
I got a turtle with a turtle's hair
This is easy
Wow
I got a turtle
With eyes
This turtle is smart
And now
The first contestant
Nole
Ready
Go
Kids
Looks like the turtle got a net
Because of that
The turtle automatically fell
Wow
The turtle is so fierce
I was attacked twice
Actually, I got a turtle
But I was attacked again
Wow
I'm scared
I hope it won't attack
Calm down, Ray, this is just a normal contest
If you want to win
You're already in the picture
That's very good for you
Don't be afraid, Ray, keep fighting
Keep going
Thank you, Nole
And the next contestant
The second one is
Ray
Please, Ray
Be careful
I'm going to win
One, two
Why isn't there a professor?
Professor Titan
I'm going to win
Yay
Yes, I did it
I got the net
Why did you take so long, Ray?
Yes, because I was in the water
Right?
That's impossible, I'm Ray
Good, Ray, you did it
And your time is
30 minutes
That means, those of you
Who haven't competed yet
Have to beat Ray's time
The next contestant
Jack
One, two
Green team
Blue team
Calm down, kids
It looks like
Jack also failed to get the net
That means, automatically
Jack also lost
How come?
He's so strong
He's so fast
So, I'm the green team
And the next contestant
Tommy
I'm going to win
Watch out, Tommy
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Twenty
Twenty-one
Twenty-two
Twenty-three
Twenty-four
Twenty-five
Twenty-six
Twenty-seven
Twenty-eight
Twenty-nine
Twenty-ten
It's time for Ray
Come on, boss
15 minutes, Alva
That's the highest record
You have to do it
But, you can't do it
Just give up
No
I won't give up
And now
Our last contestant
Alva
Please
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Twenty
Twenty-one
Twenty-two
Twenty-three
Twenty-four
Twenty-five
Twenty-six
Twenty-seven
Twenty-eight
Twenty-nine
Twenty-ten
Twenty-eight
Twenty-nine
Very good, Alva
Your time is
14 minutes and 30 seconds
So, for this first contest
The winner is
Alva
Thank you
This is all thanks to
Professor Titan
Thank you so much
This is me, Alva
Why is there no sound?
Professor Titan
This is me, Alva
No sound
Professor Titan
Alva
Why is there no professor?
Professor Titan
Hurry up
Hey, Alva
What are you doing here?
You're still sleeping?
No, professor
I just want to say thank you
Because of your advice
I won the first contest
You won, Alva
Congratulations, Alva
Congratulations
Professor
Why is it shaking?
Alva, you don't have to be afraid
What's in the cupboard
Is just a baby centaur
A baby centaur?
Yes
Because a baby centaur
Can produce
A very powerful poison
And Alva
You don't have to be surprised
And don't be surprised
If you find weird creatures
In this room, Alva
Okay
Then
Excuse me
Be careful, Alva
I'm going to lose again
I'm going to lose to Alva
I have to think
How can I beat Alva
If I have to
She can't participate in the next contest
I know how
Help
Someone is asking for help
Her voice is around here
But where?
Help
Maybe
She's in the warehouse
Hey
Open the door
Open
Hey
Wait
Open
I'll open it later
But if it's done
Open it
Oh my god
Open
It's starting
Oh my god
Open
Alva, you have to succeed
But you have to trust us
Yes, Alva
You can't lose
If you lose, I'll replace you
Raiz and Alva already know
If I already know
I'll tell Papi
This time, I'll win
Hahaha
Isn't that Professor Titan?
What is he doing in front of the warehouse?
There he is
Professor Nohara
Why are you here?
Show your spirit
Prepare it, my friend
Running, jumping, jumping
Riding the stars
Brave
Unknown
Surrender
Chase
Hope and dreams
Go, go, go
Achieve all your dreams
Never stop
Go, go, go
Ride with the power of your heart
Make yourself proud
Go, go, go
Let's dream
We will