To be continued...
Keep going...
GO, GO, GO
Make yourself proud
Come on let's dream
GO, GO, GO
We can definitely do this
Come Kids
We'll certainly find out what happened
Megantara
It is better that you take all the children out of here
and do not let a single one fly away
GO, GO, GO
Professor
Who installed this horrible magic in this gate?
I don't know either, Megantara
What's clear is that you can't leave this village
and we can't enter the village
You saved Popo
Because you saved Popo
Now you're going to hurt Popo
The magical door managed to beat the monster
and locked it in a secret cave
No one knows where the secret cave is
But
This magic is not permanent
So the monster can be released
And later we have to find out
Who is the descendant of the magical door
who can lock the monster in it?
I'm surprised
How can a snake talk to you?
I'm also surprised
But
I used to talk to a snake
Maybe it's the descendant of the magical door
Nonsense
I can't be the descendant of the magical door
I just came here once
Yes, nonsense
You can be the descendant of the magical door
You can lock the monster in it
Did your parents ever tell you about Uncle Wickham?
I don't know them
I don't even know who they are
My parents said
They died a good man
You're so stupid
Don't be silly
Dava, can you hear me?
We have to learn magic from him
If not, we'll be locked in a cave
Yes
I want to learn too
Let's learn together
What's that?
It's a small magic for me
I can get rid of it
Right?
Yes
Because he's a king
I'm the king
You're pretending to be retired
Just say it
No, I'm not
I'm really retired
It looks like they're more confident now
Because they've got a new magic
That's good
But we can't give up
We have to find out more about this attack
Professor Purwa, what do you think?
Do you have any clue?
The book doesn't mention what kind of monster it is
Let alone the weakness
If it's like this, how can we defeat it?
And we can't go home
Because the village gate is haunted by a very powerful magic
We're all trapped here
Alva, it's so scary
What's wrong, Vega?
The teachers already know about the monster
But they covered us so we won't be scared
What's worse, the village gate is haunted by a very powerful magic
So the students can't get out
That's why the professor can't get in
The professor can't get in
I think someone's trying to save us
How is it?
The monster has attacked two of our students
How long do I have to wait?
Soon, sir
They're locked in the village
All the students will turn into stone
Including that special student
So you just have to wait
I'm bored here
I want to go back to school
Yes, the food is not good
Yes
There's a story
It's about a girl
Her name is Alva
It's a story about a girl
Yes, tell us the story
Do you want this?
My chocolate is taken, give it back
My chocolate, give it back
What's wrong?
My chocolate is taken by Jack and Mike
They ran away
I don't care
I know, in a situation like this
You're still looking for trouble
Rita, don't be sad
I'll chase them
Don't worry, I'll go with you
Ray, don't be late
It smells good
What's wrong?
Why did you stop?
Let's chase Jack and Mike
Okay, let's go
Ouch
My foot hurts
Wait for me
Mike?
Mike!
That's Jack's voice
Maybe it's another monster
Let's go
Mike!
Help!
I'm scared
Jack saw Mike being attacked
That's why he's still in shock
That's enough
Let's go inside
I'm sorry, Professor Furwa
Let Mike take care of it
Okay
Alva, let's go with them
How?
Let's go
Kids
Don't go anywhere
Stay here
And always be alert
What's wrong?
Nothing
Nothing?
This is a drink for you
Thank you
You're welcome
If you drink that
You'll be calm
Now tell me what happened
Just now
I was putting on my shoes
Then Mike ran away
Then the monster came
It was scary
Then it turned Mike into a rock
It's the first time
Something like this happened
Usually
Students are attacked
When they're alone
Professor Agni
Let's read his mind
Yes, Professor
Ouch
It hurts
Mike, wait
Hurry
Mike!
The monster is huge
Looks like
The monster likes chocolate
That's weird
How can a monster this big
Like chocolate?
Wait, Professor Purwa
I have to make sure
How is it, Professor Agni?
Looks like it's true
When Tole was attacked
There was chocolate
Yes, Sir
And when Nick was attacked
In Nick's test
He was carrying chocolate
I don't know
But I'm sure
There was chocolate
Yes, Sir
I don't know
But he was carrying chocolate
Megantara
Go back to your students
Watch them
Don't let anyone panic
And take care of them
Don't let anyone pass through the village
It can be very dangerous for them
Yes, Professor
Megantara
How is Jake, Megantara?
Don't worry
Jake is resting
He's sleeping
What about Mike?
Mike is
On medication
Medication with mushrooms
Aren't you scared?
No, Sir
We're not scared
Right, guys?
Good
Who said we're not scared?
This place is getting stranger
And more dangerous
But it's our turn to help
Guys
Let's get out of here
Agree?
Now we know
The monster likes chocolate
So we have to help our friends
So they won't eat chocolate
I agree
So they won't be attacked by the monster
Let's go
Hurry up!
We're late
It's dangerous
They're running away
I'll go through the village gate
I have to stop them
Tantara!
Where are you going?
Now
It's time for the monster to do its job
To be continued...
You're not afraid
But you want to run away
Come on
Now go back to your house
We want to go home
We want to go back to school
This place is getting dangerous
So that's all you got?
Listen
You're special kids
You're spoiled kids
You're not loved by other kids
If you're afraid
You don't have the courage
What's the difference between you and other kids?
Do you know why you're asked to stay here?
Do you?
Look at this
Tantara!
This place is haunted by a black magic
If we go through it
You'll all be destroyed
What do we do now?
Let's fight it
Remember
You're special kids
Go back to being farmers
Go back to being heroes
Agree?
Agree!
Louder! Agree?
Courage?
Courage!
That's it
Now you know the situation
But
Don't be alarmed
You have to calm down
And be ready to face it
You have to be happy
We can't, we're scared
Yes, we're scared
This fear is our enemy's target
If we're scared, the enemy will be happy
But if we're happy
The enemy will be jealous of us
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
That's a good idea
I'm sorry, sir
Never mind
Ms. Futar!
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
It's not fun
Let's do it again
I want to win
We want to win!
What if we lose?
Now it's your turn
Ms. Futar
Yes, I'm so happy
Sometimes I play alone
I don't have friends here
But from now on
You won't be lonely
Because we're your friends
But if you go back to school
I'll be lonely
I promise
We'll come here often
See you later
Looks like they're having fun
I'm going to take advantage of the situation
What are you doing here?
Me?
You want to make trouble, don't you?
That's right
And you
You're going to help me do that
Opo
Are you going to help me do that?
What's this?
This is a communication mirror
If you use this mirror
Even if it's far away
We can talk
Cool
Let's try it
Fega
Can you see me?
Yes, I can
Of course, Fega
Be careful, Fega
Are you going to hurt Fega?
Opo
I know
How to make you happy
How, Opo?
How about
We make something delicious
What is it, Opo?
Opo
Let's see
Let's go
Good
Very good
Finally, my plan went well
And now
It's time for the monster legenda to do its job
You have to destroy all the chocolates in the village
If necessary
Destroy all the chocolate trees there
So the villagers can't make chocolates anymore
Yes, sir
And remember
Watch the children
Their safety is very important
Yes, sir
I will try to find another way
To enter the village
Hey, don't go
Opo
Opo, Opo, Opo
What are you doing here, Opo?
Milk
What?
Kawat, Kawat
We're all in danger
Danger?
What do you mean, Opo?
The children
I taught them how to make chocolates
Children?
Who are you?
I'm their friend
I told you to stay away
Vega
Hey
The children are making chocolates
Huh?
Chocolates?
That means
The monster is coming
Yes
We're in danger
We have to stop it
Let's go
It looks like a monster
Opo
Run
It looks delicious
Opo
Tommy, Tommy
Don't eat the chocolates here
You all throw these chocolates away
We're tired of making these chocolates
Then, why did you tell us to throw these chocolates away?
We don't know
Tommy, Jack
These chocolates are dangerous
These chocolates can lure the monster here
Don't lie
There's no monster that likes chocolates
It's you
Guys, take care of the chocolates
Don't let Alva and Rai steal them
Why?
I don't want to be told
Go away
Tantara
Why do I smell chocolate here?
Yes, Tantara
They're making chocolates
Huh?
Yes
I don't understand
Why are there so many chocolates here?
Tantara told us to have fun
But we're making chocolates
Tantara, it's delicious
Now, throw all these chocolates away
Why do we have to throw them away?
The chocolates are delicious
These chocolates
Will make a disaster for all of you
Do you know your friends?
Mike, Jack, and Tole
Why are they happy?
Because they're eating chocolates
If you're still making chocolates
It means you're ready to be eaten by the monster
Tantara, run!
Go away
And bring the food
Go, Tantara
Do your job
And destroy them
Tantara
We can do it
Huh?
This is the only way
For me to join the organization
Davatang Avanza
Yippie!
We're back!
Why is he calling us?
He must be working for us
Hey, young ladies
I'm here
To invite you to a competition
A competition?
Yes
The loser
Has to follow the winner's will
What do you think?
Why?
Are you scared?
It's delicious
We're never scared
Especially with a man
Come on, Yippie
Yippie, let's get changed
Enough!
I admit defeat
You're amazing, Putri Angsa
We don't believe in men's words
We're not men
We're men
Okay, okay
Now, you can punish me
Whatever it is
I'll do it
You can punish me
Whatever it is
But please
Don't put me in the water
Because I'm most afraid of water
Especially in this lake
There's a hole
That can lead to the magic village
Don't take me there
I'm afraid of the place
I'm afraid of the hole
He's afraid of the hole
Let's just take him there
So he won't be afraid
Because you're afraid of water
Afraid of the lake
We'll take you to the magic village
Come here
Let's go
Thank you for showing me the way
One
Two
Three
Tentara
I'm scared, dad
Lurah Galaksi
You'd better hurry
Let's go, professor
Let's go
Tentara
I'm afraid of the hole
Now you have to remember, Alva
Don't look at the sparkling eyes
Remember
Maybe
The sparkling eyes
Are the snake eyes
Guys
Don't look at the snake eyes
Wait for me
What's wrong?
It's dangerous
I have to help them
Don't, dad
It's dangerous
Just run
Help
Don't, dad
Alva
Alva is so close
Yes
I'm going to catch up with you, Nisa
You're so slow
Ri
We can enter
Let's go
Wow, this is fun
Ri, wake up
Ri
Alva
Hey
Don't look at the eyes
Don't look at the snake eyes
Alva
The phantom
Help
Alva
He's in there
He's come out
Alva
Happy Eid
I'm glad I'm not a stone, Alva
Alva
Happy Eid
Mike
Why did you turn into a stone?
Anis also turned into a stone
He's in there, Mike
Let's attack him
Infiltrate
We can do this
What are you two doing here?
Praise be to Allah
It's a normal quest
Normal?
What happened to me?
You turned into a stone
Enough
We don't want to make a scene
Let's get out of here
I'm sure our friends know what happened to us
Let's go
Hurry up
That snake is huge
Don't be happy yet, Alva
The snake is not dead
It's just running away
So the snake can come back?
It can come back if it smells like chocolate
We have to get out of here
Take the kids out of this village
I've found a way to get out of this village
But Professor
What about the mantra that has blocked this village?
That mantra is for us
Once we get out of here
The mantra will be gone
Rey
Wake up
Alva
You didn't eat the monster, did you?
No
It's all messed up
What's going on?
Maybe they're playing war
Hurry up
Hold it
Rey
Kids
Let's go back to school
Professor
What about the monster?
We managed to get rid of the monster
But it's not dead
Only you
You have to stay alert
And now
We have to go back to school
Take the kids to a safer place
But I and the teachers will come back here
To get rid of the monster
Thank you very much, Professor Adebaran
Rita
I have to go
You'll come back here, won't you?
Of course
But don't forget
To contact us through this number
This well connects to the lake around our school
And we'll go in there one by one
As soon as you get in
You have to swim as fast as you can
To the lake
You'll pair up
And the teachers will help you
Okay
Let's go
And the teachers will help you
Wait
Don't think you can easily leave this village
Nice to meet you, Ankara
But unfortunately
We have to say goodbye
Oh
Don't be arrogant, Adebaran
The knowledge I have now
Is far better than the last time we fought
Ankara
Don't talk too much
You don't even want to defeat me
How can you defeat Professor Adebaran?
Professor
It's better
To bring your children
So that one day
I'm here
To be continued
I have not lost
And I will never lose
To be continued
Everyone is already home
I'm the only one left alone
Hi, Mahlis
I don't want people to get hurt because of me
I have to face this
Don't tell anyone
To be continued
Thank God, there's a miracle
And you tell Alva
If Alva still wants this child to live
Then she has to surrender
Basar Dincik!
It's up to you what you want to say, Alva
What's important is that you have to find me in Rama
Pelita and Antaboga will be waiting for you
Huh? Antaboga?
You only have 24 hours
If you're late
Then this child will be gone forever
Forever
I will return to Sihir village
To lock the monster in Rama's cave
You take care of the children
And stay alert
Because Angkara will not give up so easily
He will definitely do everything
I'm sorry, Prof
But the professor can
Because as far as I know
According to the legend
Only the descendants of Mimasati
Who can open and close the cave
I will still try
So that the people of Sihir village can live in peace
Alva!
Don't be stubborn
If you go there alone
You'll be attacked by those monsters
Yes, sir
Let's report it to the soldiers and the professor
Yes
They will definitely accompany you
Besides
If you go with the professor
You'll be protected
Yes, sir
The professor can turn into a bird
Professor Agni can also turn into a cat
The soldiers will definitely change
No
I have to help him
Alva!
Don't be stubborn
No
I'll go back by myself
I don't want people to be in trouble because of me
I have to handle this
You guys
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Alva!
Why is it so close?
Let's report it to the professor
God is evil!
God, leave Popo!
Popo can suffer!
Popo can die!
Popo!
It didn't work
Popo
What are you doing here?
Just sit here
Why?
God Alva
Can come back again?
Yes
I'm looking for the treasure
Do you know where the treasure is?
What are you doing there?
Popo was kidnapped
Rite was arrested
I have to help her
Do you know?
I don't know
Good
Accompany me there
God Alva
It's so scary there
There's a ghost
Popo has a bad experience with a ghost
Experience?
What experience?
So
At that time
Popo accidentally
Fell into the cave
And
Popo met a ghost
Help me!
Help!
Popo
Where are you?
Help me!
I'm scared
Help!
I need help
Why on earth is there a homeless here?
Why on earth is there a видели here?
Do they know you came here?
Why on earth is there a homeless here?
The sound of a flute played by the dark lord
makes Antaboga calm and calm
And since then, Popo became close to the dark lord
So Antaboga can be calm if we play the flute?
I can play the flute
It's not just a flute
Antaboga likes a special kind of music
If you make a mistake, just hit the notes
If you're angry, Antaboga will slap you
Teach me all the notes
How? I'll think about it
Come on, Popo. Teach me. Please
Okay, I'll teach you
Seriously?
Even if you don't like it, even if you're forced to
Thank you, Popo
I'm going back to that village
Pelita wants to be kidnapped by Prof. Angkara
And Prof. Angkara said that I have to go there
No one can accompany me. I have to go alone
Pelita will be kidnapped
I can do it!
Thank you for teaching me
Popo was hugged
Usually, all gods treat Popo harshly
You shouldn't have brought me on this journey
Do you really know where I am?
Unfortunately, you're too late to know
To be continued...