To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Make yourself proud!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
It's locked.
What should I do?
I'm getting more and more scared.
I think this is an attack.
So, Professor, what is this?
This is one of the special powers of one of the students in this school.
What about Alfa?
Alfa has been locked up twice.
I was bitten by Alfa.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
This is messed up.
Alfa must be in pain.
I have to help Alfa.
Hey!
There's a snake that eats stones and papayas.
Guard!
Open the door for me!
Open the door!
Open the door for me, quick!
I'm holding the door handle.
Guard!
Open the door!
I'm in pain, Prof.
I'm freezing.
I'm cold.
I'm begging you to heal me.
I can't move, Prof.
I have to take the fire scythe.
But, Professor,
the fire scythe is in the highest tower in the school.
And I think I should move.
There's no other way.
Only the fire scythe can warm this room.
Ani,
call Megantara
and give her this bell.
Yes, Prof.
Dafatang,
the paper.
Megantara,
come back quickly.
The magic school is in trouble.
And I've brought the bell back
because Dana is freezing.
Dafatang,
the paper.
Find Megantara no matter what.
I'm so full.
I can't move my legs.
Yes.
I've used up the fire scythe.
Thank you for finishing your meal.
Now, it's time for you to drink the juice.
Yes, drink the juice.
Yes.
What's that?
I have to do it.
Yes, Mega.
You have to be patient.
I have to do it.
I have to fight this for Alva.
I can't do that for myself.
Alva, what's wrong?
Alva.
It's terrible.
My body is covered with snake skin.
What should I do?
Megatara
It's so weird.
Every time I send a letter,
I have to type it first.
This is the back button of Professor Ardebar.
It means,
there's something very important at school.
What should I do?
I have to go to school.
Alva's business is not done yet.
There's another problem.
Don't type my sentence.
It's useless.
Just type it.
Delete it.
He's used to typing.
Alright.
I'll be back soon.
But, wait.
Until Alva's business is done.
Wow.
That's so cool.
If this is the way,
I don't have to work as a teacher anymore.
You're just a lazy kid.
That's why you're left behind.
Go back to Professor Agni.
Alva's business is not done yet.
This is so scary.
I feel like I'm losing my hearing.
Now, you have to do another test.
It's a board painting competition.
You have to do it manually.
Without magic.
Without mantra.
The last one...
will be eliminated.
Please go to the painting house.
Painting is easy.
But, I'm not good at it.
Both of you will fail.
You know,
there's an old saying.
There's a noisy person,
but he doesn't have a brain.
Sorry.
If a ghost fights a human,
the ghost will win.
Who said that?
Humans are more noble.
So, humans will win.
Ghost.
Human.
You have to paint the wall that has your name on it.
Do it neatly and quickly.
The oldest one will be eliminated.
We'll start on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Twenty.
Twenty-one.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three.
Several years.
Go! Go! Go!
Won't stop to dream.
Don't ever stop.
Go! Go! Go!
Try with the power of your heart.
Make yourself proud.
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it.
Vega, you shouldn't be like this.
Because of me, you lost.
It's okay. Our goal here is to get that ring.
So if one of us loses, what else can we do?
The important thing is you have to continue.
You have to win, okay?
Just make sure my fight with Ray is not in vain.
Thank you, Vega.
I'm sorry, Vega. You have to go home now.
I'm sorry.
Vega.
You failed too.
Vega?
What else can I do?
He's weak.
And Alva is so weak.
I helped him.
And I still lost.
Vega, what about you?
You know Alva is weak.
Why did you let him win?
But the way to live is to love Alva.
What about you?
I forgot.
Why did I think like that?
I just want to talk to Alva.
Hey.
Shut up.
A forester eats pondo salad.
Vega is not stupid.
Vega is just nice.
No matter what the reason is, fighting and sacrificing for a friend...
...will never pay off.
But, soldier.
Stop saying but.
It's better for Vega...
...to fight for a friend.
To work hard.
Than you.
You failed because you don't want to eat vegetables.
Vegetable chicken.
This is the last round.
The decision will determine who deserves to get the life fluid.
You have to run until the finish line.
The one who arrives first is the winner.
Remember.
You can't use any spell here.
I tried my best.
But, I can't give up.
I want to win.
I believe in you, Vega.
One.
Two.
Three.
I won.
Alva.
Come on.
It's not that long.
It's better for you to run.
I will win.
This is what we call winning in a battle.
I'm excited.
But, Izan.
I've been waiting for you.
Alva.
Alva, wake up.
You guys.
Wake up, Alva.
You can't die.
But, I can't take it anymore.
My body hurts.
Alva.
You can't ruin your friends' fight.
It's true, Alva.
They've sacrificed for you.
Don't let them be a burden.
Alva, wake up.
Alva.
Don't be like this.
Because of me, you lost.
It's okay.
You're here to help us.
So, if we lose, what should we do?
You have to win.
Okay?
You're right.
These are my friends.
Good.
Now, stand up.
And be brave.
Be brave.
Don't let them be a burden.
Give up.
Chase your passion and dreams.
Go, go, go.
Achieve all your dreams.
I won't give up.
Now, it's time to say goodbye to the ghost.
To be continued...
Ibu.
Ibu, what's wrong with you?
How can you run that fast?
Where are you coming from?
Oh, my God.
Help me.
Chase your passion and dreams.
Go, go, go.
Achieve all your dreams.
Don't ever give up.
Raya.
What?
Do you think you won?
Wrong.
I won, you lost.
Whatever.
It's obvious.
Don't you trust me?
I won.
It's up to you.
Raya.
Thank God.
This firecracker is really useful.
But we can't go on like this, Professor.
We have to find Pelita.
And stop her before she freezes this school.
Purwa is right.
We have to find Pelita immediately.
I order all teachers to find Pelita.
Split up to find her.
Kids.
You stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
Yes, sir.
I will leave this firecracker here.
So, you won't be left behind.
Yes, sir.
Oh, no.
Because you arrived at the finish line at the same time.
Then, you two take the liquid of life.
Whoever finishes first, he is entitled to get the liquid of life.
One.
Two.
Three.
Start.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Twenty.
Twenty-one.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three.
Twenty-four.
Twenty-five.
Twenty-six.
Twenty-seven.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-nine.
Twenty-ten.
Twenty-eleven.
Twenty-nine.
Twenty-three.
Twenty-four.
Twenty-arch?
Ten.
Huh?
Wha?
Wait!
Argh.
Where's the bottle?
Hey, Afat.
Did you take the bottle?
Here, give it back!
You are such a mean!
Wait!
I don't know!
Afat!
What are you doing?
Here, give it back!
That's my brother's!
That's mine!
Give it back!
I don't know!
Raya.
In this competition,
the participants must be honest and fair.
They can't cheat.
What?
You've cheated and been unsportive by pushing Alfa.
So, you're out.
And we've decided,
Alfa will be the winner of this competition.
What?
Yes!
Thank you, jury!
Thank you so much!
Melitha?
Where's our daughter?
She's not here.
Then,
let's just look for my crystal ball.
Okay.
Then, hurry up and look for it.
Daftar,
crystal ball!
There she is!
Melitha!
What happened to my crystal ball?
I'm so sorry.
We'll soon find out where Melitha is.
Melitha!
My little sister,
why are you crying?
Who are you?
I'm a prince from a faraway land.
I'm Melitha.
Why are you crying here?
I'm a weirdo.
Everyone hates me.
I don't want to be friends anymore.
If I'm wrong, everyone will blame me.
Then, we're the same.
What do you mean?
I don't have any friends anymore.
Almost everyone in this world hates me.
I'm considered a problem.
What if we become friends?
But, are you afraid of me?
I have a strange power.
I can freeze everyone.
Since we're friends,
I'll tell you my secret.
I also have a strange power.
I can't freeze.
Are you sure you want to be friends with me?
Hold my hand.
You can see for yourself.
I don't freeze.
Professor Aldebaran,
I got a message from Professor Agni.
School is in danger.
But, who will do it?
I'll do it.
It's morning.
Where's Alvan?
Ri, wake up.
Look, it's morning.
Yes, it's morning.
What time is it?
That's why I want to ask.
Alva hasn't come yet.
What?
Alva hasn't come yet?
Alva hasn't come yet.
I'm scared.
Alva.
Are you okay?
Did you succeed?
Alva.
Are you okay?
No.
Alva.
I'm scared.
Be careful.
Alva must have been possessed by an evil magic.
What magic is this?
Alva.
It's impossible.
Congratulations. You succeeded.
Not yet.
Alva.
I'm relieved.
Finally, you're safe.
Yes, Alva.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Hold this.
To be continued...
Centara.
Forgive me.
But, thank you too, Centara.
Centara.
To be continued...
Forgive me.
What's wrong, Centara?
What's wrong?
I almost forgot.
We have to go to school.
Why?
This is a letter from Professor Ali Baran.
I got a letter from him.
Our school is in danger.
Danger? What danger?
So, we have to go back to school.
This letter will help us get to school.
Let's go.
Hold this.
Are you ready?
Yes.
To be continued...
Welcome, Alva.
I'm happy...
...that you're safe.
Thank you, Professor.
Professor Ali Baran.
I got a letter from Professor Aki.
Our school is in danger.
But, who did this?
It was Pelita.
Pelita?
But, that's impossible.
We didn't expect it either.
But, it turns out...
...Pelita has a special ability.
But, unfortunately...
...she can't control that ability.
So, when she's angry, angry, sad...
...feeling lonely, scared...
...that power will come out.
And what touches her...
...can freeze her.
So, where's Pelita now?
Until now, we haven't been able to find her.
Telescope!
Telescope.
Ray.
Try using this telescope.
Where's Pelita?
Let's go.
The food is so good.
There's ice cream.
Ferment.
Bakso.
Ray, focus.
Find Pelita.
You're the one who thinks about food first.
The food is cold. I'm hungry.
Pelita.
Can you hear me, Pelita?
That's her.
That's Pelita.
Alpha.
Pelita is with a man in a veil.
But, who is that, Prof?
Or maybe...
...Professor Angkara.
But, they look different.
I brought warm chocolate for you.
Here.
To keep your body warm.
Pelita.
Wait.
Who are you?
To be continued...
Popo?
We can do this.
Alpha.
Where are you?
Alpha, where are you?
Where are you, Alpha?
Alpha.
That's Aldebar's voice.
I can't face him with this kind of power.
Alpha.
Get up.
You're a handsome boy.
Why do you look like this?
Alpha.
Who did this to you?
How is he, Professor?
He's fine.
We should go back inside.
Let's help Alpha.
Alpha.
Megantara's feeling says...
...that Professor Aldebaran...
...is hiding something.
How long are we going to stay here?
It's going to be a long time, Pat.
Be patient.
The professor is trying to...
...let us recover.
Let's just wait here.
Because of the monster, we're like this.
The school is frozen.
We can't play.
It's so cold.
I wish we could go home.
Firecrackers.
So this is how you play when it's cold.
I know how to use this situation.
If Chris isn't there,
they'll be in trouble.
And Aldebaran won't be able to use his magic...
...because it's too cold.
Stupid.
Where are you taking me?
I'm taking you to a place where you can rest.
I don't want to.
I want to go down.
Calm down.
I'll stop.
You can go down.
Let's go.
To be continued...
This is so weird.
He's always doing this to me.
And his classmates...
He's lying.
I'm the one who sent him to his room.
Just kick him out.
Or just kick him out.
I didn't do anything wrong.
He kicked me out of school.
Because I don't want to see him again.
He did it himself.
Don't believe him.
You have to kick him out of this school.
Kick him out.
Guys, let's just go.
Don't waste our time on him.
Let's just go to the show.
Let's go.
To be continued...
I have bad news.
And also good news.
What is it, Professor?
Alfa.
I think he met the 8th prince.
The good news is...
Alfa is safe.
Even though his face is a bit wounded.
The bad news is...
The 8th prince has taken Plita away.
Purwa.
I want you to find Plita's whereabouts.
As soon as you find her, let me know.
Yes, Professor.
To be continued...
All of you can go back to the clinic.
And stay alert.
I will call Alfa.
To train him to be stronger.
Because one day...
He might meet the 8th prince.
Yes, Professor.
To be continued...
It's true what he said.
Professor is calling me.
Alfa.
I called you here...
Because I want to teach you...
The Pegasus Mantra.
Pegasus Mantra?
What is that, Professor?
Pegasus Mantra...
Is a mantra...
That can create friends when you're alone.
And you have to fight strong enemies.
Like before.
I will set an example for you.
Pegasus!
Wow!
So cool!
Alfa.
Now, go to me.
Yes, Professor.
Look, Alfa.
This friend of mine...
Will protect me till the end.
And I...
Can pull myself from the enemy.
Or distract the enemy's attention.
He's gone!
Alfa.
Which animal do you like the most?
Garuda bird, Professor.
Very good.
Now...
Concentrate.
And imagine Garuda bird on your head.
Then...
Say the Pegasus Mantra.
Concentrate, Alfa.
Yes, Professor.
Pegasus!
Why is it a chicken?
Alfa.
Your enemy can't be afraid of a chicken.
Come on.
Try again.
Pegasus!
Wow!
It's so young.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to be laughed at by the enemy.
Alright, Alfa.
That's all for today.
Now, you should rest.
We'll continue tomorrow.
Yes, Professor.
I'll go now.
To be continued...
Alfa.
What were you doing there?
I was taught a new mantra.
Huh?
A new mantra?
Yes.
So that I can be stronger than the enemy.
Who was the enemy that you met?
Yes.
He said...
It's Eid.
I'm so worried.
I don't know...
If it's going to be a strong Eid.
Don't, don't.
The 8th call.
Who did this?
Come out!
Satria El.
It's been a long time, Professor Purwa.
Until now...
He hasn't given any news.
There's a letter.
We want to invite one of your teachers.
Meet us...
In the snowy forest at the end of the mountain.
We want to see you.
Meet us...
In the snowy forest at the end of the mountain.
From who, Professor?
I don't know.
But I'll go there.
I'll go with you.
Who did this?
Satria El.
Wait.
Be patient.
We're not looking for trouble here.
Aldebaran.
Is it true?
You're the one who stole our firecracker?
You want to kiss my cheek?
You're too much.
Don't dream about it.
Professor Aldebaran.
Not me.
Don't lie.
The last person who brought the firecracker...
Was our brother.
Panca.
Yes.
Panca is my twin sister.
And we heard the news...
That Panca has passed away.
Popo is missing.
And until now...
We haven't found the firecracker that Panca had.
And someone told us...
That the firecracker is now in Silvia's school.
And our assistant, Popo...
Popo.
He has been made a prisoner.
Calm down.
Be patient.
I will tell you what really happened.
A few years ago...
I met Panca.
At that time...
Panca was fighting against the Dark Lord.
I saw that Panca was exhausted.
And almost lost.
And when I tried to help him...
The wound was too bad.
I couldn't save him.
To be continued...
Keep this.
It's very valuable.
So in the end...
Panca gave the firecracker to me.
So I didn't steal the firecracker.
He gave it to me.
Don't lie to us.
Yes.
How can we believe...
That Panca was killed?
You...
Don't accuse Professor Aldebaran.
To be continued...
Men...
They are useless.
Are they patriots?
Or are they cowards?
They didn't invite us.
They didn't take us home.
What should we do?
We can't give them the firecracker.
If we give them the firecracker...
The children will die of cold.
What should we do?
Should we help them?
I'm worried.
They will hurt Purwa.
But I'm sure that Professor Purwa can handle it.
Because he has very high knowledge.
He's lying.
We didn't do that.
We didn't steal the firecracker.
He's a traitor.
He's behind all of this.
Everything is clear now.
Lita.
You have to make a decision.
Do you want to stay here with me...
Or do you want to go to Samurai?
To be continued...
Next episode...