To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Be proud of yourself!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
I know everything.
It turns out that you're evil.
You're friends with the person who kidnapped me in the cave, right?
And you want to ruin Vega and Alva's wedding, right?
I don't want to go with you.
So, Vega succeeded...
in making the princess realize the meaning of love and sacrifice.
And finally, all this mess ended.
That's right, Professor.
That's the star.
I can't fail this time.
Thank you for helping me.
I'm sorry.
I misjudged you.
And I hit you too.
Yes.
When you landed,
they were fighting for you.
So, I took you away from there.
I don't want to hear that excuse again.
Why can't you just let it go?
I have to get the fallen star.
So, the fallen star can go back to the sky when the moon is full.
So, I have to protect Selena.
Ouch.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
I'm going to Vega's house.
Where are you going? Why are you in a hurry?
I'm...
I'm going to Vega's house.
Vega's house?
Yes.
Vega's house.
Vega's house?
Yes.
I'm going to run in the morning.
To be healthy.
See you.
Wait.
What is it?
I want to tell you.
I'm a professor.
But, I'm not in a normal class.
I'm in Menara.
Gosh.
There's a white star.
It's strong.
It can be detected.
What should I do?
See you.
Bye.
Alva.
He's so weird.
He's been like that since yesterday.
Maybe, he has something to hide.
Selena.
Wake up, Selena.
Wake up.
Selena.
I'm sleepy, Alva.
Gosh.
I have to stay awake at night.
But, I have to sleep at noon.
Yes, I understand.
But, there's a lesson here.
Gosh.
Hurry up.
You have to move here.
Professor.
Why is the lesson in Menara?
Why not in the class?
Why?
Is there a problem for you?
Alva.
What are you doing here?
Nothing, professor.
Nothing.
I ran in the morning.
I didn't mean to come here.
Kids.
Line up, please.
Come in, professor.
Everyone.
Listen.
As usual.
I will teach you...
...the magic to defend yourself.
The mantra that we're going to learn today is...
...Mantra of Transformation.
Mantra of Transformation.
Professor Agni will help me.
Everyone, pay attention.
Move.
Professor Purwa.
I think...
...you should tie your hair more often.
Quiet, everyone.
Now, I'm Professor Purwa.
Professor Purwa.
I think we should switch bodies again.
As you can see, kids.
Now, it's time to try.
We'll start with your turn.
Rega.
Tommy.
Go.
Remember the mantra.
And your turn.
Move.
Yes! I did it!
Vega's glasses are so cool.
Good.
Tommy and Vega.
Next, it's your turn.
You'll try.
Alva.
Tole.
Go.
What's that sound?
It's not anyone's voice, Professor.
That was...
...my voice, Professor.
I saw...
...Tole fell.
That's why I was like that.
Ouch.
Okay.
This is the last lesson.
Tomorrow, we'll start again.
Alva.
Tole.
Tomorrow, it's your turn.
And you have to do it.
If you don't, you'll be judged.
Okay, Professor.
Luckily, Selena didn't get hurt.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
Luckily, Selena didn't find out.
If not, what should I do?
I'm sure...
...the fallen star girl...
...is still in this school.
Yes, I agree.
Let's find out through them.
Hey.
What do you want?
Don't.
Don't attack me.
Please.
Calm down.
We won't hurt you.
Yes.
We want to give you a present.
A present?
What present?
We want to give you this.
Hey.
It's not that easy.
If you want this arrow,
you have to follow our order.
But, don't make it difficult.
Please, don't make it difficult.
It's easy.
Do you know about the fallen star?
No.
That's your mission.
Find out about the fallen star.
If the fallen star is in this school,
let us know.
And you...
...will receive this arrow...
...as a reward.
Wow.
That's cool, Mona.
I agree.
But, how can we find out about the fallen star?
I don't know.
Let's find out.
It's easy.
It turns out that the fallen star is in this school.
I have to get it first.
And give it to the Dark Lord.
My arrow.
I can't use my power.
I might get hurt.
What's that?
This is my sleeping oil.
To be continued...
Thank you for helping me.
But, who are you?
I'm Selena.
But, don't tell anyone...
...that I'm the fallen star.
Because, only you and Alva know about it.
If others know about it,
it will be dangerous.
I promise you.
I won't tell anyone.
Because, you helped me.
Okay.
With this tool,
we can catch the fallen star.
Fallen star.
Don't.
The fallen star is good.
Not like you.
It's evil.
Do you know it?
No.
I don't know it.
But, how do you know it?
Where is it?
I don't know it.
Someone must have hidden it.
I think, he knows something.
What's wrong?
I met Selena just now.
But, don't tell anyone.
How can it be like that?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Felita told me about the fallen star.
Yes.
It's on the tree.
Okay.
I won't bother you.
I'll go first.
Okay.
What's wrong with them?
Why are they so weird?
I don't know.
No one is hiding it.
Here, Felita.
Sister.
Hi, Felita.
I brought food for you.
Thank you, Felita.
You're welcome.
Yes!
Your work is good.
It means, we found it.
Yes.
Not now.
Wait until we find the fallen star.
Okay.
Go back to the school.
You'll find it.
Wait.
I'll go with you.
Eka.
You have to find it.
There must be something.
The teachers will warn us.
Don't be careless.
Tri.
Find the tool that can help me get into the school.
Wow.
It's Megantara.
You're great.
Cool.
Megantara.
Megantara, have you seen Alva?
I've been looking for her.
Mr. Ega has been looking for her too.
You're being a jerk.
Megantara is not here.
I think Alkrab is with Tommy.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Sir.
That's him.
Don't lie to me.
How dare you lie to me?
That's him.
Sir, he's lying.
Sir, that's him.
Don't play with me.
How dare you play with me?
Take the consequences.
Why can't he see?
He's clearly there.
Tole.
We have to concentrate.
We can do it.
Alva, I'm scared too.
What if he sees us?
That's scary.
We'll be punished.
The punishment will be weird.
We have to clean the toilet.
We have to clean the page.
Come on, Tole.
When are we going to practice?
What's wrong?
Vivinda Jiwa.
Salena.
That's my body.
This is bad.
Why am I in Salena's body?
What's going on?
So, this is where the door fell.
Let me go.
Let me go, Professor Ankara.
Do you know where I am?
You're a bad person.
Who doesn't know you?
Let me go.
Vivinda!
Good evening, sir.
I managed to get Putri Bintang.
Why isn't the star shining?
How can it shine, sir?
A star should shine when it emits light from its body.
Ankara.
I want you to make the star shine.
Because if the star doesn't shine, it's useless to me.
Make it shine, Ankara.
After it shines, bring it to the black cave.
I will take its power here.
How can I make it shine?
Wait!
Gawat, there's Professor Ankara.
This is Professor Ankara.
I want you to make the star shine.
Wait!
Gawat, there's Professor Ankara.
How can I be inside the cave?
This is weird.
What's wrong with me?
What should I do? I'm not Alva.
Alva!
Where have you been? We've been looking for you.
I'm not Alva.
Alva, are you sick?
What's wrong?
Come here.
Move.
Hey, let me go.
Let me go.
I'm Alva.
Alva, you must be sick.
That's why you're whining.
Where are you taking me?
I want to go home.
Alva, you must be sick.
That's why you're whining.
So, we're taking you to the vet.
Hey, I'm not sick.
Let me go.
I'm not Alva.
Do you know that?
Alva, be patient.
We're almost there.
Let's go.
To Be Continued...
Yes, I know now.
A star will shine brightly when it's happy.
And it will fade when it's sad.
Stars like to dance and sing.
If I can make it dance and sing...
...it will be happy...
...and its body will shine.
Yes.
I will succeed this time.
To Be Continued...
Where am I?
This is bad.
I'm still in Putri Selena's body.
Putri Selena must be in my body.
She must be scared.
I have to go back to school.
The key.
There's a window.
I can't open it.
Why didn't I cut it?
Where is it?
To Be Continued...
What's that smell?
Why is it me?
Sorry.
Everything is okay.
No problem.
It's very good.
So, I'm fine.
Thank you, doctor.
Okay. Welcome, beautiful.
Don't get sick.
Tomorrow is the first month.
The teacher told me...
...that we will play on the first month.
That's right.
Tomorrow is the first month.
I have to get my body back.
If I don't get my body back...
...I won't be able to go back to space.
I have to wait for the first month.
Okay, Alva.
I will give you...
...a calm down mantra.
A calm down mantra.
So, you won't be scared anymore.
So, you can sleep soundly tomorrow.
We can play.
I don't want to.
No, Alva.
Don't be naughty.
This mantra is not dangerous.
Not dangerous.
It can make you sleepy...
...and sleeping handsome.
Sleep soundly until tomorrow.
Okay, Alva.
I can't sleep.
I have to get my body back.
I don't want to be late to go back to space.
I don't want to.
That's right, baby.
Okay, Alva.
Are you ready?
No.
Alva.
What's wrong with Alva?
I don't know.
Why is she acting weird?
Why?
She's acting like a ghost.
Let's go.
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
Guys.
Please help me.
I have to go back to school.
Get me out of here.
Why can't they hear me?
I think they're hypnotized.
I have an idea.
Here's the key.
I have to go back to school.
I have to find Selena's real body.
Wait!
Gawat, there's a space probe.
Are the stars shining?
Good.
But...
if that's a dancer,
why is she going out by herself?
Maybe I've hypnotized them...
so that they can dance and sing.
Good.
She's dancing and singing.
She must be happy.
But...
why isn't she shining?
Maybe...
she's a ghost.
You!
You're not Putri Bintang!
Where's Putri Bintang?
How dare you play with me?
What?
We were right.
Anggap is going to meet Selena.
But we're not in the same class.
Let's go after her.
To be continued...
You believe me, right?
I don't believe you.
No!
Let me go!
Let me go.
I'm Bintang.
Bintang?
Yes.
You're good kids.
Now,
if you want to let me go,
I have to find out where my body is.
Let's go.
It's not safe.
Let's go back.
Yes.
Are you Bintang?
That's impossible.
The soldier said...
Bintang Jatuh is very rare.
That's true.
If you don't believe me,
ask Prita.
Yesterday,
I met Prita.
Prita,
are you Bintang Jatuh?
Putri Bintang Jatuh...
is the one who lives in the school tower.
She helped me yesterday.
No.
It's you.
I don't believe you.
It's you, Alva.
Anyway,
I'm sorry.
I didn't know...
I was in Alva's body.
Maybe...
you switched bodies with Alva.
I don't know.
When I jumped to the tower,
I fainted.
When I realized,
I was trapped in Alva's body.
So, Alva...
is in her body.
Bintang Jatuh.
Where is she?
I know how to find her.
If she's really Bintang,
I'll ask her to shine.
That's right.
Alright.
I'll do it.
She's shining.
It's true.
That means,
she's Selena.
See?
I told you.
I'm Selena,
Bintang Jatuh.
Then?
If she's not Alva,
then what is she?
So, Alva is in...
Selena's body.
Our guess is right.
Alva is in Selena's body.
What should we do?
Let's chase her.
Let me see.
She's here.
Alva is being chased by Professor Rangkarat.
What should we do?
Let's help Alva.
Alright.
It's good that we can get rid of Professor Rangkarat.
But,
what should we do?
What can we do to help her?
To be continued...
Just like a dream...
In this heart...
Attack!
There's a bad guy!
Hey!
It's okay.
It's us.
Vega?
Ray?
Lita?
Why are you guys here?
How do you know me?
Ray, of course we know you.
She's Alva's soul.
But, I still don't believe it.
Why is my outfit different?
I'm not Alva.
Where's my outfit?
I'm sorry.
I changed my outfit.
The dancer's outfit is over there.
But, your outfit...
Selena left it.
I'm sorry.
Let's talk about it later.
Right now,
you guys face each other.
And then,
you guys change your souls again.
Give me the cane.
This is your cane, Alva.
Thank you.
Let's change our souls.
Hurry up.
What's going on?
I'm back.
You did it.
Thank you, Vega.
Ray, Rita.
How are you guys?
I'm back to my body.
Now,
you're back to your real body.
Star princess.
Yes.
I'm back to my real body.
Thank you.
You're so nice to me.
You helped me.
So, now,
I just need to pray for a long time.
So, I can go back to the sky.
You have to pray for a long time tomorrow.
So, you can go back to your real body.
I can't meet Selena anymore.
Don't worry.
Later,
from the sky,
I will summon you.
So, we can play together again.
Promise?
Promise.
Who's that?
I'm being followed.
I don't know.
Help me.
Who's that?
You can't go anywhere, Star princess.
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Hey.
Your power is not comparable to Selena's.
I'm sorry.
Your power is not comparable to me.
We...
Let me go.
Good morning, Alvaro.
Megantara.
And you too.
We can do this.
Help.
Let me go.
Sir.
Star princess is very weak and hot.
I can't tie her.
Even if I tie her, she'll burn.
Don't fight her, Angkara.
Because the peak of Star princess' power is at night.
You can burn with her light.
So,
I have to fight her?
Yes.
I have to fight her.
So,
we'll wait until tomorrow.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll get Star princess' power.
And with that power, I'll defeat Aldebaran.
Then,
I'll take the chosen one from Aldebaran's protection.
Where are we?
Putri Selena.
Where are you?
She must be taken by Professor Angkara.
Oh, no.
Her heart must be taken.
Yes.
Her heart?
Rey,
if the army is explaining the history of magic,
you have to listen to them.
She said,
Star princess is very weak and hot.
Didn't she say,
Star princess is weak because of what?
Because of her hair, eyes, and heart.
They can make a great power.
Yes, it's true.
It's dangerous if she falls into the hands of a bad spy.
But we can't do it alone.
We need Professor Aldebaran's help.
Okay.
Let's go.
So,
Star princess is in our school?
Yes, sir.
I asked her to stay at the school's tower.
But because of Professor Angkara,
she was kidnapped.
Why are you hiding this from me, Alva?
Your actions can endanger yourself
and your other friends.
I'm sorry, Professor.
Because Star princess told me
that I can't tell anyone.
So,
I have to keep my promise.
If so,
we have to find out
where they took her.
Use this telescope, Professor.
It's morning already.
I'm scared.
I'm sleepy.
It's time.
Soon,
all the power of Star princess
will belong to the Dark Lord.
Even if it's Aldebaran,
he can't stop her.
We have to go there right now.
Before Angkara takes the power from Star princess.
Let's go, Alva.
I'll go with you.
There's a fruit
that's hard to pick.
It's dangerous.
Don't follow me.
But, sir,
I have to be responsible for this.
I'll go with you.
What is the matter, Angkara?
I'm worried about this.
I promised to Star princess that
I'll help her to go back to the sky.
Okay, Alva.
You can go with them.
Thank you, sir.
So, what should we do now, sir?
Well, we...
Don't follow me.
To be continued...
Are you ready, Angkara?
Yes, sir.
You go out, Angkara.
We have a guest.
It's them again.
I'll break in.
We need to break in, sir.
Face them, Angkara.
Yes, sir.
I'll fight them for you.
Good morning, Angkara.
Megatara.
And you, Alva.
Give me back Star princess.
It's not that easy, Alva.
And I'm begging you.
Don't ever bother me again.
To be continued...
Finally.
Star princess's hair is mine.
To be continued...
Star princess's hair...
will make me head over heels for you.
To be continued...
Star!
Star princess's hair...
will make me head over heels for you.
How can I resist this?
Finally.
Star princess's hair is mine.
Now, it's time for me...
to take Star princess's tears.
Tear of tears.
With these tears,
my power will be restored.
Now, it's time for me...
to take Star princess's heart.
Star princess's heart...
will be mine.
Duplika!
I must take Star princess's tears now.
After that,
I will be strong.
You must stop him.
Don't let him drink the tears...
mixed with my hair.
Because it can cure all his illness.
And he will be stronger.
To be continued...