To be continued...
Go! Go! Go!
Be proud of yourself!
Let's dream!
Go! Go! Go!
We can do it!
There's no name.
This is just a lie.
This is a trap.
The Dark Lord just wants my sweat, tears, and blood.
Give me your ring.
You're under arrest.
You only have one chance.
If you lose the ring.
Let me go!
We can't give up Alpha to them.
So, it's better...
if there's someone among us...
to disguise as Alpha.
Who?
Myself.
Who's coming?
To be continued...
What's going on, Tom?
Why are we gathered here?
I gathered you all on purpose.
I want to tell you...
that Professor Aldebaran was kidnapped by that monster.
Kidnapped?
So, we have to save the professor.
And we have to get rid of that monster.
But, how?
That monster is stronger than a monster.
Calm down.
I know how.
Actually, Alpha is the target.
Not the professor.
So, if we want to save our professor,
we have to get rid of Alpha.
Let's find Alpha now.
Let's go.
Where is he?
Alpha!
Vita, have you found Alpha?
Not yet.
He's not in the library.
Where is he?
Have you found Alpha?
No.
He's not in the library either.
Where is he?
Where is Alpha?
That's why we have to find him.
I know.
When we attacked that monster,
he was still with us.
But, he's not with us now.
Maybe, Alpha is hiding.
Maybe, he's running away.
Maybe, he's in the library.
Alpha is not that kind of person.
Where is he?
What should we do?
Let's use the kite.
That's right.
Cut the kite.
I'm going to find Alpha.
It's a ghost.
It's really a ghost.
What's wrong?
Alpha was kidnapped by that monster.
He's in the hallway.
What should we do?
It's so scary.
I'm so scared.
What should we do?
Let's tell the teachers.
Let's go.
I got a lollipop.
I'm going to save him.
Don't let him get hurt.
I will help Roger.
I won't let anyone hurt Roger.
Like he hurt my parents first.
Why are you attacking me?
I'm not attacking you.
Prof. Ragni.
Prof. Ragni is not here.
Where is Prof. Ragni?
Gosh.
Gawat.
He's not here.
Gosh, Prof. Ragni is not here.
Yes, Prof. Purwocoki is not here.
Gosh.
What about him?
Yasmin is not here either.
Gosh, what should we do?
What should we do?
This is weird.
How can they be together?
What are you guys doing here?
We're looking for Prof. Ragni.
Oh, Prof. Ragni and all teachers are on their way.
Where are they going?
There.
Long, long, long from here.
They're going to the place in the dark
to help Prof. Adebarat.
But we were asked to help Alva.
Don't worry, be happy.
Megan and Arate have disguised as Alva.
So, they went there with a fake Alva.
Isn't it amazing?
But this is even worse.
And then?
It's better if we ask the others to help Alva.
Come on, let's go.
Gosh, these kids.
Wait for me. Don't go.
I have to defeat Barga before we reach the place in the dark.
To be continued...
Alva is destroyed.
Where is Prof. Adebarat?
Hand him over.
Then, we'll hand him over.
Calm down, all of you.
When my deal with Alva is done,
Adebarat will be back.
That's not the deal.
We'll give you Alva and you'll return Prof. Adebarat.
Yes, Karan. Prove it.
Be patient, Prof. It's okay.
Let me go with them.
Did you hear that?
Alva is smarter than you.
Enough.
Why are we gathered here?
We want to ask for your help.
We have to help Alva.
Because she's in danger.
I don't want to join if it's about defeating Raksasa.
But if you want to help Pegasus,
it's up to you.
I don't want to join.
I don't want to die a loser.
You're so ungrateful.
Okay, let's go.
I'll go with you.
Me too.
What do we do now?
It's so painful.
There are only four of us.
What if we're defeated by Raksasa?
You're right, Tole.
We saw that Raksasa can't be defeated.
If we go there,
we'll lose.
And we won't help Alva.
Poor Alva.
It's not like that, guys.
Let's prepare ourselves first.
Then, we'll find out where Raksasa's weakness is.
It's useless to fight her.
But we don't know her weakness.
Her weakness?
It's better than losing.
Let's go to the library.
Let's go.
Alva is destroyed.
What's that?
It's a ghost.
Alva is destroyed.
We'll succeed this time.
We're going to lose.
What do we do?
They said that...
if we go to the house, we'll be pulled.
I'm confused, too.
Why?
We were pulled by Professor Puluak.
Why is he still strong?
I'm confused, too.
I haven't seen any other developments.
Let's look for it.
I want to look for other developments.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I was told that...
Alva gave up.
It must be in this book.
The hands and feet of the Dark Lord.
There must be a clue here.
Let's look for it.
The Dark Lord has a magical ring.
It can make monsters stronger.
I know how to do it.
Guys!
What's that noise?
It's scary.
It's the Dark Lord!
I have to find his weakness.
It's broken!
Ouch.
It hurts.
I can't stand up.
What should I do?
It's up to you, Alva.
With your blood, I can perfect your power.
Professor Aliparang.
Where is he?
Where's Professor Aliparang?
Shut up!
Don't talk too much.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Let's help Alva.
One, two, three.
Let's go!
Help!
Alva!
You're strong.
Keep going.
Hold on, Alva.
Thank you, Plita.
You're welcome.
Alva!
Hi, everyone.
Hi.
How did you know I'm here?
I saw you flying.
Yes, I'm used to it.
I want to fly by myself.
No.
We're all worried.
Then, you have no choice.
I stole Professor Aliparang.
Then, I chased him.
Thank you for helping me.
I'm strong now.
Barga can't be defeated.
Alva, the ring.
Barga's ring has a charm.
When he wears it, he'll be strong.
So, the charm is from the ring.
Let's make a plan.
But, before that...
Catch it!
You have to eat first.
If you eat, your energy will recover.
And your leg won't hurt anymore.
Okay.
Yes.
My leg won't hurt anymore.
You're right.
Okay.
Let's make a plan.
Why is it so quiet?
Alva.
Now, I'll take your blood.
Okay.
Take the blood.
Take it.
Alva.
Why are you a follower now?
I don't know.
Maybe, he's very curious.
Maybe, he's the only one who's curious.
Use your brain.
Take the hair.
If you want to take the blood,
hurry up.
You can use the old one.
Anggara.
I think something's wrong with Alva.
I think,
she's stressed.
It's up to you, Alva.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is the blood.
With your blood,
I can perfect my power.
Take the blood.
Are you done?
Have fun here, Alva.
Okay, sir.
Alva.
I got you.
You're a traitor.
I feel sorry for you.
Attack.
Don't hit me.
Rita.
That's him.
Keep an eye on him.
Yes, sir.
Be careful, sir.
I'm sorry.
Dad.
Ouch.
Alva.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
His hand is so big.
It's hard to get the ring.
What should I do?
I have an idea.
Get the oil.
Here.
Wear this.
I hope it works.
Okay, guys.
Let's attack him.
Let's go.
Attack.
Rita.
He's getting closer.
Let's go.
Alva.
Be careful, sir.
Don't.
Help.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry.
Get him.
To be continued...
Good.
With Ramwana.
You know how to do everything.
And I won't lose.
Why didn't anything happen?
Angara.
Why didn't you tell me, Angara?
I don't know, sir.
Is Ramwana in the wrong?
I bought a boxer.
I'm sorry, sir.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
It's time.
I'm going to fight him.
I want Tara.
I can use Tongsis.
I can also use Tongsis.
This is easy.
Let's go.
It hurts.
I'm hungry.
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
I'm hungry.
We're hungry.
Don't you know that?
I'm hungry.
But I don't want to eat what you want to eat.
Peanuts.
But it's not normal peanuts.
Then?
It's a magic peanut.
Don't you remember Prof. Rakmi?
Children.
Now we're going to learn about a magic plant.
It's a magic peanut.
There's a peanut in front of you.
Plant it in the ground.
But be careful.
Don't let it touch the water.
Okay, ma'am.
One month later.
Tole.
Help me, Prof.
I told you not to let the plant touch the water.
Now look what happened.
I'm sorry, Prof.
Gosh.
Don't you remember?
Try to imagine.
You want to eat this peanut.
Then, when you eat it,
you have to turn around.
Then, you have to turn around and eat it.
That's scary.
I can't do it.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'll turn around and eat it.
Guys.
I have an idea.
What is it?
One, two, three.
One, two, three. Peanuts.
Let's get the peanuts.
Let's go.
Peanuts.
One, two, three.
I'm...
dead.
Guys.
Throw the peanuts.
Let's go.
Guys.
Calculate the distance to the sky.
Get the peanuts.
I'm...
dead.
Rika.
Rai.
I fell down.
Rika.
Rai.
Help me.
Let's go.
No!
Mate.
Yeah, Brazil!
I'm so happy.
Thank you, friends.
Now, I'm the champion.
Yes, you are.
But, don't.
Run!
I'm panicking.
Stop it.
Let's go to school.
What are you doing?
Megantara is ours.
And it will be forever.
I feel so small.
To be continued...
Professor Angkara.
Where is he?
Angkara.
I mean, Professor Angkara.
Yes, Professor Angkara.
I'm sorry.
I was walking.
I'm so hungry.
To be continued...
Professor Angkara.
Emotions will never help you.
I'm sorry.
Are you attacking me?
Why?
You must be scared.
To be continued...
Take Aldebaran and leave.
He's in the next room.
Are you serious?
Run!
Before we fight.
Okay, then.
Excuse me.
To be continued...
You did it.
I don't believe it.
It's all thanks to Alva.
You guys are awesome.
Alva is awesome.
Oh my God.
You brought Professor Aldebaran back here.
It's new grip.
You guys are awesome.
Amazing.
I have to tell the other professors.
Professor Aldebaran is back.
Saved by Alva, Vega, Ray, Tole, and Pelita.
To be continued...
Where's Megantara?
What took him so long?
How's Professor Aldebaran?
There's a letter.
What is it?
Professor Aldebaran is safe.
He's saved by Alva, Vega, Tole, Ray, and Pelita.
Thank God.
We were right about them.
They are now very brave and brave.
Yes, very good.
Come on.
Let's go back to the school.
Professor Purwa.
What about Megantara?
Professor Agni.
Since the beginning, Megantara told me...
the most important thing is Professor Aldebaran's safety.
He can take care of himself.
And now?
After we've come this far...
you're just going to leave Megantara like that?
Megantara offered to become Alva.
He knows the risks.
That's right.
And now, Megantara's knowledge is high enough.
And he can take care of himself.
No.
I'm not going back.
If you want to go home, go ahead.
I'll wait for you here.
It's up to you, Professor Agni.
Goodbye, Nolip.
Goodbye.
If anything happens, let me know.
Yes, ma'am.
Mertiwi.
How is Professor Aldebaran?
It's okay.
Professor Aldebaran will wake up in a few hours.
Good.
Wait.
Why is it just the two of you?
Professor Agni and Megantara?
Where is...
Megantara is now in the Dark Palace.
And Professor Agni is waiting for him to come back.
What?
Megantara has a place in the Dark Palace?
Yes.
He offered to become Alva.
You didn't tell me.
Well, I forgot.
I was thinking about how to fight that monster.
What are you doing?
Megantara is in the Dark Palace.
And he will be defeated by the Dark Lord.
Wait.
Alva is coming.
And this time, don't you dare to come back.
Or Megantara won't forgive you.
I won't let the Dark Lord hurt Tara.
Alva.
Where are you going?
What's that?
Mega.
Why are you here?
What's going on?
Alva heard the words of the bird.
And he wants to attack Tara.
Alva.
How dare you.
Please, Professor.
Or she will be attacked by the Dark Lord.
Alva.
What are you doing here?
I want to meet the Dark Lord.
Come back.
Alva.
Don't be stubborn.
You have to go home now.
No, Professor.
I can't go home.
The army is still in the Dark Lord's territory.
Alva, I order you to go home now.
I can't, Professor.
I don't want anyone to be a victim because of me.
The Dark Lord.
I'm here.
Come out.
The Dark Lord.
What are you doing, Alva?
I order you to go home now.
Or I will punish you.
Alva.
Go home now.
Or I will kick you out of the school.
I don't want to be kicked out of the school.
As long as we are safe.
Welcome, Alva.
Kara.
What have you done?
It turns out that this is true, Alva.
If you don't come with me now, Alva.
No, Alva.
You can't go.
But, Professor.
I can take care of myself.
No, Alva.
You have to stay here, Alva.
Let me go, Alva.
No, Kara.
It's better for me if you go.
You are useless.
Let me go, Alva.
No.
I won't let you go, Alva.
Alva!
David, no!
We can do this.
Tara.
Tantara.
Tantara, wake up.
Tantara, let's get out of here.
Tantara.
Alva.
Good, Megantara.
Good.
Professor Kara.
What are you doing, Tantara?
Why?
You must not believe...
...that Megantara...
...is my son.
My son?
Megantara.
Now, you will take my son's blood.
Don't, Tantara.
Take the boy's blood.
Attack him, Alva.
Attack him.
David, no!
One, two, three.
Two, three.
Megantara.
Yes!
I hypnotized you.
Angkara.
You won't fall for the second time.
Professor Agni.
You were hypnotized.
Doctor Pertiwi.
But I, Megantara...
...can't hypnotize you.
MEGANTARA
This hypnotism is very dangerous for you, Megantara.
You must be very careful.
That's right.
If Megantara finds out...
...she will be hypnotized.
And she will become their spy.
How about we learn...
...the anti-hypnotism mantra?
Agreed.
Let's go.
Memorize the anti-hypnotism mantra.
And I'll hypnotize you.
MEGANTARA
How is it?
I think the anti-hypnotism mantra didn't work.
I think so.
Finally.
Professor Agni is back.
Just like that.
Now you, Megantara.
Me? Hypnotized?
Yes.
Who's afraid?
Try it.
Megantara.
Finally.
Finally what?
It worked.
The servant lifted the stone.
You got a lot of money.
You're all fooled.
You're so unlucky.
Angkara.
You're a cunning human.
A cunning human like you...
...must be faced in a way that is no less cunning.
Okay, Megantara.
Let's attack.
What?
Now it's time...
...to destroy him.
Let's go.
Divide!
Get ready, Alva.
He'll wake up again.
Get ready.
I haven't lost yet.
Yes!
Yes, I won!
I won!
We must not make a mistake.
We must check...
...whether he's unconscious...
...dead...
...or not.
Don't pretend.
I'm sorry.
I know...
...how to find out...
...whether he's unconscious or not.
Look.
Where is he?
He's not here.
He's dead.
Yes!
A great army...
...can fight Professor Anggara's hypnotism.
Alva.
This is all because of you.
Because of me?
Yes.
I...
...can control hypnotism.
That's because I have the confidence...
...and determination to save you.
Because of that confidence...
...that's why we succeeded.
Because I don't want...
...anyone to harm you, Alva.
Because you...
...are my beloved student, Alva.
Thank you, General.
Oh, right.
Later, teach me hypnotism, okay?
You want to be able to hypnotize?
For you...
...what do I give you?
Don't even think about hypnotizing.
Hypnotizing you to fart...
...hypnotizing you to fart.
I'll definitely give you something.
Later, I can do it.
You!
It's better...
...if we get out of here quickly.
Let's go.
Wait.
What now?
Let's run.
Hurry up.
My backpack.
Your backpack is empty.
You're a coward.
You should run while carrying your backpack.
But it's okay.
Let's go.
Hypnotizing.
100.
3.
Alva.
I won't let you go, Alva.
Wait, sir.
Wait.
Poor Alva.
Yes, you're right.
So, you don't want to come with us?
No.
If I'm wrong, I'll forget.
Professor, I fainted.
I was attacked by darkness.
I'm very hurt.
Alva.
To be continued...